www.tvsubtitles.net
but no adoption agency's
gonna touch us now.
there are ways to get babies,
carlos. $20,000.
wheels were put in motion...
i love you.
aw, thank you.
i love mike.
true emotions wererevealed...
who the hell is mike?
perception is reality,
andrew.
my name is bree,
and i am an alcoholic.
and false pretenses
became a way of life.
gabrielle solis had always been
a demanding shopper.
carlos, come on!
they're here!
and whatever the purchase,
she always expected
the very best.
whether it was exotic perfume
shipd over from paris...
a high fashion gown straight
from a runway in milan...
or designer shoes
flown in from manhattan,
but on this day,
her expectations were
going to be put to the test.
you see, gabrielle was now
shopping for a baby,
and there was a problem...
with the manufacturer.
mostly, i just wanna feel
like i'm giving my baby
to people who have what it takes
to be really great parents.
well, you won't find
another couple
with more love for a child.
(chuckles)
isn't that right, honey?
honey?
right.
right, uh, lots of le.
honey, can i talk to you
for a second?
yeah.
okay.
okay, look, we have
to find another mother.
why?
okay, this isn't easy to say,
so i'm just gonna say it,
but have you taken
a good look at her?
oh, my god.
are you trying to say that
you don't want deana's baby
because she's plain?
no, plain i can handle.
carlos, since that woman
has walked into ou ihouse,
the clocks
have stopped working.
no one can predict what
a child is gonna look like.
for all you know, her kid could
end up winning beauty contests.
with her d.n.a.,
the only thing that kid's gonna
be winning is best in show.
look, carlos, i am sorry,
but i want a pretty baby,
so let's find another mother.
mnh-mnh. i'm not gonna let
your shallow obsession
with looks screw this up.
i want a child--any child.
fine. just know
that in a couple of days,
when that thing is born,
and you're gonna have
to cuddle and snuggle up
with something
with that face on it,
don't come crying to me.
i'm sorry.
now where were we?
we were just talking about
the custody arrangement
once deana gives birth.
it's usually best
that the mother
doesn't see the child
at all.
so as soon as the doctors finish
giving their initial checkup...
...the baby
will be handed over you.
yes, gabrielle had always been
a demanding shopper.
sorry.
because she knew
there are some purchases...
that can't be returned.
cync by lanmao
www.1000fr.com
at 6:10 the next morning,
deana pruse
went into premature labor
d gave birth
to what would t tually be
an incredibly attractive
baby boy.
at 11:43, dr. hanson mills
cut the umbilical cord,
forever separating
mother and child.
at that exact same moment,
dr. ron mccready entered
the private room of susan mayer
with every intention
of severing their connection.
hey there. how's it goin'?
great.
i'm about to be released.
oh, that's terrific.
who's mike?
i...
why do you ask?
i don't know. no reason.
ah, it's jt,..
just before the operation,
just before you went under,
i said, "i love you,"
and you said,
"i love mike."
i did?
oh, is that why you han't been
in to see me since my surgery?
answer the question.
i don't even know
a mike.
everyone knows a mike.
yes, everyone does know
a mike.
actually, you're right.
i did know a mike in college.
we did this play together,
"pippin." it wasn't very good.
anyways, i never thought of him,
so you shouldn't be accusing me.
i was probably
just hallucinating.
fine, fine.
so... who's the guy
you're married to?
damn that nurse hisel!
or should i say, "who's the guy
you're cating on?"
okay, yes,
i did remarry my ex,
but it was only because
he has great health insurance.
did miss blabbermouth
tell you that, too?
you--you committed
insurance fraud?
only in the legal sense.
and i just didn't tell you
because i wanted to protect you.
susan--
okay, you know what?
you should come over to dinner
and meet karl, and you can see
that there is absolutely
nothing between us.
so wait,
once you're fully recovered
you're gonna divorce him?
oh, yeah, that's the plan.
i swear.
and you swear that you're not
in love with anyone named mike?
sure.
okay.
come here.
i believe you.
(man) next morning,
i woke up in an alley.
my wallet had been stolen.
i was lying in a pool
of my own vomit.
that's when i knew
i'd hit rock bottom.
okay, who's next?
bree.
oh! um, i couldn't
possibly top that.
thank you, though.
(indistinct conversations)
hi. before coming
to these meetings,
i never realized how messy
substance abusers can be.
we usually leave
the doughnut crumbs
for the overeaters anonymous
group at meets after us.
you know,
just to mess with 'em.
you're awful.
so... tell me, bree,
how long have you been sober?
gosh, um...
i'm not exactly sure.
oh. is somebody
still drinking?
now why would you
say that?
never met
an alcoholic yet
who didn't know exactly how long
it'd been since his last drink.
okay, you got me.
i'm not really
an alcoholic.
you don't say.
it's true. i'm coming here
because of my son.
you see, he's--he's trying
to take me to court to become
an emancipated minor, and he's
planning on lying to the judge
and telling him that
i am some sort of dreadful lush.
so i'm coming to these meetings
to give the impression
that i have changed.
but you don't
really need to change
because you don't have
a problem with alcohol.
exactly.
i'll tell you what...
here's my card.
and if you ever
do have a problem
or you just feel like talking,
give me a call, okay?
i know you think
i'm kidding myself,
but i'm not.
i'm nothing like
you people.
i just don't have
a compulsive personality.
hmm.
word is out all over town
that you're unhappy at zimms,
so why not jump ship
and come to parcher & murphy?
i swear, veronica,
you would fit in so well here.
i do need
to make a change, lynette,
but the money
you're offering...
yeah, it sucks,
but there are other perks--
the expense account,
the corner office...
i don't know.
you're just gonna have to give
me some time to think about it.
fair enough, fair gh.
okay, what is your secret?
how can you eat like that
and keep your figure?
it's the breast-feeding.
it burns so many calories.
it's like having a treadmillstrap
i didn't know
you had a child.
yes, my son donovan.
he's the love of my life.
really, veronica?
well, you know, there's another
perk that i just thought of.
oh, my gosh,
this is fantastic!
they don't have
day care at zimms.
how can they not?
for working parents like
you and me, it's a necessity.
so is the pot
getting sweeter?
would people here be cool
about my breast-feeding donovan?
the guys at zimms
were real jerks about that.
parcher & murphy
is completely mother-friendly.
no one would say a word.
oh!
what the heck, i'm in.
yeah?
well, that's fantastic!
oh, my god,
whose kids are those?
(shouting and laughing)
i have absolutely no idea.
let's go hammer out
the details.
okay.
(carlos) mm. ooh.
(gabrielle) these can't be
our only choices, mr. beale.
i mean, come on.
each girl is uglier
than the next.
look, finding a gorgeous
pregnant woman who's willing
to give her baby to a couple
with a criminal record
isn't exactly
a walk in the park.
i don't care if it's a walk in the sewer.
we are hemorrhaging money
into your bank account,
and i expect
to see results.
you know, mrs. solis,
you can catch more flies
with honey than with vinegar.
if i wanted to catch flies,
all i would have to do
is call up one of these girls.
trust me,
the flies would follow.
(intercom beeps)
(woman) excuse me, sir, there's
a libby collins here for you.
i'll be right out there.
uh, i took the liberty
of inviting this girl
down here to meet you.
now i wouldn't exactly say
she's a quality human being,
but she is attractive.
if you don't respond to her,
i'm afraid i'm out of ideas.
(sighs)
he's going to dump us
as clients
if you don't stop
being so damn picky.
we're gonna
have to stare at this face
for the next 18 years.
i don't think now
is the time to skimp on quality.
(mr. beale)
gabrielle, carlos...
i'd like you to meet libby.
well, now,
this i can work with.
so getting pregnant
was the worst thing that
could've ever happened to me,
'cause i went into debt
and i had to stop performing.
libby's a pole dancer
in a strip club.
oh!
wow, that--that sounds
like interesting work.
you'd think so,
but it gets old quickly.
my big dream
is to become a choreographer.
really?
yeah.
i made up this one move.
it's called
"the serpent's tongue,"
and all the girls at the club
are doing it now. it's so cool.
if i had a pole
i could show you.
well, we'll have to go down
to the club and check that out.
we'll make a night of it.
yeah, we'll do that.
so, libby,
who's the father?
honesty, i don't know.
i mean, there's a lot of guys
who come into the club,
and they all buy me drinks,
and sometimes i get a little bit
more friendly than i intend to.
i hope you don't think
i'm a slut.
no!
no.
no, actually,
all we think about
when we look at you
is how pretty yoare.
well, i've heard enough,
mr. beale.
if libby here likes us as much
as much as we like her,
we should just go ahead
and move to adopt her baby girl.
first, we should probably talk
about how much money i want.
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
(chuckles)
nobody's buying a baby here.
that's illegal.
money can never
exchange hands.
libby, you'll make a list
of your expenses,
and the solises here will pay.
oh, but can't they also
buy me gifts?
i knew this one girl who gave up
her baby, and she got a harley.
well, i don't know that we can
afford a harley, but i'm sure
we'll find some way
to express our gratitude.
okay.
whatever.
well, my lunch break is over,
so i have get back
to the club.
till i get rid of this kid,
they got me slinging drinks.
it was really nice to meet you,
mr. and mrs. soulless.
oh, it'sctually
pronounced solis.
sorry.
so what kind of name is that?
uh, it's mexican.
both our families
come from guadalajara.
huh.
i figured you were italian.
nope. latino.
proud of it. (chuckles)
good for you.
wow, she's... gorgeous.
yeah. my little girl's gonna
inherit some wonderful genes.
is this
libby's real hair color?
yes, it's all natural,
from her straight teeth
to her "c" cup.
and i know she's athletic
because she's a pole dancer,
so i really hope
that my little girl
inherits that as well.
no, the athletic gene,
not the pole dancing gene.
(chuckles)
(karl) susie, baby?
oh, i got your call, uh...
i thought i'd stop by.
i didn't realize
you had company. hello, ladies.
um, we'll just be a second.
just wheel me.
be right back.
just be a second.
did he just call her "baby"?
yeah. when did they
stop hating each other?
i need you to ditch edie
tomorrow night
and have dinner
with dr. ron and me.
now why would i do that?
well, for starters, because you
banged your secretary,
and you owe me
for the rest of your life.
i'll bring the wine.
well, you know,
before mike came along,
i always just assumed
they'd get back together.
why?
i thought they always annoyed
the heck out of each other.
you didn't know them
during the good times.
i mean, there was such a spark
between them, so much passion.
they would always
make each other laugh.
you actually told dr. ron
that you still love mike?
okay, will you shut up?
it's not funny. i was drugged.
right. sorry, sorry.
so how'd you
get out of that one?
(sighs) i lied and i told him
i didn't know a mike.
everyone knows a mike.
i am aware of that.
so why didn't you just--because
dr. ron hadn't come in
to see me since the operation
and i was feeling
insecure and...
(whispers) i just didn't
feel like the truth
was a luxury i could afford.
(normal voice) ygo ahead.
you may resume laughing.
uh...
ladies, always a pleasure.
and you, i'll see you tomorrow.
what?
this is just
a preliminary sketch,
but you see what
i'm thinking of?
i love it. i just love it.
let get a copy to ed.
(cell phone rings), t,
i gotta take this one.
i'm sorry. it's tom.
that's okay.
my nanny is here with my son.
i need
to go feed him anyway.
perfect! take your time.
hey, honey.
how's the big apple treating ya?
good. did those, uh,
snooty clients like yo pitch?
well, that's perfect.
excellent.
uh-huh.
um, i'm...
i'm, um... i'm gonna have--
i'm gonna call you back.
oh, my god!
(squeals)
hello there!
i thought you and your friend
might like some snacks.
he's my lawyer, and this is
privileged communication,
so get out.
andrew, there's no need
to be rude.
this is very kind of you,
mrs. van de kamp.
well, i'm still appalled
that you're helping my son
with this ridiculous
emancipation scheme,
but you are a guest in my house,
and guests get sandwiches.
you know, if you'd let me go
to his office, you wouldn't have
to pretend to be nice to him.
andrew, there may be
a judge out there
stupid enough
to emancipate you,
but until you find him,
i retain all my parental rights,
one of which is to ground your
sorry behind until kingdom come.
mr. bormanis,
nice to see you again.
and, um, please don't
get crumbs on my carpet.
you have got
to get me out of here.
that bitch
is driving me crazy.
this case
is not a slam dunk.
her drinking was supposed
to be our silver bullet,
but since
she joined a.a.--
we've gotta do something,
because if she wins,
she's gonna own me.
my advice?
convince her it's in her
best interest to let you go.
you don't wanna see
the inside of a courtroom.
why?
in family court,
appearance means everything.
if she came off abusive
or stoned or even uncaring,
we'd be in good shape.
but if there's one thing
your mom understands...
it's presentation.
can i borrow $50?
purse.
(stops playing)
why do you want
so much money?
i'm 19. sometimes i need money.
do i have to be interrogated?
you do if you want
a dime out of me.
what's it for?
danielle's having her birthday
next week.
i just wanna be sure
i can get her a decent present.
write her a poem.
it's free.
(resumes playing piano)
is there
something else you want?
do you think
i like to beg for money?
i do this because
you won't let me get a job.
looking after your brother
is a full-time job
for both of us,
and you know that.
well, screw him!
matthew!
no, i'm serious, mom,
because we have both
put our entire lives on hold,
and for what?
it's been almost a year
and he hasn't gotten any better.
i see him improving!
that's because you see
what you wanna see!
it is time
to put him away, mom.
just let some professionals
take care of him.
we wouldn't have to move.
we could have our lives back.
what's wrong?
you fighting?
matthew's friend danielle
has a birthday coming up.
we were just talking about
what gift to give her.
well,
i was thinking jewelry...
so 50 bucks should do it.
why not $20?
you don't wanna spoil her.
on page 6 is an e of
the new print ad. check it out.
i'm thirsty.
oh, shh, honey,
everyone's working.
i'm sorry.
this will just take a sec.
is it just me,
or is that bizarre?
it's bizarre.
totally birre.
we gotta make her stop this.
y, h,don't get me wrong
i find that as bizarre
as you guys do.
but right now this firm needs
veronica more than she needs us.
telling a mother how to raise
her kids is an act of war.
we willose her.
the kid is 5.
it's disgusting!
yeah, weye,
we'll just ask her
to keep the blinds
always drawn when she nurses.
and god forbid
a client sees her.
okay,so's gna tell her
you're a woman.
it's easier for you
to talk to her about
milk and boobs and stuff.
no! no, uh, please,
don't make me do it.
why don't you have
jerry tell her?
i made a pass at her yesterday.
it'd be weird.
you could do it
without offending her.
come on, lynette.
take one for the team.
okay. but for the record,
the team is made up of wimps.
well, the team's aware of that
and accepts your loathing.
yeah? hi. no. no, no.
we were just out buying some
stuff for the baby. what's up?
seriously?
okay.
thanks for calling.
what is it?
that was our lawyer.
libby rejected us as parents.
why?
because we're mexican.
what?! why, i--
that's discrimination.
it's illegal.
we could have her arrested.
it's her baby.
she can do whatever the hell
she wants to with it.
damn it.
no! no, you don't just
toss people aside
because of the color
of their skin.
we tossed those birth mothers aside
why?
becai've read
the constitution,
and it does not
protect ugly people.
let's not fight about it.
it's over.
let's just move on
to the next one.
no. no, no, no.
i want that woman's baby,
and i'm gonna get it.
and just how are you
gonna go about doing that?
well, first of all, i'm gonna
show her one of our tax returns.
once she sees
how much money we have,
i have a hunch we're gonna
look a whole lot whiter.
hey, veronica.
hi, donovan!
my, he's getting big.
how old is he?
he just turned 5.
oh, wow,
he's such a big boy.
yeah.
he you know,
breast-feeding on this schedule
must be a real hassle.
i remember i used to express
my milk into a bottle.
made my maso much so
is there a problem,
lynette?
the people in ffice
feel a little...
concerned...
that you're nursing a boy
of donovan's age.
do they know breast milk
boosts the immune system,
it's loaded with vitamins,
and in the third world,
it's not unusual to nurse babies
up to the age of 6?
yeah, well, in the third world,
they don't have juice xes.
this is donovan's decision.
he will tell me when
he's ready to stop nursing.
come on, baby birds
don't jump out of the nest.
they need to be pushed.
did you also know
that breast milk is thought
to raise i.q. scores?
yeah, maybe if you had
weaned your kids a bit later,
they'd be more civilized.
ouch.
i will not be judged
by you or anyone else,
and if people don't like
my breast-feeding,
they can talk
to my lawyer.
(laughing) and then
she took the salad bowl--
put it on the floor
and said,
"if you wanna act like a pig,
you can eat like a pig."
you know, i never thought
i'd have such a good time
hanging out with my girlfriend
and her husband.
yeah, well, believe me,
behind all the laughs,
there's still plenty of
bitterness and resentment.
oh, really?
yeah.
hey, what do you say
you and i clear the table
and bring on dessert?
no, no. i got it, i got it.
no, honey,
you're not gonna do anything.
you're in a wheelchair
for a reason, okay?
why don't you let karl and i
do the dishes?
all right, but if i catch you
guys in there talking about me,
you're gonna be the one
in a wheelchair.
oh, really?
yeah. mmm.
yeah?
well, i think maybe the dishes
can wait for a second.
(whispers) just a second?
(whispers)
yeah, just a second.
what the hell?
what's the matter?
aah!
jeez, ah, we got a leak.
oh.
i'll sop up the water.
why don't you see go see
the guy across the street?
he's a plumber,
in the gray house.
all right.
i'll be right back.
his name's delfino.
where's he going?
oh, we've gowet
of a plumbing emergency.
so you sent hi
toike's?
oh, my god.
i am such an idiot!
i wasn'ti ven thinking.
karl! oh, god!
there's just
so much water here.
what were you thinking?
oh, oh!
hi, mr. delfino? my name's ron.
my girlfriend is susan mayer.
you know,
from across the street?
yeah, yeah...
i know her.
we've got
kind of a burst pipe.
okay, um...
come on in
while i get my tools.
and you can call me mike.
oh! ugh!
oh, ah, okay.
i made it.
so... mike, have you, uh,
have you known susan long?
a year and a half.
ah! ooh!
didn't she mention
we dated?
no, no, she didn't.
she... she didn't.
oh!
can you excuse me, please?
(clears throat)
that smarts! aah!
liar!
i take it you met mike.
yeah, i did.
please,
please let me explain.
no, just let go of me.
ohh!
i'm sorry.
okay.
here, come on,
let me help you.
hey, get away from her!
are you okay?
i'm fine!
what the hell
is the matter with you?
hey, that was an accident!
that didn't look
like an accident.
okay, mike, just--it's okay.
just go home.
yeah, go home, mike.
you touch her like that again,
you're gonna be dealing with me.
you might wanna
get out of my face.
or what?
(groans) okay.
ron, what are you doing?
oh, my god!
guys, stop it.
stop it, right now!
all right, all right.
i can't believe
i wasted my time with you.
you've just been
leading me on!
you're obviously
still in love with this guy.
all right, i'm done.
no, ron, don't go!
don't call me.
(engine starts)
(susan) oh, ron!
oh!
ugh!
what the hell
isrong with you?
i thought
he was hurting you.
well, he wasn't!
and now
my boyfriend is gone.
thank you very much.
okay, but the pole
is your friend, okay?
push your boobs
up against it.
oh, i can't. they're new.
well, do something,
cecile.
i'm losing my wood
down here.
wow!
that's a kickin' outfit.
well, thank you, sweetie.
i clean up well
for a wetback, don't i?
look, i'm not
some sort of racist.
i just want what's best
for my baby girl.
i mean, why should i settle
for middle-class mexicans
when i know i can find
rich white folks to adopt her?
please. do i look
middle class to you?
well, you didn't seem all that
rich in mr. beale's office.
i mean, when i brought up
the idea of gifts
to your husband,
he acted like he couldn't
even afford a harley.
so is that what it's gonna take
to change your mind--a gift?
fine. what do you want?
i don't know.
you like jewelry?
well, here.
are these real diamonds?
honey, the one in the center
is 3 karats.
i never touched
a real diamond before.
well, my husband and i
can expose you
to a lot of nice new things.
well, only if i let you have my baby.
there's no such thing
as a free lunch.
okay.
really?
just like that?
just like that.
of course, you probably
shouldn't tell the lawyer
about our understanding,
because then we'll have to deal
with percentages and all that.
i always hated math.
what's wrong?
you never gave a crap
that we were mexican, did you?
not really.
so why put me through this?
because i thought,
if it looked like
you weren't gonna get my baby
that you might be
just a bit more generous.
wow. you're a lot smarter
than i thought.
i'm smarter
than everybody thinks.
where's my mom?
i'm thirsty.
oh, i'm sorry, honey.
your mom... is in her office
on a conference call,
and she's busy, so you're just
gonna have to wait, okay?
what's that?
that's chocolate milk.
i shouldn't be having it.
have you ever had any?
mnh-mnh.
follow me.
here. go ahead, try it.
come on, you'll really like it.
i promise.
come on, yeah.
all the grown-ups
are drinking it.
yeah, that's good.
just... chug it on down.
good.
you like that?
would you like dessert
or another glass of wine?
oh, no, thank you.
i have to run. just the check.
i have a charity event
this weekend,
and i have to find
a cocktail dress
before the store closes.
but everything
was just yummy.
(andrew)
looks good on your ass.
thank you.
yeah.
uh, hey, mrs. van de kamp.
what do you think you're doing?
you're supposed to be grounded.
i'm, uh, buying a belt.
with what?
you don't have any money.
you took that out of my purse.
give that back.
we are going home. wait till
i tell the judge about
you stealing my credit cards
and sneaking off.
it's gonna do wonders for
your little emancipation case.
i don't think you're gonna
let this get to the court.
oh, and why is that?
because then i'd be forced
to testify about my childhood.
so? you had one of the loveliest
childhoods i've ever known.
you sure about that?
'cause i'm staing
to remember some abuse.
andrew, the judge is not
seriously gonna believe
that i beat you.
oh, i'm not talking
about that kind of abuse.
you know, it's funny...
the angrier i get,
the more these repressed
memories start to come up.
you can't be serious.
like, touching me in places
you shouldn't have...
no one is ever gonna
believe a word of that.
yeah, well,
you know how people are.
they might say
that they believe you,
but...
th'll always wonder.
so if i were you...
i'd back the hell off.
come on, justin.
i'm gonna buy you
something pretty.
justin!
on second thought,
i will have
another glass of wine.
you can leave the bottle.
yeah?
hi, it's bree van de kamp.
i didn't know who else to call,
and, well, i'm in a bit
of a situation.
well...
(laughing) how did you
get stuck like that?
i would rather
not discuss it right now.
man, the other security guys
are not gonna believe this.
do you mind?
didn't.
your son threatened you
with "repressed memories"?
oh, my god,
he is seriously twisted.
i gotta meet this kid.
you sound like
you're impressed.
i sorta am.
(scoffs) i'm raising a monster,
is what i'm raising.
it's no wonder i drink.
i don't know why i said that.
maybe it's true.
no, it makes it und like
i think i have a problem,
and i don't.
look, i don't wanna get
into a fight or anything,
but you passed out
in a department store,
and in my way of thinking,
that is a problem.
tonight was
a very unusual situation.
i wish you could've
known me when...
rex was alive
and my kids were young,
and everything was...
the way
it was supposed to be.
i think you really
would've liked me... so much.
i like you just fine.
really?
because i don't.
bye.
mom?
andrew?
caleb?
hey, danielle.
what are you doing here?
happy birthday.
you really
have to go home.
if my mom knew you were here,
she'd freak.
don't you want to wear it?
no, i don't, now please leave
i can help you with it.
no! didn't you hear me,you freak?! leave!
what's wrong?
you can tell everyone
in the office to relax.
he won't
take my milk anymore.
already? (gasps)
i mean, i'm sorry.
yeah, i bet.
i mean, i'm not naive.
i just didn't think
it would be so soon.
oh, sweetie...
i know that we wanna keep them
young as long as we can,
but kids grow up.
they just do.
i know.
if that's not bad enough,
now i'm gonna get fat again.
huh?
breast-feeding
was the only thing
that kept the weight off.
every mealtime was like
doing 30 minutes of cardio.
now i'm gonna have
to join a gym!
wow, that is...
really a bummer.
it is.
it really is.
(sobbing)
hey, uh,
julie let me in.
i can see that.
so, what, did you run out
of strangers to beat up
on the street, and you're going
house to house now?
i feel really awful
about what happened.
if you don't wanna be
my boyfriend, fine.
don't beat up the only guy who
wants to volunteer for the job.
look,
i know i overreacted.
but come on,
the way he was yelling at you?
i deserved it, believe me.
after what i did...
(sighs) god,
this is such a mess.
he won't even
return my phone calls.
what'd you do?
i said something to dr. ron
before the operation,
and it just...
devastated him.
what?
i can't tell you.
yeah, you can.
you can tell me anything.
you know that.
mom, um, phone call.
it's dr. ron.
oh?
um...
i need to take this.
(sighs)
you, um, you wanna
talk about this later?
no.
no, not really. um...
what's the point?
(telephone beeps)
hi.
at that precise moment,
as dr. hanson mills was cutting
yet another umbilical cord,
other ties were being severed
all over town...
like the one
between a child and the mother
who didn't want him
to grow up so quickly...
or the one
between a case of fine wine
and the housewife
who hadn't wanted to admit
that she had a problem...
or the one between a woman
and the boyfriend
who couldn't forgive
her betrayal.
the choice to separate
from what we love is painful...
hey. how's my girl today?
how are both of my girls?
the only thing worse...
we're doing good.
we're doing real good.
is when meone we've trusted
makes the choice for us.
cync by lanmao
www.1000fr.com