This will sweep her
right off her feet.
You dog. You're gonna ask
Susan to marry you, aren't you?
I didn't say that.
They say money can't buy love.
My gift to you.
You bought us a house?
...or even happiness.
I have another child,
I only just found out about it.
I am not having an affair.
And it certainly can't ease
You don't wanna have sex
with me?
Don't take it personally.
a guilty conscience.
See, That's why I can't give you
the keys to the kingdom, kid.
No balls.
Do I know you?
Orson Hodge.
Uh, Susan's dentist friend.
The only thing that can bring new piece in your mind
You, by any chance,
recognize the jacket?
That jacket belongs
to my other son.
is to finding the truth
we have to find them,
and get Danielle back
..and sending yourself free.
- I am trying to leave,
and these morons won't let me
Bree, please, don't struggle.
Have they rung up
your prescription yet?
No, they're getting it
right now.
Good. Add that on.
You're dying your hair
honey wheat blond?
Oh, it's not for me.
It's for Danielle.
That hair is going back
to the color God intended.
You actually think
she's gonna sit still
as you towel this
through her hair?
Oh, I will tie her down
if necessary.
I'm also thinking of checking
her body for piercings
While I'm at it.
- You're overreacting.
She's just going through
a phase.
That's what
girls her age do.
They also get pregnant
and become drug addicts.
And that color hair
is the gateway.
Would you please, uh,
add that to our bill?
I'm telling you, Bree,
You're gonna have to
stop riding 'em so hard.
I am trying to ensure that they
turn into responsible adults.
Trust me, Rex,
in the end,
we will be rewarded.
How can you be so damn sure
of yourself all the time?
Why is my certainty a flaw?
I know what I'm about,
I know my values,
and I know what's right.
Why shouldn't I stay
the course?
Am I right,
Mr. Williams?
My mother always took
a firm hand with me,
and I thank her for it.
Exactly, and look how well
you turned out.
Look, you're a good mother,
but there's a limit.
You have got to relinquish
some control,
or else
you're gonna regret it.
Excuse me.
Do you have the time?
Yeah, it's just after 8:00.
- Oh, I was afraid of that.
Afraid of what?
Well, I'm only supposed
to be restrained until 7:00.
You see, I have a problem
with sleepwalking.
They just tie me up
so that I don't wander off
and hurt myself.
Yeah, well, I'm sure a nurse
will be in here soon.
One can only hope.
Of course, if a doctor
gets here first
and sees that someone
forgot to release me,
I'm sure they'd get
in a lot of trouble.
Lady, I can't let you
out of your restraints.
I'd get fired.
Oh. Well, I certainly would not
want that to happen.
What's your name?
Alfred.
Oh! Does anybody ever
call you "Alfie"?
No.
And why should they?
So, um, Alfred,
I was wondering if you could
maybe loosen my restraints.
They're incredibly tight,
and I'm sure
there are no rules
against making me
more comfortable.
Do you think I'm stupid?
I beg your pardon?
Two seconds after I loosen
these little restraints,
you'll try to scratch
my eyes out
and make a run for it.
Well, I'm not falling for it,
you psycho little bitch.
In fact, I hope they keep you
tied up for the next month.
'cause I'd get a real kick
out of watching
a prissy little whack job
like you
lying in your own filth.
Know what I mean?
Careful with those.
The last of the crystal.
- Okay.
Hey, what's going on?
Oh, hi.
Um, we're just moving.
Hey! It's the plumber.
You come over to help Susie
move into her new house?
New house?
Oh, she didn't tell you?
I bought a place for my girls.
You let him buy you
a house?
Uh, well,
he's not moving in with us.
After that speech about
wanting to go it alone,
and after I offered
to let you stay with me?
To be fair,
you just had a spare room,
and this is a whole house.
Hey, no offense,
if you're not using your back,
you're just in the way.
You saw me
buying that ring,
and you just had
to cut me off.
You bought me a ring?
Suze, let me handle this.
A man's gotta protect
his family.
Uh, Mike, about that ring...
- Put that box down.
What, you gonna hit me,
huh?
stop it! Oh, my...
What are you--
just stop it! Oh, that's enough!
Just get off! Get off! Go! Go!
Oh, my God.
What? Stop! That's enough.
Enough, enough. Back up.
And that ring--
that was for me, right?
- Not now.
oh, my...
Ohh!
Karl, are you okay?
Are you okay? Let me see.
Oh, my God.
Whew.
can you sit up?
whew.
Xiao-mei,
do you have a second?
This is probably silly,
but it's been bothering me.
When you said,
"Please don't kill him,"
did you mean Carlos?
Ralph dead, not Mr. Solis.
I know. It's just,
you said "kill," not "dead."
And I'd have to do be
pretty angry to kill someone,
so I guess my question is,
do I have a reason
to be angry at Mr. Solis?
Please, so much laundry.
Xiao-mei...
how did you rip
your panties?
I fall down.
Mr. Young, you'll need
to come up to the house
to sign
some legal documents.
What for?
Noah Taylor's will called
for an immediate transference
of his entire estate to you
upon his death.
So everything's mine?
That's correct.
Hi, Dad.
so, did you have
any luck with your grandfather?
Yeah, I talked to Noah.
He's not gonna give us
the money.
Damn it, Zach!
Sorry?
Go back and talk to him.
No, I-I don't think
he's gonna change his mind.
Terrific.
Am I gonna see you tomorrow?
No, I-I can't come tomorrow.
What about Monday?
Uh, next week's bad for me,
too.
I'll--I'll call you
when I know.
- Zach? Zach!
Is there anything I can do?
Yeah, get me a new phone
with a different number.
And fill in
this stupid lake.
Oh. Are you all right?
Uh, yeah. A little hopped up
on pain medicine, but, um,
I chipped my tooth
on the salad shooter.
Oh. Oh, you know,
you should, um,
call my friend Orson.
He's a dentist.
I'm sure he'll see you right away.
- Thanks.
So...
about that ring you bought--
Is there anything particular
you'd like to ask me?
Nope,
not as long Karl's got you
wrapped around his finger.
Okay, that's ridiculous.
Karl doesn't have me
wrapped around anything.
You accepted a house from him,
and you're nuts if you believe
he doesn't have
an ulterior motive.
He's Karl.
He's playing me.
But that house is gonna be
a great place
for my daughter to live.
And when he makes his move,
he's gonna realize that
I was really playing him.
So... about that ring...
I... I just don't want
to get deeper into this
and suddenly realize
your heart's somewhere else.
Mike, my heart is
in the exact right place.
Ugh. I can't have this conversation
now my tooth is throbbing.
Of course.
Okay.
You don't even wanna know
what my answer would have been?
Can we please
get out of here?
This place is gross.
And, God, I'm starving.
Yeah, I know, but we don't
have any money, remember?
That's why we should
go to my house.
I know the combination
to my Mom's safe.
Okay, I've told you
a thousand times,
It's way too risky. No.
- Something you should know before we embark
on this little adventure--
I can get pretty bitchy
when I'm not fed.
Listen, I hope
I'm not out of line here,
but did you ever spend
any time in prison?
What, you can tell
from my teeth?
Jailhouse dentistry--
unmistakable and not pretty.
Yeah, I did a little time
in Kansas a few years back.
Were you a prison dentist?
Uh, during dental school,
we did freebie work
on some of the poor guinea pigs
behind bars. No offense.
You know, I had the feeling
when I first saw you
In the movie theater
that we'd met before.
- I don't think so.
Oh, I'm pretty sure.
I think I know you.
Any chance I was
one of your guinea pigs?
No. the only prison work
I did was back in Virginia.
Diploma says you graduated
from Minnesota.
I'm licensed
in three states.
Open wide, please.
Don't talk.
I wouldn't want to hurt you.
Carlos, you promised
you'd come home today.
Well, I don't care
what Tanaka wants!
Rattling around
this stupid house all by myself
is not what I signed up for!
No, no, no, don't hang up on me.
I'm not done yelling at you!
Mrs. Solis.
How are you?
The best you've ever had.
What's so funny?
Me and my friend Justin
had this bet.
See who could lose
their virginity first
this summer at bible camp.
Guess I beat him
to the punch.
You were a virgin?
So it didn't show?
Uh, no.
No, I mean, I guess it was,
well, weird when
you started naming the American
presidents in order.
Ah, I wish you hadn't
heard that.
I was just trying to...
No, no, you were good.
Just, if it comes up in school,
Paul Revere was never president.
Oh. Thanks.
I, uh, had a really
awesome time, Mrs. Solis.
Well, good. I'm glad,
because this can
never happen again.
Why?
The only reason I did this
was because I was angry
at Carlos.
Now, thanks to you,
I'm not angry anymore.
Well, you should be.
I mean, the guy's never around.
Hell, he's probably off having
his own affair right now.
Oh.
I seriously doubt that.
How do you know?
Because Carlos doesn't have
an adulterous bone in his body.
What we just did
he could never do.
For him, sex isn't just sex.
It's a sign of intimacy.
It's the way he shows love.
You know, instead of
talking and listening
and spending time with me.
What was that for?
Thought you needed a kiss.
Well, since this is
our last time,
I guess we can make
the most of it.
So... you really trust him,
huh?
Completely.
Like all good mothers,
Gabrielle had purchased several
top-of-the-line baby monitors.
She had planned to use them
to keep a close watch
on her newborn child.
That plan was about to change.
So I'm gonna go shopping
and then I'm gonna see
my trainer,
and I'll definitely be gone
for, like, three hours.
Okay. Well, I gotta go.
Have fun.
not later, Penny.
Mommy's gotta change you now
'cause you stink.
Here, taste this.
Oh, man!
Xiao-mei,
that is amazing.
You like?
Oh, yeah.
Sorry if I'm making a mess.
It's okay. Mu shun pork
supposed to be messy.
I wish Gabrielle could
cook like this.
Have you ever tried
her enchiladas?
One time
they make me sick.
Ugh. He will,
and he'll meet you
for a romantic
motor home rendezvous,
and you'll propose,
he'll accept,
and you'll both live
happily ever after.
You really think
that's what's gonna happen?
It's my deepest hope.
Oh, there he is.
We're in.
POLLY? THAT'S A GOOD NAME.
NO WAY.
PAMELA.
I said I wanted Penny.
Oh, Lynette...
eight hours
of grueling labor.
That's not fair.
Neither are stretch marks,
but what are you gonna do?
I've only known one Penny
in my whole life,
And she was a slut.
- Isn't your aunt named Penny?
Yeah, that's her.
Our daughter
is officially named.
You may go now.
All right,
I'll let you win this one,
but I get to name
the next one.
You promised me
we'd stop at four.
Remember?
You wanted four kids,
I wanted one, and somehow
we compromised on four.
Can we please stop now?
Lynette, you're hurting me.
I will stop
as soon as you promise.
Okay, I promise.
Okay.
Honey, I...
I didn't mean to upset ya.
It's just...
We've been so happy.
Sweetie, sometimes when
you're at work,
and I'm home alone
with three young boys,
I'm not so happy,
and now I'm gonna be alone
with four kids.
Each one is a blessing,
yes,
but I don't think I can
take any more... blessings.
More blessings could make me
lose my mind.
Do you understand?
Yeah.
Thank you.
Honey, that really hurt.
Did it hurt for eight hours?
No.
Okay, then.
I must have been crazy,
agreeing to this.
Honey, you're gonna feel
differently
once you meet Kayla.
She is sweet,
smart little girl,
plus it'll help you get past
your resentment of Nora.
I don't...
Well, here goes.
Hey, you!
You must be Lynette.
And you must be Nora.
I guess it'd be weird
if we hugged.
Probably.
Wh-where's Kayla?
Oh, she didn't come.
We got into this huge fight,
and I was, like...
I just couldn't stand
to look at her face
on that long plane trip, so I
dumped her at the neighbors'.
But, hey, come on,
you got me.
So, anyway,
Kayla is doing great.
She's so pretty.
She's so smart.
She's practically a star
on her soccer team.
I have the cutest picture.
You know,
we wouldn't need a picture
if you had actually
brought her like you promised.
Oh, gosh, I'm sorry.
You know, but I just
haven't had much time
to get away on my own since,
um, I've been taking care
of your kid for
the past 11 years, Superdad!
Okay, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry.
I know it's been hard.
You've done an amazing job.
Thank you. I think, so, too.
Apology accepted.
Anyway, I wasn't sure
that I wanted Kayla here
if we were gonna talk
about business.
Business?
I was hoping that we could
talk about child support
Since I've got, like,
11 years coming to me, right?
You never told me
I had a daughter.
My lawyer thinks
that I have a very good case.
We can't afford this.
We have four kids.
Tom just lost his job.
That'd bankrupt us.
I'm the bad guy now
when he's the one
that knocked me up
and abandoned his child?
How could he abandon her if
he didn't even know she existed?
That doesn't let him
off the hook.
You know, you better do right
by me unless, of course,
you wanna be known
as Mrs. Deadbeat Dad!
Just take it easy.
Are we just gonna keep
talking louder?
Is that the plan?
You wanna just keep
raising your voice
'cause that's how you get
what you want, right?
You make a scene,
you throw a tantrum,
and everyone gets scared
and backs off.
Well, I don't work that way,
lady.
I don't care that my husband
was so phenomenally stupid
and/or drunk to actually
have sex with you.
I'm not gonna let it ruin
my life.
Am I talking loud enough
for that to get through to you?
I'm just gonna pay
the bill.
Karl, we've been through
a lot together.
We will always be connected
by Julie,
but... I know why
you bought me that house,
And I'm not moving into it.
Susie, come on, I--
Karl, we are not
getting back together.
Not ever. You need to just stop
and realize that it's over.
I'm gonna marry Mike.
So I need you
to sign these
because I have to be
divorced first.
Mike popped the question
No. He was going to, but then
you clocked him in the mouth
with a salad shooter,
remember?
Actually, I'm going to pop
the question to him
tomorrow night.
Guess it cuts down
on the suspense
knowing he bought you
a ring.
You would think so,
but, no, it doesn't.
This is a lot to ask
for a man
who still loves you, Susie.
I know.
But if you really do...
love me,
you'll let me go.
Okay, Susie.
I can do that.
Well, you know where to find me
if it doesn't work out.
Oh, shut up.
I don't see another way
to make this work.
We've gotta dip
into the pensions.
Oh, I don't like
the sound of that.
Well, it's that
or the kids' college fund.
We'll write Nora
one big check,
and in return,
she'll sign away her claim
for the back child support.
If we're lucky, she'll take
the bird in the hand.
Okay, what are we
talking about? How much?
Well, we need to show her
we're serious.
$30,000?
Are you kidding? $30,000?
If she takes you to court,
we'll lose
and end up paying
11 years of child support
all at once.
We could lose the house.
Oh, we are screwed.
We are just plain screwed.
- Tom!
I am trying very hard
to be strong right now,
and you melting down
is not helping me.
I'm sorry.
I know we're using up
a huge chunk of our savings,
but if it keeps that crazy woman
out of our life,
it is the best money
we have ever spent.
We will be okay.
Hey there.
I was surprised to hear
you wanted a session.
Well, there's nothing like
being tied to a bed
to change a girl's mind.
What do you wanna
talk about?
Anything at all.
As you said, I...
I have a lot of issues.
Well, I assumed as much
when you told
the ridiculous story
about your daughter
running off with a murderer.
Saw right through that,
did ya?
Well, I'm a trained
professional, Bree.
The human mind
is my playground.
Well, I'm glad
that you're having fun.
I'm sorry.
I don't mean to be flip.
But you came here
because you were troubled,
and then you refuse
any help we give you.
Things were falling apart
at home, and I just...
I just needed a place
to rest, that's all.
I think there's more to it
than that.
Do you?
I think it has to do
with your kids.
You don't want to talk
about them.
Why is that?
Probably because
I'm ashamed.
Ashamed?
My children were my life.
They were the reason that
I got up in the morning,
So to have failed them
as a parent...
You think you failed them
as a parent?
Well, my son is a sociopath,
and my daughter hates me enough
to have run away from home.
I'm certainly not gonna get
"Mother of the Year" anytime soon.
- If your kids were here right now,
what would you tell them?
- I would beg my son Andrew
for forgiveness
for having given up on him,
and I would tell my daughter
not to worry,
that I have a plan
to protect her.
And just what is that plan?
I've got everything
ready to go--
flowers, candles,
Elvis Costello CD all cued up.
But who has the ring?
- He does.
So, wait, you're gonna get
down on one knee,
pop the question,
and while you're down there,
dig in his pocket?
Then I'm gonna have to find
a way to force it on my finger.
Oh, Xiao-mei, where'd
you learn to kiss like that?
Sorry,
that's Penny's baby monitor.
It's always picking up weird frequencies.
- No, no, no! Don't turn it off.
Ohh! move over.
My knees hit the dashboard.
I move seat back. Better?
Oh, yeah.
Are you done
with my husband?
Good.
I have a little project
for you.
Okay, Gaby, can we please
talk about this?!
You're the one that gave me
permission, remember?
You said, "Go have sex with somebody"!
To have meaningless sex,
Carlos,
not to sleep with the woman
who's carrying our child!
What is the matter?!
Look, we're even!
You had an affair,
and I had an affair!
I had a reason to.
You were never here!
I've been here, Carlos.
I have tried so hard
to not be selfish
and to put your needs
above mine.
I mean, for God sakes,
look at me!
I have agreed to be
a mother for you!
Look, Gaby, you have
every right to be mad at me.
So I'm gonna go
and check into a hotel room
and let you cool down, but we
are going to work this out.
Forget the hotel, Carlos.
Get a lease.
I can go now, too?
No, you can start dinner.
What?!
You're not going anywhere,
not as long as you have
my baby in your belly.
I don't know what that meant,
but I didn't like the tone.
So just remember,
am the boss of you,
or else
I'm gonna make this
the worst nine months
of your life.
Hi.
- Hi.
Did you get the check?
Yeah, I wanted to talk
to you about that.
Do you have a minute?
Tom?!
I'm not the type of person
that can keep things
bottled up inside.
Really?
- So I'm just gonna have
to get this off my chest.
You made me feel really bad
about myself
yesterday at the restaurant.
My sincerest apologies.
You treated me
like some sort of mercenary,
like the only reason
I came here
was to extort money from you.
Well, to be honest,
first, we bought you pie,
then you tried
to extort money from us.
See? There it is again,
Lynette--that mean streak.
All I want is what's best for my child,
for Tom's child.
As the mother of 80%
of Tom's children,
I don't think
it's in their best interest
for you to drive us
into bankruptcy.
- Of course it isn't.
Here.
I signed the waiver
that the lawyer sent over
with the check.
And I'm not even asking
for any back child support.
That's--that's--that's great.
Thank you.
See, Lynette? See?
It's not all about money.
It's not even a little bit
about money. It's about family.
'cause we're all
a big family now.
Sort of.
Which is why I took
all the money that you gave me,
and I put it all down
on the sweetest little
2-bedroom house
over on Arden Drive.
Ar-Arden Drive over--
over by the mall?
Like, five minutes
from here Arden Drive?
It's perfect. I could drop
Kayla off here anytime
so she can play
with her new siblings.
She can spend time
with her Dad.
Well, to be clear,
how are you going to live?
How are you going to pay
the mortgage?
You don't have a job here.
- What is your problem
with me, lady?!
I don't understand!
You don't know me.
You don't know what I can do.
And yet you just always,
just...
just--just...
Always on the attack. It's ugly,
and you should work on that.
Here's what I think.
I think that we should
all work on this,
because I don't want
every Christmas to turn ugly
just because you and I
don't get along.
Yeah, that would be a shame.
See, I told you
she wasn't home.
Her car's not even here.
And you said the safe
was upstairs?
Damn it, my mother must have
changed the combination.
Okay. Wait here.
I'll be right back.
You did it.
You killed Melanie.
You put your jacket
on her body.
I saw it, Matthew.
The police showed me
the pictures.
Now you weren't there.
You don't know what happened.
Oh, God.
Caleb hurt her,
and Melanie threatened to bring
us all down because of that.
So your solution was to make
your brother think
he murdered a girl
and to make me think it?
What other choice did I have?
I knew that you wouldn't
had Caleb over to the police.
I knew that
you would protect him.
I would have protected you.
Well, I really couldn't
count on that.
Matthew...
you don't love me
as much as you love Caleb.
You never have.
Perhaps.
But it's because
he's needed me more.
You are always going to
find love in the world.
Don't you understand?
He was only ever
going to get it from me.
You know,
I know you believe that.
That's why I've tried
so hard to forgive you.
And who knows?
Maybe one day I will.
9-1-1.
- What is your emergency?
I need the police.
See, I told you
she had cash.
Danielle, I don't know
what you're planning,
but I need to talk to you
right now.
Give it up, Mom.
We're leaving.
I'm calling the police.
Do you remember
that girl Melanie Foster?
Matthew is the one
who killed her.
I know you don't want us
to be together,
but that's the lamest thing
I've ever heard.
His mother told me
what happened. It's true.
Let's go, Danielle.
Mom, please move.
No.
I gave up on your brother,
and I'm not gonna make
that mistake with you.
We don't have time for this.
Where did you get that?
What are you doing?!
Move away!
Danielle...
I want you to get out
of the house now.
He's a killer.
- Shut up!
Don't point that
at my mother!
Danielle!
I'm serious. Go.
What's wrong with you?!
I'm gonna shoot you!
Matthew, stop it!
If that's what it takes...
to get my daughter...
Stop it!
- To see who you really are...
Stop pointing that
at my mother!
Then fine.
What are you doing?!
Do it.
Stop!
It's okay, baby.
Hey, it's just me again.
Um...
When you got the invitation,
I thought that you gave me
the thumbs up,
but I guess
if that was actually...
some other type
of finger gesture, uh...
well, I apologize for leaving
you all these messages
and wasting your time.
This is the street
where I used to live...
and these were the people
with whom I shared my life.
I met them the day
they moved in.
And I saw
what they brought with them...
beautiful dreams
for the future.
And quiet hopes
for a better life...
not just for themselves,
but for their children, too.
If I could, would I tell them
what lies ahead?
Would I warn them
of the sorrow and betrayal
that lie in store?
No. From where I stand now,
I see enough of the road
to understand
how it must be traveled.
The trip
is to keep moving forward,
to let go of the fear
and the regret
that slow us down
and keep us from enjoying
a journey
that will be over too soon.
Yes, there will be
unexpected bends in the road,
shocking surprises
we didn't see coming,
but that's really the point...
don't ya think?
Orson.
- Oh, hey.
I wanted to come by
and see how you were doing
after your great escape,
and, uh, these are for you.
How sweet
and... unexpected.
Do you wanna come in?
I'd love to.