www.tvsubtitles.net
Previously on Desperate Housewives:
Why on earth would you let them
fingerpaint before breakfast?
It's my job to clean that up now,
so it's my call.
Some households reverse roles,
Let's give this another shot.
some old flames...
You want me back?
Yeah.
...were put out,
Has to be something you're ingesting.
Who prepares your meals?
I understand you've been having
some marital problems.
and while some learn to forgive,
Deirdre got pregnant before I went to jail.
Zach is your son, isn't he?
Yeah.
others could not bring
themselves to forget their past.
The remarkable thing about Danny
Farrell was that he had only
been a paperboy for 6 months,
and in that time he
had become the enemy of every
woman on Wisteria Lane.
If there was a puddle on someone's property,
he found it.
If a new rosebush had just been planted,
he destroyed it.
If a cat was enjoying a moment in the sun,
he ended it.
People wondered if Danny would ever change.
They should have talked to Susan Meyer.
She could have told them:
obnoxiuos boys tend to become
obnoxious men.
Just like the one she had been married to.
Hey!
Karl, I see you!
Stop right there!
Hey Suzie-cue.
What are you doing?
Just getting the paper.
That's Edie's paper. And this is Edie's house.
Do you have to do this now?
I haven't had my coffee yet.
Did you spend the night with Edie?!
Oh my God.
Suzie, just calm down.
You are forbidden from ever seeing her
again. You hear me? Forbidden!
We're divorced. You can't
tell me who I can date.
I live on this street.
Your daughter lives on this street.
I will not have you flaunting your
sexcapades in front of us!
Sexcapades?
- Forbidden!
I would love to continue this,
but it's time for breakfast.
And Edie is making me a frutada.
Well I just bet she is!
Mrs Meyer, I gotta talk to you.
Now's not a good time, Danny.
You're a month behing your payment.
I'll take care of it, I promise.
My dad says if you read
something you don't pay for,
that's the same as stealing.
Hi, Ida!
Can we talk about this later?
I just found out my ex is dating my neighbor,
and I'm really kicked off.
Same me!
I provide you with a service,
and I deserve to be paid for that service!
Yes, the women of Wisteria Lane
believed Danny Farrell to be the enemy.
Deadbeat!
They also believed:
The enemy of my enemy
is my friend.
season 2 episode 2
You Could Drive a Person Crazy
Beautiful lawns,
spacious homes,
happy families.
These are the hallmarks of suburbia.
But if you look
beneath the veneer of gracious living,
you will see a battle raging.
A battle for control.
You see the combattants everywhere,
engaged in their routine skirmishes,
fighting fiercely to have dominion
over the world around them,
all the while knowing
it's a battle they will lose.
Oh, honey, just stick that anywhere.
I'll take care of it.
Wow.
It's really pilin' up.
Don't worry. I have a system.
Really?
Yeah. Every two days, I clean.
Two days.
Yeah. Let the mess accumulate for two days,
and then I clean until it's sparkling,
and then the cycle starts all over again.
And why have I never seen the sparkling part?
'Cause by the time you get home from work,
the boys have messed everything up again.
See, that's what I would
call a flaw in the system.
What are you doing?
I think I'm asking you to clean the house.
Really? 'Cause it sounds to me like
you're criticizing me.
No!
No, nonono. No.
I'm not saying it has to be sparkling.
How many times did I come home to a mess,
and I never said a word!
Please don't take this the wrong way.
I think you are doing a terrific job.
But let's be clear: When you came home,
it was just -
cluttered.
I mean, come on. This is -
more than that.
Look at him. Just chatting away.
So inconsiderate.
Phyllis, we've only been waiting
here for 2 minutes.
Told you when we left the house
that I needed to eat.
I have low blood sugar.
You wanna see me keel over?
No.
In theory.
By the way, Mrs van de Kamp -
I heard about your husband's passing.
I'm so sorry.
Dr van de Kamp was one of my favorite
customers. Truly.
That's very sweet of you, thank you.
I'm not just being polite, Mrs van de Kamp.
How are you feeling?
Well, Mr Pashmutt -
We are holding up as best we
can under the circumstances.
I'm sorry, this is Rex's mother, Phyllis.
I'm so sorry about your son.
Thank you.
You know, the hardest thing is to lose a child.
I can't even imagine.
Come on, Phyllis,
let's get you something to eat.
We had no warning. I was doing
dishes when I got the call.
Really?
Phyllis, there are people waiting, so -
Excuse me, I'm so sorry, but -
My son just passed away.
Oh, I'm so sorry!
Thank you. I was telling Mr Pashmutt here -
My life is - is over!
My life is over!
This is ridiculous, you know that?
Pen.
Don't you think I have better
things to do than to bring you your
checks every day?
Checks that I could be signing at home.
This one's dry.
You know, taking away my access to
our account, that's just vindictive.
Thank you.
You know how long it takes me to
schlepp out here to this hellhole?
Exactly. It's the only way I
can guarantee you come and visit me.
That's ridiculous.
You're my husband, I love you.
Obviously I would come visit.
I thought it was obvious that
when you loved someone,
you wouldn't have an affair.
I was wrong, wasn't I?
I'm geting really tired of this song, Carlos.
Isn't it about time you forgave me?
You want my forgiveness, you got it.
My trust -
that you gonna have to earn.
Be careful, Carlos.
Up until now, I've been really
lonely in that big bed of ours.
But when you're rude to me,
it makes me wanna be not so lonely.
Comments like that are exactly why
you'll never again have access to my money.
Why are all rich men jerks?
Same reason all beautiful women are bitches.
So, same time tomorrow?
Sure, baby.
What do you mean, you know?
- I mean, I know.
What are you saying?
That your father actually told you
he was gonna be having a one night
stand with Edie Britt?
Uh Mom, this wasn't a one night stand.
He's been going out with Mrs Britt for
a few months now.
What?
How could you not tell me that?
We share everything, that's what we're
known for! That's our thing!
Because I knew you'd wig out!
Besides, haven't you always told me to
respect people's privacy?
I'd never apply that concept to your
father's sex life, and you know it.
Are you done?
- No!
I have not even begun ripping
into Edie Britt yet!
Och, that peroxide vulture!
I just know, as sure as I am standing here,
that she went after your father
just to tick me off.
Wrong again.
- What?
He asked her out.
- You lie.
It's true.
He called her for a date 6 months ago.
The day after my birthday party.
The one at the piano bar?
Yeah.
What is it?
Oh, uh - your father just came over
that day and - told me some stuff.
Some stuff that I haven't - that I can't
tell you.
Wait. Whatever happened to you,
we share everything.
Ain't that "our thing"? "What we're known for"?
Uhm - actually, I think what we're
known for is sharing clothes.
Yeah. I think that's our thing.
Why does he keep doing that?
He knows it's annoying.
He's just trying to get to us.
That one is working.
Knock it off down there,
do you hear what I'm saying?
Matthew. Matthew!
Sit down!
You know we don't talk to him.
That's part of his punishment.
How can you just sit here, hour after hour,
and listen to that?
Well, that's part of mine.
Carlos, what is this big emergency?
I had to cancel my hair appointment
with Eduardo today.
What is it?
I'm completely freaked out.
Why?
There's this guy, his name's Ritchie,
and he's been saying some stuff to me,
and I'm gone worried.
Honey, you and your macho pride.
Just tell him you're flattered,
but you don't swing that way.
He's not hitting on me, you idiot,
he's threatening me!
Really? How?
He said he's gonna beat me up unless
I come up with some money.
How much money?
$7,000.
$7,000?
Keep your voice down!
Why would he think you have that kind of money?
Because yesterday, in a visiting
room filled with criminals,
my wife referred to me as "a rich man".
Oh, really? Sorry.
That's why I needed you to bring the checkbook.
He's actually willing to take a check?
No! You're gonna take the money to
his girlfriend,
and if she doesn't get it by tomorrow,
I'm screwed.
Honey, I think this is a mistake.
If we give in to extorsion,
the guy's just gonna keep coming
back for more money.
What choice do I have?
You're a strong guy.
You went to college on an athletic
scholarship, for God's sakes.
Yeah, it was for golf!
You have all my pants.
Yeah, I know. Come on in.
I thought when I took my stuff
back to my house I got everything, but -
That's fine. They're in the garage.
So how've you been doing?
- Good, um -
Good.
I have a question for you.
Sure, what is it?
Where are we now?
Where are we?
Yeah.
We're not moving in together,
and we're not broken up, so -
where are we?
I don't know.
Since the guy who held me hostage
turned out to be your son,
logic dictates that I should move on...
Problem is -
I'm crazy about you.
So...
So I'm thinking we should keep it casual.
Casual.
What the hell does that mean, exactly, casual?
Uh, well -
I don't think there is anything wrong
with us seeing a movie once in a while.
Movie? OK. Is that it?
Jogging?
There's no law against jogging.
Anything else?
Shopping.
That's casual. That's fun.
Anything else we can do?
Anything at all?
Mmmm, brunch. Brunch would be nice.
Sounds good to me.
Oh, I can do this. Take it one day at a time.
Yes. Oh, oh, OK.
Thanks so much for calling.
Who's that?
Oh, someone named Alan Henley.
My electrician?
How are you on the phone
sobbing to my electrician?
Oh, he called to offer you his condolences.
Then why didn't you put me on?
Oh, well, we got to talking,
and then he had to go.
He had some very beautiful
things to say about Rex.
For God's sakes, Phyllis.
Don't you ever worry about dehydration?
Are you saying that I am too emotional?
I am saying that even Italians
take a break now and again.
My son is dead!
I'm grieving!
So am I.
But no one would never know it with
your insistent caterwauling!
Bree!
People want to know how I'm doing,
but the minute they ask you,
you jump into the spotlight and they
forget all about me!
I need consoling too, Phyllis.
Have you ever thought of that?
I'm sorry.
It won't happen again.
- Thank you.
Of course, if you didn't constantly
suppress your emotions,
people wouldn't forget to console you.
Excuse me?
It's true. You're stolid to
the point of being cold.
I am not cold. I just -
I don't like public displays of emotion.
That's fine. But people wonder why they
haven't seen you cry.
Some people actually
wonder if you truly mourn Rex.
People have said that?
A few, yes.
Excuse me, I'm looking for Rita Rivera?
Hi, are you Rita?
Yeah, who are you?
I'm Gabrielle Solís.
Our husbands are roommates at the prison.
Ritchie and I aren't married.
Oh, I see. Well,
your boyfriend asked my husband
to give this to you.
It's a - a sort of favor.
It's all there. $7,000.
Son of a bitch!
Oh, don't even think about it.
Um - hello! Is there a problem?
I want to ask you a question.
- OK.
This might seem kinda weird.
What do you think of my breasts?
Excuse me?
How do they look to you?
They're - they're nice.
Thank you. I like them too.
You're right, that was weird.
You have no idea what this money is for,
do you?
No. You seem to have - everything you need...
Ritchie wants me to get a boob job.
He wants 'em bigger.
He's obsessed with huge breasts.
So are you gonna do it?
I told him if he came up with cash I would.
I just never thought the moron would
actually come up with it.
Not that it's any of my business, but -
it's your body.
I wouldn't change anything
unless I really wanted to.
If I don't do it, he'll leave me.
Honey, he's in jail. How far is he gonna go?
Maybe it's time you stood up for yourself.
Tell him you don't need the surgery.
It's worth a shot.
There you go.
I'm so proud of you.
When Lynette went back to work,
she was aware her new job would be demanding.
What she hadn't anticipated
was the nightshift.
Hey, how are you.
Thought I heard you coming about an hour ago?
I did. I had to load the dishwasher.
You didn't have to do that.
Yeah, I sort of did.
I'm sorry. I've just fallen
behind with my housework.
I just had so many errands to run today.
I'll make up for it tomorrow, OK? I promise.
That's the beauty of my system. It's flexible.
You know, for the sake of our marriage,
please don't mention the system again.
I said I'm sorry.
What in the world -?
Don't touch it. Penny had a little -
um, spitty up here on the sheet.
And you didn't change them?
The towel's very clean.
That's disgusting.
No, it's just a little milk
spit-up on the sheet.
Please, I made a judgment call.
Please respect that.
No, I can't respect that, and do you know why?
It's stupid.
I'm gonna get new sheets.
We're not changing the sheets.
Why are you yelling at me?
I'm not yelling at you,
and this is not about spit-up.
Of course it is.
No it isn't. It's about control.
And as you and I both know,
you have some issues in this area.
Why are you fighting so hard
to sleep on baby vomit?
I'm fighting for a principle.
Being too lazy to change the sheets
is not a principle.
You know what? You're not gonna win this one.
So you better just crawl back into bed.
Let's go to sleep.
No! Come on!
No, you come on! Just get off!
Mine! Mine! Mine!
Normally, Lynette would have
spent a sleepless night telling
herself she didn't have control issues.
But she couldn't.
She was too busy figuring out how
to bend Tom to her will.
Hello?
Hi!
Welcome to the promised land.
Go on! There.
Good job!
Uh, Betty? Betty!
Betty, can I ask you a question?
Of course.
It's Susan, right?
- Yes, hi.
I was just wondering, are you having
some remodeling done on your
house or something?
No. Why?
Well - I work at home, so I'm home a lot,
and I just keep hearing these noises lately.
It's hard to concentrate.
Well, I haven't noticed anything.
Really?
It sounds like it's coming from your house.
It's like a clanging, clanging -
There, that was it! Did you hear it?
Oh. Yes.
Matthew is very handy. He's always doing
part jobs around the house.
I guess I just don't notice the noise anymore.
Even at 2 o'clock in the morning?
Cause that's kinda hard to miss.
I'm so sorry.
Matthew is something of an insomniac, Susan.
But I will talk to him,
and we'll put a stop to it.
Good afternoon, Mrs Meyer.
Hi, Matthew.
Well, it was nice chatting with you, Susan.
This is my 3rd phone call, Mr Flannery,
and if someone doesn't call me back soon,
I'm going to be irritated.
Is everything all right?
That darned insurance
company is dragging its heels on paying
Rex's policy, and I don't understand why.
Well, he died unexpectedly.
And that brings up a lot of questions.
It's probably easier when
people are just diseased.
Probably.
Hi. Hi.
- Hi, Lynette.
I'm sorry. Am I interrupting?
No, not at all.
I saw you walk in,
and I've been meaning to call
since the service, but work's
How are you doing?
Uhm, I'm all right.
Well, you look amazing.
- Do I?
Absolutely.
Well, I can't imagine what
you're going through.
Phyllis?
You're going to have to stop that.
I can't help it.
When people talk about Rex,
I-I just get emotional.
Well, I'm very sorry for your loss too,
Phyllis.
He was my firstborn.
I don't know what I will do without him.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
- Oh! Oh!
Is she gonna be OK?
Um - yeah! Sure!
Hold on a second.
Here we go. Feel better?
Lynette, you were saying?
I forgot.
That's all right. It was really
sweet of you to stop by.
OK.
So, are we ready to order or do
you need a little more time?
I've been in the insurance industry for
15 years. I've never recieved a phone
call like this.
I'm having second thoughts about Rex's death.
I've known Rex and Bree for nearly 20 years,
and I've never had any reason to suspect
they were anything but a happy, loving couple.
But just why this seems so strange?
I found it in Rex's room after he called in.
"I forgive you".
George! What are you doing here?
I'm here to kidnap you.
What?
Get your purse.
I'm gonna take you balling.
I-I don't know how to ball.
Or to the movies, or for a frozen yoghurt.
Whatever you want.
Thank you, but I just couldn't.
Bree. I'm sure you haven't
gone anywhere in weeks.
You gotta get out, do things.
It'll help, trust me.
I do. I'm just not ready yet.
But it was very sweet of you to think of me.
Uh, you know. I tried.
And I appreciate that.
It's all right. Let it out.
You want me to die in here, don't you?
Carlos, what happened?
What do you mean, what happened?
You talked Rita out of taking the money.
Is that what Ritchie said?
Yeah, the subject came up in between
kidney punches.
Well, it's not my fault.
She didn't want the money.
Why wouldn't she want $7,000?
Because it's for a boob job.
So?
- So, her boobs are fine.
And honestly, what he's
doing to her self-esteem is just cruel.
I feel sorry for her.
Please. You don't care about her
self-esteem any more than I do!
You just didn't want to give up all that money!
Well, I do think it's silly to give
someone $7,000 if they don't want it.
Listen to me.
You're gonna go back there.
You're gonna put that money in Rita's hands,
and you're gonna convince her
that life is not worth living
unless she has jugs the size of Texas,
do I make myself clear?
I just realized Rita and I
have a lot in common.
Please don't tell me you have low self-esteem.
Cause if I laugh now,
I'm gonna
crack the one good rib that I have left.
We're both controlled by our husbands,
which is idiotic because they're
both behind bars.
We should have all he power.
I'm not trying to control you!
I just don't want to end up in the morgue.
This isn't about that.
Gabrielle, the morphine's wearing off.
I really don't have time for this.
Me either, Carlos.
And if you expect me to go
back and sweet-talk her into
getting the operation -
I can't show up empty-handed.
Fine. Bring me the checkbook,
I'll make out a check for some cash.
See, I was thinking I'd be writing the checks.
Gabrielle -
Careful, Carlos.
You're not in a position to argue.
Yoohoo! Susan!
Hey, Edie.
So, whee! How much do you hate me?
What?
Oh, Karl said that you know all about
our dirty little secret.
Yess. Yes I do.
Well, I feel awful.
I should've told you that I was doing your ex.
It would've been the classy thing to do.
Well, etiquette is a lost art for
a lot of people.
You've got to believe me,
I never ever thought anything
would happen with us.
But on our first date,
Karl took me to a Mexican restaurant.
You know what I get like when I drink tequila.
Couple of shooters, and my bra unhooks itself.
Circumstances beyond your control, I get it.
So, if you'll excuse me.
Hey!
I am offering you an opportunity here!
Go ahead. Vent. Let me have it.
Come on, tell me what a bitch I am.
Yeah, for snacking on your leftovers,
I deserve a... Come on, bring it on!
Honestly, Edie, I don't mind.
You can skate off into the sunset
with Karl. Be my guest.
That's good to know.
I probably shouldn't tell you this, but -
we were in my jacuzzi last night -
uhhhh! Karl
said it was the best sex he's ever had.
Bar none.
Actually, I'm glad that you shared that,
because
here's a tidbit for you:
Karl said he's still in love with me.
Edie, what are you doing?
You are a lying liar.
We're in the middle of the street.
Would you get out of here?
Karl never said that!
Karl asked me to get back
together the day after Julie's birthday.
I said no, which I'm guessing is the reason for
the now legendary tequila bra-popping incident.
Please let go.
- Oh no.
We're not finished here.
Yes we are. I'm gonna go.
You don't have the guts!
In 5 seconds, I'm gonna punch it!
- Yeah? I'll kill your car!
Not if you're sucking my exhaust, you won't!
Take back what you said!
- No I won't!
Admit it you'd do anything to
destroy my happiness!
Edie, for God's sake.
Why would I care if you went out with
a man I despise?
Cause you and Mike are finished.
Yup. Word's out.
And now that you can't be happy,
you don't want anyone else to be. Period.
Edie, come back here! We're not finished yet!
It was an accident, Karl.
Edie knows it was an accident, right?
She knows you could have killed her.
As it is, she's got a shattered tibia.
Oh my God. I'm so sorry.
I sent roses. Did she get the roses?
Yep. She cut herself on the thorns.
Oh my God.
Why did you tell Edie
about our little conversation?
She was gloating about sleeping with you,
and I just wanted to shut her up.
Oh. So you were jealous?
No! No.
We were married.
And she's trying to make that tawdry
little affair you guys have
going on par with that.
I got mad.
Susan, you remember the morning you saw
me with Edie's paper?
Well, the night before I had asked her
if she'd like to live together.
And she said yes.
Susan?
Just give me a moment.
I'm asking God to kill me.
Look. She's fun, she goes with the flow.
At this time in my life, I need that.
Are you in love with her?
Would you care if I were?
I want you to be happy.
I even sort of want Edie to be happy, but -
But what?
I want to be happy first.
Mike and I were supposed to move in together.
This was supposed to be my time.
I heard you and the plumber
were having problems.
Is it over?
I don't know.
It's really complicated.
You never answered my question: Are you
in love with her?
I don't know.
But I can promise you this much:
I've never loved another
woman the way I loved you.
You walked out on me.
Yeah. But look how far I got.
I'm just up the street.
Mommy, Mommy, thank God you're home!
Hey sweetie!
Why? What's wrong?
Daddy caught a rat.
Wow. Did he, now?
Honey?
I'm home!
Hey, babe.
- Hey!
Hi. How was your day?
It was good.
But more importantly, how was yours?
Parker told you about the rat, huh?
Yyyup.
My God, it was so disgusting.
I can't understand.
There it was sitting on the counter,
eating a leftover grilled cheese sandwich.
The sandwiches from yesterday?
OK, yes, the house has been too messy.
Obviously, my system has some kinks in it.
But check it out, I got my act together.
- Wow!
So I take it you took the rat outside?
Oh no.
I smashed it with the shovel.
You killed it?
Not at the first blow.
Disgusting.
Hey, little guy.
I just wanted to say I'm really
sorry about what happened.
With the shovel.
Neither one of us saw that coming.
I know it's not much consolation,
but you really helped my marriage.
That's a lot for a little rat to
accomplish in one lifetime.
Well, it's getting late, so -
Hats off to you.
So you'd say the abuse started a
few years into your marriage?
It started so slowly I didn't
realize what was happening.
When he slapped me, that was a little problem.
But he'd always apologize.
Then it got worse, and one day, 8 years ago,
my son spilt soda on our new carpet.
Before I could move to protect him,
Virgil had knocked him on the ground
and began kicking him.
I went to protect my baby,
but I didn't get there in time.
What happened to your son?
He died.
I came across Monty's baby
pictures last weekend,
and that's when the nightmare started again.
The last doctor I saw said that I needed
to let go of my guilt and start living again.
Of course, that's easier said than done.
And I am getting so tired.
I want you to start on Nitrozepam.
That should do the trick.
- Thank you.
I certainly hope your
husband was punished for what he did.
Yeah. He got his retribution.
I made sure of that.
Where are you off to?
I'm - I'm going to see Rex's lawyer.
We're going to go over some details
involving Rex's will.
Phyllis -
Obviously, I'm just mortified
over slapping you.
I've just been in a weird place since
Rex's death, but that's no excuse.
I'm very, very sorry.
No need to apologize.
Your family - all's forgiven.
Really?
It's been a difficult time for all of us.
I totally understand.
Now go. Don't want to be late for your
meeting about Rex's will.
Claims, this is Joe Flannery.
Hello. Could I speak to someone
about the death
benefits for Rex van de Kamp, please?
This is his mother.
Yes. We'd already spoken to his wife
several times.
We are moving as quickly as we can.
Are you aware
that my daughter-in-law has a boyfriend?
I'm listening.
Control.
It's extraordinary the tactics
people employ to obtain it.
Some rely on deception,
while others engage in outright trickery.
Then there are those who resort to extorsion.
Why do we fight so hard for control?
Because we know: To lose it
is to put our fate in the hands of others.
And what could be more dangerous?