Previously on "Desperate Housewives"...
The riot left victims in its wake.
- Do I need a transplant?
- You need to come to terms
with the reality of what's happened to you.
We'd like to know where exactly you were
when your husband was shot.
My wife is the one person
on that backstabbing street
- that I can trust.
- So what am I supposed to do,
- just pretend Grace doesn't exist?
- Yes!
Gaby's biological daughter was erased,
and she struggled to cope.
I slept with Tom.
And Lynette learned the truth.
Tom Scavo had a 20-year-old secret.
He had once slept with
his wife's best friend.
Tom felt it no longer mattered.
But his wife, who had just
learned this secret...
felt differently.
That's why she had decided to punish him...
and torture him...
and humiliate him.
Lynette planned to tell
her husband she knew.
But first, she was determined...
to have her revenge.
What are my keys doing on the floor?
Did my pants just... rip?
- Yeah. You might wanna go up and change.
- Wow.
Thank God I wasn't going commando.
I'm sorry you had to see that.
Is that a seam ripper?
Could be. I don't really sew.
Did you do something to Tom's pants?
Lynette.
It's just a thing I do
whenever I find out he slept
with one of my friends.
- Ugh! I knew
I shouldn't have told you about us.
- But you did.
So this is how you're getting back at him?
Isn't it a little immature?
My rage needs an outlet.
And you got to admit,
it beats smashing his head in with a 9-iron.
Well, there is another option.
- You could tell him you know
and deal with it.
- No.
- Well, why not?
- Because then he'll tell me he's sorry,
and I'll cry, and he'll cry,
and then I'll get over it.
And I'm not ready to get over it.
I have a lot of anger to work through
before we sweep this
under the carpet and move on,
so please don't tell him what I'm doing.
- But, Lynette, it...
- Come on.
It's not like anybody's getting hurt.
Ooh!
Tom! Are you okay?
Yeah. I slipped on something.
Peanut butter? How... What...
Those damn kids.
Yes, Lynette Scavo had developed
a taste for revenge.
And she was finding it delicious.
We pass by these people every day.
We sense their isolation...
but we just keep walking...
telling ourselves there's nothing
we can do to help...
which we know is a lie.
Hello, reverend. Wonderful sermon today.
Thank you, Bree. Do you have a moment?
- I need to talk to you about something.
- Sure.
One of our parishioners is going
through a personal crisis.
She's in desperate need of a friend...
someone to talk to.
And you thought of me? I'm flattered.
So you wouldn't mind reaching out
to this lost lamb?
Oh, you are the very milk of human kindness.
Now, stop. I'm happy to help.
Unless you're talking about
Beth Young, in which case
- I'd rather shave my head
and join the hare Krishnas.
- Bree!
I'm sorry, but she is married to
the biggest lunatic in Fairview.
He tried to destroy our neighborhood,
and she did nothing to stop him.
Still, the Christian thing
is to offer her solace.
After all,
"Let him who is without sin
cast the first stone."
John, chapter 8, verse 7.
What about,
"the righteous will be glad
when they are avenged,"
"when they bathe their feet
in the blood of the wicked"?
Psalm 56, verse 10.
"If you do not forgive others their sins,"
"your father will not forgive yours."
Matthew, chapter 6, verse 15.
"Whoever does not obey the laws of God"
"must surely be punished
by death or banishment."
Ezra, chapter 7, verse 26.
"Bree Van De Kamp is shacking up
with her boyfriend."
Cynthia Thomas, pew 5, seat 7.
Fine. I'll talk to her.
But this is spiritual blackmail!
I'm a man of God, Bree.
I do what it takes to get the job done.
Everything's delicious, Gaby.
Thank you. I'm glad you guys could come.
You know us. We never turn down
a champagne brunch.
- Who said anything about champagne?
- I did.
Come on, people! We need some bubbly!
We gotta celebrate!
Celebrate what?
- You...
- Okay, it's kind of a long story.
It all started last year.
We're adopting a child.
You were killing the moment.
Meet Liza Hunter-McDermott.
Liza?
Guess who lost that coin toss.
She's beautiful.
There was a 2-year wait for a baby.
But we found this orphanage
that had lots of older kids.
So we figured, why not? She's 10 years old.
And if all goes well, she's ours next month.
Well, we're really happy for you guys.
Aren't we, Gaby?
Gaby, what's wrong?
Uh, nothing. I'm thrilled for you. Really.
Oh, honey. We didn't even think...
- With everything you've been going through...
- She's fine.
It's just...
I don't even know where Grace is, or...
- how she is,
or when I'm gonna see her again.
- Gaby.
We didn't mean to upset you guys.
It's fine. She's gone,
and now Gaby and I are moving on.
And we've agreed not to talk about it
because it is so painful.
I'm sure you understand.
Of course.
So, please, tell us more
about your little girl.
- What is she like?
- Uh, you're gonna love her.
- I mean, she's so smart and so funny.
- The first time
we walked in that room,
there was this instant connection.
- We just knew she was ours.
- You know what?
We should make a toast to little Liza.
I'm gonna get that champagne.
Look who I found.
Julie!
What are you doing here?
I told you not to fly home.
Oh, mom. Haven't you learned
I don't listen to a word you say?
Besides, they won't let you
mail a major organ.
Oh, no. No, don't even think about it.
- You are not gonna be my donor.
- I did tons of research.
They have these new surgical techniques.
It's no worse than a belly piercing...
- Which I did not do.
- You know, the doctor did say
that blood relatives are
your best chance for a match.
Honey, you are not going
through the rest of your life
- with only one kidney.
- But, mom...
- No. I'm going on the wait list.
- That could take years.
You know, there is another option.
Somebody who's close to you
that loves you very much.
We've been through this.
You're not the right blood type.
I meant your mother.
My mother?
Mike, I already lost my kidney.
Now you want me to lose my mind?
No, no, no, no.
We are not asking her for a kidney.
No. In fact, we're not even
telling her about this.
We're not?
Of course not. Uh... if she heard
one word about this...
- Oh, my God. Julie, what did you do?
- I'm sorry. I...
You're hurt. I thought you'd want her
to know. And, uh...
- She'll be here tomorrow.
- Oh, my God!
I-I've gotta get out of here. Unhook me.
- Unhook me!
- No, no. Susan, this is good.
You need a kidney, she's got a kidney...
That I will be paying
for the rest of my life!
"How come you haven't visited?
I gave you my kidney."
"Why won't you friend me on Facebook?
No. This is a nightmare.
You owe me, Julie... big.
You're right.
How about I give you a kidney?
Bigger than that.
Don't react.
- Aah!
- Good not reacting.
What the hell are you doing back there?
I can't let her see me talking to you.
- Who?
- Lynette. She knows.
Knows what? A-about us?
- How?
- Who cares how?
The point is, she found out.
- Why hasn't she said anything to me?
- Oh, she's saying it...
Your pants splitting open,
falling down the stairs...
Haven't you noticed you've
- been a little accident-prone lately?
- That was her?
- Mm.
- So she's responsible for my flat tire?
Mm-hmm.
- The sardines in my gym bag?
- Yep.
- The gay porn in my powerpoint presentation?
- Her proudest moment.
So she's just gonna keep
on screwing with me?
I mean, what else has she got planned?
I don't know, but she is one angry woman.
Be careful. God knows what she'll do next.
Ow! What the hell are you doing?
Testing the brakes before
I get on the highway.
Hi! I-I haven't seen you out in a while,
so I thought I'd stop by
and see how you were doing.
What do you really want?
Um...
Well, I talked to reverend Sykes yesterday,
and he tells me that
you've been going through
kind of a rough patch.
Come on in.
You know, growing up,
I didn't really have a lot of friends.
We weren't a very... social family.
But I was never hated.
Nobody hates you.
But they hate my husband... don't they?
I just wish people could understand him.
He is not a bad man. It's just,
his life has been so difficult.
He went to prison for
a murder he didn't commit.
His wife killed herself.
His son hates him.
He's been through a lot.
Well, I may not be able to
convince people to like Paul,
but there's no reason
you should suffer for what he's done.
I am having the girls over this week,
and I think it would be wonderful
if you'd join us.
Oh.
That's very sweet.
But I think we both know
those women aren't gonna want me there.
Those women are my dear friends.
Trust me. They'll be fine with it.
And if they're not?
Well, then I'll just have to
twist some very dear arms.
Okay, Mrs. Delfino. You're all hooked up.
Where's my daughter?
- They said she was down here.
Do you see her?
- Oh, God.
- Are you in pain?
- No, but I will be.
Oh! Susan.
Mom.
Oh, my poor, sick baby.
Hello, Mike. Oh, honey.
I have a surprise for you.
One of your favorite things from home.
Get in here!
Aunt Claire.
She figured I was cheaper than flowers.
Uh, Mike, you haven't met my aunt.
Uh, she taught me how to make
a Manhattan when I was 8.
I had her up to old fashioneds
by the time she was 12...
and that's a difficult drink.
She's like the bartender I never had.
Aw. So, sweetheart,
your mother tells me
you have a deformed kidney.
I told her not to sleep on her side.
Well, we're hoping to
find a donor very soon.
Oh. Wouldn't that be nice?
I wonder who it'll be.
You read all these stories...
strangers brought together
through life-threatening circumstances.
Our best bet is a match within the family.
Oh!
Like Julie!
No.
M. J.
He's 9, mom.
You don't take a kidney out of a 9-year-old.
Well, it'd take care of
that bed-wetting problem,
though, wouldn't it?
You know, we were actually thinking
that... you might be
a possible donor, Sophie.
Oh.
O-oh.
"Oh"?
What do you mean, "oh"?
Well, it... it's... it's just...
it... it's...
I can't believe this.
She's not gonna do it.
Of course, she wants to.
It's... it's just the timing of things.
Morty and I are about to take a cruise...
for three months.
A cruise?
Nonrefundable.
And you won't even get tested.
You know, we haven't even
checked in at the hotel yet.
- Uh, why don't we do that?
- Yes, okay.
We'll be back in an hour or two.
And if you're better,
if you feel like it,
maybe we'll take you shopping.
Actually, I'm having my blood washed
for the next six hours.
But go! You two have fun.
♪ I've been workin' on the railroad ♪
♪ All the livelong day ♪
♪ I've been workin on the railroad ♪
♪ Just to pass the time away ♪
Hey there.
Oh! Perfect timing.
I made your favorite...
double fudge brownies.
Well, I had a big lunch,
and I don't want any more pants ripping,
so... no, thanks.
What are you talking about? You look great.
Have one. It won't kill ya.
Yeah. Maybe later.
Are you sure? They're tasty.
Ooh. Brownies. Can I have one?
Uh... no.
Yeah. Sure, Penny, have one.
No!
I mean... I don't want her
to spoil her dinner.
Besides, I made these for your dad.
Oh, I can share.
Here, Penny. Take it.
Eat it.
No!
Aha!
You guys are weird.
What'd you put in there...
cayenne pepper? Drain cleaner?
So Renee told you.
I am gonna kill her.
Let's get back to how
you're trying to kill me!
Don't you dare act like
the injured party here.
You betrayed me! You had an affair!
It wasn't an affair!
It was completely meaningless!
It was after we were engaged!
No, we had broken up, remember?
No, no, we were taking a break, remember?
Yes, we were fighting constantly,
so we decided to spend some time apart
to decide whether we were gonna
get married or split up.
- Right!
- So I went to my mom's house
to think about it,
and I will never forget this.
I was sitting in the kitchen.
My mom was making a frittata.
And I thought,
"oh, I should make that for Tom,"
and then it hit me. There might be no Tom.
I might never see you again.
And I had an epiphany.
I didn't want a life without you in it.
Yeah. I was at a crossroads,
and I chose the path that included you,
and you know what kills me?
While I was making that decision,
you were off...
sleeping with my best friend.
Ohh! That was fun. Mm-hmm.
I've been kind of down lately, and, well...
nothing like a little retail therapy.
Yes, I'd say you had a real breakthrough
around the fourth shoe store.
Please tell me Carlos isn't having an affair
with a tiny naked person.
Celia! Juanita!
Oh, my God! What the hell are you doing?!
Playing with my new doll.
Look, she can leap off cliffs.
No, no! This is not your doll!
Then whose is it? I found it in your closet.
Oh, my God. Where's her arm?
Where's her arm?!
Ohh. For God sakes.
Celia, this is not a toy!
Yeah, it is.
No! It's not! It's something
special that belongs to me!
It is mine, and no one
can take it away from me!
I'm sorry. I couldn't help overhearing.
Is everything okay in here?
Mommy's mad because we played with her doll.
Go to your room. Go! Both!
Your doll?
Of course it's not mine.
It's... a gift for Bob and Lee.
They're adopting a little girl.
Let me get your discharge papers,
- and I'll be back to wheel you out.
- Thank you.
Hey, uh, Mike's bringing
the car around front.
I will, uh, get your bag.
Hey, what is that on your arm?
Did you get a blood test?
- I just... wanted to see...
- I am not taking your kidney.
Relax. I wasn't a match.
But if I was and I didn't check,
I never would've forgiven myself.
Come here.
You know...
When you were growing up,
sometimes I felt like I was just winging it.
And then I see
the incredible woman you've become,
and I know I did something right.
Wh-where's my daughter? Did they move her?
I'm telling you,
it's the other end of the hall.
I'm here!
Ohh! Hello, sweetie.
What are you doing?
Well, you're getting discharged today,
and I came to help.
Let me take that bag.
No. I wouldn't want you to pull something
and not be able to play
shuffleboard on your cruise.
Well... how about I take us all out
for a nice lunch?
I can't. I'm on a restricted diet,
and M. J. is waiting for me at home.
I'd like to be there for my child.
Come on. Let's go.
Let me at least push your chair.
I'm good.
Susie, I want to help.
You do not get to "help"
by pushing my wheelchair.
You had your chance to help.
Susan, be fair.
No!
How could you refuse to even be tested?
My own mother!
Julie couldn't wait to hand
over one of her kidneys.
Well, there you go. Problem solved.
I wasn't a match.
That is not the point.
You only had a 15% chance of being a match.
That meant there was an 85% chance
that I'd never know
how little you cared about me.
I could've gone the rest of my life
thinking you were a wonderful mother
- who had the wrong kind of kidney.
- Now wait a second here...
No, no, no, no, Claire. It's okay.
I am... sorry I disappointed you, honey.
Hey.
Can we talk for a minute?
That depends. Are you alone?
- Yes.
- Then we can talk. You wanna come in?
- That depends. Do you have beer?
- Yes.
Then I'll come in.
I, uh, I need a favor.
I want you to let your mom off the hook.
No way. I'm... I'm done with her.
Susan, there are some...
things you don't know.
Like what?
What could you possibly tell me
that would excuse her behavior?
I'm her daughter. This is my hour of need,
and she's not even trying to help.
No. I'm not gonna forgive her
for this, ever.
She has cancer.
What?
Breast cancer.
They caught it early,
and... we'll see how it goes.
She's starting chemo next week.
Well, what about the cruise?
That is the cruise.
That's the story we're telling
because she didn't want you to know.
And that's why...
she can't give you a kidney.
Why wouldn't she tell me?
This doesn't make sense.
You know mom. I mean, since when
has she passed up a chance for attention?
Exactly. When she heard about
what you've been going through,
she... she decided no, not this time.
She wasn't gonna burden you.
And I jumped all over her.
I gotta go talk to her...
No, no. Don't tell her you know.
Why not?
Susan, please.
Respect what she's trying to do here.
She's trying to make up for
a lifetime of "me, me, me."
Let her.
Oh, dear. This is why people
should never let children play with dolls.
But don't worry.
I'll have Princess Valerie
all sewn up and good as new
- by the end of the day.
- Thank you so much.
Can I ask you something?
Of course.
Am I... weird for being
so attached to a doll?
I only bought her because
I thought she was beautiful,
and she reminded me of someone,
but lately... I'm starting
to feel like I need her.
She... calms me down when I get upset,
and I enjoy spending time with her.
The thought of leaving here without her
is really upsetting.
That's crazy, right?
Come with me.
You know, what you've been
feeling is absolutely normal.
Well, tell that to my friend Bree.
I was holding that doll,
and she looked at me like I was insane.
Most people will never understand,
but I do.
Let me introduce you to someone.
This is Mrs. Humphries.
I saw her in a window in a tiny shop in Ohio
and fell in love,
and the more time we spent together,
the more I got to know her story.
Her story?
Of course. Every doll has a story,
and it turns out Mrs. Humphries
started her own business,
just like I did.
She has a music shop, and she teaches piano.
And she... told you that?
Gaby, dolls don't talk.
But even so,
Mrs. Humphries is always there for me.
You see, her sister passed away
around the same time mine did.
Ever since...
she's brought me such happiness.
Isn't it... funny how a doll can do that?
And the best thing is,
they'll never leave you.
So...
what's your doll's story?
I don't know.
Oh, of course you do.
Tell me.
Uh...
Uh... her... name is Princess Valerie.
She's a princess.
But she wasn't always one.
Really?
When she was born, there was a mix-up,
and she was given to the wrong family.
Nobody knew for a long time.
But then one day,
she finally found her way home.
From that day on,
Princess Valerie never left the palace.
Her real mother kept her hidden away
so no one would take her.
And they were never separated...
ever again.
I know I'm not sleeping in here tonight.
Tonight?
Look...
I am unbelievably sorry about this.
I-I wanted to tell you so many times, but...
I-I could never find the right moment. It...
Really?
In 20 years of marriage,
there was never a lull in the conversation
for you to say,
"Hey, guess who I slept with"?
When would have been a good time?
The day I found out you were pregnant
with Porter and Preston?
Parker's 1st birthday party?
The morning that Penny took her first steps?
We have had...
such beautiful moments together.
I-I didn't wanna ruin a single one of them.
I hope you can forgive me for this.
It would be a shame...
a shame if some meaningless
encounter 20 years ago
ruined this wonderful life
that we have built together.
Susan.
I'm sorry I didn't call first.
You're not busy, are you?
I'm just packing.
Uh, my cab's gonna be here soon.
So... y-you have time to talk?
Sure.
I, um...
Well, I just...
wanted to apologize for yesterday.
Oh. No need.
This is... a horrible time for you,
and you've got so much on your mind.
It's... it's not that horrible,
and the doctors are very optimistic
that we're going to find a donor.
I'm not worried.
Oh. I'm so relieved.
You know what the one good thing
about having a health scare is?
No. What?
Makes you think about
what the important things are.
That's very true.
We all think that we're...
gonna be here forever,
that we have... all the time in the world
to say the important things, but we don't.
Why don't you and I ever tell
each other how we feel?
We don't need to.
We know how we feel.
Do we?
You're right.
You already know how much I love you.
And you already know
that anytime I accomplish anything,
you're the first person I wanna call,
'cause I love making you proud.
And you know that...
no matter how much you make me crazy...
part of me enjoys it because it reminds me
that nobody else has a mom like you.
Yeah.
I don't have to tell you that.
Just like I don't need to tell you
that my life began the day you were born.
And it's been such a happy one.
Aren't we lucky we already
know those things?
Yes?
Yes. I'll be right down.
It's my cab.
You go, and I, uh...
I'll call you later.
Okay.
You know, one of these days, I would...
I would like for us to take a little trip,
just the two of us.
Oh, I'd like that.
You know, we'll go someplace hot
and just lay out and drink some daiquiris.
Oh, we'll... absolutely do that.
Just as soon as I'm done with my cruise.
Yeah.
No offense, Penny, but soccer's boring.
Yeah, it's as boring as...
actually, there's nothing more boring.
You can tell us about it later.
But you have to go. It's a playoff game.
They're the best team in the league.
I need your support.
- Oh, who cares? You guys suck anyway.
- Yeah, they may suck,
- but they still would've beaten
Parker's team.
- Hey, Preston, uh,
how did the baseball team do senior year?
Shut up. At least I played.
Oh. That's true.
Remember that time he struck out five times?
By the third time,
the crowd started laughing.
Yeah, that was hilarious.
Your last at-bat,
the other team sat on their mitts.
- Oh, so embarrassing.
- Shameful.
Come on, you guys. Please?
I got stuff to do. Like what?
Stare in the mirror and wait
for the first mustache hair?
Relax, Penny. At least you won't
have to share your snacks
with us after the game.
Okay, fine. Don't go.
We're just messing with you.
We're going.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
I'm even gonna drive you,
but I'm gonna warn you,
if you lose, you're walking home.
Oh, please.
Yeah. I'm not driving losers in my car.
Does that mean you're not taking Preston?
- Here you go, ladies.
- Wow.
Oh, Bree, that looks amazing.
Thank you so much
for putting this together.
It really feels like old times.
Well, you have been through so much,
and I wanted you to feel loved and embraced
by all the people in this room.
And while I'm on the topic
of embracing people,
I have invited our neighbor Beth to join us.
Cheese puff, anyone?
Beth Young?
- Married to Paul Young?
- The lady with the bad hair?
Oh, forget the hair!
Her husband caused the riot.
Which caused Susan a kidney.
Why would you do this, Bree?
I just felt sorry for her.
The poor woman has been shunned
by everyone in this neighborhood.
Because she's married to a monster.
So? Why should she have to suffer
for the sins of her husband?
Oh, crap. She's been talking to a priest.
Renee, help us out. Tell her she's crazy.
Uh, actually, I'm with Bree.
Please, you've never given Beth a chance,
and speaking as
the other new kid on the block,
you guys are like the mean, pretty girls
who won't let anyone sit
at your lunch table.
That is so unfair. Who invited her?
Okay, that's Beth.
Now, please, ladies, make an effort for me.
I'm actually excited.
I always wanted to be one
of the mean, pretty girls.
Yeah, I got a delivery for Van De Kamp.
Ooh, how lovely.
I don't see a card. Who are they from?
Uh, beats me.
Must be my boyfriend.
Would you mind setting them over there?
I'll go get a tip.
Is it her, or can I wipe
this fake smile off my face?
It's a deliveryman. Someone sent me flowers.
Was it the pope?
Here you go. Thank you.
Oh, good! You made it.
Hello.
Ladies, Beth's here!
You're sure this is okay?
It isn't gonna be awkward?
Of course not! The girls
are delighted you're here.
We are going to have a wonderful time.
That is a really good deal on potting soil.
Yes.
Well, again, I had a coupon.
That is fortunate.
- Maybe I should go...
- No, no, the evening
has just gotten started.
I'm gonna need some help in the kitchen...
you, you, you, and you. Now.
By the way,
I know somebody who can really
help you with that hair.
Renee!
What is wrong with you people?
You said you'd make an effort.
I am making an effort...
an effort not to tear out my deformed kidney
- and cram it down her throat.
- Yeah,
so Beth's feeling
a little lonely these days.
Why is it our responsibility
to make her feel loved?
Okay, look, I didn't wanna bring this up,
but let's talk about the last woman
who was married to Paul Young...
a woman who was in pain, and we ignored it.
Do we really want Beth
to end up like Mary Alice?
We're back.
We've decided to kick this party up a notch.
Oh. Lovely.
Yeah. Sit here. We'll pour you some vino.
Thank you.
Is red okay? Because we have white, too.
Uh, no, red is fine. What in the world?
Somebody lose a gun?
Oh, my God. What is that doing there?
Bree?
No, I keep all my weapons in a locker.
Let me see that.
It's a 38 caliber.
The police said... Paul was shot with a 38.
I think I finally understand
why you invited me over.
Meaning?
I'm just thinking how convenient it is...
a gun that may have been used to shoot Paul
was under my pillow?
A-and now has my fingerprints on it?
Hey, I was sitting there before you were,
and I didn't feel any gun.
Yeah, speaking of convenient...
You're alone in the room, we came back,
and suddenly there's
a gun under the cushion?
Where would I get a gun?
Oh, I don't know.
How about the one you pointed
- at me on Halloween night?
- You never told us that.
You mean the night you broke into my house
and tried to kill my husband with a club?
You never told us that, either.
I'm allowed to have a private life.
The point is, she owns
a gun just like the one
that magically appeared when
she was alone in the room.
You're all in on this.
You wanted to set me up.
I can't believe you would say to that to me
after I reached out to you.
Well, I think it's time
I did some reaching out of my own.
I'm calling the police.
We don't have to get up early tomorrow.
So I was thinking... maybe we could...
I still cannot believe
that I fell for Beth's act.
Or we could talk about this some more.
Well, she is just as twisted
as that husband of hers,
and I am a fool.
You're not a fool.
You're a kind and generous person.
That's what I love about you.
That and the fact that you can go from...
mad to passionate in a heartbeat.
I suppose you do deserve some loving...
Mmm. Mmm.
After those beautiful flowers you sent me.
At the risk of... going to bed frustrated...
I didn't send you any flowers.
You didn't? Then where did they come from?
We pass by these people every day,
but we never look at them.
We don't wanna see the sadness
in their expressions...
the longing in their hearts...
the loneliness in their eyes...
But there are times
we should stop and look
at these isolated people.
Why?
Well, if we look close enough...
we might just recognize them.
Sync by YYeTs.net
Corrected by MystEre
www.addic7ed.com