Previously on...
Susan showed a certain
flair for her new job.
There you go. You know,
you're getting good at this.
Renee rented a house.
- Wow, that is so...
- Wonderful?
Close.
There's something I have to tell you.
Gaby learned the truth
about her daughter
being switched at birth.
Beth!
Paul Young continued to surprise everyone.
Well, I see you've all met my wife.
And Tom came home
with a mysterious affliction.
I'm not feeling well.
Again?
I'm just gonna lie on
the couch and watch some TV.
Tom Scavo was depressed,
and his wife had done everything she could
to cheer him up.
She had made his favorite meals.
She had told her funniest jokes.
She'd even worn her sexiest lingerie.
But nothing worked.
Finally, Lynette insisted
her husband to go to the doctor.
Unfortunately, what he came home with
was a prescription... for trouble.
Antianxiety medication?
This is what he gave you?
- Dr. Weiler says it will help.
- He spent 20 minutes with you.
- Lynette...
- And let me guess. Did he write this
with a pen that has the drug
- company's name on it?
- I need this medicine.
Then take it, but I gotta tell ya,
those drugs scare the crap out of me.
I gotta do something.
I am so tired of feeling this way.
But you've gone
through rough patches before.
You could come out of it.
So wait around to get better?
That's your answer?
You don't know
what it's like inside my head!
Okay, you're right. I'm sorry. Hey! Hey!
Remember when Susan kept having
all those headaches?
Who was that guy that she went to?
Doctor... Dr. Ross.
- How is he gonna be any different?
- He's holistic.
He tries to stay away from heavy meds.
Susan loved him.
And if he says I should be on this?
Then you have a second opinion.
Whatever he says, I'll go with it.
Shh. Shh. Shh.
Well...
I saw Dr. Ross.
Oh! I'm so glad.
Did you like him?
Loved him.
And you were right.
He... he doesn't believe
in pharmaceuticals.
He only prescribes stuff
that's totally herbal and natural.
That is fantastic.
So what did he suggest?
Medical marijuana.
Yes,
Tom Scavo had been battling depression,
but he was now facing a much bigger battle
with his wife.
Happiness...
it's something we all want,
and so we search for it.
Little girls find it
in the taste of chocolate.
Well-dressed men discover it
at their local mall.
Teenage boys experience it
when talking to a pretty girl.
And then there are housewives,
who simply can't be happy
until they've learned everything they can
about the newest neighbor on the block.
Hello!
Hi. So sorry to interrupt.
This will just take a second.
We wanted to officially welcome
you to the neighborhood.
- Oh!
- This is my friend Lynette and Susan,
and I was telling them
about you, and we...
- Just had to meet you.
- Immediately.
That's so sweet.
Oh, you... you're my landlady, right?
Yes, but I really want you
to think of me as a friend.
Are those pictures hung on
the wall with nails or...
Um, we wanted to invite you
to our weekly poker game.
Shoot. I don't know how to play poker.
Oh, don't worry. We'll teach you.
Does that ficus tree
have a saucer underneath?
Because those are hardwood floors.
And while you're learning
all about Texas Hold'em,
we'll learn all about you.
Aw! That sounds fun.
Okay, well, uh, we should be going.
We'll see you later.
Okay.
- Bye.
What did those women want?
They invited me to play cards with them.
But they were just being friendly.
On this street,
never confuse being nosy
with being friendly.
They were digging for dirt.
So...
do you not want me to go?
No, no. You will go.
Give them all sorts
of meaningless information.
And hopefully, they'll start
to think of you as a friend.
But... if you don't like them,
why do you want me
to be friends with them?
In time, it will be useful.
- Where's the pen?
- Don't you wanna read it first?
Why? Did a nurse get drunk
and swap it with a different document?
By signing this,
Mr. Solis, you are agreeing
not to bring any legal action
against this hospital.
Do you understand?
And in return, you'll stop searching
for the other family.
Do you understand?
Done. Gaby.
Babe, we talked about this.
We don't know
how this other family will react,
and we need to protect Juanita.
I am sorry, Gabrielle.
I can only imagine how you must feel.
You can't begin to imagine how I feel.
The only person who could is
the woman who has my daughter.
If signing can spare her this pain...
then I will do it.
I love it!
Somehow I get the feeling
you don't love it.
Okay, I-I don't love it. It's just so...
yellow.
Trust me. This will be great.
Besides, when you're in the room,
nobody's looking at the walls anyway.
Well, you certainly know
how to sell yellow.
Excuse me.
I hear you're gettin' divorced.
And good morning to you.
I'm getting divorced, too,
so we both need guys.
I'm thinking we should hang.
Uh, I don't know
how much Lynette has told you about me,
but I'm really not one for... hanging.
Look, one woman at a bar is just sad.
But two, and it's girls' night out.
So what do you say?
You up for a little stud hunting?
That's a lovely offer,
but I think I'm gonna pass.
Oh, come on.
We gotta get back in the game,
cut loose, let our hair down.
That hair does come down, doesn't it?
Really, Renee, that is just not
how I like to meet men.
Well, how else you gonna meet 'em,
sittin' around your house?
You'd be surprised.
You've met someone already?
Maybe.
Wow.
A beautiful, classy woman
who can get a man
without leaving the house.
I don't see us being friends.
I don't know
how everything gets so dirty in here.
Uh-oh!
Is that a piece of lint?
Oh, no!
It got my apron!
I'd better sign off
before I'm completely naked.
See you tomorrow, boys.
I'm busy!
Honey, it's Maxine!
Oh!
A star is born!
Did you watch?
Oh, not only did I watch, I kvelled.
Oh! I have to admit,
I am sort of getting into it.
That whole thing
with the vacuum just came to me.
Well, that's how it happens
with the great ones. Oops.
Here's a bonus for you.
Whoa!
What's this for?
Well, it's a little something I do
for the girl who gets
the most hits in a month.
You just unseated Stacy Strauss,
and with the caboose on her,
that's not easy.
- Oh, Maxine. You're so good to me.
- Oh, honey.
- Mmm.
- You know what?
Mike and I are finally starting
to save some money.
Well, don't save it all.
Buy yourself something nice.
You deserve it. Oh, by the way,
have you decided what
you're gonna do for tomorrow's show?
I'm gonna damp mop in bikini briefs.
Ooh! Are you trying to make me cry?
Bye, doll.
This is a great sandwich.
What's in it?
Oh, it's nothing.
Just a little Parma ham
cured by Italian monks
and some cave-aged gruyère,
and of course I make my own fig mustard.
Cooking is a passion of mine.
Of course, it's not much fun
cooking for one,
so, um, if you're free this weekend...
Babe, you gotta try
this sandwich. It rocks.
This is my boss, Mrs. Van De Kamp.
This is Stephanie, my girlfriend.
You have a girlfriend?
Of course you have a...
a girlfriend who's young and pretty.
Nice to meet you.
I'm sorry, Bree.
What were you about to ask me?
Oh, it's, uh, wasn't important.
You enjoy your sandwich.
Inside, over there.
Let the stud hunt begin.
Come on. Come on. We're gonna get started.
You okay?
Oh. Yeah.
Yeah.
Let's play cards.
When I was 8, daddy left mama,
and we were pretty much alone.
Most of my friends were
either stuffed or plastic.
Of course, there were
always mama's boyfriends,
but as soon as I'd learn their names,
mama would kick them out,
and there'd be
a new toothbrush in the bathroom.
Uh, l-let me know if I'm sharing too much.
No. Not at all.
Keep pouring the chardonnay.
She's cracking like an egg.
Okay, quarter ante.
So, Beth, how did you
and Paul meet anyway?
Oh, I don't wanna bore you.
We won't be bored. More chardonnay?
Mm.
Well... I saw his picture
in the paper during his trial,
and there was just
something about those eyes
that spoke to me.
What about the headline?
"Arrested for murder"...
that didn't speak to you?
I'll admit that gave me pause.
But then we started corresponding,
and I discovered
what a wonderful man Paul really is.
Bree, let's forget about hittin'
the clubs tomorrow night.
Clearly, all the best guys
are on death row.
But, hey, you can't help
who you fall in love with, right?
And Paul's a real lady-killer.
We... we always fogged up
the plexiglas with that one.
Well, it's good
that you can laugh about it.
The thing is,
in my heart, I always knew
he was innocent,
and I was right.
Well, he is.
Yeah, so let's play cards.
What are you doing?
Preparing to take my medicine.
I've heard that an increase in appetite's
a possible side effect,
so I'm taking the necessary precautions.
Necessary precautions being
your own weight in cheese doodles?
I never smoked pot before,
so I wanna be prepared.
Headphones?
Pink Floyd.
Apparently, it complements
the medicinal properties
of, uh...
blueberry bliss.
Listen to you.
You are loving this.
Tom the college nerd
gets to finally smoke pot and be cool.
Hey, I was plenty cool in college.
The only reason I didn't smoke back then
was because I signed the abstinence pledge
with my Dungeons & Dragons club.
So... what do you say?
Care to join me out back behind the garage
for a little doobage?
"Doobage"?
That's what you're calling
your medicine now?
Come on. You need to take this seriously.
I-I am.
Really? 'Cause I'm pretty sure
I've never asked you
to join me behind
the garage to split a midol.
Lynette, you said you would go with this.
I know, but how is it gonna look
to the kids?
I don't want them seeing their dad stoned.
Oh, you... you don't have to worry
about them seeing me stoned.
They'll never know.
Hey, the...
Okay.
So what do you wanna do saturday night?
Well, I was thinking
that we could go to Chez Naomi.
Isn't our price range
more Chez chicken hut?
Mike, it's our anniversary.
Besides, we've been working
really hard. We deserve it.
Okay, but bring your big purse
'cause we're taking the dinner rolls home.
So...
Chez Naomi, huh?
Expensive place.
Yeah. Yeah, I guess it is.
Must be nice.
Um, have we met?
I'm in 1b. Susan Delfino.
Oh, I know who you are.
I'm 1f.
Stacy Strauss.
Uh, y-you're one of Maxine's...
Yeah.
Oh, well, it's nice to meet you.
Guess we...
kind of do the same thing.
Oh, sometimes we do
exactly the same thing.
What does that mean?
I keep an eye on the competition.
You lifted one of my moves.
- No, I didn't.
- You expect me to believe
you just woke up one day
- and decided to put
a feather duster in your mouth?
- You do that?
It's my signature bit, and you stole it.
I swear. I...
I-I don't watch the other girls perform.
Okay, so I guess it's just a coincidence.
Well, here's another coincidence...
you're getting the big bonus check,
and I'm not.
That's not... really
what you'd call a coincidence.
- That's really more...
- All right, college.
Just keep the duster out of your mouth.
And watch your back.
Everything okay?
Oh, yeah.
I am wasted.
Really?
I am Lucy in the sky high.
So...
this must be pretty intense for you.
And don't forget
tomorrow we have to
trombone 3-d banana patch.
Remember?
Man, this is, uh, really strong stuff.
Snow shovel.
Exactly.
You know, I was just upstairs
watching Paige sleep,
with her little fingers
and her little toes.
I-I must've watched her for,
like, an hour.
She's just so perfect.
And I am so lucky.
I couldn't feel happier
than I do right now.
I mean just so happy it's working.
Yeah.
What do you think? Does this say
"happy anniversary, Mike.
I'll love you forever"?
No. I think it says
"credit card declined."
Aren't you and Mike on a budget?
Yeah, but things are starting
to turn around lately.
I've been selling a lot of my jewelry.
Get out!
Out there and keep selling.
Oh, hello, silk!
Oh, how I've missed your soft touch.
I'm going to the dressing room.
Mm, you two have fun.
Mommy?
Oh. You're not my mommy.
Are you lost, sweetie? What's your name?
Kiki! You scared me! I couldn't find you.
I have a little girl, too.
Sometimes they get distracted
and wander off.
Let's go.
Wait!
- How old is she?
- 8.
My daughter's 8.
When's your birthday?
Uh, we've really gotta go.
Uh, okay, but, uh,
what hospital was she born in?
Was it Fairview Memorial?
Standing there in the mall,
it just hit me.
I can't spend the rest of my life
wondering if every little girl
I see is my daughter.
Not knowing where she is,
it... it's like my heart
living outside of my body.
I have to find her.
Well, there's a private detective
I work with.
But Sanchez is a pretty common name.
It's not surprising
the hospital couldn't find 'em.
But I know something the hospital doesn't.
When I was in labor,
the other woman's mother
came into my room by mistake,
and we got to talking.
She lived in El Paso,
and she was so excited to have
her granddaughter baptized
at Santa Maria's church.
That's gonna help.
So you think you can find her?
We'll do our best.
Carlos is on board with this, right?
Absolutely.
Okay, then give me ten porterhouse.
Hey. I just came by to pick up
my envelope for the week.
Okay. Inside.
And don't listen to this conversation.
It's about your Christmas gift.
I'm buying all my girls steaks.
You got a preference?
Whatever meat you put
in my stocking will be fine.
Ooh, that sounds dirty. Use that.
I'm back.
What else have you got for me?
Rib eye? I like it.
Is that a piece of lint?
That's my bit.
Max... Maxine!
What?! I'm on with the meat guy.
Yeah, but Stacy Strauss
is stealing my vacuum bit!
Oh, my God. Well, if she's gonna do that,
at least teach her how to use the nozzle.
Hey there. I'm ready to party.
Are you? 'Cause you look like
you're ready to tour the Reagan library.
This is a cocktail cardigan.
Look closely. The buttons are shiny.
Where's your closet?
I have never seen so many sweater sets.
Are you sure this is a closet
and not a portal to the 1950s?
There is nothing wrong with my clothing.
Bree, you're going to a hot young club
full of hot young people.
You need to dress the part.
Well, I happen to find it distasteful
when mutton is dressed as lamb.
Look, when women go out clubbing,
there's two ways they can pair up...
pretty girl/pretty girl
or pretty girl/grenade.
Which do you wanna be?
Fine.
Now we're getting somewhere.
Love the plunging neckline.
That's the back.
Ugh. This place is dead.
Really?
I forgot we were in the sticks.
Clearly, everyone hooked up early
so they could be home
in time for "nightline."
Actually, tonight's "nightline"
sounds very interesting.
- It's about the genocide in r...
- Hold on.
Fresh talent at the end of the bar.
Oh, that's my contractor.
Well, call me a fixer-upper.
Oh, don't... don't bother.
He's, uh, got a girlfriend.
If I don't see her, she doesn't exist.
What's so funny?
My girlfriend's about to
make a fool of herself.
She's hitting on that guy,
and I happen to know
he has a very beautiful,
very young girlfriend.
- You talking about Keith?
- You know him?
Yeah, and Stephanie
dumped him this afternoon,
which is why he's here,
drowning his sorrows.
Bree. Wow.
I didn't recognize you.
Keith, what a lovely surprise.
I didn't know you were here.
Yeah.
But I'm bagging.
I gotta work tomorrow.
Boss is pretty strict.
Good. I mean, yes, I'm very strict.
See you in the morning.
There ya go. That's how you bait the hook.
Oh, I won't need a ride.
I'm going home with Keith.
Oh, I don't think so. He just left.
Oh, he's pulling the car around.
Now you think I should play
the "I hate going
into a dark house alone" card,
or the more blatant
"I'm not wearing underwear"?
'Cause I'm not.
Okay, before you do anything hasty,
he just broke up with his girlfriend.
He's very fragile.
Oh. I'll be careful when I unwrap him.
Renee, wait.
Please don't go home with Keith.
Why?
Oh, he's the one you like, isn't he?
I am... I am thinking about you.
You don't want to come off like a slut.
Aw, gee, then chip won't ask me
to the prom.
Renee, wait! What about me?
Oh, it's getting late.
Stay in the dim light and
don't play hard to get.
Keith, hi. It's Bree.
I-I don't know if you're in bed yet,
but I'm having a bit of an emergency.
Oh, thank you. That's lovely.
Why would somebody do something like this?
Far be it from me to understand
the minds of hooligans.
I'm so sorry to call you
over here at this hour.
Oh, it's okay.
I wasn't doing anything special.
Good.
I would love to show my appreciation.
I was wondering if perhaps
one night this week,
I could make you dinner.
Oh. You mean...
like a date?
Well, we don't have to put a label on it.
Just two adults eating... food together.
Calling it a date is quicker.
Well, I see no reason to argue.
Shall we say...
8:00 P.M. on Thursday?
M-Mrs. McCluskey, right?
Yeah.
I was hoping I might see you
at the girls' poker game.
Not anymore.
You get caught with
a couple of aces in your bra,
- and you're banned for life.
- I-I couldn't help but notice
they don't seem to like
my husband very much.
Do you know why that is?
Nope. Nobody tells me anything.
Mrs. McCluskey, I really need to know.
Okay, fine. They think he's a murderer.
But he was exonerated.
Felicia Tillman framed him.
Yeah, for that crime.
What do you mean?
Before Felicia showed up around here,
her sister Martha was murdered.
And, all due respect,
you're shacking up
with suspect number one.
Does everybody think that?
Felicia may be a few fingers short
of a high five,
but if she's crazy, we all are.
Well, that's enough dusting
for today, boys.
I guess all that's left
is a little vacuuming.
Ooh! Yay! Get the vacuum.
I think I got some schmutz on my apron.
Ooh, get that off.
Oh, I love this show. Mm.
Hello, boys.
For those of you
who might be switching over
from other channels,
welcome.
I have a very dirty apartment.
Open up!
Uh, little busy!
I know you did it.
Did what? I don't know
what you're talking about.
Oh, so you're not just a thief.
You're a liar.
Be careful how you talk to me,
you gigantic freak.
Oh, I am about to slap
that cheap blush right off your face.
Is that supposed to scare me, man hands?
I'm gonna show you
a whole new place to stick
that feather duster.
Well, I'm sure wherever it is,
you copied the idea from watching me.
- I need those bonus checks!
- So do I!
You don't get it. I am trying
to get out of this business!
Oh, and you think I wanna spend
the rest of my life
- dusting in my underwear?!
- Hey! Hey! Hey!
You're off camera!
Roll left.
Oh, Maxine. I'm so glad you're here.
What are you doing?
- She attacked me.
- That's because she broke into
my apartment and...
Hang on. This isn't a bit?
No! I was in the middle of doing my show,
and she burst in here
and started hitting me.
Did you do that?
Yeah, but...
You know the rules, Strauss!
You never, ever interrupt a show!
Now go to your room.
- But I...
- I said go.
You all right, honey?
Yeah.
All right. Good.
I-I gotta call tech support.
You girls had so many hits,
it fried my router.
So...
a roving gang of hooligans
destroyed your sprinklers?
- Shameful, isn't it?
- You know what I think?
I think this is the handywork
of a lonely, desperate woman.
You left out "resourceful."
Nobody steals a man out of my bed.
But you know what?
I've been looking for a new hobby,
and taking you down is as good as any.
I think you'd be wise
to stick to your original hobby
of forgoing undergarments.
Be seeing you, Bree.
Looking forward to it.
Maxine says I can't go back online
until I apologize to you,
so... I apologize.
Wow. And I thought
your acting was bad on the web site.
Fine. I am sorry, okay?
I shouldn't have stolen your bit.
What was going through your mind?
I freaked out
when I didn't get that bonus check.
See, my family's in Virginia,
and I'm saving up to move back home.
Yeah, well, I know what that's like.
And even with that extra money,
I always feel like
I'm living week to week.
Really? 'Cause when I broke
in your apartment,
I noticed that you had
some awfully nice stuff.
Flat screen TV,
closet full of new clothes.
I know. Probably shouldn't
have bought all that.
But you know how it is.
Every once in a while,
you want a little splurge.
Yeah, I get that.
But... definitely by the end of the year,
I'm going to be outta here.
Me, too.
How long have you been doing this?
Um... gosh. I guess
I'm going on six years.
Hey, um... would you mind
if we just stayed home
and ordered Chinese for our anniversary?
Wait. No suit?
No tie?
No pretentious euro waiter
listing specials
that I can't understand?
Dang it, Susan! Why?
Seriously, why'd you change your mind?
I thought you wanted a little treat.
Oh. I think we should save that money
and stay focused on
what we're trying to do.
And we can have a fancy
dinner and celebrate
when we move back home.
I had a lovely time
at the poker game the other day.
Really? What's the neighborhood
saying about me?
Well...
For starters,
a lot of people seem
to think you killed...
What's her name? Martha something.
Huber.
I guess Felicia Tillman spread
her poison pretty wide.
I guess she did.
I'm not a murderer, you know.
I know.
But I fell in love
with you before I knew that,
so even if you were...
I'm always gonna be on your side.
Remember that.
Everything okay? You...
You look a little...
It's been an intense couple weeks.
I'm sorry, buddy.
What if I told you
I could ease some of that stress?
You're not gonna offer me
a back rub, are you?
Nope.
A mind rub.
So you got this from a doctor?
Really cool doctor.
Now I gotta warn you,
this stuff is chronic.
I got totally baked off
of it this morning.
I did not have you pegged as a stoner.
Dude...
There's a lot
that you don't know about me.
Tom?
I hate to break this to you, but...
this isn't pot.
Tell me that in five minutes
when we are soaring past
the rings of Saturn.
Trust me, cheech. This is oregano.
No way. I bo... I bo...
I bought it at a legit dispensary.
Then somebody must have
switched it on you,
'cause the only thing getting baked
with that herb is lasagna.
Who would do that?
- You!
- Oh, jeez. You scared me.
I know what you did.
Whatever do you mean?
Oh, yeah. That was me.
Th-this isn't funny, Lynette!
Tom, you thought you were getting stoned
on a pizza topping. It's a little funny.
My sense of betrayal
is huge at this moment.
Well, why don't you snort
some baking powder?
- You'll feel better.
- I'm glad you're enjoying this.
Glad you enjoy making a fool of me.
That was not my intention.
I only threw out the pot because
I didn't think you needed it,
and you know, I was right.
You got happy all on your own.
Don't try to justify what you did
by making it seem like
some sort of "master plan."
It wasn't a master plan.
I lucked out because for some reason,
while you were... high on oregano,
you made a decision to live in the moment.
You stood over our daughter's crib
and you let go of the stress and the fear,
and you focused on the good in your life.
But I am sorry I tricked you.
You're evil. I should have expected it.
Where are you going?
To look at our beautiful daughter.
Then I gotta turn that bong
I made back into a lamp.
Anything?
We found them.
Oh, my God. What'd they say?
I haven't called them yet.
Are you sure you still wanna do this?
What? Yes, of course.
Gaby, you need to realize,
once we call these people,
and they know what's happened,
it'll change your family forever.
Call them.
Juanita, come in here.
I didn't do it.
I know.
I was putting on some makeup.
I thought you might like some.
Can you put the big fake eyelashes on me?
Of course, and... big rosy cheeks.
Look how grown-up you are.
Before you know it,
you're gonna be going to college,
have boyfriends, get married.
I'm not getting married.
I don't wanna leave you and daddy... ever.
Juanita...
Do you know how much I love you?
To the moon and back.
That's right.
No matter what happens,
I will always love you
to the moon and back.
Hey, Carlos, I need to sit down
with you and Gaby.
Why?
I just called the family.
It got pretty intense.
What are you talking about?
And now in a selection
from Dior's fall line,
the world's newest supermodel... Juanita!
Hold the world in contempt.
That's it.
Now you look like a model.
Oh, hi, daddy.
Hey, Carlos. What's wrong?
I just spoke to Bob.
Sweetie, why don't you go to your room?
And I'll be there in a sec.
- How could you have done this?
- Carlos...
We talked about this! We agreed.
No, you agreed. You rushed me
into signing that piece of paper
without giving me a chance
to think about what I was doing.
Don't you understand what could happen?
She is our flesh and blood,
and she's out there!
I need to know how she's doing.
I need to know she's okay!
And what if they want Juanita back?!
They can take her from us.
They can do that now!
They're not gonna wanna give up
their own daughter.
We don't know that!
We don't know anything about them!
And you have no idea
what you've started here!
Mommy!
Coming, sweetie!
If this ends badly,
I will never forgive you.
I mean it, Gabrielle.
We're done.
Happiness...
it's something everyone searches for.
Some are sure they'll find it
once they've moved back home.
Some think they'll find it
by making a new friend.
Some hope to find it
once they've defeated the competition.
Then there are those
who stop searching for happiness
because they look up
one day to discover...
It was right there in front of them
all the time.
Sync by YYeTs.net
Corrected by MystEre