Previously on
"Desperate Housewives"...
I need a C.F.O.
I'm prepared to give you
stock options,
access to the company jet.
Tom got a job offer
he couldn't refuse.
- I am in.
- Yes!
At dialysis, Susan made a friend.
Beth took her life,
which led to Susan
getting a kidney...
Honor Beth's life by allowing you
to make her well.
And Felicia being freed.
I just heard
from the parole board.
They've decided
to grant your request
for humanitarian release.
Alex left me.
Oh, honey.
I guess he just got sick
of living with a drunk.
And Bree helped her son
face his addiction.
When Bree Van De Kamp
decided to stop drinking,
her recipe for sobriety
was the 12 steps
of alcoholics anonymous.
She admitted she was
powerless over alcohol...
She asked God to remove
her shortcomings.
She made a list of all the people
she had harmed.
So when her son Andrew
decided to stop drinking,
Bree was pleased to see him
follow those steps
as successfully as she had.
Let me see it again.
Ahh. 30 days sober.
I am so proud of you.
I feel great, mom.
And it gets better all the time.
Just keep going to meetings
and working those steps.
Yeah, I kind of stalled out
around number eight, though.
Ooh, that is a tough one.
No one likes to make lists
of people they've done harm to,
particularly with
your penmanship.
No, I wrote the list.
But now I have
to make the amends,
and there's one person
I've been really awful to.
Well, I know it seems difficult,
but give it a chance.
Some people are more forgiving
than we give them credit for.
- You thought I meant you?
- Well, of course I did.
Aw, mom.
Uh, no offense,
but you're way down the list.
I think you're, like, seventh.
Seventh?
I'd like to know about
these six people ahead of me.
Did you steal their pocketbook?
Did you wreck their car?
Stick a kitchen knife through
an oil portrait of them?
- Okay, calm down.
- I will not calm down.
I resent you thinking you've
harmed anyone more than me.
Well, I have.
And if I'm gonna make amends,
I need to start now...
with the top of the list.
And who might that be?
Who is this victim number one?
Mr. Solis.
Yes, Bree was diligent
about following the 12 steps.
After all, I did sort of kill his mom.
But even she could
recognize a step too far.
Andrew, stop!
Sync by YYeTs.net
Corrected by Addic7ed
www.addic7ed.com
We teach our children
to apologize when
they make a mistake.
We tell them that it's wrong
to blame others...
or pretend it never happened...
or try to cover it up.
But there are those times
when apologizing...
Hey, Carlos! You got a minute?
- Is the biggest mistake of all.
- Be right there.
Andrew, stop. You really
need to think about this.
Mom, you know
what the step says...
Make direct amends
to those we have harmed.
Unless to do so would
injure them or others.
And if Carlos finds out,
trust me,
he's going to injure others!
Hey, buddy. What's up?
You know, there's something
I never told you...
Uh, yes. How wonderful
you were to him after Rex died.
You were like a...
surrogate father.
Oh, I don't know about that.
You were.
You took him on hunting trips,
football games, car races...
I didn't know you were gay then,
- or I'd have thrown in a few musicals.
- Ha ha ha ha!
The point is, you've always
been so kind to people,
never inuring them... or others.
Well, that was the same year
that my mom died,
so I was working
through some grief, too.
It was great that we could
be there for each other.
So... that was what
you wanted to tell me?
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, just, uh... thanks.
No problem.
Someone just earned another pie.
Hey!
Whoever's in here,
I own this house,
and I want you out now!
Well, hello, Paul.
What the hell
are you doing here?
I'm just nosing around
to see what I'll need
to buy before I move in.
Not much, apparently.
I had no idea
the place came furnished.
Have you lost
what's left of your mind?
This is my house!
Now get out!
Oh, I know you bought it.
You bought a lot of houses
on this street,
but you didn't want
people to know,
so you put this one
in Beth's name.
So what?
I was her husband!
And since she never made a will...
Oh, but she did, Paul, years ago.
And according to that will,
I own this house
and everything in it.
Oh, my goodness!
Is this a Gustav Stickley?
Do you really think
the people on this street
want a manipulative
psycho for a neighbor?
Well, they let you live here,
so I'm guessing the zoning laws
aren't all that strict.
If they wanna shun me, let them.
I won't be alone.
I'll have my daughter with me.
My God. You stole her ashes?
I did not steal them. You are
so quick to think the worst of me.
I just went to the mausoleum
and I explained my legal rights.
Your rights?
What about my rights?
She was my wife!
Did I say you couldn't visit her?
Drop by anytime, Paul.
My door is always open.
Everything looks great, Susan...
Your blood work,
creatine levels.
You're, like, the poster girl
for kidney transplants.
Does that mean I can have
salty food and sex again?
Salt in moderation.
You should wait two more weeks
before resuming
normal sexual activity.
Mike and I have already
waited a month.
There's not going to be
anything normal about it.
Okay, well, I'll see you
at your next checkup.
Where are you off to?
Well, I am definitely
going to the mall
to enjoy the last few hours
of my handicap placard.
First I'm going
to the dialysis center
to visit my friend Dick Barrows.
Oh, you don't have to go
to the dialysis center.
He's here in the hospital.
He was admitted yesterday.
Hey, tall, dark, and jaundiced.
Delfino.
Come closer.
I wanna see if you still have
that new kidney smell.
What are you doing here?
Where else can you get
a large Jamaican nurse
to give you a sponge bath
for 4 grand a day?
Another viral infection.
I'm sorry.
I can't believe you got
a kidney so fast.
I don't suppose you have
any more suicidal neighbors
with donor cards?
I didn't laugh when you wrote it
on my get-well note,
and I'm not laughing now.
I'm telling you, you are
the luckiest person alive.
You should take advantage.
Do you gamble?
A little.
Ah. Oh-ho, great.
When I get outta here,
I'm taking you
to that casino by the airport.
I've never won in that place.
You could be my rabbit's foot.
I'm not big on casinos.
I'm more of an
around-the-kitchen-table,
gossip-with-my-girlfriends,
win-all-the-M&M's kind of gal.
Ah, it's time for my spinal tap.
You see?
You're not the only lucky one.
Hey, babe.
You're home late.
I got called down
to the legal department.
Is everything okay?
There's no easy way to say this.
Oh, no. What is this?
That, my dear...
is my signing bonus.
$100,000.
No way. It is not $100,000.
"One..."
It is. It's $100,000!
I can't believe it!
I know!
What are we gonna do with it?
Um, how about this...
go to the bank,
get 100,000 singles,
and roll around naked on them,
and then apologize
to everybody at the bank
and come home!
- I like the naked part.
- Oh, my gosh!
Oh, my gosh!
Okay. Okay, let's think. Um...
Obviously, we should put some
in the kids' college fund,
and then top off
our retirement account...
Or actually start
a retirement account.
Definitely.
We should do all of that...
with 90 grand.
The other 10
is for you to spend
on something fun
and totally frivolous,
like a mink vest
or a diamond frisbee.
No, no, no...
No. Lynette, do you know
how long I have waited
to be able to say this to you?
Go crazy.
It's on me.
Fine.
If you're gonna be
a jerk about it,
I'll spend $10,000 on myself.
Aah!
We should celebrate!
Mm. Let's go out to dinner. Mwah.
Oh, definitely. But not tonight.
I've got a ton of work.
- Okay? How about Friday?
- Okay. It's a date.
Wait a sec.
"One..."
Nope. That's $100,000.
And I'll call.
9, 10, Jack, queen, king...
a straight.
Eat it!
I was going to say how nice it is
to have you back in our game,
until you so charmingly
told us to "eat it."
- For the third time.
- I'm sorry.
I've just never been
this hot before.
My friend called it today.
He said I was on a lucky streak.
Well, you are lucky.
You got a kidney transplant.
And if you take any more
of my money,
you're gonna need
a face transplant.
Okay, is anyone going to notice
what's different around here?
You cut your hair?
- No.
- Well, you should.
I mean the coffee.
Tom gave me part
of his signing bonus
and said, "Go crazy," so...
I bought a grind and brew
coffee master.
Wasn't even on sale.
Check me out.
Shall I say it?
No, please, allow me.
You're pathetic.
You finally get
a little mad money
and you buy
a kitchen appliance?
But I don't really need anything.
Oh, honey, look around.
You need everything. Two.
Well, it's hard for me.
Tom's only had this job a month.
I'm used to clipping coupons
and buying in bulk.
- I even color my own hair.
- Ah. Mystery solved.
Hey.
How did you let this happen?
Don't look at me like that.
I tried. I tried for years.
I couldn't even get her
out of flip-flops.
Oh, maybe I can
take a shot at her.
Don't do it.
She'll break your heart.
Well, I'm bored.
Look, after this game,
I am taking you
to a clothing store...
That doesn't also sell
patio furniture and meat.
I'm out.
I'll bet $20.
I'm all in.
You didn't even look
at your cards.
I don't need to.
So what do you say,
Van De Kamp?
Did you come to play?
Huh. Let's see
what you are made of.
Three kings.
Oh, look at me!
I should buy a lottery ticket right now.
Yes, you should,
and then you should "eat it."
I so don't belong here.
That saleslady knows it, too.
Did you see the look
she just gave me? Come on.
- What?
- Wait.
Um, excuse me.
We'd like two prosciutto panninis
and a couple of iced cappuccinos.
There's a café across the street.
Oh, please don't make me go
to the enormous hassle
of buying this place
just to fire you.
Nice.
Now let's get started.
Oh, you have got to try these on.
Nah. I don't...
I don't need boots.
You will once you try them.
Ahh.
It's like the boot
is French kissing my foot.
Walk around in them.
Oh, dear.
What they are doing
to my feet now...
I can't even say.
Oh.
Now... try these.
$500 for jeans?
I wouldn't pay that if they
had $400 in the pocket.
Try them.
Look at my ass!
Where did that ass come from?
- It came with the jeans.
- Ohh!
- You like it?
You should see the ass
that comes with the $900 pair.
Do I even wanna know
how much that is?
You just want to put it on.
Thank you for shopping
with us, Mrs. Scavo.
Uh, that dress should be
altered by tomorrow.
We open at 10:00.
Let's make it 8:00.
And... bring croissants.
Hey, Bree!
I hope Andrew
brought his rain gear.
- I hear it's gonna pour up there.
- Up where?
- The cabin.
- What are you talking about?
Didn't Andrew tell you?
- He came by this morning
to talk to Carlos. - He did?
Yeah, Carlos was just leaving
for a hunting trip
and invited Andrew to come along
for old times' sake.
Andrew is with Carlos
in the woods with guns?
- I have to call him.
- Why? Is something wrong?
Oh, yes, something's wrong.
- Has Andrew lost his mind?
- I tried to talk him out of it,
but he's taking this
A.A. thing seriously.
Okay, see, this is the problem
with sobriety... it ruins lives.
Damn it. I still can't get through.
- There's no reception up there.
- I'm starting to get scared.
Oh you're scared?
I'm gonna be the one
raising two kids
with a husband in jail for murder!
And Andrew's gay, so it's a hate crime.
That's ten more years!
Let's not panic. It may not be
too late to stop this.
You're right.
We have to get up there.
I'm gonna see if Lee
can watch the girls.
And I have to get something
out of my nightstand.
Bree, aren't there gonna be
enough guns up there?
When one of them is in my hands,
then there'll be enough guns.
I just want to say I'm sorry
for the way I behaved yesterday.
You're sorry?
I'll give you two reasons
I don't believe you.
I knew you'd be upset to find
you'd bought me a house.
But I still had to twist the knife.
I guess old habits die hard.
You think that's what upset me...
the house?
And Beth's ashes, of course,
but I wanna make that up to you.
You're giving them back?
No. I don't think
either of us should keep them.
I think we should scatter them,
together.
So you've picked up on the fact
that I long to spend
more time with you.
There's a pretty little lake
about an hour north of here.
When Beth was a girl,
it was her favorite place.
I think she'd be happy there.
You could just do this on your own.
Why do you want me there?
Because Beth loved you.
It's what I think she'd want.
And I don't have a car yet.
Shall we say tomorrow
around 10:00?
10:00 will be fine.
Shall I make us some sandwiches?
If it's all the same to you, Felicia,
I'll bring my own.
Dick, are you awake?
Oh, good.
You were right
about the lucky streak.
Guess who won at poker?
Are you looking for my Uncle Dick?
Uh, yeah. Did he go home?
No, um...
I'm afraid we lost him last night.
What?
Oh, my God.
Yeah. He never let on
how sick he was.
I'm Wally, by the way.
- Susan.
- Susan Delfino?
Uh, he left somethin' for you.
.
He was always bugging me
to go out to that casino with him.
Now I wish I'd gone.
Bree, Gaby,
what are you doing here?
He's not here.
Where's Andrew?
He's hiking over by the cliffs.
- In the rain?
- Well, it wasn't raining when he left.
Why'd you two come
all the way out here?
We were worried about Andrew.
Because he... forgot his medicine.
So when is he gonna be back
from his hike?
Soon, I hope. Those rocks get
awful slippery when they're wet.
Oh, my God! Is that blood?
Yeah, I cut myself chopping wood.
What's that?
A shovel?
With fresh dirt on it!
Why is there fresh dirt?
Damn it, Carlos.
What did you do to Andrew?
- What are you talking about?
- Don't pretend!
- We know he came clean
about your mother! - My mother?
It was an accident!
He didn't mean to run her over!
You should blame me!
I'm the one who helped him
get rid of the car!
Mom?
Andrew!
Oh, thank God you're all right.
- What's going on?
- You killed my mother?
What? No. No, who said that?
We thought you told him.
In the woods alone?
What am I, crazy?
Well, you weren't here,
and we saw blood...
And the shovel with fresh dirt!
- Explain that!
- Do you see a bathroom in here?
- You son of a bitch. Carlos!
- I'm warning you. I have a gun...
In the car.
Park ranger!
Come in, please!
Hey.
Sorry you people picked
such a lousy weekend
- to enjoy our park here.
- Actually, we were just leaving.
Oh, 'fraid not.
Just got a radio call.
Big old pine tree just fell
across the access road.
We can't clear it up till tomorrow.
So you're gonna have
to sit tight till then.
You mean we have
to stay here all night?
Yep!
I got a deck of cards in my truck
in case you get bored.
Oh, I wouldn't worry about that.
Ahh.
Here. In case you're planning
to put your champagne
in a paint bucket.
I think I'm good.
Wow.
The sad caterpillar has turned
into an extravagant butterfly.
I am checking Tom's E.T.A.
so I know when to preheat the oven,
and I'm not talking about... cooking.
- I'm talking about...
- Uh,
I know what you're talking about.
Please stop.
Hey, Mr. C.F.O.,
the kids are gone,
the champagne is on ice,
and my bra actually
matches my panties.
I was just gonna call you.
I'm on my way to the airport.
I've got to get to Montreal
tonight on the jet.
What? No.
No, this is our celebration night.
Can't you reschedule?
I'm sorry. I can't.
I'm a hero for landing this meeting.
I got to be there.
Fine. I'll take another rain check.
You're starting to owe me
a lot of rain, you know?
I love you.
Travel safe.
Hey. Get your mitts off that.
We'll have it tomorrow
when he gets back.
Oh, Lynette.
Tomorrow it'll be something else.
Tom is a big shot now,
and the bigger he gets,
the less you're gonna see of him.
Hey...
you want the clothes
and the jewelry
and all the other perks.
Well, this is what they really cost.
You came to the funeral.
What?
My mother's funeral.
You sat in the second row,
behind the family,
consoled us all.
What was that like?
Kind of... funny?
Of course not.
It was very awkward.
Awkward.
Gosh.
So sorry her funeral
was so tough on you.
God, I'm so hungry.
Can't believe you guys
didn't bring any food.
Actually, I brought something.
This is all the dinner I need.
Oh, great. We've got tension
and firearms. Let's add alcohol.
Carlos, please put that away.
Andrew's only been sober a month.
I heard.
A whole month without a drink.
You must be thirsty.
Help yourself.
No, thanks. I'm... I'm good.
Okay, let me put it this way.
To mama Solis. May she rest in peace.
Are you gonna drink to my mom?
Or you gonna insult her memory?
- I... I guess I'm gonna drink
to your mom. - Yeah.
Carlos, stop it.
You have every right to be angry,
but please, think of all the years
we've been friends.
Friends?
You think that we're still friends?
How long have I watched you
play miss high-and-mighty
to the whole damn street?
And the whole time,
you were just covering your ass!
Hey. Get mad at me,
not the people
who just knew about it.
People?
Who else knew about this?
That's not important.
Gaby, what was that?
Nothing. It was a moth.
You knew.
Her I can understand,
but my own wife?
Oh, for God sakes, Carlos,
let it go. This is ancient history.
Not to me.
I mean, not a day went by
that I didn't think I should have
found the guy that did it.
Well, I didn't have to look far, did I?
I was taking him to ball games,
inviting his accomplice
to dinner parties,
and my wife knew.
You know what?
To hell with all of you.
Wait. Carlos,
where are you going?
Anywhere but here.
I don't trust myself
to be in the same room
with you people.
Carlos!
Ladies and gentlemen...
please discontinue use
of all electronic devices
so we can begin our meal service.
What are you doing here?
We are about to take off.
Not anymore.
I pushed your flight back...
half an hour.
You... what? How?
Well, let's just say your pilot's
back at the terminal,
having coffee with
a few dead presidents, so...
now it's just you, me...
oh, and two unfortunate lobsters.
Hey, you know what
you can do on a private jet?
Anything.
Absolutely anything.
I can't believe you did this.
I know. What a wife, huh?
No, no, no. No, I mean
it's really gonna screw me up.
I'm supposed to sit down
with my team the moment I land.
I need every second
to prep for this meeting.
I understand.
You have been working so hard.
I just wanted you to have
half an hour of fun.
Thank you,
but you need to realize...
this is fun.
Honey, I love this job.
I have never felt
so valuable before.
I... I walk into a room,
and people stop talking.
They want to know
what Tom thinks.
I got to tell you,
this company is a rocket ship.
It's taking me
on the ride of my life.
Wow.
That's...
I am really happy for you.
And don't think I have forgotten
why I have this gig.
You gave me the confidence
to jump at it,
and I am so, so grateful.
This is all 'cause of you.
- Can... can... yeah.
- What? Oh.
Back to fun?
Uh, I should take this.
I'll... I'll call you when I land.
Okay.
- You look great, by the way.
- Oh.
Hey. I got a little hung up
on the ground, but I'm on my way.
While I got you on the phone, um,
who is gonna be in
on this conference call?
Yeah... no.
N... n... not Ted.
I... I want to try to keep this...
Susan.
Roy.
I didn't know you came here.
Every Thursday,
Karen sticks 50 bucks in my pocket,
pats me on the butt,
and tells me not to come home
till I blow it or double it.
So slots?
I can't speak for those two,
but I think Lottie gets around.
No. Slots.
Oh! Oh, yeah. Hey, sit down.
Oh, thanks, but, uh,
I'm gonna try the poker room.
Oh, you don't want
to go in there.
Those guys are just
a bunch of sharks.
I'm sure I won't be here long.
I'm playing for a friend.
100 bucks?
You're an honest woman.
When somebody gives me
money to gamble,
I pocket it and tell 'em they lost.
Except you, Lottie.
You actually lost.
What's so funny?
Just wondering what Beth would
think if she could see us now,
driving along like
we're off to a picnic.
I think she'd be glad.
Our hate was what killed her.
She couldn't please either of us
without hurting the other,
so she just walked away.
So maybe she's thinking,
"Oh, great. Now they get along."
Or "Better late than never."
- Tell me something, Paul.
- What?
Did she suffer at the end,
in her last conscious moments?
I don't know.
I wasn't there when she died.
No, I didn't mean Beth.
I meant my sister.
You were there for that one.
For God sakes, Felicia.
I've wondered
about this for years.
I'm not wearing a wire, Paul.
And I'm not gonna frisk you
to make sure, so let's drop it.
Think about it.
We both saw someone
we love be destroyed.
First my sister drove
your wife to kill herself.
You admit that? Finally?
Yes, Paul, I do.
You loved your wife,
so you killed my sister.
I loved my sister,
so I tried to destroy you,
and who paid the price for it?
Beth.
I just hope that
by doing this together,
we can put a stop
to this awful cycle,
and reach some sort of... closure.
I'm all for closure.
Well, I lost my $50,
but I ate my weight in shrimp.
So all in all, a good day.
How you doing?
I'm okay.
Yeah, you got a little left.
What's that, 60 bucks?
Good for you, kid.
Those are $1,000 chips.
I'm all in.
$1,000? Y... you bet $6,000?
What are you, nuts?!
She's nuts.
We're taking these back.
Hands off the table, sir.
Grandpa must know something.
I'll call.
2 pair, kings over 4s.
Three aces!
The kid had three aces!
Susan, you won over $12,
I know.
I just...
keep...
winning.
And you cry every time.
You're weird.
Susan, what's wrong?
My friend...
Your friend is gonna be thrilled.
You just won for him.
He died yesterday.
He wanted me to come here.
He said I was on a lucky streak.
And he was right.
I am.
But...
Why?
Why do I keep winning
while other people lose?
And why did I get a kidney
while good people died?
It doesn't make any sense.
I served in Korea with this guy,
Joe Dansak...
Funny as hell, he made
whiskey sours in his helmet.
One day, we're out on patrol.
I felt something whizz past my ear,
I turned and looked,
and Joe was on the ground.
He was dead?
Yeah.
That night, I asked the sergeant,
"Why was it him and not me?"
He sort of shook his head
and said, "Why ask?"
So you're trying to tell me...
that it is... random.
I'm trying to do anything I can
to get you to stop crying, honey.
You're on a lucky streak.
Who knows why?
Just enjoy it.
But what happens
when my luck runs out?
I know.
"Why ask?"
Why ask?
How about right here?
What do you think, honey?
Is this a good spot?
Would you stop talking to the urn?
You're creeping me out.
Must we bicker? I thought
the point of doing this together
was to make a fresh start.
Do you really think I'm that stupid?
That just scattering some ashes
is gonna make me trust you?
Ugh. I know you don't trust me, Paul.
It's why you brought a gun.
What?
You're not gonna deny it.
Okay. So what?
You show up at my house and say,
"Hey, let's go to the woods together."
I'd be crazy not to bring a gun.
I know... and I'd be crazy
to let you keep it.
What?
How did you get that?
Prison's not a very nice place to live,
but I did pick up a few skills.
I just brought that
for self-defense.
So now I'm supposed
to believe you?
See, that's our problem, Paul.
How do you trust somebody
who doesn't trust you?
You fear me, so you bring a gun.
I fear you, so I take it.
Where does it end?
Just put the gun down.
It could end right here
with me shooting you
just so I can sleep easier.
Go ahead. Shoot me.
At least I'll die knowing
you'll rot in jail forever.
Oh, I don't think so.
I'll plead self-defense.
It is your gun, after all.
You pulled it on me,
we struggled, it went off.
I could kill you right now
and go scot-free.
Or I could do this.
I don't want you dead, Paul.
And I don't want us
to fear each other.
I just want this over.
Don't you?
I think you should do the honors.
Well, just keep looking.
It's not that big a forest.
Finally! Next time you drop
your girls off for a few hours,
you might mention you may not
be home that night.
The roads were closed.
We we trapped in the woods.
Could have been worse.
Could have been at my dinner party
when I tried to serve the tiramisu
- and the "tira" had been licked off.
- Look, Lee, I'm sorry, okay?
My guests were another
gay couple who were thinking
of adopting a child.
They're not anymore.
Lee, cut me some slack.
My husband is missing.
Don't try to play me.
Carlos called this morning.
He did?
Yeah. He asked if
I could watch the girls
for a few more hours
while he drove out to Littleton.
I said, "Why not?
I have very few breakables left."
What's he doing out in Littleton?
I know. Come on.
What? No, wait. Gaby, wait!
I'm hungry.
Of course you are.
You'll be pleased to know
that Paul was very touched
when we scattered the ashes.
He even teared up
a little at the end.
'Course...
He thought it was
really you in the urn...
not just some sweepings
from the fireplace.
But I would never scatter you
in the woods.
No. You're going to stay
where you belong,
right here...
with me.
And don't you worry about Paul.
I'll make him pay
for what he did to you.
But not just by shooting him, no.
That's too quick, too...
merciful.
No.
Death is the easy way out.
But look who I'm telling.
Oh, Carlos...
thank God you're okay.
You really scared us.
Aw. Flowers for your mom.
How sweet.
Save it, Gaby.
You never liked her.
Maybe you're right.
Maybe I didn't see why
she had to be in your life so much,
why she couldn't just let go.
But I wasn't a mother yet.
I didn't realize you never let go.
Listen, uh, Carlos...
We are so deeply sorry
for what we did.
Andrew was only 16
and already abusing alcohol,
a habit that he learned from me,
so I...
Quiet, m... mom, please.
I'm just trying to defend you.
I know. I know.
It's what you've always done.
And I've let you. That's why
my life has been such a mess,
but I need to do this.
This is between me and Carlos.
- Just please, wait in the car, okay?
- But, Andrew...
The car, mom!
Bree, let's go to the car.
I'm gonna make this right.
You can sue me.
You can go to the police.
Whatever it takes.
I know this must hurt.
I'm not hurt.
I'm proud.
Sit down.
Yes, whenever we make mistakes,
we need to apologize,
and then we need to move on.
We must try to accept
the changes in our lives...
Or choose to trust
an old enemy,
or learn to stop fighting
our children's battles.
But sometimes the pain
we've caused is so great,
there is no moving on.
Carlos, I want to thank you
for forgiving Andrew.
You are a generous man,
and I am so grateful to you.
May I come in?
- You can go to hell.
- Carlos.
Excuse me?
I did forgive Andrew.
He was a kid that made a mistake,
but you were an adult... my friend...
who covered up for him.
Carlos, please...
Mnh-mnh. Listen carefully,
because this is the last thing
I am ever going to say to you.
We are no longer friends,
not you and me,
- and not you and Gaby.
- You can't speak for me.
I just did.
No barbecues,
no cocktail parties,
no poker games.
You are not even
to wave to us on the street.
That's how it's going to be.
You can keep your muffins.
Sync by YYeTs.net
Corrected by Addic7ed
www.addic7ed.com