Previously on
"Desperate Housewives"...
I don't feel well.
Susan's health
took a turn for the worse.
Someone call 9-1-1.
You have given me so much, Keith.
One relationship came
to a bittersweet end.
- I know who you are. Get out!
- Forgive me, please.
- Please! I love you.
- No, you don't.
And another ended in betrayal.
The suburbs are full of parents,
and each parent
has their own style.
There's the disciplinarian...
the smotherer...
and the negotiator...
But the one thing
they all have in common...
is they love to judge
the parents next door.
Take your sister inside, sweetie.
I need to have
a little chat with Lee.
Hi! I see Jenny's
practicing again.
Two hours a day,
five days a week.
Wow. She is really
into that violin.
Sometimes. Mostly I have
to force her to do it.
Ohh. Big mistake.
Really? Seems like you have
an unsolicited opinion.
Look, I know you're new
to this parenting thing,
so I'm gonna tell you
how it works...
You can't force
a kid to do stuff,
'cause then it just leads
to a lot of door slamming
and name-calling,
and then the kid gets angry, too.
Well, here's the way
I think it works...
Jenny told us she wants
to play the violin,
so it's my job to make sure
she sticks with it.
By pushing her.
I'm not pushing her.
What? She wanted
to learn Mandarin.
Look, I don't mean to devalue
the two and a half weeks
you've had as a father.
I'm simply telling you what works.
So let me ask you...
what's Juanita pursuing on her own?
Huh?
As you know, the school
talent show is coming up.
Jenny's playing the violin.
What's Juanita going to do?
Well, that's hard to say.
See, the beauty of my method
is that Juanita has explored
so many... things,
it's hard to know
which one to showcase.
Well, this should be interesting...
Two different parenting philosophies
and a talent show to prove
which one of us is right...
in front of hundreds of people.
Yes. Will it be the overbearing,
hypercritical father...
Or the loving mom
who still looks hot in these sweats?
Game on.
Hey, sweetie, I heard
the talent show's coming up.
- What are you gonna do?
- Oh, it's going to be great. Watch.
Yes, each parent
has their own style.
But deep down,
they're all afraid
they're doing it wrong.
Sync by YYeTs.net
www.addic7ed.com
There are many things
that bring us pleasure...
baking for our friends...
having a good laugh...
donating to charity.
But the things
that bring us pleasure
may not be enough
to give our lives meaning...
Without someone to love.
Morning, dear.
Just back from the store.
What the hell?
I thought for dinner I could
make those lamb chops,
you love so much.
I got a great tip from the butcher
on searing the meat first.
I kicked you out of this house.
Oh, dear.
You're still angry with me.
But you know, Paul,
every couple has their fights.
And I'll admit, ours was a doozy.
That wasn't a fight.
That was the end.
Y... you don't mean that.
You're just upset.
But don't worry.
We will get past this.
Are you out of your mind?
You actually think
I would take you back?
Wait. I get it.
This is another ploy
cooked up by your sick mother.
My mother.
Yes.
She's the one you're mad at.
It's all her fault.
She told me you were a monster
who killed aunt Martha.
But then I fell in love with you.
And I realized...
you never could have
done such a thing.
It was all a lie.
Oh, Beth. That was no lie.
You don't mean...
My God.
Now we both feel betrayed.
Painful, isn't it?
- You know what this is?
- Uh, a closet?
No. It's a graveyard...
A graveyard filled with
all the stuff we bought
because you told us you wanted
to do something and then quit.
Remember this? Remember how
you begged us to buy you a guitar?
The strings hurt my fingers.
What about this?
Very expensive.
You've never touched it.
That's not true.
I use it to pretend
I'm playing guitar.
Juanita, you are full of ideas,
but you never see
any of them through.
Well, guess what? You are doing
one of these things at that talent show.
But I'm already doing something.
Not that.
Fine. If you won't
pick something, I will.
Tap.
- No.
- Yes.
You enjoyed it. You actually
set your personal record
for sticking with something...
two months!
But it's hard.
Let me tell you
something about life...
Anything that's
worth doing is hard.
- That's what life is?
- You're going back to that tap class,
and you're gonna practice
two hours a day,
seven days a week
until you nail it.
No, I'll do something else
at the show.
- Like what?
- I'll tell jokes.
A Jewish guy and
a Mexican walk into a bar...
No.
Thank you, Bree.
It always brightens my day
when you invite me to visit.
Well, reverend Sykes,
I very much enjoy your company.
As I do yours.
So... have you killed someone?
Excuse me?
I've always found the treats
you prepare for my visits
are a reliable indicator
of your level of spiritual turmoil.
The more exquisite
the baked goods,
the more anguished
your soul. This...
Is a hazelnut chocolate
chip scone with currants.
So I ask again...
have you killed someone?
No. It's just...
lately I feel like Job.
You know, Job,
from the Old Testament?
I'm familiar with the book,
thank you.
Why do you think you're Job?
I just feel that God
has taken everything away from me.
I lost my business,
my children never call me,
and... my boyfriend
Keith has left me.
Well, it's not exactly
body boils and dead camels,
but I understand what you're saying.
When I complained
after I was not accepted
into Yale divinity school,
my father had no sympathy.
Instead, he drove me
from our lovely home in Connecticut
to a dangerous section of the Bronx
and forced me to hand out
blankets to the homeless.
I see. That's the reason
you've always been
- so sensitive to the plight of the poor.
- Perhaps.
It's certainly the reason
my father was buried
in a sport jacket he detested.
The point is, looking at
what has been taken from us
is a bad way to go through life.
Looking for what we can give
to others is far better.
Could you pass me the tape?
I'm so glad I asked you to help.
I'm sorry. I'm feeling a little faint.
What is that smell?
It's like sneakers
mixed with cologne
mixed with "I ran around the block four
times wearing a shirt made of cheese."
That's Porter and Preston.
Well, get the place cleaned.
Yeah. I think I'm gonna
hold off on that for a while.
Why?
Because...
I kind of love this smell.
Okay, now you're
becoming delirious.
We've gotta get you out of here.
Hey, you don't have children,
so you don't get it.
But raising kids is
an amazing experience.
It is the most meaningful
thing I've ever done.
So anything that reminds me
of them is a good thing.
You must be pretty sad
they're gone.
No.
No, it's right.
They're moving on
with their lives.
It's wonderful.
Then why are there
tears in your eyes?
Um... that's the smell.
You're right.
Let's get outta here.
So... any idea
what's going on with me?
As much as I enjoy
passing out at restaurants,
I'm starting to get
a little concerned.
According to these tests,
your creatine levels are increasing.
- That's not good.
- Oh. Why is that happening?
I realize this isn't
a satisfying answer, but...
we don't know.
So, uh...
how serious is it?
I'll tell you what I tell
all my patients...
We are going to do everything
we can to get you a kidney.
But in the meantime,
live your life.
If there's things
you're thinking about doing...
do them now.
I think for our anniversary
we should have a picnic...
in the woods...
where we got married.
Sure.
That's a great idea.
I think we should do it now.
But our anniversary's
not till July.
Were we not at the same
appointment just now?
I thought that dialysis
was supposed to keep you healthy.
I guess it's just
not working for me.
- How bad is this?
- Pretty bad.
Yesterday, the doctor's secretary
handed me this free parking pass
with this... sad look.
It was like,
"yeah, you're doomed,
but your parking's free."
- So is this pass good for a month? A week?
- Gaby!
I just wanna know
what we're facing here.
All I know is...
I need a new kidney,
and there's nothing I can do
till they find me one.
Well, have you thought about
trying to find a donor yourself?
So far, you've only asked family.
Yeah, widen the circle.
Ask friends and neighbors.
Well, there's not much point.
I mean, finding a match
is like 1 in 1,000.
So ask a thousand people.
Yes. We can help.
We can canvass the neighborhood,
put up signs, go door to door.
Guys, it's a vital organ.
Susan, people care about you.
You might be surprised
what they're willing to do.
I appreciate the thought,
but I just can't ask anyone
to make that kind
of sacrifice for me.
I can't.
I'm gonna get you more coffee.
Maybe she can't.
But I can.
Donate a kidney?
Have we met? I'm like 112.
But, Karen, it's for
our dear friend Susan.
I'm not having elective surgery.
I take enough risk
just climbing out of the tub.
I don't know.
Aren't there serious risks?
Actually, the mortality
rate is quite low.
I meant the scarring.
I've spent a lot of time
at the gym working off
my love handles, and I will not
give up a chance to go shirtless.
- No.
- But I...
- She's really...
- No.
- Would you ju...
No.
Bree...
Yes?
No.
I want a baby.
Here.
I also have a 9-year-old.
One of my own.
Preferably a boy...
and in brown.
Wait.
You're serious?
Where did you get
this incredibly rash
- and not-thought-out idea?
- From you.
You know what you said yesterday
about kids giving your life
meaning? I want that.
I want... meaning.
- In the form of a baby?
- Mm.
Exactly.
I already made an appointment
with an adoption agency,
which was right next door
to my manicurist.
It was like it was meant to be.
Are you sure about this?
I mean, your social calendar
is very full.
A baby would change all that.
It requires a lot of sacrifice
and compromise.
Maybe the way you do it.
Excuse me?
You work your life
around your kids.
I intend to work
my child into my life.
No offense, but I think
you make it a lot harder
than it has to be.
You know what?
You might be right.
But before you commit
to being a mom,
why don't you give it
a test drive?
What do you mean?
You could watch Paige some night.
Tom and I haven't
been out in a while.
Really? You'd let me babysit?
Yeah!
Which one is Paige?
This one.
I accept. Wow.
My first step toward being a mom.
Oh, you watch.
I am gonna be a natural.
Oh, uh, does she eat shellfish?
Maybe.
So I got us caviar,
shrimp pâte, smoked salmon.
If there's a part of a fish
they can overcharge for,
we have it.
Can you put these in the back?
Thanks.
- Sweetie?
- Yeah?
- I just want to thank you for doing
this today. - You're welcome.
And you can thank me again
when we go back in July
for our real anniversary.
And I'd really love if,
for the next eight hours,
I'm not sick.
No talk of kidneys.
Let's just have a fun,
normal day, okay?
You got it.
One fun, normal day
in the woods, coming up.
Nothing's gonna ruin this trip.
Hey. How was tap class?
It's too hard.
I don't wanna do it anymore.
Oh, sweetie...
You're doing it.
We're not a family of quitters.
Ugh! You quit all the time.
Yesterday we played
hide-and-seek.
Celia and I looked
for you for an hour
before we saw your car was gone.
So I found a great hiding place
at the shoe store.
It's not quitting.
All right, look,
let me ask you something...
Are you getting better?
- I guess.
- Well, there you go.
Now go upstairs and change.
Oh, and remember,
tomorrow's lesson's two hours.
You're gonna make
my feet fall off.
I can't wait for this to be over.
Why are you working her so hard?
It's a lousy school talent show.
You think Bob and Lee
are going easy on their kid?
No! They push her.
That girl's so good at the violin,
she's practically Asian.
So that's what this is about.
You're competing with Bob and Lee.
Pfft. That's ridiculous.
This is about Juanita.
I'm building her self-esteem
and giving her a chance to shine.
And if a couple of
same-sex parents
end up crying at home
in their silk kimonos, so be it.
Oh, Mike, look at this place.
Isn't it as beautiful
as you remember it?
Yeah. Lucky I didn't leave it
on the roof of the car.
Ugh. Will you forget
about the picnic basket?
I guess you're right.
What's important is we're together.
And there's no...
Damn it! They forgot the fries!
Unbelievable.
Okay, Mike, look at me.
Think back eight years,
when we stood in this spot
and we pledged
our love to each other.
Oh! I know.
Let's renew our vows.
That's a great idea.
I, Mike Delfino,
promise to love...
I, Mike Delfino, promise to...
It's just a bird. Forget it.
Promise to love and honor...
Okay.
Now he's just mocking me.
Mike!
Mike, stop!
Oh, my God.
I... I can't believe
you hit that bird.
Yeah, I know.
I was aiming for that one.
As the gayest person
at this brunch,
I feel it is my duty
to say... "fabulous."
- Yeah, Bree, what's the occasion?
- Oh,
nothing, just a little
get-together for friends.
- Smoked salmon tartare cornucopia?
- Mmm.
This feels weird.
She's up to somethin'.
Oh, what are you talking about?
It's just a brunch.
Excuse me. If I could borrow
a moment of your time
for a brief presentation.
- Oh, God, you're right. It's an ambush.
- Mm-hmm.
It seems many of you
have some misguided ideas
about kidney donation,
so I have invited Craig Lynwood,
transplant coordinator
at Fairview Memorial
to dispel some of those myths.
Mr. Lynwood, is it true
there's an age limit to donating?
No, not necessarily.
And does the surgery
cause unsightly scarring?
It's laparoscopic.
The scarring is minimal.
Well, I don't know
about the rest of you,
but I find that very reassuring.
So now that we have the facts,
I am sure you'll all
want to get tested.
- Okay, fine. I'll go in next week.
- No need.
Nurse Dearborn?
So the line forms over here.
And we won't take no
for an answer.
You're gonna get tested?
No. I think I can take Gaby.
I don't know how Paul
found out, mama, but he did.
And then... well...
he threw me out.
He was just... so cold.
What a sad story.
If only someone had warned you
what a bastard he is.
I know. You were right all along.
I should have listened to you.
But I'm going to make it up to you.
Oh, Beth.
I can't allow you
back in my life.
You have failed me
in every possible way.
No. I didn't.
Paul confessed.
Really?
Did you get it on tape?
Did he write it on a napkin?
Of course not.
Because you have never
done anything right
in your life.
Give me another chance.
I'll do anything.
I have no more use for you.
Good-bye.
Wait!
I have nowhere to go.
What's going to happen to me, mama?
You're going to live
a lonely, depressing life
in some ratty apartment
with plenty of time to think
about all the people
you disappointed...
most of all... me.
Guard, I'm done here.
Take her off the visitor's list.
The Oakridge School talent show
will start in five minutes.
So... checking out Fairview's
answer to Itzhak Perlman?
I don't know what that is,
but if it's German for
"cat strangler," then yes.
It's like that, is it?
So when's your daughter
start stomping off to Buffalo?
She's on right before Jenny.
So you might want to keep
your sunglasses handy, because
Juanita is going to be dazzling.
Honey! Are you okay?
Were you being chased by a bee?
No, it's my routine.
That's the first time
I've nailed the finale.
Oh, that... that was you nailing it?
To the floor. Bam!
Performers to the stage.
Well, uh...
Where are my tap shoes?
I don't know.
I left them right here.
Oh, honey. I guess you lost 'em,
and the show's about to start.
Dang it!
I can't believe this.
I was so excited. I worked so hard.
I'm sorry. You want to stay
and watch your friends?
We can go after for ice cream.
Who cares?
I will see your shirt
and I will raise you one bra.
Nicely played.
Do you hear something?
Hmm. Probably just
a peeping raccoon.
Oh.
No. No, I think
there's someone out there.
This way! There they are!
- What the hell?
- I got him!
Identify yourselves.
Are you northern agitators?
Do we look like
northern agitators?
W... we're just
celebrating our anniversary.
You guys...
playing paintball or something?
No, madam, we are not playing.
I am Major General Jedediah Garrett
of the Confederate Army, and we are...
Kevin... Kevin... Kevin.
Hi. Hi.
Uh, we're part of a
civil war reenactment group.
Yeah, I know, I know.
Get a real life, right?
Can't you guys just have
your pretend war over there?
Pretend?
You, sir, are interrupting
the Battle of Fredericksburg.
Actually, we have
the entire park until 6:00.
Kyle, show 'em the permit.
I... i... it's fine.
We believe you.
No, it's not fine.
This is really important to her.
Just give us a couple hours.
No, sir. Now begone!
Men, we must be ready to attack
the enemy should they attempt
to retreat into Maryland.
What a douche.
A douche, you say?
Yeah.
Mike! Let's just go.
Eyes closed, Kyle.
You're supposed to be dead.
I died with my eyes open.
It happens.
Close 'em, Kyle.
And now to close our show
is a violin solo
by Jenny Hunter-McDermott.
She lives next door to me.
We're getting those
double-paned windows.
Okay.
Ouch!
Poor Lee. He must be
pretty embarrassed.
Does he look embarrassed?
She always stumbles over that part.
She really stumbled over it today.
But she powered through it.
We couldn't be prouder.
Wait! Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Nobody move!
Okay, don't leave yet.
There's still, uh, one girl
who hasn't performed yet.
But I lost my tap shoes.
Oh, that's right.
Oh... oh, hey! Wait!
Is that them in the back room,
behind the radiator?
Aah!
Whoo! Bravo!
Oh, look, we had a great day.
Think of it this way...
now we have a funny story
to tell people.
Two funny stories?
Hello?
Bree, it's Craig Lynwood.
I have some great news.
All your efforts have paid off.
You found a match?
We found two.
Oh, my God.
It's a miracle.
Who are they?
Well, one of them is you.
Bree? Are you there?
I'm sorry. It's just, uh...
I... I wasn't expecting this. Um...
Who's the other one?
Woman named Beth Young.
Beth? I didn't even
know she got tested.
- Apparently she saw one of your flyers.
- And she wants to do this?
Well, I don't know yet.
We're having a hard time
getting in touch with her.
So... should we continue
to look for this Beth Young,
or is the donor going to be you?
Fancy. I thought we were
just gonna grab a burger.
Renee was really
talking this place up,
so I thought we could splurge.
Or we could stay home
and eat money.
We better order. Any second,
my phone is going to ring,
and Renee is gonna beg me
to rush home and get Paige.
I don't know.
She might surprise you.
Oh, great.
One night out and
we have to listen to that.
Who brings a baby
to a place like this?
Hey. Let's give the parents
that dirty look that we always get,
like, "huh."
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
It's Renee...
on a date...
with our baby.
Unbelievable.
And you thought
she'd be good at this?
Ohh, look at that.
What? What is she doing now?
Nothing. The filet mignon
just went by. It looks amazing.
S... so should we just
go over and get Paige?
Not yet.
I want to watch.
Look, look, there you go.
She's probably ordering
milk for Paige.
Or she's giving our baby away.
Wow. She really is bad at this.
Ugh!
Excuse me.
Oh, hi. I'll be right over
to take your order.
Why did that woman
give you this baby?
She gave me $100 to see
if I could calm her down...
But I don't mind.
I love children.
I'm actually expecting my third.
Really? That's beautiful.
Listen, how would you like to make...
$200?
Are you ready to order?
Uh... have you
forgotten something?
Oh, your drinks will be right out.
No, no. Not the drinks.
The baby.
I gave you a baby.
Where is it?
Oh, I had orders backing up,
so I gave it to a busboy.
What? What busboy?
Um... he should be
here somewhere.
Oh, I hope he didn't finish
his shift and go home.
You better find me that baby.
Or I'm gonna take that one now!
Uh, hey, busboy.
Are you the one that has a baby?
I'm looking for a baby...
2 feet tall, big head, drools.
I'm looking for... a baby.
Um... did anyone pass you a baby?
Has anyone seen a baby?!
- Had enough?
- In a minute.
That vein in her head
is really going.
Do you know
where there's a baby?
Because they gave it to me.
I don't know where the baby is!
Lynette...
and Paige.
How... did you get Paige?
What are you doing with Paige?
You took our baby on a date.
Well... Brian called.
It was his one night in town.
Well, then you say,
"sorry, Brian, I can't make it tonight."
That's what being
a mother is about...
making sacrifices, something
you know absolutely nothing about.
Ugh! Come on, Tom.
Beth? It's Bree Van De Kamp.
Um...
coming.
I, uh, went to your house.
Paul told me you were here.
We aren't together anymore.
I'm so sorry.
It is what it is.
Thanks...
for checking on me.
Well, actually,
the reason I came by...
has the gentleman
from the transplant office
reached you?
Why?
Am I a match?
Yes.
Wow.
So... what do I do now?
Is there someone I need to call?
Are there forms?
Well, that won't be necessary,
because I'm a match, too.
What?
I know.
Two in the same neighborhood.
We're very blessed.
Anyway, I, uh,
am going to be Susan's donor,
but I wanted to thank you for...
getting tested.
When you moved onto the Lane,
I didn't give you a chance.
I saw you as a woman
who married a man I hated,
and I see now that you're
so much more than that.
I'm sorry it took me
so long to realize it.
Well, I...
I should go.
I want to do it.
Beth, no...
Please, Bree.
Let me help Susan.
It would really mean a lot to me.
Beth, what I'm about to say
may not make sense to you,
but, um...
I've been going through, uh...
a dark time...
feeling alone and unconnected
and wondering if I have a purpose,
so for me to be able
to do this for my friend...
It may mean a lot to you...
but it means everything to me.
Thank you for understanding.
Sorry about last night.
I bought this for the baby.
Wow.
Expensive, fragile, pointy...
if only it were flammable.
I'm not really cut out
to be a mother, am I?
No.
And there's nothing wrong with that.
It's not for everyone.
What's sad is how many people
go ahead and have kids anyway.
Well, what do people do
to fill up the hole in their lives?
No matter what I do,
no matter who I'm with, I...
I feel alone.
You'll find something,
and when you do,
you'll be glad you have the room.
Lots and lots of room.
Thanks. Mm.
I'm so glad I stopped by.
Hey.
We're about to eat.
Why don't you join us?
Okay.
But keep the baby
on your side of the table.
What? I'll probably
let her play with my knife.
Ow! Son of a bitch!
Let me look at it.
No.
You okay?
Mike, are you okay?
No, I'm not okay.
We never should have come here.
Instead of waiting
for our real anniversary,
we wasted our time
on this disaster.
Is that why you are yelling at me?
'Cause I...
'cause I moved up our anniversary?
Because you're dying.
You're dying,
and there's not a damn thing
I can do about it.
Look, I'm sorry, but it...
it feels like you're getting ready
to say good-bye...
like you're bailing on me.
Bailing?
I am fighting.
I... I am scared,
I don't know what's gonna happen,
but I am fighting my ass off.
I want to see M.J. graduate.
I want to grow old with you.
I want all of that.
But in the meantime, I...
I am gonna enjoy every...
every moment of every day.
Let's get outta here.
Hey. Lean on me.
I'm a lot stronger
than you think.
Our lives are brief.
That's why it's important
to search for meaning.
We find it in
our daughter's smile...
in the warmth of our friends...
or the comfort of our faith.
Okay, coming through.
Then there are those
who make their lives meaningful
by making a great sacrifice.
Hello. My name is Beth Young.
I'm here to donate a kidney.
I just found out I'm a match
for a friend of mine.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
You're in the wrong place.
You want the transplant office
on the fourth floor.
These are my forms.
I think you'll see
they're all completely filled out.
Again, ma'am,
you want the transplant office.
This is emergency.
My friend's name
is Susan Delfino.
It's funny. At first,
we didn't get along very well.
Actually, we never got along.
But that kind of thing
seems so insignificant
when someone is in need.
That's great. Fourth floor,
elevator's down the hall.
I really don't mean to trouble you,
but these forms have
to get to the right place.
I don't want to mess this up.
It's the most important
thing I've ever done.
Okay.
I'll take care of it.
Thank you so much.
You're very kind.
Wheelchair is on its way.
We need some help over here!
Sync by YYeTs.net
www.addic7ed.com