Previously on
"Desperate Housewives"...
Paul was shocked to find
Felisha was back on the lane.
Well, hello, Paul.
Tom's new job came with perks.
You know what you
can do on a private jet?
Anything.
A relationship was forced to end.
We are no longer friends,
not you and me,
- and not you and Gaby.
- You can't speak for me.
- I just did. - And Susan got
her transplant, thanks to Paul.
I'm sure as I sign the papers,
they'll be contacting you.
After Susan Delfino's
kidney transplant,
her doctor ordered her
to abstain from sex...
for six weeks.
But what the doctor
couldn't prevent Susan from doing...
was dreaming about it.
These dreams were filled
with torrid caresses...
with passionate kisses...
and with soft cries of ecstasy.
Ahh.
The only thing missing
from these dreams...
was her husband.
Are you okay?
Uh... yeah, I just...
Had a dream.
Yeah, I know.
You know? What do you know?
- Was I saying something? Was I talking?
- More like moaning.
Oh, moaning! Oh, God.
Yeah, you mentioned him, too.
Oh, don't be embarrassed.
So you had a sex dream.
It's not surprising given
how long we've had to lay off.
Tell me... what were we doing?
Uh... we...
Hey, maybe we could recreate it
when we end our drought
in 2 days, 17 hours,
- and 35 minutes.
- Well, uh...
needless to say, it was
some pretty kinky stuff.
Like, did we--
did we do that thing--
- that thing we talked about?
- Mike, it was my dream, not yours.
Oh, God, I'm desperate.
Can you give me some details?
Uh... or could show you
in 2 days, 17 hours,
and 34 minutes.
That'll work.
I can't wait. We'll send M.J.
to Mrs. McCluskey's,
and have the whole night together.
Yes, Susan was having
dreams about sex.
Just the two of us.
Uh-huh. Just me and...
you.
And they were becoming
a nightmare.
Sync by YYeTs.net
Corrected by Addic7ed
www.addic7ed.com
The residents of Wisteria Lane
are nothing if not loyal.
They love their country.
They root for the home team.
They support their favorite brand.
But the fiercest loyalty
on Wisteria Lane
is the one between friends.
All right. I gotta run.
I'm meeting the girls for coffee.
Stop.
Which girls? Will Bree be there?
She better be. She's buying.
Then you're not going.
Wait. You were serious about us
never speaking to Bree again?
That woman satour table,
spent the holidays with us,
all the while knowing
her son ran over my mother.
- Yeah, I'm serious.
- Fine, then you stop talking to her.
But you're not gonna control me,
'cause I have the secret weapon.
You'll withhold sex? Please.
You always fold before I do.
That's not true.
The last time you tried,
you got so turned on
telling me what you
weren't gonna do to me,
- you wound up doing it to me right then.
- Damn it.
Well, you're still
not gonna stop me
- from seeing Bree.
- Yes, I am.
Our relationship
with that woman is over,
and I forbid you to see her again.
He forbid me.
Who is he to forbid me?
I mean, what is this, 19...
Whenever it was that husbands
got to forbid their wives?
Gaby, he has every reason to be upset.
I hate to say this,
but I think we should
keep our distance for a while.
What? I'm not giving in to this.
I've already caused Carlos so much pain.
I think it's the only thing we can do.
So what are you saying?
No more poker?
No more lunches?
No more shopping?
I'll miss it as much as you do.
Oh, really? Doesn't sound like it.
- I think this is easy for you.
- Easy?
I wanna come over there right now,
so you can drag me
to the mall kicking and screaming,
but we can't.
I have to go.
I have scones in the oven.
- I love your scones.
- Stop.
Good-bye, Gaby.
You're not hanging up.
But I have to.
- Hey, Lynette! You're not gonna
believe this. I-- - Shh!
I had to walk Paige
around the block
eight times to get her down.
Nothing is so important that
you need to raise your voice.
Not even this?
Weisman leadership conference?
Seriously?
You're invited?!
- And so are you.
- Oh, my God!
Warren Buffett
goes to this conference,
and Bill Gates and Oprah--
It's one of her favorite things.
Oh! Look at this!
All the great speakers.
- Plus they've got the spa, and--
- And no kids, right? No kids?
No kids.
Yes! Yes!
You take her.
I gotta figure out what to wear.
Hey, you two!
Thanks for watching him.
Hey, can you watch him again
on Wednesday? Mike and I are--
Yeah, I know.
Your big night, huh?
Mike told you?
Didn't have to.
I caught him staring at my cleavage.
So... post-transplant sex, huh?
If it's as good
as my post-cancer sex,
you're in for a treat.
Fingers crossed.
Hey, have you looked
at your old house lately?
It's kind of a wreck.
Does look a little neglected.
You should go over and
talk to Paul. I'll watch M.J.
Oh. I... can't do that.
Um, I mean, he might be
in the middle of something.
Or he might be hanging
from the showerhead.
Do me a favor and check.
'Cause if he's dead in there,
I live downwind.
Susan?
Paul?
Paul.
Uh... hi there.
Um... I-I was just
in the neighborhood,
and it-- and it looked
like things were piling up,
and would you mind
closing that robe, please?
Oh, sorry.
And sorry about the mess.
I haven't been getting
out of the house much.
You look thin.
Are you eating?
Yes.
I'm fine. I'm a little behind
on my chores.
So if there's nothing else...
Paul, um...
are you sure you're okay?
Yes, Susan.
Fit as a fiddle.
Good-bye.
I've already spotted
two ex-senators
and three covers of "Forbes."
Everybody here is definitely A-list.
Oh! Bob! Lee!
- Hey, hey, you fancy hotshots.
- Hi!
- Mwah.
Hiya. Hi.
Glad you've done
this conference before,
'cause I'm definitely
gonna need somebody
- to show me the ropes.
- Nothing to it. Just don't talk politics.
And don't push Warren Buffett
in the pool.
I didn't push him.
He got between me
and the margarita bar.
Oh, let me introduce you
to Barry Weisman.
Prepare to endure the single most
bone-crushing handshake
of your life.
Bye.
Come on.
Well, with this line,
it's gonna be hard to get drunk.
Lesson one--
The power of the words
"The president's council
of economic advisors
want their martinis now."
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
That's a little trick I learned
when I was too cheap
to buy my own newspapers.
How fantastic is it that
Chris Cavanaugh is speaking?
I thought "Flashpoint"
was the best business book
- of the year.
- I agree.
I've heard him speak before.
He's even better in person.
We're in for a treat tomorrow.
Meg Butler, president of Amtech.
Oh, um...
Uh, Lynette Scavo.
My husband is the C.F.O.
of Morris Technologies.
Oh. You're a plus one.
What's that mean?
Unfortunately, it means you
won't be seeing Chris Cavanaugh.
The seminars are only for participants.
Wha--
What am I gonna be doing?
I will tell you what--
japanese flower arranging.
Did I weep at the simple beauty
of my design last year? Yes.
- Yes, I did.
- I don't want to arrange flowers.
Why are they dividing us up like this?
Maybe it's because
some of us spent our lives
working our way up
the corporate ladder,
and others just
married someone who did.
Excuse me.
Oh, no. That's--
Wow. That is ridiculous.
I really want to see those seminars.
Hey, don't worry.
You are going to love
what they have planned for us.
Attention!
If I could have all
of my plus ones find a buddy,
we're going to get to know
each other with a scavenger hunt.
Bree.
Gaby. What are you doing here?
I just came by to talk to Lynette.
Oh, she's out of town.
She asked me to water the plants
and collect the mail.
Oh.
You look good.
You, too.
New coat?
You noticed.
I should go.
Can't you just stay and talk?
- Maybe have a cup of coffee?
- Gaby, we shouldn't.
- It's just coffee, Bree.
- But your husband...
He'd never look for us here.
Oh, come on.
It's been really hard
for me not seeing you.
Aw, it's been hard for me, too,
especially with Lynette out of town.
I mean, there's Susan, of course,
but lately whatever
topic you bring up,
she manages to steer it
right back to kidneys.
Tell me about it.
Well, I guess I...
could put on a pot.
I like mine with cream.
I know how you like it.
Hello, Karen.
Felicia. Hi.
When did they let you out?
About a week ago.
I just stopped by because
I wanted you to have this.
It belonged to my sister, and...
she was always so fond of you.
That's sweet.
It's my small way of saying thanks
for keeping my secret
all those years.
Yeah, not much a secret anymore.
Don't I know it.
But I've kept your secret.
I never told a soul about
your role that night,
and I never will.
Um...
It's not really a good time
to talk about that.
I understand.
But I hope you'll stop
by my place sometime.
We have so much
catching up to do.
Sure. I'll do that.
Uh, wh-where are you staying?
Haven't you heard?
I'm moving in next door.
We're going to be neighbors.
Who was that?
Just an old friend.
Old friend?
You look like you've seen a ghost.
Make me a drink, will you, sweetie?
Toby!
Here, kitty, kitty.
Toby! Where are you?
Here, kitty, kitty!
Toby!
Oh, Felicia, help me out.
Ida Greenberg's lost
her stupid cat again.
What happened to you?
Is that blood?
You never saw me.
- I have to go.
- Your hand! Let me call you an ambulance.
You love my sister, right?
Martha? Y-yeah.
And you know Paul Young
murdered her?
There's no doubt in my mind.
Oh, my God.
Did you kill Paul?
No!
He killed me.
What?
They'll find my blood in his house
and my fingers in the car,
and he'll spend
the rest of his life prison
if you say you never saw me.
- Don't ask me to do this.
- Please, Karen!
Paul got away
with Martha's murder,
but... he won't get away with mine.
Toby.
Here, kitty, kitty!
Ikebana is all about bringing
together nature and humanity.
The three main branches,
or shushi, represent chi-- earth,
ten-- heaven, and jin-- man.
Interesting.
Nothing to represent woman.
How about this insignificant
clump of moss?
We could stuff it down at the bottom,
where it will only speak
when spoken to.
- Does my chi look a little droopy?
- Did you hear me?
Yes.
Yes, Lynette, I heard you.
I heard you during yoga,
during the fashion show,
all through salsa dancing--
"Life is unfair."
- Olé!
- Well, I'm sorry, but I came here
to learn new things
and meet interesting people,
not to pretend that
putting sticks in a vase is art.
Are we still having a problem?
Yes, we still are.
Doesn't it piss you all off
that we're stuck in our gilded cage,
forbidden to go
to interesting seminars
- just because we're plus ones?
- No.
This is fun.
I really feel like I'm in Japan.
This is the United States of America
in the 21st century,
not some oppressive
patriarchal regime.
It may be small and red,
but this lanyard
is no better than a burka!
- Oh, dear. - We need to storm the gates
and demand to be let inside!
- If you're not gonna use the rest
of your flowers, can I--
Come on! Rise up!
If we do it together,
we will not be denied!
4:00, people!
I think you've all earned a cocktail.
No. No!
No, do not drink those!
Those are the--
the cocktails of oppression,
make from equal parts tyranny
and blind obedience, and...
Oh, screw it.
Mmm. This is the best
pineapple upside-down cake
- you have ever made.
- You know why?
It has an ingredient my cakes
have never had before...
Danger.
I know! Sneaking around
makes everything taste better.
When I was with John Rowland,
every sense was heightened,
it was like this...
Skip it. You wouldn't understand.
Oh, really? Wouldn't I?
What? You? No way.
Just because I don't trumpet
my indiscretions like you do,
doesn't mean I haven't had
a little walk on the wild side.
- You cheated on Rex?
- Of course not.
What do you take me for?
I cheated on Orson.
With who?
Karl Mayer.
Oh, my God!
He was a slimeball,
but he was hot.
Mm. We'd meet at this cheap hotel,
and as guilty as it made me,
I still felt this... tingle,
this frisson I'd never felt before.
And now this week with you...
it's back.
Hmm.
Just wish Lynette didn't have
to come home tomorrow.
Actually, that motel story
gives me an idea.
Gaby, I'm flattered,
- but I really don't think we should--
- Not that.
There's a great new spa
that just opened on Foster Lake.
We should go next weekend.
Do we dare?
I think we both know
the answer to that.
I went by our house today.
It's looking a little run-down.
Yeah? You want me to talk to Paul?
He's supposed
to be keeping the place up.
Uh, actually, I already did. Uh...
he seems kind of run-down, too.
Wh-what are you doing
talking to Paul?
Well, I was picking up M.J.,
and he came out of the house,
and... kind of worried about him.
Why? Who cares?
Mike, he gave me a kidney.
No, Beth gave you a kidney.
Paul did everything
he could to block it.
Yeah, but we talked,
and after, he seemed so sad.
I don't give a damn!
I know you feel bad for the guy,
but I don't trust him.
Please... just do me a favor
and stay away from him.
Okay.
Now can we talk about
something a little more fun?
Like our plan for sex night?
Okay, hold that thought.
I'm gonna take a shower.
May I come in?
Please.
Lynette, what are you doing here?
I thought you had a spa thing.
Oh, please.
I can get a face full of steam
standing over a pot of spaghetti
any night of the week.
I wanna see Chris Cavanaugh.
I know, and I asked,
and they said no.
The keynote speech
isn't for spouses.
They said they've got
other activities planned for you.
Activities that they plan for me?
Tom, I'm not a child.
I'm a grown-up.
I'll decide what I want to do.
Come on. Don't you know
how much I wanna see this guy?
Can't you pull some strings?
I don't have any strings.
When I've been five or six times,
then maybe I can ask
for a favor, but not now.
There you are.
Someone's been naughty.
Let's go, Mrs. Scavo.
I think it's somebody's spa time.
This is why you keep us drunk, huh?
So we don't fight back.
This hits the spot.
I remembered you like your coffee
same way you like your men--
strong... and Irish.
So how did you get out
of jail so soon?
Was it good behavior
or bad behavior with the warden?
Oh, Karen.
How I've missed your
frank and salty questions.
Actually, it was, uh,
what they call humanitarian release.
You see...
my only daughter
passed away just recently.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know you had a daughter.
Such a sweet girl.
So young.
She was barely 30 when she died.
I wish could have met her.
Actually, I'm pretty sure you did.
Her name was Beth.
Beth Young.
Can I... freshen that?
So we'll cut you back to ten
every other day
on the prednisone and take it from there.
Any questions?
I do have one.
Shoot.
Is it common for patients
to have sex dreams
about the husbands
of their dead donors?
I have to admit,
I did not see that coming.
Understand-- awake, I have
no conscious desire for this man.
But in my dreams...
- Susan, I'm not a psychologist.
- But you went to med school.
You must have learned
something about dreams--
a course, a book.
Okay. What did you talk about
before you went to sleep?
- I was talking about him.
- Oh.
I mean, he's not doing
very well, and I got
in an argument with my husband
about whether I should help him.
Well, maybe the dream is telling you
to follow that impulse.
The man's wife died.
You're alive because of it.
It's natural to be concerned about him
and want to make sure he's okay.
Mike really doesn't want me
to talk to him.
It's your call, but my guess is your
dreams won't stop until you do.
When Paul went to jail,
his one goal was to make me
pay for putting him there,
so he wrote to Beth,
begging her to come see him.
He said he was innocent,
that he was a good man.
Paul's very charming when
he wants to be, and Beth...
she fell in love with him,
just like he knew she would.
Well, didn't you try to warn her?
Of course. She just said
I didn't know him like she did.
When he was released,
when he had defiled her,
the real Paul came out.
He said he'd never loved her,
that she was stupid
and that she didn't deserve to live.
S-so she killed herself...
just like he knew she would.
Bastard.
I hope you'll keep
this story between us
at least for now.
Beth would hate
for all her friends to know
what a fool she was.
Okay, but the one thing I don't get
is why do you wanna live
on the same street as that monster?
So I can watch him!
It's too late for Beth and my sister,
but I won't let him
destroy another woman
the way he destroyed them.
Well, you're not watching him alone,
because I'll keep my eye
on that S.O.B., too.
Now if you need anything--
anything at all--
you give me a call.
Oh, Karen.
I'm so lucky to have a friend like you.
Wonderful what a
4-handed massage can do.
One more hand,
and it would've been perfect,
but this ain't that kind of spa.
Yeah.
No, no, tell him he has a choice.
He can sign those papers before
I shove them down his throat
or after they come out the other end.
Yes.
- I guess someone didn't see
the "no cell phones" sign. - No.
I guess that rule
only applies to plus ones.
I'll talk to you later.
I wanna grab a soak before
the keynote speech. Bye.
Oh, Ms. Butler?
Huh? Oh, hi.
Yes, I'm her. She's me.
Meg Butler. Meg.
Oh, we have a seat
for you up front.
Oh, uh...
Uh... great.
Welcome, ladies and gentlemen.
Now to introduce
our keynote speaker--
the president of Amtech,
Ms. Meg Butler.
Come up.
Come on.
Hi.
Those of you who know Meg
know... I'm not Meg.
Nutmeg. That's funny.
Uh, anyway... Meg asked me
to introduce Chris Cavanaugh
because she knows
what a huge, huge fan I am.
Where are ya,
ya big-brained rascal?
Oh, there he is.
Almost as hot
as his author photo.
Anyway...
Those of you who haven't read
"Flashpoint," do it immediately.
Put it in your kindle, your iPad.
I don't know. Buy the book.
It will make you smarter,
because what Chris Cavanaugh
has to say about human nature,
about creativity,
- is absolutely--
- There she is!
That's the bitch who stole
my lanyard and my clothes!
Ladies and gentlemen,
Chris Cavanaugh.
Hi. I called you a bunch of times.
- Your phone must be broken.
- It is now. Please respect my privacy.
Paul, you have to let me talk to you.
Why?
Because you're a mess, and
someone has to do something.
And okay, I'm having dreams about us.
Dreams? What kind of dreams?
Regular dreams--
lots of daylight, lots of clothes.
Look, I'm your landlord.
I have a right to come in.
But I'd like you to invite me in.
Getting ready to cook something?
I see onions, potatoes,
this long green and white thing
with scary little hairs on the bottom.
This is food, right?
It's called a leek.
I was trying
to make potato leek soup.
I love potato leek soup.
Of course, that was before
I knew what a leek was.
You want some help?
Come on. Soup I can do.
Making soup? Is that what
we were doing in your dream?
No. No, we weren't.
That reminds me.
I need to wash my hands.
Hey. How was the big conference?
Okay.
You meet any guys for me?
I'm not picky.
You know what they say.
Ugly plus money equals handsome.
Well, apparently,
crazy plus wife equals laughingstock.
Uh, you two having a fight?
Yeah, kinda.
Well, you won't even know I'm here.
Tom, why don't we
finish this later?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Do you not wanna be embarrassed
in front of your friend?
Well, she just embarrassed me
in front of the whole fortune 500.
I don't know how many
different ways I can apologize.
At some point,
you're gonna have to let it go.
I kinda don't feel like
letting it go, Lynette.
It's not just the fact
that you humiliated me.
It's that after all those years
that I supported you,
took a backseat to your career,
you couldn't do the same for me.
What happened?
It was awful.
All weekend,
I was treated like a plus one,
a second class citizen, a--
A wife!
Lynette, in Tom's world,
that's what you are.
You're gonna have
to get used to it.
What if I don't
wanna get used to it?
Well, take it from someone
who spent eight years
being "Mrs. Third Baseman,"
you can be a wife...
Or you can be a first wife.
I'm home.
Hi, honey. How was your day?
Worked straight through lunch
and I'm starving.
What's this?
It's a pineapple upside-down cake.
Wow.
Reminds me of the cake
your old friend Bree
brought to dinner last month.
Huh. I-I don't remember that.
'Cause obviously Bree
didn't make this one,
since I don't see her anymore
because I know...
how you feel about her.
So... where'd this come from?
I... m-made it.
Really?
Hmm.
The woman who ordered in
Chinese food
for Christmas dinner made
a pineapple upside-down cake.
Well, it's not that hard.
It's just some pineapples and...
upside-down cake.
You know what?
This looks... so good.
I would love for you
to make me one...
just like it.
Right now?
Yeah, and I'm gonna sit here
and watch you...
every step of the way.
Sure. No problem.
Uh...
First, I'm gonna get some flour,
'cause you can't make a cake
without flour, right?
Oh, no! Got it all over me.
Maybe I should take my top off.
In fact...
why don't you and I go up
to the bedroom and--
Make the cake.
Well, you really are hungry.
Well, let me freshen up first.
He wants you to make
a pineapple upside-down cake--
The woman who ordered in
Chinese for Christmas?
Yes, we've already covered that.
Now what am I gonna do?
If I can't make this,
he's gonna know
I've been seeing you.
Just stall him.
I'll make one and slip it to you.
No, he wants to watch me make it.
Okay, don't panic.
We can do this.
How?
Okay!
One pineapple upside-down cake
coming right up.
First, preheat your oven to 300.
First, I'm gonna preheat
my oven to 300.
Then we're gonna start
with the caramel topping.
And then we're gonna start
with the caramel topping...
for which I will need...
sugar.
Brown sugar.
And butter.
How much butter?
Who are you talking to?
Uh... my... grandmother.
See, this was her recipe,
and talking to her
makes me feel like
we're making it together.
How much butter, grandma?
Quarter cup. Got it.
And?
It's very good.
It is?
Hot damn.
You know, truthfully,
I was just kinda winging it.
Oh, and if you don't taste the wine,
it's 'cause I drank it.
Ahh.
So last time you and I
had a meal together,
had to be...
before Mary Alice died.
That was a long time ago.
Maybe we should start
doing that again.
Susan... why are you doing this?
Why do you care?
M.J.! No running.
Ah, leave him alone.
It's nice to see something
moving fast in here.
Thanks. And just to warn you,
we... might be a little late
picking him up.
Yeah? Looks like
you're going to be
a little late getting started.
I remember a guy that
used to live on this street.
He taught my daughter to swim.
He made a killer barbecue tri-tip.
He had a laugh you could
hear three houses away.
- I liked that guy.
- I'm not that man anymore.
I think you can be.
Oh, you know, I'll be right back.
What the hell are you doing?
I asked you not to come here.
I know, but Paul is suffering,
and everyone else
has turned their back on him.
You know why?
'Cause he's a bad guy!
Look, you might
have fallen for his act,
but I haven't, and I'm not gonna
let you put yourself in danger.
Get in the car. We're going.
I'm not going anywhere.
Mike, I--believe it or not,
I am not an idiot.
I don't need to be rescued
from whatever trouble it is
you think I'm getting myself into.
You don't know this guy like I do.
I know the look in somebody's
eyes when they're hurting,
and I'm not leaving until
I know that Paul's okay.
So you're going back in there.
Yeah. Support me or not.
That's what I'm doing.
Ugh!
I heard an oven timer go off.
Let's take a look.
No!
Aah! Not yet!
Secret's all in the cooling,
and in fact, it'll probably
cool faster on the windowsill.
Hi. We're collecting for juvenile--
out of my way!
Hot cake!
Okay, but while we are waiting,
there's just one thing
I have to say.
Hey. This is not about a cake.
This is about trust.
It is a sad day when a husband
forces a wife to bake for him
just to prove she's not a liar.
Do you have any idea
how offensive that is?
Cake's ready.
Ahh. There. One perfect
pineapple upside down cake.
If only trust were so easy to make.
You look surprised.
I am.
After the way I talked to you,
I was kind of expecting
the firing squad.
I thought about it,
but I decided to go
for the romantic dinner.
Figured, less cleanup.
Honey, I... I understand
how you feel about Paul.
I know you're just
trying to protect me.
And you're just being you--
the woman that makes me
pull over to the side
of the road in a rainstorm
to pick up a sick raccoon.
It my defense,
I did think it was a cat.
The point is...
I can't stay mad at you
for being the kind,
compassionate woman you are.
Especially since it's been six weeks
since we've had sex.
That, too.
You sure you're okay
watching the girls all weekend?
Hey, can't miss your old
modeling friend's funeral.
Yeah. We were really close.
Well, you get to see
some old friends,
- maybe even reconnect with a few.
- Maybe.
Look, I know it's been hard
for you to not see Bree,
but it has meant a lot to me.
- Nice coat. Is it new?
- Yeah. I just bought it this week.
So then this long red hair
must have got on it pretty recently.
It's not what you think.
I... took Juanita
to a kid's birthday party,
- and I hugged a clown.
- You hugged a clown?
His monkey died.
He was very emotional.
So you're off to a funeral, huh?
What are you doing?
Don't-- don't open that!
I packed it very carefully!
I can see that.
One, two, three bikinis.
Is your friend being buried at sea?
Stop it. I'm gonna be late.
Late for what?
Weekend getaway with Bree?
Damn it, Gaby.
I forbade you to see her.
Well, that was your first mistake.
What did you expect?
I expected you to choose me!
You know, ever since
we moved to this street,
and--and you got so tight
with those women,
I always feel like you put them first.
You know that's not true.
Prove it.
Choose.
Who do you want in your life--
me or Bree?
Don't do this.
I am doing it, Gaby.
Choose.
Yes, the residents of Wisteria Lane
are nothing if not loyal,
but there are times
when that loyalty
is put to the test...
By the desire to help
a stricken friend...
By the need to protect
a long-buried secret.
By the movement
of two lives in opposite directions.
And sometimes just as one
test of loyalty ends...
another begins.
Gaby, I thought we said
we'd meet at the spa.
Little change of plans.
Carlos knows.
About us?
Yeah.
Can I stay with you for a while?
Of course.
Thank you.
Girls, come on. Go on in.
Sync by YYeTs.net
Corrected by Addic7ed
www.addic7ed.com