Previously on...
That maniac was serving a life sentence.
Hello, ladies.
Paul Young came back.
- Doug is leaving me.
Lynette's friend had nowhere to go.
I've spent eight years loving
someone else's daughter.
A baby was switched long ago,
and Carlos made a decision.
- We're not telling Gaby.
Susan got a job offer.
Women doing housework in lingerie.
While Bree's contractor...
With your red hair,
you will look so hot in this room.
Brought possibilities to light.
All set.
Now that you're a biker chick,
there's one other thing
you gotta know how to do.
Thanks, mister.
It had been a long time
since Bree Van De Kamp was a little girl,
but she could still remember
everything she'd ever been told about sex.
Her grandmother informed her
it was a woman's burden.
Her minister warned her it was a sin.
Her teacher taught her it was unhealthy.
Yes, everyone had told Bree
her sexual urges were dangerous.
But no one had ever told her...
how to get rid of them.
Hey. There you are.
I'm off to the bank.
Before you go, I wanna show you something.
Come here. Whole new idea.
I wanna panel the study in this.
Oh. Well, that's, uh, unusual.
Historical birch from
a Wyoming snow fence.
Over 200 years old. Feel it.
No. Really.
Feel it.
You know what they call this?
Witness wood,
'cause it's seen so much history,
unlike me, who slept through history
and had to go to summer school.
I have to go. It's late.
Yes, when Bree was a little girl,
she'd been taught
her sexual urges were dangerous.
Unfortunately, she was about to learn...
those urges were dangerous...
for everyone.
Juanita. Oh, hey. Oh.
Sync by YYeTs.net
Corrected by MystEre
www.addic7ed.com
The doctors and nurses
at Fairview Hospital
are experts at healing.
They can set bones...
bandage wounds...
and treat diseases.
Sadly, one thing
they don't know how to heal
is a guilty conscience.
I don't know what happened.
She just came out of nowhere.
Oh, honey, this could've been any of us.
Kids on that street are always playing
where they shouldn't be.
Still, I would just feel better
if they would come out
and tell us something.
Juanita was talking
when they put her in the ambulance,
so I'm sure everything's gonna be fine.
And I just spoke to one of the nurses.
- She seemed pretty positive.
- Well, that's a relief.
Paul?
W-what are you doing here?
I heard about the accident,
so I-I rushed right over.
That's what neighbors do, right?
Well, that's very thoughtful.
We'll tell Gaby you stopped by.
Yeah, don't feel like
you have to hang around.
There's nothing we can do.
We can pray.
Dear lord, we ask
that you be with this young child
and with the doctors caring for her...
and that she may be
returned in full health
to her loving family. Amen.
Amen.
Well, I have to get home.
I'm expecting someone.
Please extend my good wishes to Gaby.
Dear lord, please don't let
that creep ever touch me again.
Amen.
Oh, Gaby, thank God.
How is Juanita?
She's gonna be fine.
- They're keeping her a couple days
for observation.
- Oh.
So I told Carlos
he doesn't even have to fly back
- from his business trip.
- That's great news.
Yeah, it is.
Uh, Bree, Andrew,
can I talk to you for a second?
Thanks for coming.
I feel so blessed to have such wonderful...
What the hell is wrong with you people?!
First you take out my mother-in-law,
then you go after my daughter.
Are you trying to kill off
every Juanita Solis on the planet?!
I admit it was a terrible coincidence.
You're gettin' sloppy, you know.
- This one was in broad daylight.
- I'm sorry.
She just came out of nowhere.
Have you seen my daughter?
She never comes out of nowhere.
Uh, on a related note,
I just wanna say how much I appreciate
you not telling Carlos
about me running over his mom.
I'm gonna give you that one
'cause I wasn't fond of her.
But as for the rest of my family,
learn to swerve!
Why does this keep happening?
I don't know. I mean,
maybe God's punishing us.
Or God is punishing the Solises,
and we're just doing God's work.
I feel awful.
I should never have been fiddling
with that radio.
Radio? Mom, I saw you
from across the street.
You were checking out Keith's ass.
That's preposterous.
You were looking at that contractor's butt
like you were waiting
for a side of steak sauce.
Watch your mouth. This isn't
one of your homosexual dance clubs.
I'm telling you, it was the radio.
Okay. Fine.
But while we're talking about the radio,
uh, you do know that
that particular model is, like,
15 years too young for you, right?
Who is it?
Maxine.
Oh!
Oh, uh, hang on a second.
Ah, I was just wrapping up
my first session.
I know. I was watching.
And?
What'd you think?
It was like watching a dream.
And you know why? 'Cause I was asleep.
Sit down, honey.
It's time I gave you a few pointers.
Now... you see what I'm doing here?
Ohh.
And let's not forget the duster.
Okay. Okay, I-I get it.
And what have we here? Smudges.
Uh, we eat off that table.
Am I making my point?
We are selling a fantasy here.
You gotta, you know, loosen up.
I want to. I just...
I can't stop thinking about
all those men out there watching me.
Yes, they're watching you.
They are spending
their hard-earned dollars
to see the perfect woman.
You, my darling,
have all the power here.
Now...
Is that a crumb I see on that rug?
- Mm.
- Oh.
Oh.
That's it.
Ah!
- That's my girl.
- Ooh!
Doug, if your lawyers don't sweeten
the settlement offer,
I will sue you for half of everything,
and that includes your
girlfriend's new implants.
You paid for 'em out of our joint account,
so technically,
one of those puppies is mine.
Oh, I don't know.
Maybe throw it in the pool
and use it as a floatie.
Uh, Renee.
Oh, she's gonna be dating soon enough.
It's time she learned
what men are all about.
Now, sweetie,
what did auntie Renee
teach you about marriage?
Never sign a prenup.
Oh! Jeez!
Hey!
- What are you doing home from work?
- I'm not feeling well.
- Again?
- Yeah.
That's the third time this week.
You need to go to the doctor.
No, I'm fine.
I'm just gonna lie on
the couch and watch some TV.
Okay.
Oh!
Before you fire up the golf channel,
you think maybe you could make a quick run
- to the grocery store?
- I'm tired. Can't you do it?
I'm a little busy right now.
I've got five kids
and a useless houseguest.
Hi there.
I need you functional.
Either go to the doctor and get some help
or quit complaining and give me some help.
Fine. I'll go tomorrow.
Man, the sympathy in here
is just overwhelming.
What?
Nothing. It's none of my business.
But...
You may wanna be careful.
You two are starting to sound
a lot like me and Doug.
I appreciate the concern,
but Tom and I always do that.
Doug and I always did that, too.
Look at us now.
I'm telling you, we're fine.
If you say so.
Good.
The doctors say she's gonna be fine.
They're only keeping her
in the hospital as a precaution.
- She'll be home in a few days.
- Oh, thank God.
Can we please not have another ugly scene?
- I only came to check on Juanita.
- She's fine.
Fantastic.
So I see you let
our tomato plants whither...
Just like you did our relationship.
Well, that's what happens
when you grow needy, whiny tomatoes.
Boys, boys, it's been a month.
Can't you just kiss
each other's bottoms and make up?
Isn't that what they do?
Who is that?
She looks lost.
Should we help her?
Aah! Son of a bitch!
- We should help her.
- Son of a...
Oh! Oh!
Miss, is everything okay?
No.
I am so lost.
I gave the cab driver the address,
but I only had a $20, and it turns out
that only gets you
as far as hibiscus circle,
so he dumped me,
and I had to walk in these shoes,
which broke,
and that is the last time
I am buying footwear
- over the Internet.
- Uh, were you looking for Wisteria Lane?
Yeah, that sounds right.
Is my fish moving?
If he goes belly-up,
this is going to be the worst day ever.
Who is it you're here to see?
Uh, Paul Young.
Really? A-are you a friend of his?
W-well...
Beth!
Oh! I thought you were gonna
be here hours ago.
Well... I see you've all met my wife.
Sorry, it got... really hot in here,
and I thought you'd be gone for a while.
So how is Juanita? Is she okay?
Um, she's doing much better.
Thank you for asking.
Thank God. How are you doing?
Um, me? I'm okay.
How's the work coming?
Pretty good.
Just getting ready to put, uh...
Shoot. It's on backwards.
Bree?
You sure you're okay?
I'm fine. Fine.
It's just been a very... stressful day.
I think I know what you need.
It's okay.
Hitting that little girl was an accident.
It could've happened to anyone.
I have to let you go!
Huh?
After you let me go.
Everyone should just let go!
Are you firing me?
Why?
You're too messy.
Your tools...
they're scattered everywhere.
Well, this is a construction site.
And you're getting paint
all over the place.
And that cologne of yours...
it's overpowering.
I don't wear cologne.
That's just you?
Oh, dear.
Anyway, obviously...
I will pay you for the time you've put in,
- but I think you should go.
- You can... send me a check.
Bye, guys.
Have a great day.
Hey, aren't you going to work?
Oh, my first class isn't till 11:00.
I thought I'd spend
the morning making more jewelry.
Wow, you really are determined
to bring in some extra money.
You have no idea.
And you don't let me put
my feet on that table.
Mike! Uh, what are you...
What are you doing home so quick?
I forgot my thermos. What are you wearing?
Uh...
Uh, I was, uh, just...
just doing housework...
O-obviously,
and, uh, the air conditioning
isn't working,
so it got really hot in here.
I'll say.
Mind if I join you?
No! No! Uh...
Oh!
Uh... you know what?
Why don't we take this in the bedroom?
What's wrong with right here?
I am one lucky guy...
to come home to a hot fantasy like this.
Yep. And I am one lucky girl
to have a... have a husband like...
you. Ohh.
Any luck finding an apartment?
Not with my settlement.
With New York prices,
I'll be forced to live
in a place smaller than this.
Oh, my God. How will you keep
from bumping into yourself?
You know what I was thinking?
Why don't I just find
a place here in Fairview?
Fairview?
Uh... no.
No, no!
You're a new yorker.
You love the theater, museums.
You said yourself,
you can't even get a decent
cup of coffee around here.
Uh, no, I meant here, Lynette.
Really, how hard is it to clean the pot?
Hey! How'd it go with the doctor?
Yeah, can, uh, we, um...
talk about that?
So what did the doctor say?
You're gonna wanna sit down.
Tom, you are scaring me. What is it?
I have postpartum depression.
Come again?
I know it sounds weird,
b-but it's... it's...
it's a recognized problem
for fathers my age.
I've got all the classic symptoms...
headaches, mood swings,
fatigue.
Wow.
Tell me, did he check you
for a yeast infection
while he was down there, too?
Why don't you learn the facts
before you make fun of it?
"Men and postpartum:"
"The bitter seed."
Yeah, I'm... not buying it.
Show me one stretch mark,
one chapped nipple,
and we'll talk about your postpartum.
It's a legitimate medical condition.
And you're the one
who told me to go to the doctor.
So you could be of some use around here,
not so you could, uh...
oh, "take long baths or
get in some extra naps"?
Do me a favor. Read the whole pamphlet.
Gosh, I wish I could, Tom.
Unfortunately, I have to go take care
of my other baby.
I love the house.
Oh. Well, I did the best I could.
I think it needs a woman's touch.
Oh.
I-I don't have
much experience with decorating.
If I so much as moved a chair,
mama would throw a fit.
Mm, then you must be happy
to finally have your own home.
I guess.
Look at this...
No plexiglas.
I never dreamed the day would come
when I could reach out and touch you.
I didn't either.
There is one thing
I'll miss about prison...
your letters.
Some days, they were
the only things keeping me going.
I'm glad you liked them.
Uh, thank you again
for going to so much trouble.
Dinner is wonderful.
I wanted tonight to be special.
Since the prison
didn't allow conjugal visits,
this is... kind of our wedding night.
About that...
I can't wait to start cooking for you
and making things nice around here,
but there are certain other...
wifely duties that
I don't want to rush into.
Oh?
We're still getting to know each other.
Mama said you'd understand.
Oh, I suppose I do.
You're not upset?
Of course not.
There's more to marriage than sex.
Oh, Mrs. Solis, can I talk to you?
If this is about Juanita
and the dessert cart,
I told you not to leave it unattended.
No, I was reviewing her chart,
and I realized we still had
a couple of questions.
- Is she allergic to any medications?
- Uh, not that I'm aware of.
- Okay. All her vaccinations up-to-date?
- Yes.
And how old was she when you adopted her?
I know it's hard to believe
that the little acorn
gave birth to the mighty oak,
but believe me, I did.
Okay.
Maybe I'm confused, but the other day
when we talked about
possible blood transfusions,
you told me you
and your husband were type-O.
Yeah, we are.
So?
W-well, your daughter is type-A.
Two 0's can't have an "A."
Oh.
Never mind.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. What... what was that?
What was that "oh. Never mind"?
It's none of my business.
No, no, tell me. What are you implying?
Nothing.
I'm simply stating that
the odds of Mr. Solis being
the biological father of a type-A baby
are roughly... nil.
Are you suggesting I cheated on him?
I'm simply stating that the
odds of Mr. Solis being
- the biological father are...
- Listen, nursie.
I know you spend
your days emptying bedpans
and shaving the groins of senior citizens,
but there's no drama here.
I've been faithful to my husband.
I have nothing to hide.
Give me that.
Ah.
Good morning.
Did you have trouble sleeping?
Ah, I was up kinda late.
Boy, that Tom sure can talk.
You were up with Tom?
Huh? Oh. Yeah. I guess
he had a lot on his mind.
No surprise after the way things
went between you two yesterday.
He was complaining about that?
Oh, I don't want to get in the middle.
Honey, you had a pajama party
with my husband
at 3:00 in the morning.
You're in the middle.
Well...
Tom feels that you don't listen to him.
Okay. G... Sure I do.
I heard that whole spiel
about male postpartum,
otherwise known by its initials... B.S.
See, that's just the thing.
He thinks you hear, but you don't listen.
Okay.
Okay, you stop.
I don't need you
troubleshooting my marriage.
And I don't want you having any more
of these little conversations
with my husband.
Okay. Fine.
And I mean it.
There you are! I called you an hour ago!
I was at school.
Hi, sweetie! The kids
in your class made you a poster.
- Look what Brittany said.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. She loves it. Come on!
Come on!
Oh! What is going on?!
Okay.
Do you remember eight years ago
when we went on that ski weekend?
Uh... vaguely.
No, no, no, no, no! It can't be "vaguely."
- I need you to focus.
- Oh! Oh! Okay.
Okay.
Remember how you and I had
dinner with that French guy?
The one you referred to as le package?
Exactly.
Okay. Tell me everything you remember.
Ooh! I remember I had the fondue
and I lost my strawberry,
and the waiter
almost caught me when I put my...
I'm talking about me and the package!
- Why are you yelling at me?
- 'Cause I'm mad! You went off to bed
and left me and frenchie
drinking at the hotel bar,
and friends don't let friends flirt drunk!
Now for the love of God,
do you at least remember
when I came back to the room?
I remember the sun was coming up.
Oh, God.
Gaby, you're not saying...
Yeah.
I think Juanita might be French.
When Carlos returned
from his business trip.
He stopped at the hospital
to visit his daughter,
who had been sleeping peacefully.
Then he came home to see his wife,
who had been plotting frantically.
Oh, you're awake.
Mmm. You're really awake.
What...
Carlos, what are you doing?!
Me? I just got into bed!
You climbed on top of me.
- I did?
- Yeah.
You were kinda making out with me.
Not that I'm complaining.
Oh, no. It's happening again!
What are you talking about?
My sexsomnia.
Your what?
Yeah, it's like sleepwalking, except...
instead of using your legs,
you use your... you know.
Sexsomnia.
It's real. Look it up.
Since when have you had that?
Well, definitely
before the girls were born.
I've never seen you do it before.
Well, it mostly only happens
when I'm really tired,
like when I work out too much
or go skiing.
Well, then first thing tomorrow,
I'm checking out airfare to Aspen.
No! No, no, no. It's not a joke.
It's dangerous.
It doesn't matter who I'm next to.
I could have sex and not even know it.
Wow.
Well, since you're up...
No, I'm too tired...
And ashamed. Good night.
Hey, I thought I'd return this.
- I borrowed it from Orson a while back.
- Oh. Thank you.
So where's that chippendale dancer
you hired to fix your house?
If you mean my contractor,
his name is Keith,
and I had to let him go.
Why? You catch him, uh,
grating cheese on his abs?
It just wasn't working out.
Must've been pretty bad for you
to kick that shirtless wonder
out of your front yard.
I was finally reaching
my target heart rate on my walk.
You mean at your age,
you still have urges to...
I'm not dead, Bree.
I may like my bed and my food soft,
- but I like my men...
- Okay. Okay. Just curious.
I guess I was hoping...
Hoping what?
That one day I might outgrow all this.
Ah, that's why you fired Keith.
I just can't have him around.
He's too distracting.
And I refuse to make a fool of myself.
And how would that happen?
Well, let me run the numbers for you.
My marriage ended six days ago,
Keith is 15 years too young for me,
and my track record with lovers...
two dead, one in a wheelchair.
Bree, I can't tell you
how to live your life.
All I know is that not living
your life isn't the answer.
I've just... never been
very good at taking risks.
Well, then get good,
because take my word for it,
once they turn into regrets,
it's too late.
Okay.
Hi.
Don't feel like you have
to help or anything.
Cool.
Oh.
Where's your dad? His car's gone.
Uh, he and Renee went out to dinner.
He and Renee?
Yeah. They went to
that French restaurant dad likes.
They said you could join them if you want.
Oh, I want.
Okay, you unload these groceries
and look after your sister.
Nah, I've got plans tonight.
I don't want to get stuck babysitting.
Cool.
Hey.
Hey. Good, you got the message.
Loud and clear. So you guys sure look like
you're discussing something heavy.
Ahem. What's up?
To be honest, I was talking about you...
and your tendency to be critical,
and how frustrating it is
to have my feelings invalidated
whenever I bring up
something you don't like.
Uh-huh.
Renee, sidebar.
Did I or did I not tell you
to butt the hell out of my marriage?
What did I do?
I was just finishing my dessert
and listening to the guy talk.
"How frustrating it is
to have my feelings invalidated"?
That's got your $500-an-hour shrink
written all over it.
- I was just trying to help.
- That's a load of crap.
You need a project,
and since you're currently without
a house to remodel, you've decided
to put the wrecking ball to my marriage.
- Oh, please.
- This is what you do.
You take other people's lives apart
for your own amusement,
and then you get
the fun of putting them back together.
Well, I'm not letting you do it this time.
My marriage is not some guest bathroom
in your summer house.
Fine. Let's just say that you're right,
and I'm a terrible person.
But there's still a man
in there who is in pain,
and his wife won't listen to him.
That's not my doing.
I think this sidebar is over.
Hey, Susan?
Hey.
Oh, those are beautiful.
What's the occasion?
I called the bank
to see if they would give us
an extension on our car payment,
and the guy told me you already paid it.
Had a good week with my jewelry.
You're amazing.
You teach,
you bust your ass
with this jewelry business,
and I come home yesterday,
and here you are, as happy as can be,
working to make this place a home.
I'm so lucky to have a wife like you.
Mmm.
Wow.
There ya go.
That's quite a haul.
You know, you're gettin' good as this.
I didn't think that was gonna happen.
I'm also getting good
at lying to my husband.
I didn't think
that was gonna happen either.
Hello, Keith.
How'd you find me?
You follow the scent of
my nonexistent cologne?
No. Your answering service said
I might find you here.
I was a little out of sorts the other day,
and... uh, well, long story short,
I was hoping you'd consider coming back.
I've got a buddy, loves sports cars.
I told him to buy an old Pontiac G.T.O.
They run great, they're easy to work on.
But he bought a Maserati.
The thing is always in the shop,
very temperamental,
real pain in the ass.
You seem like kind of a Maserati to me.
I'm no Maserati, Keith.
I'm a family sedan with a beige interior
who's going through a divorce.
Well, I'm sorry about that,
but I'm still gonna pass.
I-I need you.
You've seen my house. It's kind of a mess.
And the truth is,
my life's kind of a mess, too.
And when you came in
with all your energy
and your wonderful ideas,
I started feeling like
maybe you were gonna help me
put it all back together...
My house, not my life.
I just want you to work on the house.
Wow.
I really do sound like a Maserati.
Um...
Thanks for listening.
Hey!
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God! Are you all right?
- I didn't see you there.
- You've got great legs.
You ever consider
just jogging from place to place?
What were you doing behind my car?
I thought about what you said.
It'd be a shame
if we didn't finish what we started.
Are you sure? It's a big job,
and the boss is kinda nutty.
I love a challenge.
Now can I get your insurance information?
So...
How are you doing?
What's this? Genuine concern?
No asking if my breasts feel swollen
or if it's a heavy flow day?
I know I was dismissive before,
and I want to apologize.
I read the pamphlet,
and it actually made sense.
Becoming a new dad
at your age can be pretty scary.
I mean, just looking at that little girl
and knowing you might not be
around for her wedding...
Is this supposed to be helping me?
I'm saying it's real, and I get it.
And now in order to demonstrate that
I am a loving and caring wife,
I have two options.
One, we can have a long,
sensitive conversation
about your feelings, or option two...
Mmm.
As much I like option two,
I think tonight...
I wanna talk.
Oh.
You got it.
What... what's that?
I got you a little something.
Oh.
Try it on.
Paul...
This isn't... really my style.
Let me be the judge of that.
We talked about this.
You said we could take it slow.
It's been almost a week.
Isn't that slow enough?
Try it. Maybe it'll put you in the mood.
- It won't.
- Come on.
Paul, no.
How could you possibly think
I would wear something like this?
What are those?
The letters you sent me in prison.
Oh.
Read this.
- Paul, please don't get upset...
- Out loud.
"I long for you to kiss my neck,"
"to whisper in my ear while
you unbutton my blouse."
Go on.
"And then... make love to me..."
"all night long."
Did you write these?
It was a fantasy.
- I never thought it would be real.
- It is real.
- Paul, please...
- We're married now. What did you expect?
I thought you would stay in prison.
I didn't mean that.
I'm sorry.
It's not a surprise to me
that you have some issues.
I mean, you married a man
in prison for murder.
Clearly, you are a disturbed young woman.
The good news is,
I'm willing to help you.
All I ask in return is
for a little affection.
Do you think you can offer me that?
I'll try.
Good.
I'm a patient man, Beth.
But just so we're clear,
I won't be patient forever.
Don't worry. I cleaned the pot.
The way things have been going lately,
I'm not as worried about
taste as I am poison.
Look, what you did was borderline evil.
But you were right to make me talk to Tom,
so I thank you for being a good friend,
and don't ever do it again.
You're welcome.
You know,
when I don't feel like killing you,
I think I like having you around.
Good to know since I just rented
the most charming bungalow
right here on Wisteria Lane.
You're kidding.
Edie's old house?
Wow, that is so...
Wonderful?
Close.
Um, I-I'm trying to calm the baby,
but apparently I don't have
the right equipment.
Did you hear the big news?
Renee is moving in just
a stone's throw away from us.
You do know that's
just an expression, right?
We'll see.
Do you really think it's a good idea
for you to move here?
Of course. It'll be a nice, fresh start.
Plus I can be close to my dear friend.
It's just, um...
- I wanna be sure...
- Tom, that was a million years ago.
It doesn't matter. She can never
know what happened between us.
Have you seen my wife?
Yeah, she's in the cafeteria.
Oh, while I've got you,
could I have you sign these release forms?
Then you'll be able to take Juanita home.
What's this torn page on her chart?
Let's just say your wife has
a bit of a temper.
What happened?
Well, it's not really my place,
but she did have a strong reaction
when I told her
your daughter's blood type.
Gaby did this?
I need you to tell me
exactly what happened.
Oh, crap.
Gaby, come back here!
It's not my fault! I have a disorder!
- Gaby, we have to talk!
- Damn it! Aah!
Gaby!
See you in about two seconds.
Okay, here's what happened.
It was on that ski weekend
eight years ago.
I don't normally go for French guys,
- but you know how I get
when I drink too much champagne.
- What?
Well, I didn't think I slept with him,
but I must have,
because why else would
our daughter have type-A blood?
You're not killing me.
Why aren't you killing me?
Baby, come with me.
There's something I have to tell you.
There are certain kinds of pain
that can't be treated in a hospital,
so those who are suffering
do what they can
to heal themselves.
Some cure the ache of loneliness
by making new friends.
Some soothe their excruciating guilt
with an infusion of cash.
Some alleviate their burning desire
with small acts of kindness.
But sadly,
there will always be those
who can't begin to heal...
because they realize there is more pain
yet to come.
Sync by YYeTs.net
Corrected by MystEre
www.addic7ed.com