Previously on...
I really don't want you to go.
This will make us enough money
to get Paul out of our house.
Mike took a job in Alaska.
I'm trying to treat
you like a lady.
Bree's new romance got serious.
So you're saying you like
me how I am. Very much.
Paul's bride pushed him
to the breaking point.
I want you gone by
the end of the week.
But she was strongly encouraged...
Bye, mama.
To save her marriage.
Humiliation...
It's something we
all try to avoid...
Whenever possible.
But unfortunately,
there are some days when
we can't help but fall...
Flat on our face.
You okay?
I'm fine! Mortified,
but... Whew! Fine.
What happened?
I don't know. I was...
thinking about how hot it was,
and I didn't pay attention
to where I was going.
Oh. For a second there,
I was wondering if
you fell on purpose.
On purpose?
A broken leg would
be a great excuse
to get out of dinner
with my parents.
Don't be silly. I'm looking
forward to meeting your parents.
Can we sit for a minute?
The heat is really
starting to get to me.
Really? It's not that hot.
Are you kidding? It feels like...
...Someone turned on a furnace!
Are you okay? Have I been
pushing you too hard?
No, no! I'm having
the time of my life.
Whew. I just need to
rest for a tiny little...
So what happened?
I'm not exactly sure.
She probably just
overexerted herself.
This is beyond embarrassing.
There's a lemonade stand over there.
Should I get her something to drink?
Good idea.
She might be dehydrated.
This is ridiculous.
I had a bottle of water an hour ago.
And I did not overexert myself.
I happen to be in very good shape.
Your heart rate is a bit elevated.
Well, probably from the stress of
having all these strangers gawk at me.
Oh, my lord.
It's happening again.
Do you see this?
It's like a wave of heat just...
coursing through my body.
What is happening to me?
Am I having a stroke?
Honey, you're just
having a hot flash.
A what? Yeah, it's no big deal.
We all have to go through
the change sometime.
Wait, are you saying...
Yep. You've started menopause.
Humiliation...
So did we figure
out what was wrong?
It's something we
all try to avoid.
It's no big deal.
She just had... indigestion.
I never should've let
you buy me that hot dog.
Especially women who date...
Younger men.
It was morning in suburbia...
A time for women to attend
to their husbands' needs.
And while Tom Scavo's wife was
setting out the sports section,
and Carlos Solis' wife was
removing lint from his suit...
And Roy bender's wife was
cleaning his dentures...
Paul Young's wife was resting
because she had already attended
to her husband's needs...
All night long.
Thank you.
For what?
For the most amazing night.
So I didn't disappoint you?
Are you kidding?
I'm so glad.
I must say, for a virgin,
you were certainly open-minded.
My whole life,
I heard people talk about sex.
They always made such
a big deal about it.
And don't get me wrong,
it was very interesting.
But lying here quietly...
This is my favorite part.
It's wonderful, isn't it?
So would you like to do it again?
I hear that men like
sex in the morning.
I must say, so far,
your research is flawless.
Beth, I'm gonna need a rain check.
Why? I have business to attend to.
Who is that man?
Derek Yeager,
my cellmate from prison.
So have you thought
about my offer?
I have.
I actually think starting
an interior design business
is... interesting.
Interesting? It's... it's genius.
You know what an
artistic eye I have.
Oh, my God. Oh, are you doing
what I think you're doing?
If you think I'm trying to stuff
my boob in my daughter's mouth,
then yes.
Ugh. It's so unnatural.
So...
What do you say? Mm.
I will woo the clients,
be the face of the company,
uh, while you do all
the business-y stuff.
It would be nice
to be my own boss.
Okay.
I'm in. And if we work
out of your place,
I can bring the baby with me.
Ooh, well, that... won't work.
Everything at my place
is metal and sharp.
No, it isn't. Well,
then I'll have metal and
sharp things brought in.
No babies in my house.
Well, then we'll have
to work here. Right.
Potential clients
will be so impressed
when they walk into this...
tipped-over hamper.
Get a nanny.
I've been trying.
It's not that easy.
Well, then I'll find someone.
Mm, there's gotta be some
poor schlub out there
who's trustworthy and
desperate for money.
I don't like this kind.
Oh, honey, it's cheaper.
But it doesn't have a prize.
The prize that comes
with this cereal
is we can afford the milk.
Okay, that's $61. 48.
Even with all the coupons?
Well...
Nothing in there.
Let me see if I can put
something back. Uh...
My fabric doesn't
have to be that soft.
And hey.
Meat is murder, right?
Okay, you know,
just put $20 on this
and I'll pay the rest in cash.
Care to donate a dollar
to St. Matthew's kids?
What?
It's for poor people.
You give a dollar,
I ring the bell,
everyone knows you donated.
Has that piercing
affected your sight?
I'm counting pennies here.
Lady, we're supposed
to ask everyone.
Calm down.
"Calm down"?
Yeah, I can't afford to buy
my kid the cereal he likes.
He's gotta eat this
cardboard crap.
Ooh! Nickel in the swear jar!
And that used to be a
quarter in the swear jar.
We've even had to
mark down our swears.
So don't talk to me about the
poor 'cause I am the poor!
Where's my little jar
at the checkout stand?!
There is none!
Don't feel bad. She screamed
at our dry cleaners, too.
Your burnt the meat loaf again?
It's just a little crispy.
It'll be fine.
And what's with the candles
and the good China?
Is it our anniversary?
Ow! Why are you hitting me?
Because you don't listen to me.
I told you last night Bob
was coming for dinner.
Oh, right.
Bob.
What was that for?
Not knowing when
our anniversary is.
Okay. When is it?
I don't have time for this!
Bob is gonna be here any second.
Do I have to eat with you guys?
Bob and I have nothing in common.
I'm sorry he's not all...
"See the game last night?
Check out the jugs on her.
Hey, pull my finger!"
I did that one time.
At my cousin's funeral!
You're right.
I am unfit to socialize with
your classy gay boyfriend.
I should be forced to eat by myself...
in front of the game.
No. You are having dinner with Bob,
and that is all there is to it!
For God sakes, he helped us
find our biological daughter.
We owe him more than
we can ever repay.
Then shouldn't we take
him out for a nice meal
instead of forcing him to eat
that briquette you call meat loaf?
I hope the pot roast
isn't too dry.
It's good.
He's an ex-con. He's just happy
there's no ground glass in it.
It must be nice for you two
to see each other again.
Uh, how long were you roommates?
Cellmates. Yeager and I
spent two years together.
We kind of... looked
out for each other.
That's lovely.
If I may ask, Yeager,
what were you, uh...
I believe the phrase is "in for"?
Well, you know, uh,
sometimes when
people steal stuff...
They give it to another
guy who sells it for 'em.
Yes. A "fence."
Right.
I killed a fence.
Oh.
Well, how about that?
Uh, we may wanna keep
that story to ourselves.
I'm sure the people on the Lane
would be unsettled to learn that
their new neighbor was
a convicted murderer.
Neighbor?
Yes.
Yeager's going to be staying
at my old house for a while.
He's doing a little work for me.
What kind of work?
It's nothing you
need to worry about.
I'm not worried about it.
I just wanna know.
Darling, I'm not
trying to exclude you.
I'm trying to protect you.
From what?
Beth, let's enjoy our dinner.
We have a guest.
Ah. And this was
grace at Halloween.
Oh, she's beautiful, Gaby.
And so sweet.
Getting to know her has
been such a blessing.
Carlos and I will never be
able to thank you enough.
Hey, I just made some calls.
No, you did more than that.
You changed our lives.
Oh. So...
We wanted to give you these...
as a token of our appreciation.
Orchestra seats to... "Cats."
What's wrong?
I thought you love musicals.
That was Lee.
He was the show queen.
When I found out he saw
"Annie" six times,
even I wanted to gay bash him.
Oh. Okay, well, I wanna get
you tickets to something.
Do you like the opera?
Figure skating?
Beauty pageants?
Barbra?
Sorry.
Ever think the reason Lee broke
up with you is you're not gay?
Hey, what can I say?
Give me a beer and a
college basketball game,
I'm happy.
You're kidding.
Who you like this year?
Well, Duke's got most of its
starters coming back this year, so...
Hey, hey, hey!
You kiss boys with that mouth?
Bob, I get basketball
tickets all the time.
You wanna go to a game this week?
Are you serious?
Oh, I'm in. You know,
there's a game on tonight.
Maybe after dessert,
we can turn on...
What's wrong?
I thought I knew you.
Now all of a sudden,
you're talkin' beer and basketball?
It's like you're not even a...
a tired gay stereotype?
Exactly. It's very upsetting.
Tell you what,
let us watch the game.
During halftime,
I'll come back in and tell you
how great you look in your
Dolce & Gabbana. Versace.
Just go. I can't even
look at you right now.
Menopause? You're not old enough
to be going through menopause.
And more importantly,
I'm not old enough
to have a friend going
through menopause.
This has completely blindsided me.
These last few weeks being with Keith,
I have felt so alive.
Even when I was young,
I didn't feel this young. But now...
Oh, I hate to spoil the announcement of
your death sentence, but life does go on.
And there is an upside.
I'd love to skip
those three days a month when
I'm cranky and irritable.
Just three days, huh?
This couldn't have
come at a worse time.
I'm sure it'll be the end of
my relationship with Keith.
Why do you say that?
Oh, here's why...
"check out my girlfriend,
the one with the pit stains
and the estrogen patch."
Exactly. Now he'll be looking
for some fresh, young thing
who doesn't retain water and
can still bear him children.
So why tell him?
I have to.
We're in a relationship.
Where'd you get that?
"The big book of staying single"?
There is no reason you
have to tell your boyfriend
the absolute truth about yourself.
Yeah, we lie to men
all the time. I don't.
Oh, please. You're telling me you
never pretended you like football?
Mm, or laughed at a
three stooges movie?
Or faked an orgasm
just to make him stop?
Hey, just for the record,
I love football,
stooges are damn funny,
and I've never asked
a man to stop.
Interesting.
Susan? Renee Perry here.
Listen, Lynette and I are starting a
fabulous interior design business.
Anyway, I hear you've got
some time on your hands,
and we could really use your help.
The pay's good,
and the hours are flexible.
Now we're at Lynette's
if you're interested.
What just happened?
Oh! Your mommy just got a
job as an interior designer!
... With that ash.
Susan!
I came over as soon as
I got Renee's message.
Oh, I would love to
help you guys out.
But...
I told her about the job.
Renee...
Oh, why not?
She's obviously flat broke.
No one lives downwind from
a pet store by choice.
It's true. I need to work.
Well, obviously,
you're more than qualified,
but are you sure it won't be weird?
I mean, we're friends.
Oh, I think that's a plus.
I just wanna make sure that...
Oh, for God sake,
the woman wants to be your nanny.
Hire her.
Excuse me for not wanting to ruin
one of my closest friendships.
You didn't worry that working
together would ruin our friendship.
Go figure.
Well, if you're cool with this,
I would love you to start right away.
What do you think?
I-I think my dear friend
just offered me a job.
How could I say no?
Mrs. Van De Kamp?
Hi. I'm Dr. Wagner.
Oh. Um, I usually see Dr. Shapiro.
She's on maternity leave.
Oh. Well, there's some
salt in the wound.
Yes, so I see you're here
to talk about menopause.
And frankly, you're in luck.
In addition to being a
gynecologist for 20 years,
I am going through
the change myself.
Is it awful?
The way I look at it,
we've earned this.
It's like getting a watch when
you retire from a job well done.
I suppose, but still,
I was hoping you could give me
something to mask the symptoms.
See, I'm recently divorced,
and I'm dating someone who is
significantly younger than me.
I understand.
And might I add, check you out!
Well, I must say,
I highly recommend the
younger man experience.
The stamina can be
quite invigorating.
I've heard tell.
And in the interest of keeping
this going as long as possible,
I am prepared to... lie.
So do you think you can help
me put menopause on pause?
I think so. We have a duty
as woman of a certain age
to keep this sizzling
relationship going.
So let's talk about
some therapies.
Hey! I was in the
neighborhood and thought,
you know who I haven't
seen lately? Gaby.
Okay.
I'd love to catch up,
but it's 11:00,
and I was about to go to...
So how are things?
Love the highlights.
You totally make those shoes work.
They're slippers. Uh-huh.
Uh-huh. So that was fun.
Hey, talked to Bob lately?
Anything new going on with Bob?
I don't think so.
Don't cover for him.
He's seeing someone.
What makes you say that?
Jason told Hunter who
told Sergio who told me
that Bob has been seen out three
times with some hunky Latino.
No, no, no.
Bob's not seeing anyone.
Oh, fine. Then I
will go tell Hunter
to tell Sergio to tell
Jason that he's a liar.
No. No, no, no, no.
The hunky Latino is Carlos.
He and Bob have been hanging out.
What?
Yeah. So you have
nothing to worry about.
No, no. That... that means we both
have something to worry about.
Huh? Look, I hate
to break it to you,
but Bob's always had a
major crush on Carlos.
What? I hate to break it to Bob,
but Carlos is as
straight as they come.
So was Bob's college roommate
and his thesis advisor
and his basketball coach!
Oh, that's why he
likes basketball.
Bob's college nickname was
"flipper,"
and it wasn't because
of his dolphin tattoo.
Okay, this is crazy.
Bob isn't going to "flip" Carlos.
Okay, let me...
let me tell you his game.
First, he takes them out drinking,
then he gets them really hammered.
Then, when their defenses are down,
he flips 'em.
Well, I mean, not literally... Yeah,
actually, sometimes literally.
Um, Lee, I think I
know my husband.
He's not passing up these chimichangas
for a plate of franks and beans.
Okay, I don't...
I don't know what that means,
but you just ruined
Mexican food for me.
Oh, my God. I can't let
Bob see me like this.
Well, use the back door.
I always do.
Hey!
Where you guys been?
The game ended hours ago.
We went out to a bar.
He kept buying me drinks.
I'm so hammered.
So I've come up with a marketing
plan and a billing structure.
Oh, and I filed for a
license with the city
so we can get a discount...
with our suppliers.
Are you listening to me?
I'm sorry. That was so dull,
I actually started to dream.
Hey! How's it going?
Oh. Fine. Paige is asleep.
That quickly?
What's your secret? Whiskey?
I'm not judging.
I just wanna know.
No, just rocked her.
Hey, have you heard from Mike?
How's Alaska?
Uh, he's fine. Thanks for asking.
Did you guys know
that the state of Rhode island
can fit into Alaska 424 times?
Read that once on a cup.
Never forgot it.
When we're wooing clients,
let me do the talking.
So, uh, since I'm not busy,
where do you keep
your dirty laundry?
Oh. Honey, you don't
have to do the laundry.
Sit down. I'll open some wine.
No, thanks. I'm on the clock.
I'd rather get work done.
Well, if you're looking
for something to do,
I'd love some more iced tea.
Renee, that is not her job.
That is her job.
Susan, I didn't mean you needed...
You're right. This is my job.
I don't know what to do, mama.
He won't tell me why he's
trying to buy all these houses.
And now he's got a murderer
moving into one of them.
Hold on.
I've got an idea.
Well, hello there.
Paul went to the store.
Will he be gone for a while?
Yeah.
It sure is a mess in here.
Can't help but wonder
what you boys are up to.
You wanna know what's going on?
Talk to your husband.
You saw me. I tried.
He's keeping me in the
dark for some reason.
That's between you and him.
You want to keep his confidence.
I get that.
But, please...
I'm just so worried.
Lady, I'm not comfortable
with you gettin' this close.
Why?
Oh!
You're a parolee.
You can't afford to get
in any trouble, can you?
That's right.
If you got accused of a crime,
they might lock you up for good.
Huh?
What are you doing?
When I tell people you attacked me,
I want it to look realistic.
What the hell? I never
hurt a woman in my life!
You think the police are
gonna care about that?
You're a convicted felon.
You can't be doing this.
I already got two strikes.
I don't like to be unpleasant,
Mr. Yeager.
Really, I don't.
But I am going to find out
what my husband is up to,
one way or the other.
Hey, hon.
We have to take the girls
shoe shopping this weekend.
What's better for you,
Saturday or Sunday?
Neither. I'm going to rancho
pines for the weekend.
Or you're gonna play golf?
This sounds like fun.
Yeah. Bob invited me.
Bob? You're going with Bob?
Uh-huh. He got us a
suite at the lodge.
Oh. So this is a-a sleepover?
Well, it's a 6:00 A. M. tee time.
Bob says that'll be a lot easier.
I bet he did.
But why not get your own room?
Bob says he got the
last one available.
Wow, you're just trustin' Bob
left and right, aren't ya?
What do you mean?
I'm just surprised, that's all.
One week, we hate the gays.
The next week,
we let 'em watch us shower.
It's kinda kooky, don't you think?
What the hell are
you talking about?
Oh, open your eyes!
This trip is not about golf for Bob.
It is about... seduction! Really?
That's great,
'cause I was actually planning
on turning gay this weekend.
Don't joke like that.
Can't you tell I'm upset?
I can, but I don't know why.
Even if Bob wanted to seduce me,
which I doubt,
do you really think I'd go
along with it? Well, no.
Then why does this
bother you so much?
I don't know! It just does!
Fine. I won't go.
Really?
Oh. Thank you.
I certainly wouldn't
want to do anything
that makes you think I'm gay.
In that case,
ditch the moisturizer.
Oh, I really hope
your parents like me.
Relax. I already
laid the groundwork.
I told them you were
smart and beautiful
and a terrific cook. Thank you.
And what did they say
about the age difference?
Nothing. I didn't tell them.
What? Why?
Because you look so fantastic...
I don't even think
they're gonna notice.
But I don't want them to think
we're trying to put one
over on them. Here we go.
Dad, mom, I'd like
you to meet Bree.
Well, hi. I'm Richard.
This is my wife Mary.
Well...
Check you out.
Bree,
Keith tells us you're
a professional chef.
I was. Now I just cook for fun.
Oh. Me, I'm retired from the army.
So as long as it doesn't come in a can,
it tastes good to me.
Oh, a military man. You must
have some fascinating stories.
Ah, no. Mary's the
one with the stories.
Guess what she does for a living.
Yes, take a wild guess.
She's a doctor.
As matter of fact,
I have a brand-new,
incredible work story.
Would you like to hear it?
No. No, because I realize
that as a doctor,
you're prevented ethically
from talking about your...
patients.
Depends how drunk I am.
So the army...
Can I just thank you for
keeping our country safe?
Let's talk about you, Bree.
I don't know if you realize this,
but you are
the first girlfriend that Keith
has introduced to us to... mm.
So you must be very special.
Yes. Keith, it seems serious.
I mean, is... is Bree the one
who's gonna be giving
me my grandchildren?
Mom... huh?
Ignore Mary. No, no,
no, ignore Mary. I...
Grandchildren are her big thing.
Well, no, I just think
that when you reach this
point in a relationship,
it's something you
should talk about.
Well, there's plenty
of time for that.
No, not as much as you
may think. Waiter!
Mary!
Stop it. I think you're
embarrassing Bree.
Oh, no, no, I'm fine.
It's just a little... warm in here.
Are you sure? 'Cause this is
exactly what happened to you
at the park the other day.
Mom, could you take a look at her?
Of course.
Bree, why don't you
tell me your symptoms?
Honestly, it's nothing.
I just get a little
warm sometimes.
Would you say that the
sensation comes on suddenly,
like a...
Like a flash of hotness?
No. Not at all.
Let's just... drop it.
Well, you seem so irritated.
Before, you were so pleasant.
Would you say that your moods
swing suddenly like this?
What are you doing?
Stop badgering. I just...
I'm not badgering. I'm simply
asking her to tell the truth.
Is... is that something
that's also difficult for
you these days, Bree?
Telling the truth? Oh,
for God sake!
I am going through
menopause, okay?!
That is what Dr. Wagner is
so delicately trying to say.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I am going to the kitchen
to ask them if I can stand
in their walk-in freezer!
Guess what else?
That's not her real
hair color either.
Okay.
Sorry.
We should get going, Barbara.
We have a 7:00 reservation.
And we have a whole
presentation for you
after dessert.
Oh, I don't know if I
can wait that long.
Can I have a sneak peek? Um...
Sure.
This is for your daughter's room.
Uh, we were thinking
all the furniture
in an antique white,
and, uh, pale rose for the walls.
It's both elegant and feminine.
You don't feel it might
be a little old for her?
She's only 7.
Oh, no. No, trust me.
This color works for all ages.
It's a... it's a classic look. Mm.
Or...
Just an idea, but maybe you
could do something more playful.
I painted the characters from
the knights of the round table
in my son's room, and he loved it.
And maybe you daughter
has a favorite character
from a-a-a movie or a book?
I'm sorry. We haven't been introduced.
I'm Barbara Fine.
Uh, this is Susan Delfino.
The nanny.
Well, Susan, it's a great idea.
I'm gonna call my daughter
and see if there are
any characters that she would
love to see on her wall.
You should show her your
other sketches. She's good.
What the hell was that?
Uh, it... it was just a thought.
I think she liked it.
I don't care! You made
us look like idiots.
That was not my intention.
Regardless, I do not
appreciate being upstaged
by the woman who does the dishes.
She had no right to
talk to you like that...
No, no.
I... crossed the line.
Okay, done. You ready to go?
Yeah.
Hey, Bob, can I borrow
a couple of eggs?
Hey. What the hell was that about?
Your husband canceled
our golf trip.
Did he?
He said you think I'm
planning to seduce him.
We should talk about that...
after I get the eggs.
Why would you even go there?
Look, I know about
your history, Bob...
Or should I say "flipper"?
Ah. Well, Lee's a
fine one to talk.
Did he tell you about the
summer he stalked Ryan Seacrest?
Okay, look, I don't want
to fight about this.
How could you think that,
Gaby? You know me.
No, I don't! I thought I did.
I thought you were a fun gay guy
who I had something in common with,
and then I find out
you're into sports
and spending time with my husband.
What the hell was that about?
It's about me being lonely!
You ever see anybody coming
around here to visit me?
You ever see me going
out on a Saturday night?
Ever since Lee left,
all I do is work and come
home to an empty house.
You know, I was so happy to
get your invitation to dinner.
And when Carlos
wanted to hang out,
I thought, this is great.
I got a social life again.
Now to find out you
thought I had an agenda?
Oh, Bob. I'm sorry.
I-I didn't know.
Well... now you do.
Let me get those eggs for you.
Carlos can go on the weekend.
Really? Yeah.
Thanks.
Oh! And if you ever
do feel the need
to flip a straight
guy on the Lane,
I'd start with Tom Scavo.
I always felt he was
three beers away.
Two.
How was your meeting?
Good.
Barbara's going to hire us.
We're officially a design firm.
That's great.
Can I ask you something?
Are you upset with
this arrangement?
Because I'm getting a vibe.
I should go.
You are out of diapers.
I'll pick some up tomorrow.
Susan, please. I need to know.
Are you angry with me?
Yes. Yes, I'm angry.
Why? All I did was give you a job.
Yeah, the wrong job.
When Renee called me,
I thought you were asking me
to work with you in the
design firm. Oh, no!
I was so excited.
I knew I'd be good at that.
And then I find out you just
want me to be your nanny.
I had no idea. But you know...
and don't get me wrong,
I love you for the gesture,
but I hate you for it, too,
because I'm not in the
position to say no.
I-I am beyond sorry.
It's okay.
It's just this awful reminder
that all of my friends
look at my differently now.
I'm the poor one.
Susan!
These money troubles...
They're temporary,
but how we feel about you,
our friendship...
That's never going to change.
Thank you for that.
Ohh, come here.
You know, I've never said
this to a nanny before...
How about we go downstairs
and get a little drunk?
Well, you're the boss.
Are you coming to bed?
I wanna make love again.
With an invitation like that...
No.
Let me.
You've turned out to
be the perfect wife.
That's sweet,
but not entirely true.
You don't think I'm trustworthy.
What?
You won't tell me why you're
moving your ex-cellmate
into your old house.
Darling, I'd prefer not
to discuss that right now.
We don't need to.
Yeager already told
me what you're up to.
What?
We had a nice long chat.
He told me what you've got
planned for our neighbors.
I must say, I was shocked...
To say the least.
I know what I'm doing
might sound crazy to you,
but you don't understand how
much I despise these people.
You don't understand how much
I need these people to suffer
for what they did to me.
Well, that's where
you're wrong, Paul.
I understand vengeance.
Completely.
Wow.
You really are the perfect wife.
I'm sorry I left the
restaurant like that.
I just couldn't go back to that
table and face your mother.
Oh. Whew.
So why didn't you tell me about
the whole menopause thing?
I was afraid of how you'd react.
You really think I would care
about something like that?
Oh, Keith,
I like you...
More than I ever intended to.
I always knew there
was an expiration date
on this relationship.
What?
You are 17 years younger than me.
That's a big number.
It means something.
Not to me.
It might.
There are other considerations.
So you can't get pregnant.
Who cares?
That doesn't bother you?
No.
We could adopt.
So long as I get to teach
someone how to throw a ball,
I don't care whose
D. N. A. They got.
Oh, Keith.
Not only can I not
have children...
I don't want them.
I've already done that.
It was wonderful,
but I've done it.
Oh.
And you...
You are gonna be such
an amazing father,
and I would never ask you
to give up that experience.
Why are we even
talking about this?
I... we've been dating
for two months. Why...
I... it's... it's too soon to
talk about kids, right?
I suppose.
Let's... let's take our time.
I-I just wanna... I...
I-I just want us to
keep being happy, okay?
Hey, I was just about to
head over to your place
to pick up Carlos. Yeah,
about that... uh, I've decided
Carlos shouldn't go
with you this weekend.
What? Oh, for God sake.
Ah! Wait! Let me finish!
I've been thinking
about what you told me,
and I realized there's somebody
else you'd have more fun with.
Yeah, go. Shh!
You've gotta be kidding me!
Gaby called to say that you
were lonely and depressed,
and once I stopped laughing,
I actually felt bad for you.
We only broke up four months ago.
How did you gain this much weight?
Okay! Okay, now that
we're done saying hello,
let's talk about this
fabulous weekend.
Did you seriously think I
would take him? We broke up!
And it's time to put the
pieces back together.
Let's be honest. You've
been miserable without Lee.
And you've been
miserable without Bob.
That's why you're gettin' so fat.
You may not think I'm
your friend, but I am,
and I am smart enough to know
that you need something
more in your life
than a straight guy
to go play golf with.
You need somebody to love.
And...
You need somebody who
will love you back.
Gaby, I appreciate
what you're doing,
and I think... Lee
knows I still love him.
But...
There are still huge
issues between us.
Huh.
Maybe it's time to work those out.
I'd hate to see that fabulous
resort weekend go to waste.
Oh, come on. Talk to each other.
Do it for me, as your friend.
Oh.
Oh, I forgot. One more thing...
Okay! Never mind. I'm... I'm good.
Humiliation...
It's not always
something we can avoid.
We may have wives who
insult our masculinity.
We may take jobs...
We feel are beneath us.
We may have boyfriends
who make us feel old.
Yes, there are all sorts of ways
to be humiliated in life.
But the surest way to
get your dignity back
is to get what you've
been waiting for.
I found out what Paul is up to.
He told me everything.
Oh, baby.
I'm so proud of you.
Thank you, mama.
Sync by YYeTs.net
www.addic7ed.com