Renee and Tom discussed their past.
I seem to remember you caught
me in a towel then, too.
Bree's Thanksgiving dinner...
- I want a divorce!
- I'm happy to oblige!
Dad! Mom!
Went up in flames.
Look who's here!
Gaby's dinner ended
when Hector got arrested...
- I think they're illegals.
- I have to move out of our house!
And she was afraid of losing
her biological daughter Grace.
Stay with us until
we can figure things out.
- And Paul's plan...
- You are the proud new owner
of your old house.
Was set in motion.
So Paige and I will be
at the park for about 30 minutes.
Great. I should have all
the clothes packed up by then.
Oh, shoot. I forgot the pacifier.
I didn't. It's in the diaper bag.
Have a good time.
There are certain things
every parent must remember...
Which toys can't be thrown away...
which vegetables must not be served...
which clothes should never be mended...
but the one thing every parent can forget...
is how quickly their children grow up.
What's going on in here?
Uh, Lisa Ellison is pregnant,
so I'm gonna give her some baby clothes.
Paige has grown out of all her onesies.
Wow, that was fast.
So fast. Isn't there a way
we could keep her small?
Well, we could stop feeding her.
Then we could save money
on food and clothes.
Hey, are you okay?
Yeah, it just hit me that
this is my last onesie.
After Paige, no more babies.
- Isn't that what you wanted?
- Mm.
I mean, weren't you
the one who threw confetti...
after the doctor tied your tubes?
Yes, but now I'm thinking that
it's just going by too quick...
- Ohh.
- And before you know it,
they'll be grown, and...
just be you and me.
- Yeah. You know what
the best part of that is?
- No.
It'll just be you... and me.
What are you doing?
Giving you...
a preview of what
our retirement's gonna be like.
What about... what about the kids?
They all left for school. I saw 'em.
But... in the nursery?
In front of Peter Pan?
It's about time he grew up.
Yes, there are certain things
every parent must remember.
Ohh! I... forgot Paige's doll.
I'll-I'll... I'll tell her it's dead.
Locking the door...
is one of them.
It's a question we all ask ourselves.
Do I trust the folks who live next door?
Can I count on the woman
who lives down the block?
Will that couple across the street
be there when I need them?
Yes, good neighbors are
people we can rely on.
Great neighbors
are the ones who do exactly
what they are told.
So this is what you want me to sign?
Yes. Down at the bottom.
Is there a problem?
I-I'm just a little sad, that's all.
Now, what do you have to be sad about?
I'm paying you well over market value.
I know. It's just... I love the Lane.
Everybody's always been so kind to me.
To just up and move at my age...
The neighborhood is about to change.
In a few months,
you won't recognize this street.
It's better to go now,
with your memories intact.
What do you mean, it's gonna change?
You don't have to worry about that.
All you need to know is
that I'm helping you.
I am so sorry. I got hung up.
Don't worry. It's done.
Mr. Scully sold? But...
I had a lot of details to work out.
I mean, length of escrow,
- disclosure agreements...
- You'll still get your commission.
- Okay. So... what happens now?
- Now?
Now I let the neighborhood in on my plan.
Plan?
You have a plan?
Hi!
Oh, so now she knocks.
It's Susan. I'm entering the house.
It's okay, Susan. We are totally clothed.
Sweetie...
you avoided making eye contact
with us all day yesterday.
Can we move past this?
Yeah, I think the only fair thing now
is for us to see you and Mike naked.
Okay, you were right. It's not funny.
Yeah?
I just want to say "congratulations."
For what?
Well, I don't mean to be crass,
but when I walked in on you guys,
I couldn't help but notice
that Tom is quite...
gifted.
- Oh, that.
- "Oh, that"?
When I opened the door,
I thought you two had company.
I mean, I'm not sure if it
was all the tiny furniture
in the nursery, but he looked...
I get it, I get it.
I'm a very lucky woman.
So why haven't you ever mentioned it
to me and the girls?
- Mention it?
- When we went for margaritas that night
and we all kind of told each other
about our husbands'... accomplishments,
how come you never told us you
were sleeping with Tommy tripod?
Tommy tripod? How many
more of these do you have?
Six.
I'm serious.
You were so tight-lipped,
that we just assumed
that Tom was one of those, you know,
button-on-a-fur-coat kind of guys.
It's just something
I don't care to advertise.
What do I care if people
think he's got a dinky one?
Hey, Carmen.
What's with the map?
I just spoke to Hector.
Oh, my God. How is he? Where is he?
Staying with his cousins
in Sabinas... Mexico.
Grace and I will be leaving
for Texas in two days.
What? So soon?
Gaby, we discussed this.
We're staying with people we know
for a few weeks until
Hector crosses the border and joins us.
And then what?
I guess we'll try to get jobs,
find a place to live.
Where? What jobs?
You have a daughter
you're dragging into all this.
Grace is a strong girl.
Yes, I know, but is this
what's best for her?
Okay, look, I'm just...
putting it out there.
Let Grace stay here with us.
Just until you and Hector get settled.
That could take months.
I don't mind. That way
she can at least stay in school.
She'll be safe, be with family.
Hector and I are all the family she needs.
She comes with me.
Carmen, I don't mean
to make you mad. It's just I...
I have a say in this, too.
I'm her birth mother!
And I'm Juanita's!
Does that mean I should take her with me?
Take her where? To run? To hide?
That's the life you're making Grace live!
But here, she can have anything
she wants, just like Juanita!
Oh, so she can become a spoiled
girl who never thinks of others,
just like Juanita.
Hey, there is nothing wrong with my kid.
No, you're right.
It's not her fault
she's being raised by a bad mother.
And if a life of running and hiding
keeps that from happening to Grace,
then that's what I'll do.
So we'll just tell people that
you slipped in the bathroom
and bumped your head.
We're old. People expect that.
What were you thinking with that book?
I thought it would add a little spice.
"Kama sutra." Kama sutures.
Where'd that come from?
Wasn't there yesterday.
Take these. Take these home.
I gotta make sure people know about this.
Go! Go, go, go, go.
"Correctional center"? What is that, a jail?
I called the city.
They say it's "transitional housing"
for felons under house arrest.
- A halfway house for convicts,
on our street?
- Exactly.
I don't understand.
The city bought this house?
No. I did.
You're responsible for this?
Sure am.
What could you possibly be thinking?
The day I was released from prison,
I felt so blessed.
I knew that I was coming home
to the loving embrace of
this beautiful neighborhood.
And most inmates, when they're released,
don't have that kind of support.
Most of them are isolated,
which leads them to commit more crimes.
Bringing them to a place like this,
where they can interact with folks like you,
might just keep a few of them
from making that unfortunate choice.
Come on, Paul. We've got children here.
And I'm not spending my golden years
borrowing a cup of sugar from
drug dealers and rapists.
I'm all for charity,
but our neighborhood
can't handle something like this.
Apparently, I have more faith
in you people than you do.
Oh, my God.
In a way, this halfway house
will be a testament
to how I feel about each
and every one of you.
Renee?
Oh, I've really got to start knocking.
What?
Lynette asked me to bring over
this birthday card
that got delivered to her house by mistake.
Thanks so much. You can toss it.
You're not gonna read it? Come on.
Someone who loves you took
the time to send a card.
"Happy Birthday from..."
"Dr. Frank at Midtown Dental."
Oh, look! You're due for a cleaning.
- Good-bye, Susan.
- No, wait.
So it's your birthday, huh?
Do you have something special planned?
I haven't celebrated my birthday
since the third time I turned 28.
Hey! What do you say you and I go out?
No candles, no cake, no singing.
Just enough booze to wash away the pain.
Why do you assume I'm in pain?
I was talking about my pain.
I've really been missing Mike
since he's been in Alaska, and...
- ugh, I have a bunion that's bothering me...
- Fine, fine.
We'll have dinner. Let's just make it early.
I want to have a backup dinner lined up
just in case this one gets too depressing.
Oh, I promise you're gonna
have a great... time.
Hey, there's my favorite lawyer.
As it happens,
I need some good legal advice.
You mean free legal advice.
Well, yeah. Free is good.
So let's say hypothetically
I know a woman who's
in this country illegally.
You mean Carmen.
She's not the only illegal I know.
Half of Carlos' family
scaled a fence at some point.
Now, let's say this woman's daughter
is an American citizen.
You mean Grace?
Hello! Still hypothetically.
Now, could the daughter stay
here with another family
if, say, somebody
anonymously reported
the mother to immigration?
Yeah, as long as it's not the somebody
who called immigration,
because hypothetically,
she'd be burning in hell.
Oh, come on.
Carmen wants to drag Grace
all over Guadala-somewhere
while Hector figures out a way
to sneak back into the country.
Gaby, you can't do this. They're a family.
Just tell me... is it legal
or not for me to keep her?
Yes, technically, it's legal.
But just because something's
legal doesn't make it right.
Okay, jeez! You don't have
to jump down my throat.
Like I said, it was just... hypothetical.
Yeah, hi. Can I get the number
for the immigration department, please?
What do you want for dinner?
Pasta? Meatloaf?
I don't care. Meatloaf's good.
Why don't you talk about my penis?
Excuse me?
I overheard you and Susan talking.
I was surprised to find you'd never...
bragged about me.
There's a reason
they call them private parts.
And why would you care anyway?
I know what you gals talk
about when you get together.
Gaby lets everyone know
how much money Carlos has.
Susan talks about what a badass Mike is...
So...
So do I always have to be the joke?
The-the one who paid too much for the car,
the one who cried when
the cop pulled him over...
you don't have a problem
sharing my screwups,
but God forbid you give me
this one little victory.
Are we really having this conversation?
I am just saying,
for once it would be nice
if you gave me a little good press.
You know,
tell your friends...
what I bring to the table.
Please don't put it on the table.
I'm sorry. I was looking for
my contractor boyfriend,
not a... suave international spy.
Well, the restaurant is pretty, uh...
How do the kids say it? Snazzy?
You look wonderful. Hmm.
Shall we?
Hang on. Yeah, I just gotta
grab one thing out of my room.
Okay.
Oh, hey, Bree. I heard the door.
I thought you were pizza.
Hello, Richard.
Are we going to bed or getting up?
I don't know. Let's see.
Ahh. "Wheel of fortune." Getting up.
So how are you doing?
Not so hot. Mary's lawyer called today.
We're starting our divorce proceedings.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, the marriage has been
over for a long time,
but I had no idea what a kick
in the gut this was gonna be.
I guess it's just hitting me
that I could be alone
for the rest of my life.
Richard, that's ridiculous.
Take a look in the mirror.
I mean, after you shower.
You are a catch. You're smart,
adventurous, very handsome...
For a tired old guy in his 50s...
Stop wallowing in self-pity!
You were a major in the army.
Be strong.
The army is easy. There's structure.
They tell you what to do,
you do it. But this...
Fine! Then I'll tell you what to do.
Turn off the tv,
get dressed, and get out of this apartment.
And do what?
Ready to go?
Change of plans.
I've invited your father to join us.
I hope you don't mind.
Bree could see that I'm a little down.
No. No, it's fine.
It's not like I had
anything special planned.
Okay, I checked the bylaws.
We can all relax.
Paul can't open a halfway house
on this street
without approval from
the homeowners' association.
And since he only has one house...
He only gets one vote.
No way he gets a majority.
Thank God. Let's call
a meeting of the association
and take a vote so
we can get this over with.
Does this seem too easy?
I mean, Paul's a smart guy.
He wouldn't pull a stunt like this
unless he thought he could get away with it.
I wish Mike were here.
He'd just go over there
and scare some sense into him.
Do we know any other macho guys
who could do the job?
What about Carlos?
Oh, forget Carlos.
We've got a guy right here
that can do the job.
Roy.
Not me.
Hey, what about the gay?
He looks like he could do some damage.
Okay. How about
I just refresh everyone's coffee?
'Cause it looks like
that's all I'm good for.
Oh, can you be a love and
bring back more of these cookies?
You okay?
Bob? Roy?
Your friends think everybody on
the street is tougher than me.
That's ridiculous!
Hey, how about we send Lynette over there?
- She got a set of cojones on her.
- You see?
- You see? This is all your fault!
- Wh... h-how is it my fault?
'Cause you never say anything
positive about me. God forbid
- you talk me up, make these people
think I'm a real man.
- A real man?
Are you suggesting we make this
meeting a forum for your talent?
Why is it so hard for you
to say nice things about me?
I do, all the time.
Oh, but you prefer to emasculate me.
Emasculate you? No, I don't!
- Yes, you do. Yes, you do.
- Oh, you want me to talk you up?
- Yeah, that would be great!
- Fine! I'll talk you up.
Listen, everybody. I've got an idea.
If we need someone
to intimidate Paul,
Tom can do it in the men's room.
What?
Oh, you didn't hear? Tom's packin'!
We're talkin' big, circus big. So big,
he can drive in
the car pool lane when he's alone.
L-L-Lynette...
If it falls in the forest,
believe me... it makes a sound.
Th-that's enough. That...
The Washington monument
looks at it and says,
"I want to be you when I grow up."
Jeez, you'd think she'd smile more.
Grace, you want to go
to the kitchen for a little bit?
Why?
Maybe make yourself a snack.
You are such a brave little girl.
If anything bad ever happens,
you are surrounded by people who love you.
What are you talking about?
Gaby, immigration's here.
The men who took daddy?
Oh, don't worry, Grace.
Everything's gonna be okay.
Mama!
Grace, listen to me.
Go upstairs to Juanita's room
and do not move until I tell you.
No, mama! I want to stay with you!
I'll be fine.
I love you.
Go, go.
These people are going to take me.
I need you to look after my baby.
You're not going anywhere.
Can I help you?
I'm Agent Jackson from I.C.E.
We're looking for
Carmen Sanchez. Is that you?
Okay, Mrs. Solis,
I'm going to the store now for oven cleaner.
Are you Carmen Sanchez?
Ma'am, we're from U.S.
immigration and customs enforcement.
Ay, dios mio!
I might be late tomorrow.
This is lovely, Keith.
Yeah, but it feels like something's missing.
What is it? Oh, I know. My father.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I know we've been having a lot of dinners
- with him lately.
- Oh, it's okay.
It's really sweet the way
you've been looking after him.
- But I'm really glad it's just us tonight.
- Me, too. Mm.
I'll check on our table.
Wanna grab me a drink?
Yeah, whiskey up, ice water back.
Can I help you?
Watson, party of two.
I'm the one who called earlier.
Oh, yes, of course.
Would you like the ring delivered
in our chocolate souffle?
Oh, no. I'm too nervous to wait for dessert.
How about an appetizer?
We have the jumbo shrimp cocktail.
Not jumbo.
I-I don't want the shrimp
to make the ring look small.
Thank you.
Bree?
It's me, Tracy! Tracy Miller!
Of course! Oh, it's been years!
You look...
Incredible. Look at me!
I'm a stick. I've lost a ton.
Good for you.
What's, uh, Adam doing these days?
Sitting in his studio apartment
and cursing my divorce lawyer
for taking all of his money.
I'm so sorry.
Oh, don't be. I'm doing great.
They're ready for us.
Oh, my God. Is this Andrew?
I can't believe how grown up he is.
No, this is my boyfriend Keith.
Wow. I guess we're both doin' great.
After the mudslides,
there was an outbreak of cholera.
Half my village died.
That's when we paid the coyote
to bring us over the border.
Jeez, cholera? Getting shot at?
Doesn't anyone have a happy story
about coming to this country?
Gabrielle Solis? Your husband is here.
Oh.
Uh, good luck. I'm sure
I'll see you all again.
You seem like a very persistent lot.
You okay?
As long as you're not mad at me.
Are you kidding?
It's a very brave thing
that you did for Carmen.
Yeah, well, you know me,
always thinking about others.
So where are Carmen and Grace?
Carmen was too scared to stay at the house,
so I put them up at a motel.
Oh. Well, you can tell
them everything's fine.
- They can come home now.
- Gaby...
you just made fools out of
a U.S. government agency.
Our house isn't safe anymore.
Carmen and Grace are leaving
for Texas in the morning.
Isn't this romantic?
Like I said, I wanted this
to be a special night for the two of us. Mm.
Son of a bitch.
Well, hey, you two.
Richard, hi! What are you doing here?
I thought if Keith were bringing
a great cook like you here,
it's gotta be good.
So I thought I'd order some takeout.
Takeout. Good idea.
Yeah.
I thought maybe I'd, uh...
take the food home and
eat in front of the tv.
Of course, it is Friday.
There's probably nothing on.
So I... guess I'll just eat over the sink.
Well, uh, Richard, if you don't have plans,
would you like to join us?
Of course he has plans.
Didn't you hear about the sink?
I would love to. Let me get another chair.
What are you doing?
The man is clearly in pain.
It's not your responsibility
to cheer him up.
When he is tired of being alone,
he will meet somebody.
Maybe sooner than you think.
Tracy, I cannot get over how great you look.
- What is your secret?
- Revenge.
After I lost the weight,
I took a picture of myself naked
and sent it to my ex to rub his face in it...
or to show him what he can't rub his face in.
Am I right?
You know, Richard, speaking of...
Tracy here has an incredible singing voice.
- Oh, really?
- Yes, we met in church choir.
Didn't you say you sang
in your church choir?
Still do. I love it.
Yeah, I don't sing anymore...
Or believe in God.
- Really?
- Yeah, it's kind of hard
to believe in a higher power
when you're on your knees
begging for help for
your nightmare of a life,
and you get squat!
So, yes, that's how we met... the choir.
Well, Tracy, not that God needs defending,
but as someone who's been in combat,
I have found my faith to be
a comfort in difficult times.
Isn't that refreshing?
A man with old-fashioned values.
I think we should cut all
funding to the military
and pour it into the schools.
I hope they'll teach
arabic in those schools.
So shall we order?
Bree, can I talk to you for a sec?
"Shall we order?"
Are you not sitting at that table?
This plan of yours isn't working.
I admit, she was much nicer
when she was fat.
Look, you need to get them out of here.
I have to talk to you
about something really important.
What is it?
I can't just blurt it out.
It needs to be done just right.
Hey! Did anyone order a shrimp cocktail
with a puny engagement ring on the side?
- Oh, crap!
- Keith, what is that?
- No, no, no. Forget you ever saw this.
- But, Keith...
I don't wanna hear your answer, Bree.
This is not how this is happening.
You never should have
invited him to stay here.
You ruined this entire thing.
And-and so did you, and so did you!
Well, he certainly killed the evening.
So on Sunday, I make a big roast chicken,
then on Monday,
I turn that into chicken salad,
and on Tuesday, chicken soup.
It's amazing how you can
stretch a simple chicken.
Into a 45-minute story.
When you said you were
the fun one on the Lane,
who was your competition... the mailbox?
I was just trying to cheer you up.
Well, who said I need cheering up?
Well...
I saw you crying yesterday.
For God sake. This is a pity dinner?
No. I just... I know what
you're going through.
Birthdays are hard,
especially when you're single.
But I guarantee you
you're going to meet someone.
You're a very attractive woman.
You think that's what I was crying about?
Hey. You find me attractive?
Yes.
Would you wanna go out with me?
Yeah. But we have to be very discreet,
because my girlfriend...
See? I have no problem getting a guy.
Ugh. So why the sob-fest?
Do we really have to talk about this?
No. On Wednesday, I made chicken potpie...
Okay, okay.
Here's why I was crying...
I was thinking about this...
great guy from my past.
Oh.
It was over 20 years ago.
We only had one... weekend together, but...
the way he made me feel...
and the older I get, I keep thinking that...
he was the one...
and I let him slip away.
Well, that... that doesn't sound like you.
There was someone else in the picture.
Listen...
we never know what's going to happen.
I mean, Mike and I had
our share of setbacks.
But I never gave up.
I never stopped dreaming
that maybe one day...
it would work out.
And neither should you.
You know what, Susan?
I just figured out your thing.
You aren't the fun one.
You're the smart one.
Oh.
Oh, you're good. I'll give you that.
It speaks.
Just when I think you can't find
new ways to embarrass me,
you top yourself. Well done, nutcracker!
Wait a minute. Wait. Wait a minute.
We were having a discussion
about the future of our community,
and you attacked me
and turned it into
a referendum about your manhood.
You know, I wish I didn't have to do that,
but I'm tired of all of our friends
thinkin' that I'm just a buffoon!
Buffoon?! Are you insane?
Every woman on
this street constantly tells me
that I have the perfect husband.
- They do not.
- They do! Gaby says that she wishes Carlos
was thoughtful like you.
Susan wishes Mike had your sense of humor.
Bree says she's never seen a better dad.
Then why do you sound annoyed by that?
How many people go up to you
and tell you you have the perfect wife?
Take your time.
Well...
Uh, lots.
Oh, wrong. I know how our friends see us...
you're the hardworking,
nice guy, and I am the bitch.
I am the one who's constantly
emasculating her husband.
I'm the one who can't wait
to get away from her kids
- and go back to work.
- No. People don't say that.
See? You are so nice,
you can't even tell me the truth.
For almost 20 years,
all I've heard is how incredibly lucky I am
to have a guy like you.
So if I don't constantly
brag about how great you are,
it's only because I don't wanna be reminded
of how much I don't deserve you.
You know, I'm the one
who should be bragging to all the neighbors,
telling them how lucky
I am to be married to a woman
who's still... sexy as all get out...
who makes me laugh...
and whose heart is so big,
that even after raising five children...
she still cries when she has
to pack away the last onesie.
I didn't cry.
Okay, I teared up a bit.
You know what I'm in the mood to do?
I have an idea. Hmm.
It did everything but
tap me on the shoulder.
And that's how you get out
of payin' for a taxi.
Well, we weren't in a taxi.
We were in my car.
But now I know why you showed me your boobs.
Okay, that's a lot of stairs.
How does sleeping on the couch sound?
You know something?
I told Lynette you were
this mousy little loser.
Actually, you told that to me.
Oh, I'm sorry.
'Cause I really like you now. You're nice...
much nicer than that Susan.
Okay.
Nighty-night.
You gonna be okay?
Mm, I thought I was.
I thought I could live down
the street from him,
but it's so hard.
Wait. The guy you're in love with...
He lives here?
Yeah.
Tom.
Tom?
Tom Scavo?
Yeah.
Oh, the love of my life.
Hey, Richard. I was looking
for Keith. Is he here?
No, he went for a walk.
You wanna wait for him?
If you don't mind.
I am so sorry that I ruined your evening.
Well, to be fair, you had some help.
Still, if I had any idea
he was gonna propose...
No one was more surprised than me.
This is none of my business,
but if he'd pulled it off,
what would you have said?
Speaking as your prospective
father-in-law, of course.
Um... I don't know.
It's all a little... sudden.
Yeah, that's Keith.
He's always been an impulsive kid.
Never really thinks things through.
Well, actually, his spontaneity
is one of the things I love about him.
Can I be honest with you?
I... would never...
put you and Keith together.
Oh?
Yeah, I see you with someone...
steady. More...
reliable.
Someone who shares your faith,
your old-fashioned values.
Someone more your own age?
Well, that being said,
I really do love your son.
Oh, hey, I-I love him, too.
Like I said, he's a great kid.
I should go.
Really?
Please tell him that I stopped by.
It's been so wonderful getting to know you.
You, too, Mrs. Solis.
What are you doing?
Memorizing your face.
Texas is far away,
and I don't know when
I'm gonna see you again.
Maybe someday.
Yeah, maybe someday.
Can I tell you something, Grace?
I grew up just like you.
I didn't have a lot of pretty things.
But I never let that stop me
from going after any dream I wanted.
So you remember that, okay?
- Okay.
- Gaby...
They need to go.
Oh, I wish you could stay with us.
Gaby...
Oh. Okay.
I'm sorry about what I said
about Juanita the other day.
Don't worry about it.
We should go.
Carmen...
Thank you.
Thank you for taking care of my baby.
Thank you for taking care of mine.
Oh, God.
Hey, everybody quiet down.
This shouldn't take too long.
We only have one order of
business on the agenda tonight,
and that is the new halfway house...
that is scheduled to open in the property
owned by Paul Young...
So let's jump right to the vote.
All those opposed to the halfway house?
Madame chairwoman? Point of order.
According to our bylaws,
we have to have a 48-hour
notice before a vote.
We'll still vote the same way in two days,
- and you'll still lose.
- Yeah, that'll be 14 to 1.
Then we'll take another vote to
- kick you off the street.
- That'll be 14 to 1, too.
You might wanna check your math.
I have at least seven votes.
How do you figure that?
With the acquisition of Mr. Scully's place,
I now own seven houses on Wisteria Lane.
What?
I used the settlement I got
from my wrongful incarceration
to acquire the extra property.
Didn't I, Lee?
You knew about this?
He was my realtor.
Couldn't have done it without him.
He just hired me. I didn't know he was evil.
How much money did you make
from these deals, anyway?
Not that much.
So that's why you tried to buy my house.
You never told us about that.
Well, I made it pretty clear
how I felt about his offer.
Well, none of this matters.
Seven houses isn't enough to win the vote.
That's an excellent point, Gaby.
I need one more.
And since this halfway house
means a lot to me,
I intend to get it.
Well, we're not gonna sell to you.
I don't need all of you to sell, just one.
So if you're sure it won't happen,
there won't be a problem.
But if someone should sell...
you'll have hardened
criminals on this street.
And what do you think that
will do to your property values?
Oh, my God.
- You can't scare us.
- Well, maybe not you, Carlos. You're rich.
But what about, uh, Mitzi Kinsky?
What about me?
We all know you've been laid off.
I can offer you well above market value.
Or you, Mrs. McCluskey?
I bet your entire life savings
is tied up in your home.
And, Susan, my offer still stands.
We all know Mike had to go to Alaska
because of your financial problems.
But if you lose half
the equity in your house,
will he ever be able to come back?
How much above market value?
Mitzi!
Look, I don't wanna sell,
but if somebody else does, I'm screwed!
No one else is gonna sell.
- We have to stick together.
- Hey! Hey! Hey!
- What's with all the whispering?
- This is private. Do you mind?
Yes, I do. We're all waiting for
you to tell Paul to shove it.
We're just trying to figure
out how to handle this.
There is nothing to figure out.
Hey, moneybags, don't yell at her!
This is exactly what he's trying to do!
I am not yelling.
I am simply trying to explain...
He's trying to turn
the whole Lane against...
What the hell were you thinking?
Well, I didn't know what he was up to.
You sold him seven houses.
You didn't think that was a little strange?
This is not his fault,
so just back the hell off.
Okay, guys. Come on, everybody. Calm down.
We're not gonna let you destroy this street.
I don't have to.
You're going to do it yourselves.
It's a question we all ask ourselves...
do I trust the people who live next door?
Will that couple across the street
be there when I need them?
Can I count on the woman
who lives down the block?
Yes, good neighbors are
people we can rely on.
But if we discover
our neighbors can't be trusted,
then it may be...
time to move.
Sync by YYeTs.net
Corrected by MystEre
www.addic7ed.com