Previously on...
I was thinking about
this great guy from my past.
An evening of drinking led to a confession.
- Tom.
- Tom Scavo?
Love of my life.
I have to talk to you about
something really important.
Did anyone order a shrimp cocktail
with a puny engagement ring on the side?
Keith's plan to propose was thwarted.
I really do love your son.
Yeah, I see you with someone...
more your own age.
- What are you doing?
- Memorizing your face.
Gaby said good-bye to
her biological daughter Grace.
A halfway house for convicts on our street?
I now own seven houses on Wisteria Lane.
And Paul needed one more house...
I can offer you well above market value.
- How much above market value?
- We have to stick together.
To achieve his goal.
We know what they look like.
We know how they dress...
and we know how they behave.
Yes, we can all recognize
the wrong kind of people.
And when we see them coming,
we do what we have to to protect ourselves.
Lynette!
How are you this fine day?
Who are these people?
- Old friends.
- Ex-con friends?
- Mm.
- Uh... aren't you jumping the gun?
Until the homeowners association votes,
you don't have approval for your project.
These men have volunteered
to get my halfway house ready.
Most of them live in
a dreadful facility on skid row.
I told them that
if they participated in the remodel,
I could get them transferred here.
You're wasting their time,
because this place is never going to open.
Oh, I think it will.
And won't it be nice
for these men to live on a street
where children play in their front yards
He doesn't have the votes.
He's got something up his sleeve.
What it is I don't know.
Are we positive no one's planning on
selling him their home?
We can't take anyone for granted.
We need to talk to everyone on the street.
Good idea. We'll shore up support.
- And if we sense anyone starting to waver...
- How could they?
Everyone knows what's at stake here.
I pray they do.
I love this neighborhood,
and I don't want it to change.
Let's go.
And with that,
my friends went to work
trying to stop Paul Young.
He knew what they were up to.
But he didn't care.
He should have.
Paul had forgotten
what ordinary men and women
will do to protect themselves...
from the wrong kind of people.
It was just before sunrise
on Wisteria Lane...
when a cab arrived...
and a woman departed.
She left the street quietly.
But news of her disappearance
would soon spread.
And the sound would be deafening.
But first...
a young man in love
had plans to make some noise of his own.
Bree, I love you, and I want this to be
the last morning you wake up
without me next to you.
It's 6:00! How long have you been
kneeling there?
I don't know,
but after you answer this question,
you're gonna need to help me up.
Bree...
will you do me the honor...
May I say something first?
After that embarrassing
night in the restaurant,
I really appreciate you taking
another stab at this, but...
That's a long "but." I'm getting up.
Hold on. I'm not saying no...
exactly.
It's just so soon to be
talking about marriage.
Maybe I can use this as a tiny napkin ring.
Wait!
I have a proposal for you.
I love you, too,
Keith Watson,
and I also want this to be
the last morning I wake up
without you next to me.
So I'm asking you,
will you do me the honor of...
moving in with me?
For the third time, no.
I'm not gonna sell my house to Paul Young.
I'm sorry. I just had to make sure.
The vote is today.
Do you really think that
I would let dangerous ex-cons
move in next to my own mother?
I don't know. As a teenager,
you were pretty nasty.
But you're all grown up
now and so very nice.
Thank you for your support.
Excuse me.
Lynette Scavo?
Yeah?
Brent Ferguson, president
of the hydrangea circle
homeowners association.
Ohh.
We've all heard about your situation.
We'd love to help.
- Really?
- Sure. Last year we had
a similar scare on our street.
Some old hippie wanted to
open up a drug rehab center
- on our block.
- I remember.
Didn't that old hippie get
beat up by a neighbor?
He made the mistake of mouthing off
to one of my neighbors
who's an ex-green beret.
Newspaper made it sound
way worse than it was.
Well, nice to meet you.
You say the word,
and I will have the homeowners association
of ten different streets
here to back you folks up.
Whoever's trying to open up
this halfway house,
we could really scare the hell out of 'em.
Well, I appreciate your offer,
but I think we'd prefer
to handle our situation
in a more...
civilized manner.
Okay. Well,
you change your mind,
you know where to find me.
"Hydrangea circle," got it.
So we're at dinner, and Renee
is going on and on about this guy
she once had a fling with and
she still has feelings for,
and she gets so drunk that
she tells me it was Tom Scavo.
What am I supposed to do with that?
You look so hot right now.
Mike, focus. I know
you've been in Alaska for a month.
A month, 19 days, and 7 hours.
Yesterday I put boobs on a snowman.
I need to come home.
I miss you, too.
So am I making too much out of this?
I mean, it happened 20 years ago,
and Tom's a good guy, right?
Yeah, he is, but...
even good guys make mistakes
if the circumstances are right.
Interesting point. Wish you hadn't made it
while you were 2,000 miles away
and clearly horny.
Susan, I am in the middle of nowhere.
The only female I've seen has antlers.
So should I tell Lynette?
Well, not just yet.
Maybe just keep an eye on the situation.
Thanks for the advice.
Just so you know, when you come home,
I'm gonna make you forget all
about that snowman.
Her name is Carol.
Okay, you really need to come home.
Mommy?
Why are you crying?
Oh... just...
having a sad day.
You've been having a lot of sad days.
Is it because Grace left?
Why would you say that?
That was when you started being sad...
the day she went away.
No, it's just, you know...
I got really close to
that whole family, and...
I knew I was gonna miss Carmen and Hector.
And Grace?
Why are you wearing my necklace?
I'm playing dress-up.
Not with real diamonds. Hand it over!
Fine. Here.
Take it. Jeesh.
And I don't want you playing in
my room anymore. You understand?
I liked you better when you were crying.
Mitzi!
It's Lynette Scavo!
If you're in there,
please open up!
- Hey, Lee.
- Hey.
You wouldn't happen
to know where Mitzi Kinsky is,
- would you?
- No. Why would I?
I thought maybe you and Paul
convinced her to sell her house
and then stashed her away
someplace for safekeeping.
Lynette, I have to say, I'm offended.
I have to say, I couldn't care less.
You know...
For the millionth time,
I had no idea what he was up to!
You were his real estate agent!
You didn't think it odd...
him buying all these houses on one street?
He was paying me commissions.
What-what am I supposed to do?
- Complain?
- Maybe you didn't know,
and if Paul is voted down at
tonight's meeting, I'm sure
in time people will forget
you had anything to do with this...
- I...
- But, Lee, if he finds
a way to open that house,
I don't think anyone on
this street will ever forgive you.
Hello?
Look out your window.
Oh, it's you. I'm hanging up now.
Look, I understand you're annoyed with me.
- I feel awful.
- Well, you should.
Because of you, everyone on
this street hates me now.
That's why I'm calling.
I put you in an awful position.
I'd like to make it up to you.
And how are you gonna do that?
Well, first, you should
know that Mitzi Kinsky
agreed to sell me her house yesterday.
What?
I suggested she leave the lane for a while.
The taxi picked her up this morning.
Oh, my god. So why...
why are you telling me this?
Because I have a little proposition for you.
And given how the neighbors
feel about you these days,
I suggest you listen.
Hey, Mitzi, it's Lynette.
Um, still haven't heard from you.
I need to make sure we're
all on the same page
for tonight's meeting. Call me back.
- Ay.
- Hey.
I know you're probably busy.
I really need to talk to somebody.
I would love to, but the meeting's tonight.
I got a bunch of phone calls to make.
- Can't you talk to Susan or Bree?
- No. It's gotta be you.
Why?
You're the only woman
I know who's lost a child.
And ever since Grace left,
I can't stop crying.
I break down at the mall, at the market.
I'm starting to freak myself out.
I was the same way after I lost the baby.
I finally went to a therapist.
- I didn't know that.
- Yeah.
- Did it help?
- It did.
In fact, she had me do something
you might want to try.
Write Grace a letter.
A letter?
You don't send it.
You just pour out your feelings.
Tell Grace how happy
you are to have found her
and how much you love her.
Trust me. After you've written it,
you'll feel so much better.
Gaby! Where are my keys?
Uh, I have them!
Wait. I'll be right down!
You're moving in together?
No one's more surprised than I am.
So you did propose to her?
I tried. Bree said
she's not ready for that yet.
This was the compromise.
I figure we'll do this for a while,
then in a couple months
we'll start talking about a wedding.
Yeah, I-I guess that could happen.
You "guess"?
It's just...
if Bree was in love with you,
seems she'd want to...
lock it down. That's all.
Dad, I get where she's coming from.
She just divorced a guy.
That's my point.
She's ready for some fun,
not something serious.
She may be looking at you as a diversion.
No, Bree loves me. This is going somewhere.
Just make sure.
If Bree's not willing to make
some sort of a commitment,
- then maybe...
- Dad, you're starting to piss me off.
I hope I'm wrong. I really do.
And if I am...
You let me know when to rent
the tux for the wedding.
Okay.
- Any sign of Mitzi?
- Oh, not yet.
God, where could she be?
If she sold her house to Paul,
she better be on the run.
Not that it'll do any good.
- I'll still hunt her down and kill her.
- Uh-huh.
Lynette? We've been here for 20 minutes.
- Don't you think it's time you started?
- Relax,
Paul. We're not taking
the vote until everyone's here.
Well, while we're waiting,
may I make an announcement?
I suppose.
May I have your attention, please?
I wanted you all to know
That the mayor of Fairview
will be here friday
to present me with an award
for outstanding public service.
- What?
Yes, it's-it's-it's sort of a big deal,
and I would love it
if all of my friends would attend.
If you'd invite your enemies,
you'd get a bigger crowd.
Ah, I love your sense of humor,
Mrs. McCluskey.
- How we'll all miss it after you're gone.
- Hmm.
Hold it. Now, what kind of
public service did you do?
The halfway house, of course.
Oh, shoot. Did-did I bury the lead?
I now have all the votes I need to open it.
How do you have the votes?
Someone sold you their house?
Oh, yes.
We shouldn't have sold.
We should have just gone under
with the rest of the neighborhood.
Which would have been
very noble and very stupid.
Mitzi sold. She's not gonna be around
for everybody on this street to pummel,
which means they would have taken
their anger out on you.
Didn't have a choice.
What the hell?
Mitzi, what are you doing here?
I live here.
Oh, I guess you would have noticed,
if I was a hot guy with abs.
But we thought you left.
Weirdest thing. Get this call?
This guy says he has
a job for me in the city.
Puts me up in a nice hotel,
and then he never showed.
Huh, and I got stuck
with the minibar charges.
So, wait. You didn't sell
your house to Paul Young?
What?
Please. I'm not gonna
screw over my neighbors.
Lee?
What the hell have you done to us?
No, I'm sorry. Lynette is not here.
She's trying to deal with
this whole Paul Young mess.
Yes, I will have her get back to you.
Ok-okay.
What is happening to this neighborhood?
Some van just pulled up,
and these creepy characters are getting out.
That is a school bus, Renee.
Those are children.
Well, I don't like the way
they're looking at me.
Can you come over and install
a dead bolt on my door?
Sure. I will be right over,
as soon as I find
where Lynette keeps the toolbox.
Great. I have to jump in the shower.
I will leave the key under the mat.
You know, I had to use
that key the other night.
Yeah?
Yeah. We went out, and Renee got hammered,
so I had to take her in and put her to bed.
Well, that was nice of you.
Yeah...
and she told me this fascinating story
about this guy that she had
a fling with 20 years ago.
W-w-why-why-why was that fascinating?
Well, apparently the one weekend
they spent together
made quite an impact on her.
W... did she say any... thing...
else a-about that guy?
No, not really.
Hmm.
Only that his name was Tom Scavo.
Okay, look...
this happened before
Lynette and I were married.
It meant nothing.
Well, it meant something to Renee.
She's still in love with you.
- She said that?
- She slurred it.
Look, this is not something
I wanted to know,
but now that I do,
I am in a horrible position.
No, no, no, no, no. You can't tell Lynette!
Sh-she would freak out!
I don't want to tell her,
but she's my best friend,
and I'm freaking out knowing
that you're at Renee's
fixing her dead bolt while
she's in the shower.
Look, this was forever ago,
and I don't feel anything for her.
A beautiful woman who still wants you
is living 100 yards away,
and her breasts are 95 yards away.
Why do you want that temptation?
Hey, I didn't ask her to move here.
Well...
maybe it's time you ask her to leave.
So the whole right side
of the closet is yours,
and I emptied out
the top drawers of the bureau
for your socks and those cute
little boxer briefs you wear.
Thank you.
And after we've gotten you settled,
I want us to go over and tell the girls.
They're going to die.
Bree Van de Kamp living in sin.
Come here.
What is it?
- We love each other, right?
- Mm-hmm.
Why don't you just go ahead and wear this?
- Keith.
- No, if-if... if marriage is
where we're headed,
I just keep thinking, what's the harm?
Because we're not there yet.
Look, I'm not trying to rush you,
but I need a bigger commitment
than just the top couple
drawers in your bureau.
We talked about this.
I'm not ready to make that kind of promise.
That's a problem.
Because I don't wanna wake up one day
and find out that I was just some diversion
that, uh, you needed to amuse yourself
while getting through your divorce.
If you really think I feel that way,
then why are you even here?
I'm-I'm starting to wonder that myself.
Do you think us living
together is a mistake?
No. No, I think us is a mistake.
I wish we had been nicer to Paul.
I wish we had stood by him
when he was on trial.
I think about what
he must have gone through in prison,
and I understand his rage. I do.
But I won't allow him
to destroy this street.
It's not right.
Don't worry.
We will stop this son of a bitch.
That's a promise.
Hey. M.J.'s spending
the night at a friend's house,
so I don't care
if this protest goes all night.
I'm here to the bitter end.
- How can I help?
- We need more signs painted.
- Okay.
- Hey, Susan.
Look on that paper. We came up
with a whole list of slogans.
Just so you know, we got plenty of
"think about the children,"
and we need a lot more
"who let the cons out?"
so, what exactly are we hoping
to accomplish with all this?
The mayor is in a close
race for re-election.
He needs every vote he can get.
If we can make
a big enough stink
in front of the news cameras,
maybe we can embarrass him
into shutting that place down.
So if this protest works,
and the place doesn't open,
what happens to all those ex-cons?
What happens to them?
I mean, I... if they don't get
to stay here, where will they go?
They'll just go back to
where they came from,
or some house in another neighborhood.
- But what if that neighborhood
doesn't want them either?
- Well...
I mean, if they've done their time,
and they need a second chance,
wouldn't it be better for them
to be in a nice neighborhood?
In theory, yes, but that's
not the way the world works.
We have to think about
our neighborhood, our children.
Ourselves?
Don't be cute. Some of these men
may have good intentions,
but some of them could
still be really bad guys.
But if we don't even try to help them,
are we so sure we're the good guys?
Richard.
Keith told me what happened. I'm so sorry.
Thank you.
So, uh, why are you here?
He also mentioned all
that work that needs to be done
in your backyard. Luckily,
I taught him everything he knows.
Uh, wait. Uh, you don't need to do that.
It's not a problem. I'll have
it done by the end of the week.
But if you wanna thank me,
think you could find me
something cold to drink?
Mayor Franklin. What an honor. Paul Young.
You must be the good samaritan
- I've heard so much about.
- This is my wife Beth.
- I've never met a celebrity before.
- Well, now you have.
The media will be arriving shortly,
as well as some of the mayor's supporters.
Uh, with the election just a few days away,
- we thought this could be
a terrific photo op.
- No problem.
While you're waiting,
would you like a tour of the facility?
Absolutely. I must say,
I don't know how you got your neighbors
to agree to a halfway house on their street,
but they must think a lot of you.
Honestly, this is all happening
because of what I think of them.
Richard? Is that you?
The lemonade's not quite ready yet.
Richard, would you like
a sandwich with that...
Who are you?
This the halfway house?
Uh, no. That's next door.
Ah.
So I guess we're gonna be neighbors.
Well, I'm sure you're in a hurry
to get settled in over there, so...
I'm in no hurry.
What's going on in here?
Uh, this, um, gentleman just,
uh, wandered into my home.
I made a mistake.
Won't happen again.
It better not.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine, I was just,
uh, taken by surprise.
You're shaking. Come on. Come on. Come on.
No, really... really, I'm fine, just, um...
Thank you for taking care of that.
What are you doing?
Something I've wanted to do for a long time.
You're gonna have to leave.
Okay. Maybe I misread some signals.
There have been no signals.
I was dating your son.
Okay. If that's the way you feel,
then I'll finish up out back and go.
I want you to leave now.
Look, I made an error in judgment.
I'm-I'm sorry.
- Please let me finish the work.
- I said now.
I will leave when I'm finished.
Okay. Yeah, yeah, here we are.
Well, here's trouble.
Bunch of geeks with "vote Franklin" signs
just showed up.
Looks like we're outnumbered now.
Oh, I'm not worried.
Who the hell are they?
The cavalry.
Hey, guys. Guys!
- I'm not too late, am I?
- Nope.
You're just in time.
Oh, yeah.
Okay! Here's the plan.
Once the mayor begins his speech,
I'll give the signal.
That's when we all begin chanting,
okay? You got it?
All right! Let's go!
We need to talk now.
Quite a turnout.
Look at those news cameras.
Uh, do I need a little base?
Hi-def is killing me.
Hey, Franklin!
Where did all these people come from?
I don't know.
But it looks like things are
about to get very interesting.
No, no, no! How did she find out?
You told her the other night!
Oh, while we were drinking.
You were drinking. She was listening!
- Oh, my god.
- Yeah, this is bad.
What else did you say to her?
I mean, she thinks that
you still have feelings for me.
Oh, well, that's just... ridiculous.
She's not gonna say
anything to Lynette, is she?
No.
Does she want you to tell Lynette?
No, she had a different suggestion.
And I think it's a good one.
I'm going outside to watch the protest.
Stay in your room and
look after your sister.
Oh! Don't get into those cookies I made.
Those are for after supper,
and yes, I counted them.
Juanita, what's wrong?
What is that?
The letter you wrote to Grace.
Okay.
Honey, you really shouldn't
have read this...
'cause it doesn't mean anything.
Grace is your daughter, isn't she?
That's why you've been crying
since she left.
You love her more than me.
No. No, no, no!
That is not true.
You are the most important thing
in this world to me.
You believe mommy, don't you?
Oh...
You're not my mommy.
Juanita!
Come back here!
Ladies and gentlemen, I give you
mayor Harold Franklin!
Save our street!
Save our street! Save our street!
Good afternoon, everybody.
It's a pleasure and an honor to be here...
I thought you said
the neighborhood was behind this.
Did I? I appear to have been wrong.
With a troubled past that's
is in their neighborhood.
Save our street! Save our street!
The Fairview street is an inventory
of compassionate, understanding people!
If I ever get my hands on Paul Young,
I will kill him.
Can we talk about this in the hotel?
There's a lot of angry people out there.
I know.
Save our street! Save our street!
Save our street!
Your actions are a blueprint
for others to emulate.
And that certainly describes
the people who live here...
- on Wisteria Lane.
- Hey! I talked to Tom.
This is not the right time to discuss this.
- Save our street!
- Hey, we are discussing it.
Tom told me about your little,
uh, suggestion
that I need to move off the lane.
And I want you to know,
that ain't gonna happen.
You know, if you were
really Lynette's friend,
you would know that
you cannot live two doors down
from her husband... a man you still love.
- That is none of your damn business.
- Really?
'Cause I am Lynette's friend,
and I'm not gonna stand by
and watch you screw up her marriage.
- So help me, Susan...
- Hey, get your hands off me.
Save our street! Save our street!
Save our street!
I'm parked three blocks away.
It's crazy out here.
Did you finish up everything?
Oh, yeah. I'm done.
Blueprint for others to emulate.
Because the only way we're gonna have...
Hey. I got your message.
What's wrong?
I think you should know
there's been an incident with your father.
Save our street! Save our street!
In particular, there is one man,
Paul Young...
Th-though he was unfairly incarcerated,
he has chosen...
Carlos! I can't find Juanita.
You let her outside with all this going on?
- No, she ran away!
She found out about Grace!
- How?
Look, I'll tell you later.
Just help me find her!
Juanita!
Juanita, where are you?
- Can't I go back and get it?
- It's not that important, Lee.
She signed that program after
her concert at Carnegie Hall.
She was a drug addict. Let it go.
Can you move, please?!
Come on!
You son of a bitch.
Come here.
Hey.
- What's wrong with you?
- Look, I made a mistake, okay?
Hey, don't push me. Oh!
Hey, one of those cons is beating up a guy.
Get him!
- Keith! What are you doing?
- Come on!
Get him!
- Oh!
- Save our street!
Through his generosity.
He has chosen not to be angry or bitter...
Get off of him!
And I'm honored to present this medallion
to a man...
And in conclusion, love thy neighbor!
Susan!
Listen to me!
If you don't care about my life,
think about what you're doing to Lynette!
I am thinking about Lynette!
This would destroy her!
Get off of him!
Juanita!
You're pushing!
Susan.
Stop pushing!
Susan!
Go around them! Go around!
I can't! There's people everywhere!
Maybe we should go back in the house.
Please don't leave me.
Hey! Frank, wait! Wait!
What the hell are you doing?!
- I'm gonna make sure
this halfway house never opens.
- Oh, my god!
This is what you want, isn't it?
No, no! Not like this!
Give me the bat! Please!
You know what? Go hang out
with the rest of the kiddies.
Frank! Frank, wait!
- Lynette! Lynette!
- Oh!
- Help me, please.
- Oh! Mrs. McCluskey! Oh,
my god! I've got you!
I got you.
Just drive. They'll move.
Hey! It's them! The ones that sold!
Oh, crap!
Renee! Renee, get off of there!
I'm looking for Susan!
It's not safe! Get down!
I saw her fall! I think she's hurt!
Get out of the car! Now!
It's gonna be okay. It's gonna be okay.
It's gonna be okay.
Help. Help!
Juanita!
Mommy!
Get off! Get off!
Give her to me! Give her to me!
- Mommy!
- Come here. Come here.
Paul! Paul!
Go inside, darling.
This is all on you! I hope you know that!
Me? Those are your friends
out there, Lynette...
the solid citizens of Fairview.
Tell me again
Why you think they're better
than a bunch of ex-cons?
Stop!
Stop it! Leave him alone!
Leave him alone! Stop!
He's my neighbor!
Stop it!
Take him over! Get him over here!
Come on!
Somebody help!
Thank you.
It was just before sunrise
on Wisteria Lane.
You could no longer hear
the screams of frightened bystanders...
or the angry chanting of protestors...
or the cries for help from the injured.
There were just the footsteps of a man
who had finally punished
those who had betrayed him.
The silence was broken
by something the neighbors
would later say...
sounded like a gunshot.
But Paul knew
it was the sound of revenge.
Sync by YYeTs.net
Corrected by MystEre
www.addic7ed.com