Previously on Desperate Housewives...
Bree discovered she had a romantic rival.
I've been looking for a new
hobby, and taking you down
- is as good as any.
- Susan got a bonus.
For the girl who gets
the most hits in a month.
Since the prison didn't
allow conjugal visits,
- this is our wedding night.
- Paul's bride said no.
There are certain wifely duties
that I don't want to rush into.
Once we call these people,
it'll change your family forever.
And Gaby decided to
meet her real daughter.
Call them.
Carlos Solis loved his wife
more than anything...
If there's a woman on this
planet with better skin,
I'd like to meet her.
Even though she was vain...
Do we have to give money
to the church every Sunday?
I mean, it's always the same show.
Selfish...
I told you to buy me couture!
I can't wear off-the-rack
with these shoes!
And spoiled.
But in those moments when his
wife was simply vulnerable...
You okay?
Carlos loved her just a little bit more.
This is where we're meeting them?
I think so.
I don't know what I'm supposed to say.
Start with "hello."
And then what?
"Thanks for raising our daughter
for the last eight years.
Hope we didn't ruin yours"?
It's gonna be fine.
Mrs. and Mrs. Solis? I'm Hector Sanchez.
Nice to meet you. And please,
call us Carlos and Gabrielle.
Oh, thank you. Uh, where is...
Juanita is at the swing
set with her sister.
We thought we should talk a little first.
Oh. Sure.
Uh, my wife is over here with our...
She's with Grace.
That's her name? Grace?
Yes.
So how are you and your
wife handling all of this?
We're still in shock.
Since your lawyer called us,
we haven't been able to sleep or eat.
This whole thing is so crazy.
We feel the same way.
They couldn't have switched our babies.
It's got to be a mistake.
Maybe we should take a blood test.
Mom!
I told you to bring the green jacket!
I can't wear red with these shoes! Ugh!
Yes, Carlos Solis loved his wife...
I don't think we'll be needing that test.
And he knew her D.N.A.
when he saw it.
It's called a purse,
and as every woman knows,
it can hold just about anything,
from a personalized cell phone...
to a romance novel...
to much-needed medication.
Whatever you find inside,
there's one thing you can be sure of...
every purse says something
about the woman who owns it...
whether she knows it...
or not..
Carlos and I feel like we
shouldn't tell the girls,
you know, about what happened.
What do you guys think?
We should protect them.
Yes, but since we wanna get to
know our biological daughters,
we were thinking maybe the families could
- get together every now and then?
- Maybe once a month?
Mm, that sounds reasonable.
Uh, w... what do you think, Carmen?
Um, I guess.
Look at them.
Yes, I have a feeling that they
will become very good friends.
Can you believe those are our daughters?
Grace looks just like
me when I was her age.
And Juanita looks so much like my mother.
Mommy, can I have money for ice cream?
You just had lunch.
But they have chocolate chip. Grace.
Oh, let her have some. It's
hot. Come on. It'll be my treat.
Your purse is beautiful.
I know. Would you like to hold it?
Uh-huh.
It's so soft. I bet it cost a lot, right?
Grace, you don't ask about money.
I'm sorry.
Oh, that's okay, sweetie.
And just so you know, it's Chanel.
You can have one of these
by working very hard...
Or by marrying a man who works very hard.
Thank you!
What a polite little girl.
You have obviously done a
wonderful job, Mrs. Sanchez.
I mean, we didn't know what to expect,
but I can see Grace couldn't
have had a better mother.
You know what I mean.
Uh, y... you've done a
wonderful job with Juanita.
Thank you. You know, when I got pregnant,
I didn't know how I would handle
the whole motherhood thing...
Mom.
But I think I turned out
to be pretty good at it.
- Mom!
- What?!
I need money for ice cream.
What is the magic word?
I don't know. "Hurry"?
Now come on. The truck's pulling away.
"Please." The magic word is "please."
Fine. Please.
What, we can't afford more than one scoop?
I'm sorry. What was I saying?
You were talking about
what a good mother you are.
Say good-bye to your truck loan.
God, can you believe it?
Just two months ago, we
were up to our neck in debt.
Now we're only up to our ass.
If we keep this going,
we could reach flat broke
in time for Christmas.
Hello? It's Maxine.
Um, uh, I'm in here with Mike!
It's open!
Hello, Michael!
Look at this punim.
Oh, Mike, if I was 15 years younger,
I'd ride you like a hobo rides a boxcar.
Thanks. But you still have
to fix the air conditioner.
Eh, it was worth a shot.
I'm gonna take a shower.
I need to talk some business with you.
Me, too.
I just bought a fur-trimmed
Teddy and some floor polish.
Tomorrow is gonna be a heck of a show.
Fantastic.
- I think you should quit.
- What?
The web site's going through some changes.
I've taken on some partners
who are pumping a lot of
cash into the business,
and they're running the show
now, and they want a huge
U.S. presence.
No. No, no, you promised me
that no one here would ever see me.
I did, and that's why
you need to get out now.
But Mike and I are just
getting back on track.
Yesterday, we got our first water bill
- that didn't come with a threat.
- Honey, I'm sorry.
Well, how long do I have
till all this happens?
A couple of weeks, a month tops.
Okay. I'll work right
up until the last day.
Give me double shifts, extra
shows. I'll do anything.
You got it.
I'm gonna miss you, honey.
No one will ever wear the rubber
gloves and the fishnets like you do.
Okay, we get it. You're unhappy.
We got it in every aisle at the market,
we got it four times during the night,
- and we get it now!
- Mom, I'll put the groceries away.
Oh. No.
Stop. Freeze.
Do nothing. No sudden movements.
The eyes are closing.
But we bought ice cream.
Let it melt.
Hello? Hello? Yes, this is she.
Oh. Of course I did.
Thank you. Thank you. I... I will be back.
Everything okay?
No, I left my license at the store,
so I have to drag Paige back there,
which will lead to another
2-hour screaming fit.
If I didn't look so good in
that photo, I'd get a new one.
- Why don't you leave the baby with me?
- Oh, honey, I don't know.
Mom, you leave her with the boys,
and they don't change her diaper
until it weighs as much as she does.
Good point.
I'm back.
I'm back! Everything okay?
She woke up, so I went with plan "b."
- You traded her in for a quieter baby?
- Nope. I changed her diaper.
Now we're doing a little floor time.
You changed her diaper.
Where'd you learn how to do that?
I've seen you do it a hundred times.
You're so good with her.
How would you feel about
me taking a quick shower
to wash some of this
vomit out of my hair...
from yesterday?
Why don't you take a bath? Light
one of those scented candles.
Whoever raised you did a brilliant job!
Mwah!
Shoot.
I'm out of aspirin.
Do you have a headache?
Uh, no. My back is a little sore.
You do realize, darling, that
your back wouldn't hurt so much
if you weren't sleeping
on a couch every night.
Uh, n... no. Uh, the couch is fine.
Um, I just pulled a muscle.
Hey there.
- Lee.
- Congratulations.
You are the proud new
owner of your old house.
You bought your old house?
Actually, Lee, why don't we talk later?
Okay. Well, here are your keys,
your complimentary
endangered species calendar,
and a kitchen magnet with my face on it.
Yes, I know I look cross-eyed,
but they assure me they will
correct that in the next batch.
Enjoy.
Why would you buy that house?
Our lease won't be up for a year.
I thought it was a good investment.
But why buy... that one?
There are other homes
for sale around here.
Escrow's closed, Beth.
I see no point in discussing this further.
You won't discuss it?
I'm your wife.
Isn't it convenient how
during the day you're my wife,
but at night, you turn
back into a house-guest?
No, no, no. Don't look at
them yet. They're not done.
This isn't about the shutters.
It's about our... date Friday.
You still haven't told
me what we're doing.
Well, I can't tell you yet,
but I've been working on something
that I'm pretty... stoked about.
Well, that sounds lovely.
I, too, am... stoked.
You got a little paint...
- What are you doing?
- Shh!
Are you spying on Bree again?
Why would he want her
when he could have me?
- She's way too old for him.
- You're the exact same age.
- I am not. I'm only thirty...
- Are you gonna lie about your age?
We were college roommates.
All right, damn it.
Besides, Bree's always looked young.
When she used to go out with her grandkid,
people would think he was her son.
Wait. Bree's a grandmother?
How did I not know this?
Okay, sweetie, I am taking
the baby over to Gaby's.
The girls are meeting for
poker. I'll be back in a few.
- You're not staying?
- No. I'm really just doing a drive-by.
Last week, Paige spit up on Gaby's couch,
so now she's pretty much baby non grata.
Why don't you just leave her with me?
Then you can stay for your game.
But we usually play for a couple of hours.
Give me a kiss.
So? You'll be right
next door if I need you.
Oh, don't toy with me.
I'm operating on two hours
of sleep. I'm vulnerable.
Go. We'll be fine.
I love watching my baby sister.
- Oh!
- It's fun.
Penny Lynn Scavo,
you are officially my favorite.
We are gonna leave
everything to you in our will.
Keep in mind we're poor,
so it's rely more of a symbolic gesture.
Listen, guys,
uh, before we start...
I've been keeping something from you,
but I'm gonna tell you because
you're my dearest and oldest friends.
Well, I've only known you two weeks,
but I don't want to be
rude and tell you to leave.
See this picture? This
is my daughter Grace.
Oh, my God. Gaby.
I can't imagine what you're going through.
I'd be out of my mind.
How can you function?
Well, we were knocked sideways at first,
but since we met Grace,
it's been a blessing.
Thank God the parents are lovely.
I mean, this is the kind of
thing you see on the news.
- Who else knows about this?
- Very few people,
and I need you guys to keep it that way.
Well, of course we'll be discreet.
Definitely, for Juanita's sake.
Oh, don't worry about me.
Up until today, I
thought you were Juanita.
So... tell us what it was like.
Amazing.
I looked into her eyes and felt that pull.
Well, you carried her for nine months.
There's this one thing she
did that was incredibly moving.
She came up to me...
and within two seconds of touching my bag,
she knew it was expensive.
Now that is a hallmark moment.
You don't understand.
When I was a kid,
I used to sneak "Vogues"
out of my aunt's hair salon
and make my own high fashion paper dolls.
I know what it's like to be that kid,
with her face pressed against
the department store window.
Grace is me at her age.
So I decided to do something for her.
Her own little starter Chanel.
You are the best mother ever.
Paul?
- What are you doing?
- Please go home.
I just wanna understand, that's all.
Are we going to move here?
No.
Then why would you buy this house?
It must be filled with so
many unpleasant memories.
I don't see any unpleasant memories.
I see the couch
where my wife and I would sit
and have our morning coffee
I see the Christmas tree in
the corner by the fireplace.
I see the chair...
where I would sit and
read stories to my son.
I was loved in this house.
I had a real marriage here.
Our marriage is real, Paul.
It's just...
this is hard for me,
and... and you keeping things from me
doesn't make it any easier.
You're right.
There should be no secrets between us.
Secrets are why this
house is empty right now.
Sorry I'm late, but I
think you'll be happy
when you hear why.
Black Eyed Peas. Row 15, center.
How cool is that?
Wow, that's just...
Wow.
- You like them, right?
- Of course.
You sound a little... underwhelmed.
No. Not at all.
I live to rock.
You know, I'm not as
old as you might think.
- Grandma!
- Surprise!
What are you doing here?
Visiting. We're here all weekend.
Um... hello.
- Hi.
- Keith,
this is my daughter
Danielle and this is my...
her, uh, son Benjamin.
Danielle, this is my, um... friend Keith.
We were just... going out.
Grandma! Grandma! Look what I bought you!
It's slippers.
My grandma has bad
circulation. Don't you, grandma?
Please stop calling me that!
You... precious child.
You know what? You guys came all this way.
You should spend tonight together.
No. No, no, no. If... if you
guys had plans, you should go.
We'll be fine.
Bree, there's... there's nothing
more important than family.
We'll go out another time.
You're very sweet.
Nice meeting both of you.
Uh, thank you so much.
Uh, I guess I heard wrong.
You seem to be bouncing back just fine.
What are you talking about?
When your friend called,
she said you were having a
hard time since Orson left.
Uh, by any chance,
is this friend named Renee?
She sent us first class tickets.
I wish I had a friend like that.
Oh, trust me, you don't.
Oh, come on. Come on.
What the hell?
Maxine, pick up.
They're already putting up a billboard.
You... you said they weren't
gonna start advertising
for a couple of... oh, my God!
- Wait! Wait! Stop!
- Huh?
- You... you can't put that up there! That's me.
- So?
So... so people will see!
My friends will see!
Lady, with a body like that,
no one's even gonna
notice you have a head.
No, no, no! No, no!
You can't! No, stop! Oh!
- What the hell are you doin'?
- Protecting my dignity!
Hey there, Mrs. McCluskey.
Nice day, isn't it?
I've seen better. What do you want?
You're direct.
I love that about you.
Truth is, I was wondering
if you had any interest
in selling your home.
Well, get ready to love me again.
No.
Aren't you tired of
caring for this place...
the big lawn and all these stairs?
Yeah, your concern is touching.
What's your game here?
I just love this neighborhood so much,
I'd hate to see this house
fall into the wrong hands
after you're gone.
I'm not going anywhere.
I hope you're right,
but the years do he a way of flying by,
and I thought you might
wanna unload this place
while you still have the upper hand.
Upper hand?
Yes.
Right now you're sharp as a tack.
But one day, your hip will break
or you'll suffer a massive stroke,
and the doctors will say you
can longer live on your own.
And when that day comes,
potential buyers who don't
care about you like I do
will know that you're desperate.
They'll smell the blood in the water.
People will start smelling your blood
if you don't get off my porch.
All right. Didn't mean to upset you.
My offer still stands.
As I said,
it all comes from my great love
for this beautiful neighborhood.
Be careful on those stairs now.
Look who's missing her big sister.
Oh. Oh, oh, oh.
There. You are really so good with her.
Listen, I'm gonna take a quick
jog. Be back in 20 minutes.
- Mom.
- Yeah?
I've got a test today. I
cannot be late for the bus.
I hear ya loud and
clear. I'll be back in 15.
You might wanna smell her diaper.
I think she left you a little present.
Hey, Lynette?
Um, I need to talk to you.
Sure.
Oh. You're jogging again.
Where's, uh, the baby?
Uh, Penny is watching her.
It is the most amazing thing.
Only when you've spawned as much as I have
do you learn the glorious truth...
the older ones can watch the younger ones.
Babies having babies... bad.
Babies raising babies... genius!
I'm happy for you.
You don't look happy.
That's why we need to talk.
Okay.
She flew them here first
class? That is vintage Renee.
Yes, a voracious libido
and unlimited funds...
a deadly combination.
And now she's taking Keith
to dinner tomorrow night.
How did you find that out?
Well, he called to
make sure it was okay...
which, course, it isn't.
But what could I say?
Don't say anything.
Wait till she's crossing the
street and then run her over.
No, I'm too fond of my car.
You have to fight back somehow.
It's the only thing Renee understands.
But how? I mean, you
know her better than I do.
What could I do to humiliate her?
She once slept with a rodeo clown...
But he's a senator now. Uh...
Oh, she's got this
really weird belly button.
But by the time he finds that
out, they're already getting it on.
She used to freak out whenever
"The wizard of Oz" was on tv.
Why?
Mm, I think it was the munchkins.
There's something about little people
that gives her the heebie-jeebies.
Oh, crap! Penny's gonna
be late for school.
Sorry I couldn't help.
Oh, no. You helped.
Penny!
I'm sorry! I forgot my phone!
Uh, grab your stuff, and I'll drive you!
Wha...
where's my baby?
Stop breathing on my sister!
Hi. I'm Lynette Scavo.
I need to find my daughter Penny.
Yeah. We've been expecting you.
Principal's office is in the back.
Oh. Thank you.
You're in so much trouble.
So...
You left your 2-month-old baby
in the care of your 11-year-old daughter.
What can I say?
I'm not one of those helicopter parents.
Come on.
Give me a break. I am raising five kids.
You have no idea how hard that is.
Eight?
Well, clearly, you're very competitive.
I talked to Penny.
I think you should know
she's helping you out
more than you realize.
What do you mean?
Do you know Penny takes the
baby monitor to bed with her
so she can get up for the feedings?
She does?
As a result,
the poor girl is exhausted.
She fell asleep in
social studies yesterday.
I had no idea.
Oh, my gosh.
Yes, I will talk to
Penny when she gets home,
and I will fix this.
Yes, that would be nice.
Okay.
You know what? Enough
with the judgmental tone.
Come on. Who among us is a perfect mother?
Gaby.
Is everything okay?
Yeah. Yeah, everything's fine.
I was just hoping Grace would be home.
I thought we were supposed to call first
if we wanted to see the kids.
I know, I know, but I
was in the neighborhood.
Uh, is she here?
No.
Okay. Well, could you
give this to her for me?
Thank you, but Grace already has a purse.
Really? Is it Chanel?
No. We bought it at a flea market for $2,
and she's very happy with it.
I know, but don't you think she'd
like this one a little better?
Not if she never sees it.
Don't you think I would like
to give my children nice things?
We're not like you.
We can't afford luxuries. We can
barely afford the necessities.
Look, if you guys need help...
What we need is for you
to let us be who we are,
not who you are.
Goodbye, Gaby.
Please, call next time.
You said I had a month.
I said I thought it was a month.
It's the Internet.
Everything moves very fast.
How many billboards are there?
They talked about a big ad
campaign, so I guess a lot.
You have got to call them.
Get them to stop it, or at least
put some other girl up there.
Something.
Honey, I tried to warn you.
It's beyond my control now.
Please help me.
What if Mike sees me splayed
across that billboard?
He's gonna recognize those panties!
He gave them to me for our anniversary!
I'll make a call.
I'm sorry I took the baby to school.
I had a math test, and
I didn't want to be late.
Hey, sweetie. Hey. Hey.
You didn't do anything wrong.
I did.
Come here. Sit down.
I understand you've been
taking the baby monitor
into your room at night.
Just so you can sleep.
I appreciate that,
and I appreciate how often
you have been looking
after your little sister.
Well, I know how you like
to go see your friends
and go jogging and stuff.
Yeah, I do.
And you're different when
you get to do those things.
You laugh more. You're not as cranky.
You stay up late and
play board games with us.
I like that mommy better.
I like that mommy better, too.
But it's not your job to take care of me.
Your job is to...
watch television and
eat way too much candy.
And my job is to make sure
that's all your job is.
Okay.
Off you go.
That...
was really sweet.
I know.
Get me a nanny.
What?
I am drowning here.
You heard what Penny said.
I'm not myself anymore.
And when I'm not taking
it out on the kids,
I'm taking advantage
of them. So I need help.
How about if I pitch in more?
Oh, Tom.
What a lovely, hollow offer
that you'll never back up.
Get me a nanny.
You bought an 8-year-old
girl a $1,400 purse?
Oh, lighten up. It's not like
I got her the matching wallet.
So what did Carmen say?
She went all "Grapes of wrath" on me,
'cause God forbid that woman let
her daughter have nice things.
"That woman" is her mother,
and I'm with her on this.
You have no right to give
Grace expensive gifts.
- Yes, I do.
- Why?
Because she was supposed
to have all this stuff!
We were supposed to give it to her.
This is why I didn't
want us to look for her,
because we had no idea what
would happen once we found her.
But you looked, and we met her,
and now we're falling
in love with this girl.
And if you spook these people,
they can take her away from us forever.
Morning, Mrs. McCluskey.
How are you today?
I feel great. Sorry to disappoint you.
Oh. Oh... what?
Just had my annual physical.
Doc says I'm gonna be around for years.
So you can tell that
vulture husband of yours
he'll have to pick at
someone else's carcass.
What are you talking about?
Something smells good.
I'm making stew.
So... how was your day?
Fine.
Anything interesting happen?
No, not really.
You didn't...
talk to anyone?
Who would talk to me?
I'm gonna go wash up.
You are going to love the sea urchin.
Looks a little sketchy.
Most of the fish I eat
comes in a basket with fries.
You're funny.
And you eat out of a basket.
I like that.
Everything okay?
I just thought I saw...
never mind.
So... anyway,
I thought after dinner
we could go to a club.
What do you think of jazz?
I think it's the sea urchin of music.
Okay, um, did you see that?
See what?
It was probably nothing. Um...
I thought I saw...
Okay, you're...
you're just a kid.
What is the matter with you?
I'm so sorry.
I don't want you to think I'm odd.
Y... you see, when... I was a child,
there was this incident... at the circus.
And ever since then,
I have always been terrified of...
Hey! Don't I know you?
Get him away! Get him away! Get him away!
What's wrong?!
Is he there with his tiny hands?
I can't look at his tiny hands!
I am... I am so sorry.
I don't know what the hell she's doing.
It's okay.
Obviously, I made a mistake.
Oh, my God. Did he go? I can't look.
He's gone.
So come down.
Everyone is staring.
You should've seen the look on her face.
Well, I couldn't see her,
but I certainly heard her...
and it was magnificent.
Happy to help out. Bye,
Bree. See ya in church.
$9,000?
Hey, my partners spent a lot of
money printing those billboards.
And they'll agree not to put them up,
but they are not gonna eat the cost.
Honey, I did the best I could.
I talked them down from $12,000.
It's still a huge hit.
I mean, it puts us
right back where we were
before I started doing this stuff.
I know.
And what's Mike gonna say when
he notices the money is missing?
Oh, God. I hadn't even thought of that.
Maybe I should just let
them put up the billboards.
At least then when he
kills me, I'll be famous.
You know, there is another way.
What do you mean?
Well, you could earn that
money back, and fast, too.
But you'd have to...
Never mind. Forget I said anything.
No, no. What? What... what is it?
Well, there are other services
our web site provides...
things I've kept hidden from you
because of the boundaries you've set.
But if you're willing to go
beyond those boundaries...
Are you talking about prostitution?
God, no!
Nothing like that!
Just private on-screen interactions
of a... racier nature.
How racy?
How much money do you wanna make?
How dare you.
Good morning, Renee.
How dare you exploit a
traumatic childhood memory.
Yes, I heard you had some sort
of episode with a little person.
Oh, look. He followed you home.
Very funny. I wonder how Keith will react
when I tell him it was
you who ruined our date.
About the same as when he finds out
you used my grandson to ruin ours.
Oh. Here's Keith now.
Why don't we ask him
who he wants to be with?
We can't...
put him on the spot like that.
Bree, you're getting all red.
Is that a hot flash or
you just losing your nerve?
I was gonna finish up with those sconces.
Everything okay here?
Not exactly.
Can we ask you something?
If you had to choose between...
forest green or brown
for the trim, which would you prefer?
Forest green... I guess.
Great. Then why don't you, uh,
run down to the hardware store
and have them mix you up a batch?
Scoot.
What's the matter,
Bree? Afraid you'll lose?
You know what?
I think I am.
He's all yours.
Well, that's not any fun.
I thought you liked him.
I do, but... I don't get his references.
I can't stay up late like he does.
I'm being silly.
I feel like one of those
clichés people make fun of...
the desperate, predatory divorcée.
You mean like me?
Well, yeah.
Do you know why people make fun of us?
They're jealous,
because we still have the
guts to go after what we want.
You think he can make you happy?
I think so.
Then go for it.
My gift to you.
Why are you being so nice to me?
Based on my dinner under
the rainbow last night,
I'd rather have you as
a friend than an enemy.
Now go.
Keith, hang on! I think I'll join you!
Uh, really nice of you to have us over.
- Maybe next time you
can come to our house.
- Absolutely.
You know, I think it's great
that out of this unfortunate situation,
we could all end up being friends.
Yes. We're very lucky people.
- Bet you can't catch me!
So now we pinch off a small piece of masa,
and you roll it into a ball.
Is this big enough?
It's perfect. Ay.
I really love your house Mrs. Solis.
Oh, well, thank you, honey.
Would you like a tour?
Uh-huh. Come on.
Wow. It's so big.
You have a tv in your bedroom?
Lucky.
Yes, we are very lucky.
Is that a jewelry box?
You want to take a look?
Yeah.
It's all so pretty.
I can't wait till I grow up
so I can have beautiful things.
You like that?
It's a gift I bought myself
with my first big modeling check.
I want you to have it. You
deserve beautiful things.
I don't know. My mom might get mad.
Then we'll make it... our little secret.
Thank you.
I want a purse like that someday.
Well, then I'm gonna make sure you get it.
It's called a purse,
and as every woman knows,
it can hold just about anything...
from a bottle for a baby...
to a check for protection...
to a gift for a new friend.
Whatever you find inside,
there's one thing you can be sure of...
every purse says something
about the woman who owns it...
whether she knows it or not.
sync by yyets.net - corrected by chamallow
www.addic7ed.com