Previously on Desperate Housewives...
Your ex-husband was
part owner in a business.
Susan came into an inheritance.
Who do I speak to about selling
my share of herpes on parade?
Lynette acquiesced...
- Looks like we'll be going to therapy
together. - That is great news! Thank you.
As soon as graduate
high school,
I'm going to New York
to be a model.
Angie's concerns
made her more protective.
You know I've always felt bad
about the way we've had
To raise you,
being on the run and all.
The door stays open.
- I want it closed.
- You stink.
And you're a whore!
Here's the difference.
I can get clean.
- Stop!
- Say "please".
- And Orson expressed his feelings.
- Please!
That's the life
I'm facing now...
Having to ask people for help,
for everything.
Do you know how hard
that is?!
Orson Hodge
was smiling again,
And it was starting to worry
his wife.
You see, since his accident,
Bree Hodge had grown accustomed
To her husband's
severe mood swings.
She had grown used to
his unexpected rage...
His sudden anguish...
His deep depression.
But lately, an odd tranquility
had settled over orson,
And his wife had the feeling
something was terribly wrong.
Sadly, she was right.
What's, um, going on here?
Hello, Bree.
Just thought I'd give away some
things I don't need anymore.
Hey, Orson.
You got these in 8 and half?
Sorry, Roy.
Just carry men's sizes.
Look, I can understand
Why you might want to give away
your sporting equipment,
But why would you give away
your books and your cds?
And for god sakes, you can
still use your headphones.
These are amazing!
Give me those.
What is wrong with you people?
Don't you realize
you're taking advantage
Of a man who is
emotionally distraught?
- He seemed to be in a great mood.
- Until lady sunshine walked in.
- We're sorry, Bree. We assumed you guys had talked about
it. - Well, we didn't, and that doesn't excuse the fact
That you're all acting
like a bunch of vultures.
It's a good thing I came home,
Or you'd be
picking through his closet.
Um, you know what, guys?
We should go.
And please leave
your plunder behind.
Hey, come on. At my age,
it's just a short-term loan.
What has gotten into you?
I'm sorry, darling.
I had no intention
of upsetting you.
Keep my things,
give them away.
Ultimately,
it doesn't matter.
Yes, Orson Hodge
was smiling again
And Bree would soon learn
the reason why.
You see, her husband...
Had decided to kill himself.
Sync by fant0m
www.addic7ed.com
In this never-ending drama
we call life,
Everyone has a part to play.
Some are cast
as romantic leads.
Others end up
playing the victim.
And a few provide comic relief.
But if the drama is to be
really compelling,
There must be a hero...
And a villain.
Hey, Mrs. Kinsky.
Oh, look who's here!
The garbage police.
I hate to bug you,
But you're still not separating
your glass and plastics.
The city passed
that ordinance, remember?
How I envy you...
Young, pretty, able to crouch
for hours behind a bush,
Waiting for a neighbor
to dump her trash.
Look, maybe you don't get
how easy it is to recycle.
Oh, I get it.
I just don't want to do it.
I've been throwing styrofoam
into the trash
Since before you were born,
And the sky is still blue
and the grass is still green.
Maybe now, but what will it be
like for our grandchildren?
My son is shooting blanks,
And my daughter likes
the ladies.
Grandkids are
the least of my concerns.
- So you don't care about our planet at all?
- By the time it's a problem, I'll be long gone.
Let the cockroaches
and the robots fight over it.
What was that all about?
Oh, what do you think?
Come on. Look, one old crank
doesn't want to recycle.
You don't care about that stuff
anymore, remember?
- Of course I still care.
- Yeah, fine. Yeah, you can care.
Just... Don't be
blowing our cover.
So what am
I supposed to do?
Stand back and watch her
defile our planet?
That's exactly what
you're supposed to do.
"Sometimes you... you chain
yourself to the tree,
And sometimes you go after
the guy with the saw."
That's what Patrick
used to say.
We don't talk about
Patrick anymore.
- I'm just saying.
- So am I.
So the lawyer says
you sign right here,
And you are officially bought
out of the strip club business.
Let's hope I don't get
my share in singles.
And here's a little something
to remember us by.
"Lap dancing...
It's a grind."
Well, I will be sure
to wear this
On the next field trip I take
with my students. Thanks, Jimbo.
- Good luck.
- You, too.
- Bye, Mrs. D.
- Take care, Robin.
"Moby Dick"?
No, it's not what you think.
It's about a whale.
Yes, I know.
Uh, it's a classic.
Well, I saw an article about
A hundred books you should
read before dying,
And I thought, you know,
With all the high cholesterol
in my family,
- I better get crackin'.
- Oh, good for you.
So what are you
gonna do now?
Oh, um, uh, well, this was,
uh, never really my job.
I'm actually a teacher.
Really?
Oh, that is so cool.
I thought about being a teacher.
I actually went
a couple semesters,
But then my family had
some money problems,
And, well, nine years later,
I'm still wearing tassels.
Robin, you're being requested
in the V.I.P. Lounge.
Well, um, good luck
with those hundred books.
Thank you.
Oh, not this guy again.
I keep telling him
to keep the tips
And buy himself
a toothbrush.
Robin, wait.
You don't have to keep doing
this if it makes you unhappy.
Well, I've got bills to pay,
Mrs. Delfino.
No, I know, but you don't
have to work here.
- You could do anything you want.
- That's easy to say.
Well, I mean it.
It is never too late
to change your life.
Robin, now.
Thank you.
You're taking that
with you?
When customers get grabby,
I like to have something to wha.
I almost killed a guy with
"war and peace".
So I'm driving.
- This guys pulls out in front of me.
- Cuts him off.
- Yes. I was a little pissed.
- You were furious.
But at the stoplight, when I
start to tell the guy off,
Tom leans over and says,
"sorry. Uh, no big deal.
- She's just having a bad day." - You
didn't have to take the guy's head off.
- He was a maniac.
- She flipped him the bird.
- I was sticking up for you!
- Yes, but Tom was driving, Lynette.
Whether he chose to ignore it
Or try to run the man
f the road, it's his decision.
Let him be in the
driver's seat sometimes,
Literally and figuratively.
Bringing the score to Tom 4
and controlling bitch 0.
There's no scoreboard
in this room. You know that.
I think you both did
some great work today.
- Next Tuesday, same time?
- Thanks, doctor. It felt really great.
Yeah, great.
I always feel so much better
when we get out of there.
- Yeah, I bet you do.
- What, don't you?
I mean, I really think
she got this... Working.
Yeah, I think
she's got this... Working
And this...
Is getting beat up.
Come on, Lynette.
Don't feel like that.
- It's true. She always sides with you.
I want a second opinion. - Lynette.
Maybe we should think about
seeing another therapist.
When we started,
you loved her.
Yeah, and when we started,
I loved you, too.
Things change.
Now let's go.
Hold on.
I think I left my keys.
No, I can't. I have
dress rehearsal tonight.
Okay. Talk to you later.
I'm sorry.
I forgot my keys.
Oh, that's okay.
Um, I didn't mean
to eavesdrop.
Did you say you had
dress rehearsal?
Oh, that.
Yes, I'm sort of in a little
play that runs this weekend.
Really?
You're an actor, too?
Well, I dabbled in college.
I have a bit of a gift,
so I try to keep it alive.
Wow, what's the play? I mean,
we'd... we'd love to come see it.
"Antony and Cleopatra." but it's
just a community production.
I would never force you
to sit through it.
Oh, okay. Well, if you don't
want us to come...
Here's a flyer.
Matinees are half-off.
- Hey. - Hey! I need Ana
to watch the girls
While I run to the store,
- And big shock, she's not answering her cell.
- Oh, no problem. Come on in.
They're just
up in Danny's room.
Ana!
Gaby's here!
So they're in Danny's room?
Oh, yeah.
They were listening to music.
It was so loud,
I made them shut the door.
So they're
by themselves...
With the door shut?
Just a couple of teenagers
alone with their genitals?
Ana!
Get your ass down here!
Gaby, what's the big deal?
- They're just hanging out in Danny's room.
- With a mattress. Why don't you just crack
A bottle of champagne
on Ana's pelvis
And wish Danny a bon voyage?
Ana! Now!
Hold on. I'm coming.
I'm sure she meant
she's on her way.
What's going on?
I have to run to the store.
I need you to watch the girls.
That's it? Jeez, I thought
the house was on fire.
Let me grab my stuff.
So... You worried
they might be doing it?
Yeah. What I don't get is
why you're not worried.
They are
healthy, red-blooded kids.
- They're gonna do what they're gonna do.
- So we say nothing and just fluff their pillows?
No. We make sure they don't
do anything stupid.
Have you gotten Ana
birth control?
I make her spend time
with Juanita and Celia.
- I was hoping that would do it.
- Come on, Gaby.
You have to talk to her
about safe sex, condoms.
She's only 17.
She's too young!
How old were you
when you first did it?
Ana, hurry up!
Gotta hit the pharmacy, too!
I didn't hear you come in.
"Dearest Bree,
I will always love you,
"but the will to fight on
has left me,
So I've chosen to...
Exit life on my own terms."
Is this a suicide note?
Well, it's really more
of a suicide rough draft.
Oh, my God!
I didn't mean for you
to find out this way.
But now that you know,
- At least we can discuss it like adults.
- There is nothing to discuss.
Orson...
This is obviously
the depression talking.
- We will get you some medication.
- Bree. Bree.
There's no need for you
to feel badly about this.
I've had a good life.
Let me go.
I will do no such thing.
I forbid this.
Do you hear me? You will
not be killing yourself.
I will remove every knife, rope
and pill from this house,
And if I have to, I will be
with you 24 hours a day.
Well, being bored to death
wasn't how I was planning to go,
But we can try it your way.
Orson!
I'll give you some time
to adjust to this.
But understand me.
It's going to happen.
What's with the condoms?
Calm down.
They're not for you.
Ah, just what every man wants
to hear from his wife.
So?
Ok, hear me out. You know
how Ana is dating Danny Bolen?
- I'm gonna kill him.
- And we have to be realistic.
- With my bare hands... - Because
they're not gonna listen to reason.
- And bury him under the porch.
- No, Carlos. What choice do we have?
They're two teenagers who are
getting seriously involved.
- Isn't it better to be safe than sorry? - But giving
them these is like giving them our blessing.
And that's how I felt
at first,
But like Angie said,
nature's gonna take its course.
Yeah, easy for her to say.
She's got the boy.
What if the condom breaks?
What if he forgets to put it on?
If he knocks Ana up,
- Who do you think's gonna end up raising
the kid? - God, that would be awful.
Getting up
for those 3:00 A.M. feedings
After you've worked all day?
Not me. You.
You'll end up
taking care of the baby.
So you better convince her
to keep her legs crossed
- Until she's out of this house. - Wait. How is
this my problem? She's your trampy niece.
Because if she gets pregnant,
I'll be in prison
For killing what's buried
underneath the porch.
Mrs. D.!
Robin.
I hope you don't mind
me just showing up,
But I thought about what
you said, and you were right.
- It's never too late to change your
life, so I quit Double D's. - You did?
I was pretty scared at first,
- But now I think it's the best thing I ever did.
- Well, that's great.
Now I never would have had
the guts without talking to you.
- You're like my role model.
- Really? That's sweet.
My old role model was Candi,
down at the club,
But she o.D.'d.
Well, I will, uh,
try to do Candi proud.
Good for you, Robin.
I know change
takes a lot of courage.
Oh, it sure does.
So what do I do now?
- Huh?
- You know...
What's my next move?
Where do I work now?
I'm sorry.
You quit without having
anything else lined up?
I know it was
a little hasty,
But you said I could do
whatever I wanted.
You sounded so sure.
You're still sure, right?
Yes, yes. I'm very sure.
The world is your oyster.
You have saved up, right?
She stripped for nine years
and didn put anything away?
Apparently there was a boob job
and a bad relationship
And the rising cost
of glitter.
I have to find a way
to help her.
And why is this
your responsibility?
Because I'm the one
that told her to quit.
I didn't think she'd listen.
No one listens to me.
I keep telling you
how much I hate that shirt,
- And there it is. - Okay, we'll help her.
What do you have in mind?
We need to find her a job.
Well, what can she do?
Does she have skills
that don't involve
Picking up a dollar
without using her hands?
Why are you so sad?
Well, M.J.,
I need a job,
and I don't have any skills.
You're so pretty.
You could be a princess.
Oh, look.
M.J. is so smitten
with her.
He's a guy.
And she's good with kids.
That's it.
They've been looking
for an assistant art teacher
Down at the school.
She said she always wanted
to do something like that.
- Well, you think she can handle it?
- We glue macaroni to shoeboxes.
It's not the hardest
job in the world.
Now see, how come when I say
that, you give me that look?
And there it is again.
Thanks for cheering me up, M.J.
You're so sweet.
You can give me a bath
if you want to.
Jeez, you scared
the crap out of me.
Where's Orson? You're supposed
to be watching him.
Don't worry. I stuck him
in the laundry room
And put a broom
through his spokes.
Hello, Bree.
Can we please cross Roy off
the suicide watch list?
Hey. You're alive.
My job's done here.
Where have you been?
You were supposed to
be back an hour ago.
I am sorry, but I had to stop
and pick up our guests.
What guests?
Orson, meet Chris and Ron.
Now I know you won't listen
to me, but you might listen
- To them, since you have
something in common. - Really?
Are you Gilbert and
Sullivan fans, too?
Sense of humor.
That's very important.
Now I know you think there's
no reason to go on living,
- Because you're paralyzed...
- So you thought, "hey!"
"You know what might cheer him
up? Two more paralyzed guys."
Please. Just hear them out.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I'm going to make some tea.
So your wife tells us
you in a pretty negative place.
- Well, that's to be expected, but eventually...
- Look, I know you mean well,
But I don't need
a handicapped pep talk.
Hey, we're not handicapped.
We're handi-capable.
Oh, lord!
We play basketball, dance,
we make love.
And I hope
you're very happy together.
I, unfortunately,
don't have
- Someone to join me on this journey.
- You have a wife who clearly loves you.
Wow. Paralyzed and blind.
You must always be the first
one to board the plane.
Look, we know what
you're going through.
A lot of us feel unloved after
something like this happens.
No, you don't understand.
My wife stays with me
solely out of obligation.
Orson! Could you say
such a thing?
It's true, isn't it?
You feel guilty because you know
I never would have been hit
by that plane
- If I hadn't gotten in a fistfight with your lover.
- This is the thanks I get? I have bent over backwards
To make your life easier.
I should just let you
hang yourself.
Hey... Don't we have
a basketball game at 2:00?
Can you be honest
for one moment?
- You don't love me.
- Yeah, we should go.
Please stay. I've made tea.
See? You can't deny it.
Go ahead, Bree. Correct me.
Say you love me.
I...
Care very deeply for you.
That's what I thought.
I'm feeling a little upset
right now.
Would you mind
rolling yourselves out?
Ana, let me ask you something.
Are you happy?
Why?
Well, Carlos and I want you
to be happy.
- Over the last few months, we've come to
thing of you as our own daughter. - Really?
In fact, your uncle
Thinks it's about time you
and I had that little talk...
About the birds
and the bees.
- Oh, God! - That's how I feel,
so we're not gonna be doing that.
Okay.
- Instead I'm going to write you a check.
- A check?
A check big enough to cover one
whole year of modeling school...
And to rent a decent-size apartment...
In New York.
Okay, what's the catch?
That's so cute that
you think there's a catch.
This isn't signed.
That's the catch.
I will sign it once you
graduate high school
Without having had sex
or more sex, as the case may be.
Are you serious?
Ana, I could talk
to you about morality
Or saving yourself
for marriage
Or statistics about S.T.D.s,
But I think
you're the kind of girl
Who responds
to cold, hard cash.
You know me well.
So do we hava deal?
Are you gonna be a successful
model with a nice apartment
Or a teenage mom
with no future?
Well...
When you put it
like that...
Good girl.
Oh, and to answer
your earlier question,
I'm now very happy.
I can't believe
I let you talk me into this.
Three hours of Shakespeare
- For a woman who has to pee
every 20 minutes. - Come on!
Dr. Graham's been
so supportive of us.
- Can't we be supportive of her?
- This isn't about support.
This is about
little Tommy teacher's pet
Wanting a gold star
for butt-kissing.
That's not true.
Nay, but this dotage...
Please.
You brought her a
40 dollar box of chocolates.
Last mother's day,
you threw me a bagel
And called it
breakfast in bed.
Admit it. You just have
a problem with her
Because you hate it when
someone points out your flaws.
That's not true.
I can take constructive
criticism justine.
You're being
a little loud.
Sorry.
See? I can take
constructive criticism.
- You're still talking.
- You're still annoying. Relax.
She's making her entrance.
Grates me... the sum.
Nay! Hear them, Antony!
Fluvia Perchance is angry.
Or... Who knows?
If the beard...
If the scarce-bearded Caesar
Hath not sent you
his powerful mandate...
"Do this or this.
Take in that kingdom
and enfranchise that.
Perform it".
"Or else we damn thee."
Hey. How was the play?
Lincoln had a better time
at the theater.
Really?
So how bad was it?
You remember how horrible your
second grade arbor day play was?
But at least we were
drunk for that.
Honestly, how did
Dr. Graham get that part?
Is she sleeping
with the director?
Sleeping with, bathing,
donating a kidney...
It's still not enough.
I just hope that I can erase
this from my memory
Before our next session.
Are you kidding?
We're not seeing her again.
- Why not? - We're not going
to continue to take life lessons
From a woman who burped
during her death scene.
That has nothing to do
with her skills as a therapist.
Really? Did she not tell you
she has a "gift" for acting?
- Yeah. - Well, I can't
trust the judgment
Of someone with
absolutely no self-awareness.
We're not going back.
This is an excuse.
You have been looking
For a reason to dump her
ever since our last session.
Tom, I learned
two things tonight...
Dr. Graham has no insight
into real human behavior,
And there are 428 tiles
on the ceiling of that theater.
Say what you want. We are
going to our next session.
And, by the way,
It was 429.
Robin Gallagher,
teaching assistant,
Reporting for duty.
- Hey, look at you!
- I wanted to look professional.
Do you like the glasses?
I don't even need them.
You look great.
That's a beautiful suit.
Thanks. It is so nice
to wear work clothes
That don't rip away
to reveal crotchless panties.
Yeah, you're preaching
to the choir.
So, um, I'm just gonna get
the kids started painting.
And why don't you hang those
globes that we made last week?
Okay.
Um, can I say something?
You really
took a chance on me.
No one's ever done
that for me before,
So thank you.
You're welcome.
I'm really glad you're here.
Oh, hey, careful.
Never let the kids
see you cry.
If they sense weakness,
you're done.
Sorry we're late.
- Forgot his backpack.
- Oh, that's okay, Mr. Linwood.
Come on, Kyle.
Let's get you painting.
Who's that?
That's my new teaching
assistant, Miss Gallagher.
No, Bobby. That's not
how we use pipe cleaners!
I'm sorry.
Do we know each other?
I don't think so.
Are you sure?
You look so familiar.
I guess I just have
one of those faces.
What did you want to see me
about, Principal Hobson?
You are aware, aren't you,
That as a private school,
We depend
on the financial support
Of our more affluent
parent donors?
I am aware of that.
Good.
Because I just got a call
from Kyle linwood's father,
A major donor.
Is it true that your assistant
can break a 5 dollars
By shaking out her underwear?
- I don't want to take a bath!
- Well, that's too bad.
It's time to give the earth
back some of its dirt.
Go!
Hey, I'm gonna be
upstairs for a bit.
What are you guys
up to tonight?
- We're just gonna stay home
and study. - Good girl.
Why are you getting me
all worked up?
I thought you made
your aunt a promise.
I promised her
I wouldn't have sex.
I didn't promise
you wouldn't.
Fine! I'll sort it myself!
Mr. Solis.
Okay, don't freak out, okay?
- What the hell are you doing? - Hey,
I'm sorry. This won't happen again.
- Uncle Carlos, it's no big deal. - You think
you can come into my house and do this?!
Answer me!
Answer me! Answer me!
I catch you near her again,
I will kick your ass, boy.
- Let go of him! - You know what I
caught your son doing in my house?
- I don't care.
- Carlos, what is going on?!
I said let go!
Oh, God!
Angie, what the hell?!
- Wait for me outside.
- Ma, please don't.
Outside!
Look, I came in and
found him on top of her.
I don't care. He's my kid.
You ever touch him again,
you're dead.
Hey, Bolen!
I see you tried to separate
my glass and plastic.
Suck it, earth!
Ma!
Come on, ma. Let's go.
So maybe you shouldn't
just think
About what you want to say
But about how you say it,
so Tom can hear you.
That's...
A theory.
Is something bothering
you, Lynette?
It's the pregnancy.
This morning
she got mad at me
Over the way I drank
my orange juice.
Is that all? You know
you're in a safe place here.
We can tell each other
anything.
Okay.
Since this is a safe place...
Tom and I saw your play
the other night.
You did? Well, why didn't you
come backstage and say hello?
Well, the truth is, I didn't
know what to say, because...
I didn't really like it.
I know.
Our antony was dreadful.
You weren't the only one
who thought so.
No... Actually,
I was talking about you.
You were...
Really not very good,
And now I've sort of
lost confidence
In you as a therapist.
Okay.
Do you want to elaborate?
No. I think I said
what I needed to say.
See, this is the same thing
in your marriage.
You criticize Tom,
but you won't be specific.
It's sort of
the coward's way out.
Coward?
Okay.
You sucked.
You were really, really bad.
Three words...
Stink, stank, stunk.
Specific enough?
Good for you, Lynette.
I commend you
for your honesty.
Although, the "fairview herald"
had a different take.
They found my Cleopatra
"incandescent."
Oh... My God!
You actually believe that?
See, this is why we
can't see her anymore.
Tom, you haven't
weighed in yet.
What did you think?
I thought you were great.
What? Liar! You said
you've seen seals playing horns
- That put on a better show. - There's no
need to bully him into agreeing with you.
I wouldn't have to bully him
if he would man up for once.
- Lynette, you're attacking. - Of course.
Because I'm always the bad cop,
He's always the good cop.
Could you just once
not be such a wuss?
Damn right I'm the good cop.
Someone has to be,
Because bad cop-bad cop
doesn't work.
I grew up in that house,
and it doesn't work.
That is not it.
You like me being the bad guy.
That way you c always be
the good guy. But guess what?
I'd love to be the good guy
once in a while, but I can't,
Because when things get hard
Or a difficult decision
has to get made,
You run from confrontation,
And if I don't step
into the void,
Things grind to a halt.
Because I got news for you...
Good cop-good cop
doesn't work either!
You're right.
Really?
I like to be liked,
And because of that,
A lot of the ugly stuff
I defer to you.
And I'm sorry.
Your performance was
aggressively bad.
At one point during
the second act, I started
To choke on a mint and thought
about not fighting it.
Thank you.
This was quite
a breakthrough.
And you're right.
You're a wonderful therapist.
Thank you, Lynette.
Now, both of you, get
the hell out of my office.
So we catch her son
on top of our niece,
- And we have to apologize?
- No, we have to apologize
Because you almost put
her son's head through a wall.
When are you gonna learn
violence is not the answer?
I shouldn't have to tell
you this! You know better!
We've been doing it for 19
years. You're smarter than this!
This is not the first time
we've had this conversation.
I feel like I'm talking
to a wall here, huh?
What is going on here?
What the hell is wrong
with you?!
Oh, God!
He's ripping Danny a new one.
- Damn it! Angie!
- Okay, Nick, just leave me alone!
No, no, no, no. Hey!
You are getting sloppy.
- We should go.
- Yeah, we should.
First you get into it
with that crazy lady
About her recycling,
which I told you not to do.
And then guess what?
She comes over this morning
- And says she's thinking about
suing us. - Okay, I lost my cool.
Well, get it back! Because
this rock we are hiding under
Is not that big, and if people
start poking around, we're done.
He fires her for something
she used to do.
It's so hypocritical.
I mean, why not get mad
at the kid's father?
He obviously goes
to Double D's.
I just hope I didn't get
you into any trouble, Mrs. D.
I feel awful.
No, no, no.
This is not your fault.
When I'm sad, my mom
gives me a big hug.
Down, tiger.
What am I gonna do?
I have no money for rent.
I'm just gonna
end up homeless.
You know, maybe I should go
and beg for my old job back.
No, no, no.
You can't do that.
Quitting that place
took a lot of guts.
How do you feel about
letting her move in here?
Julie's gone.
We have her empty room.
- It's just until she gets on her feet.
- You're asking if I'm okay
With letting a stripper
live with us?
- I'm gonna go with no.
- Why not?
- I have no idea. I'm just really sure this is a trick
question. - She's a nice girl, and she's in trouble.
You know, I think of myself
As a good person
who cares about others,
And how often do I actually
get to walk the walk?
This is an opportunity
to really help someone.
I want to do it.
Okay.
Okay, let's go make
ex-stripper
And a little boy very happy.
What's this for?
The Lackeys'
50th anniversary party.
Don't you remember?
I'm sorry. I thought
I'd be dead by now,
So I wasn't paying
much attention
To our social calendar.
Well, regardless,
you're going.
And if you're still around
next Saturday,
We've got brunch
with my family.
Well, now you're
just daring me.
Orson, Walter is about
to make a toast.
Don't you want to hear it?
A speech about the joys
of wedded bliss?
Pass.
Walter and Shirley
are about to dance
To a song that was played
at their wedding.
But before they do, walter would
like to say a few words.
I want to thank
you all for coming.
But 50 years... Would
it hardly seems possible.
And now I'm not gonna lie to you
And say it's always been easy.
I mean, we've had
our share of tragedy
And we've said a few things
we wish we could take back.
But for the most part,
we've been lucky,
Because no matter
how old we get,
We've always been able
to remember
What made us fall in love
in the first place, right, hon?
Orson!
Orson! Stop!
Don't you dare throw yourself
in that pool!
I want to die.
Why can't you let me?
Because I want this, too.
I want a party like this someday
toelebrate our life together.
What is there about
our life to celebrate?
Look at Walter and
Shirley in there.
I was watching them dance
with such passion in their eyes,
But I know they haven't
always been like that.
They've had their rough times,
too, but they stuck it out.
Because they're in love.
I asked you if you loved me,
and you couldn't answer.
Fine. I'll answer you now.
I loved you once.
Can I love you again?
I don't know.
But I would like to recapture
whatonce had.
And how can we do that
if you're not here?
So... I'm asking you...
Please stay.
In this never-ending
drama we call life,
Everyone has a part to play.
Some are cast
as romantic leads.
Others end up being the victim.
and a few always
provide comic relief.
And then there are
Those who end up
playing the hero...
Especially if they feel
there's a villain...
Who lives just
across the street.