Previously on Desperate Housewives...
Why didn't you tell me you
were having money problems?
Susan made a difficult decision.
- You can't sell your house.
- We're not selling. We're renting.
Bree was blackmailed by Sam.
I'm talking about your son
running down Carlos' mother.
I want you to sign
over your company to me.
Patrick got what he needed
to force Angie to do what he wanted.
You're gonna make me another bomb.
But Angie managed to send
out a call for help...
and Lynette discovered
that Eddie was the killer.
In those first awful moments,
all Lynette Scavo could
think of were her children.
She thought of the moment
her daughter began to walk...
And the day her son
won the spelling bee...
And that time her twins
scared her with a frog.
Yes, this is what Lynette thought about...
While a disturbed young
man was holding her hostage.
Eddie, please.
Don't talk to me, Mrs. Scavo.
- I really need to think.
- I know you must be scared.
But I am your friend,
Eddie. I want to help.
Look, what... what... what can you do?
You can't do anything.
I can tell people what a mean,
angry drunk your mother was,
how she abused you,
how defenseless you are.
- You almost didn't have a choice.
- And what about the others?
What others?
The other girls I killed.
Oh.
Still think you can help me? Look...
I don't want to hurt you.
Look, we'll drive till we're
in the middle of nowhere.
I'll drop you off, and by the time
- you find anyone to tell, I'll be gone.
- No.
Look, I don't know what else to do.
- I can't have you going to the police.
- I can't go anywhere.
Yes.
All Lynette could think
about were her children...
My water just broke.
Especially the child she
was about to give birth to.
corrected by chamallow
www.addic7ed.com
Teresa Pruitt used to be a nurse.
For 33 years, she worked
in the maternity ward
at Fairview Memorial Hospital.
She spent her days caring
for newborn infants...
and looking after brand-new mothers.
It was a job she had
loved with all her heart.
But that was many years ago.
Now Teresa Pruitt was back
at Fairview memorial...
But this time as a patient...
A patient with a secret.
Hello, Teresa. I came as soon as I could.
I'm so sorry.
Don't be.
It's my time.
You're very brave.
Hmm, I wish that were true, father.
Did you know I used to be
a nurse in this hospital?
Yes. You just retired
a few years ago, right?
I didn't retire. I quit out of guilt.
What do you mean?
I did something awful.
Do you want to take confession?
No. Confessions are private,
and the people who run this hospital
need to know what I did...
because they have to make it right.
Oh! Excuse me.
I need to see Nick
Bolen. What room is he in?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Visiting hours don't start until 9:00.
Okay, but this is an emergency.
Ma'am, he just came in out of a coma.
Unless you're immediate family,
you need to come back at 9:00.
Okay, I get it.
You're just following the rules.
You're a nurse... an underpaid,
underappreciated nurse
who might need some help making ends meet.
So what do you say to... $12?
Oh, wait. I'm gonna need $10 for parking.
Ma'am.
How about gum? Do you like gum?
Come back later.
Hey, Lorna, Dr. Burke
needs you in radiology.
Thanks.
Hey! You with the ponytail.
- I gotta see Nick Bolen.
- Are you family?
Forget about it. I'm his wife Angie.
Really? Well, then who's that
blonde lady who's been here?
His whore?! She was here?
Oh, I'm having her whacked!
Oh, no! I could be wrong.
Maybe I should get my supervisor.
Do I look like I got time for supervisors?
I got sauce on the stove, ziti in the oven
and a mustache that needs
to get bleached. Let's go!
Come on! Let's go!
Thank you.
W... wow.
Did we... did we get
hammered last night or what?
No, you got hammered.
Preston and I just followed you
around apologizing to everyone.
Mm, another thing we
won't be telling your mom.
Hey, do you think I woke
her up when I came in?
- When you came in?
- Yeah.
No. When you jumped up on the coffee table
and sang "margaritaville"? Maybe.
Guys. I just checked on
mom, and she's not there,
and the bed looks like
it hasn't been slept in.
Oh, God. She did hear me.
Oh, she must have stormed
out of here first thing.
But why didn't she wake
you up and yell at you?
Have I been stabbed?
You're back. What happened with Sam?
And did you tell him his
services were no longer needed?
I tried to. He responded
by blackmailing me.
What?
He knows what happened to Mrs.Solis.
Gaby. What does she have to do with this?
I'm talking about Carlos' mother.
What happened to Carlos' mother?
Ten years ago, she died
after being hit by a car
that Andrew was driving.
Oh, my God.
- How did he find out?
- Danielle told him.
- What? Why?
- I don't know.
I think it was some idiotic
attempt to bond with him.
Wait a minute.
You never told Carlos and Gaby?
Of course not. That would
have destroyed the friendship,
not to mention Carlos would
have sent Andrew to jail.
So what does Sam want?
My company, and I'm
going to give it to him.
- Are you crazy?
- If I don't, he'll go to the police.
- Let him.
- Andrew!
Mom, I'm not letting you give
up everything you've worked for
just 'cause that psycho thinks
he has something over on us.
They will send you to prison.
- Well, maybe it's time I paid for what I've done.
- Absolutely not.
Bree, you can't give in to
blackmail. It's not right.
And if Andrew wants to
take responsibility...
Orson, this is really
just between me and my son.
Would you mind?
Of course not.
What's going on?
Why am I wet?
Beats me. I'm not a doctor.
Gaby, what are you doing here?
Angie's in trouble. Look,
she wrote me this note.
"Danny and I held hostage. No cops. Get Nick."
I don't understand.
There was a guy with her.
He said he was her brother.
She doesn't have a brother.
Is it Patrick Logan?
You know about Patrick?
She told me everything.
Whoa, whoa, what are you doing?
I gotta get him outta there.
Wait. Are you crazy? In your condition?
Why can't we just call the cops?
Because the second Patrick feels cornered,
Angie and Danny are dead.
Oh, my God.
Are you gonna be all right?
No. You're gonna have to drive me
- to help me get him outta there.
- Okay.
I know. I'm sorry. I'm putting
you in a dangerous position.
Forget about it.
So you're done?
Yes.
When you push the detonator,
you got 30 seconds till it blows.
You got what you wanted.
You gonna let us go now?
Not yet. You're coming with me to Oregon.
You didn't say anything about that.
Ange...
What if the bomb's a dud?
I mean, you did run off with
another man and take my son.
I've got some trust issues.
Will you at least let Danny go?
No. See, if the bomb doesn't go off,
I'll put a bullet in your head
and then come back and kill him.
So...
You sure you're done?
I guess I could take another look.
My grandson's visiting. He'll love this.
How about we give you 100 bucks?
Look at the price tag. 50 cents.
Please, Susan. Let us help you.
I don't need my arthritis
medication this month.
Look, I can almost make a fist.
Thank you, but we're not looking
for a handout. Just a hand.
Hey, I just got off the phone with Lee.
- He thinks he might have found a renter.
- Already?
Well, that's a good thing, isn't it?
Yeah, yeah. It's great.
Stranger living in my house... yippee!
Hey, Susan, how much
for this dining room set?
I paid $1,200 a year ago.
You can have it for $300.
I'll give you 50 bucks.
I thought you weren't looking
for a handout, just a hand.
That's not a hand. That's a finger.
Susan, I'm not neighbor Kinsky
right now. I'm business Kinsky.
So I'm gonna be Frank.
You don't have a pot
to pee-pee in right now,
and our neighborhood knows
it. What's it gonna be?
Jeez, Kinsky. Have a heart.
The woman needs the money.
Oh, keep out of it, McCluskey.
You know the yard sale game.
If you lost the stomach for it, walk away.
No, Mitzi. You walk away.
Excuse me?
You're nothing but a vulture.
I want you off my property.
Hey, lookie here.
I'm on a public sidewalk.
Now what you gonna do?
Mitzi, I am not "neighbor" Delfino.
I am "woman who's about
to move into an apartment
behind a gas station" Delfino,
and if you don't get out of my face,
I am gonna ram this thigh
master down your throat.
Fine. $300.
Sold.
I found some aspirin. Will that help?
This isn't a headache.
These are contractions.
I need you to take me to a hospital.
No, I can't, you'll tell someone about me.
Eddie, I swear to God. I
don't care about you right now.
All I care about is this baby. Please.
Porter, I found her. She's at Eddie's.
If I'm not back in 15 minutes,
it means she did not accept my apology,
and it was fun being your dad.
Okay. I'm trusting you here.
Thank you. You have my word.
Eddie! It's Tom!
I need to talk to her again.
Quiet.
Honey! I can see your car.
I know you're in there.
Lynette!
Okay, I get it.
You're giving me the silent treatment.
Well, when you cool off,
I will be home
with a gigantic bouquet
of your favorite flowers.
I'm sorry.
I had to do that.
I'll take you to the hospital now.
It's too late. It's too
late. This baby is coming now.
And you have to help me deliver it.
Mr. Chase, you got a minute?
Oh, sure, father. Come on in.
I just came from Teresa Pruitt's bedside.
She passed.
I'm sorry to hear that. I,
uh, I remember her fondly.
She was one of my best nurses.
Before she died, she told me something...
An awful secret that she'd
been living with for years.
Uh, father, I'm, uh, I'm
not trying to tell you
how to do your business,
but aren't those things
supposed to be confidential?
She wanted you to hear this,
but I think you should sit down first.
Hey, lady, unless you want
to be carried into the truck,
you need to get off that chair.
I see. Like you're the mover. Funny.
Have you seen T-Rex?
The dinosaur? Well, check in the boxes.
No, honey. We sold it to Roy.
No!
Yeah. You put it in the "sell" pile.
What's a "sell" pile?
Uh-oh.
I want my t-Rex.
Well, buddy, I'm sorry. We sold it,
- so there's no way we can...
- We're getting it back.
- What are you doing?
- Loving my child.
Thank you, mommy.
Susan, I don't think you
should have promised him that.
Roy bought it for his grandson.
It's bad enough that we are dragging him
from the only home he has ever lived in,
moving across town where he
doesn't know a single soul.
If that silly dinosaur
brings him a moment's comfort,
then we need to March over
there and take it back.
What the hell? We're moving.
Let's go piss off some neighbors.
And somehow the dinosaur
got into the pile,
and now M.J. is begging us to get it back.
Sorry for the confusion, Roy.
No, I get it. It's just...
I already gave it to my grandson.
Aw, I remember when we gave it to M.J...
Right after his puppy died.
Okay, okay.
Let's go get it before
you take out your violin.
I guess the excitement
of getting a new friend
wore him out.
- I'll wake him up.
- Oh, you don't have to do that.
Why don't you just
slip it out of his arms?
- And we'll leave a note.
- A note?
And cash. Mike, give the man some cash.
No, we're not taking money.
He's got tons of other toys.
He'll be fine.
Oh, God, he's deaf.
Shouldn't we stop this?
Just let it play out.
There you go.
You are now the sole owner
of Mrs. Van De Kamp's old fashioned foods.
Of course, my lawyers
will have to approve this.
Of course, and you'll
see there's a codicil.
If you breathe one word
of Andrew's involvement in that incident,
you'll be forced to pay
me all sorts of money.
Don't worry. I'm much
better at keeping secrets
than your daughter.
One can only hope.
I didn't want it to be this way.
And I understand if you need to hate me.
I don't hate you, Sam.
I feel sorry for you.
You came into my life
hoping to be a part of my family,
and all you're leaving with
is a client list, some
mixing bowls and my name.
Well, you'll soon see that's not enough.
You'll always have a hole in your heart
because you don't really
care about anybody,
and I have a horrible feeling
that no one will ever
really care about you.
Now would you please be a dear
and close the door on
your way out of my life?
So I'm gonna put the bomb in the trunk,
and that's how long you have
to say good-bye to our son.
♪♪♪
you can't go with him. He's
never gonna let you come back.
I don't know how this is gonna play out,
but whatever happens, you gotta know,
that I was out of choices.
Okay, Angie. Car's loaded.
Come on.
We got a bomb to explode.
Okay, okay. I gotta push again.
No, you have to look.
- But it's so gross!
- I don't care. You're going to to have to catch her. Go.
I see something! I think it's the head!
Aah!
Wait. There's something around her neck!
What?
I think it's the umbilical cord.
No! No!
She's turning blue.
Okay. Okay. Um...
Listen to me.
You have to... Hook the umbilical cord
with your finger and
pull it over her head.
- No, I can't.
- You have to!
No, Mrs. Scavo, I'm serious!
Listen to me.
You have the chance to save... a life.
Please!
Okay.
Oh, oh, is it done?
Yeah. I got her.
Yes! Yes! Yes.
She's okay?
Oh!
Ahh!
Thank you.
I know.
Where is he?
I'm sorry, sweetie. T-Rex is extinct.
Yeah, buddy. I'm sorry we
couldn't get him back for ya.
But he's mine. That's not fair.
M.J...
That's life. Life isn't always fair.
Sometimes you can be a good person
and you can do the right thing,
and life still won't give
you your dinosaur back.
In other words,
we're gonna take you to pizza world,
and you can play all
the video games you want.
Okay.
Susan, life didn't take your dinosaur.
I did.
So please, just let me have it.
Okay. Yeah.
I resent you.
I love you, I respect
you, but you know what?
I mean, you blew it! And thanks to you,
I have to leave the home where
I raised my children. Look.
Look, this... this is how tall Julie was
when she started kindergarten.
And... and this is her in junior high.
And this is M.J.
The day we brought him home from
the hospital and stood him up.
And this... this is where
I thought he'd get to.
Here.
In this house...
And now I'm never gonna
know, and it's all your fault.
There it is.
Hey.
We're gonna get it back.
I promise.
And in the meantime...
Well... that's done.
It's Sam's company now.
So you did it.
You actually gave up a business
you spent eight years building.
What other choice did I have?
I can always start a new company.
What I cannot do is send my son to jail.
You sent me to jail.
You insisted I turn myself in.
You said it was the only
way you'd take me back.
That was a completely different situation.
Really?
I ran over Mike and told no one.
Andrew ran over Carlos'
mother and told no one.
How is that different?
Andrew was a child at the time.
He's not anymore.
Orson, please.
I don't mean to upset you.
I'm just curious why
you're not demanding Andrew
do the same thing as well.
Fine. I was wrong.
I never should have asked
you to make that sacrifice.
I don't want an apology.
I respected you for
demanding better of me.
You showed me you had
principles and ideals.
You insisted I live up to your standards,
and I loved you for it.
What are you saying?
From the moment you told
me what Andrew had done
and what Sam was threatening
to do, I saw this as a test,
and I hoped worth all my
heart that you would pass it,
but you have failed miserably.
Where are you going?
Pack my suitcase. I'm leaving.
What?
You are not the woman I thought you were.
For God sakes, Orson.
He's my son. I have no choice.
We always have a choice,
and I no longer choose to be your husband.
All right, I'm gonna go around back,
see if I can climb in a window.
You think you can keep Patrick
occupied for ten minutes?
Honey, you're talking to a woman
who never paid for a
drink in her life. Please.
Oh, man.
You okay?
Yeah. Just a little light-headed.
Just give me a second.
By the way, thank you.
I can't believe you're
helping us out like this.
I don't know. I guess it's...
I guess it's because I know what it's like
to have secrets, too.
It's a lonely feeling.
And that night on the plane
when Angie told me hers,
I promised I would help her...
Whatever it takes.
Nick? Nick.
Oh, my God. Don't pass out.
Nick!
Come on! I can't do this alone.
She's so small.
Not for long. They grow up so quickly.
I wish I could see her grow up.
So... I'm gonna go now.
If you could just...
Wait a while before you call the police.
Wait.
That day you left my house,
you told me your life would
have turned out different
if I had been your mom.
So I'm gonna be your mom... now.
Will you listen to me?
I don't think you should leave.
I think you should stay
here and call the police.
I can't.
Yes, you can.
I don't want to spend the
rest of my life in jail.
Honey... don't you see
you're already there?
No matter where you run to, in your head,
you will still be angry.
You'll still be in pain.
And as long as you want
to keep hurting people,
you will never be free.
I'll be good. I swear.
But people will never see that you're good
unless you show them.
Please, if you pick up
the phone, they will know.
And I will be so proud of you.
Will you call them for me?
Of course.
Why don't you hold the baby?
Hello. Fairview hospital?
I need to know how to
bring someone out of a coma.
I'm not sure if it's a coma.
Somewhere between a coma and a nap.
How should I know if he's clammy?
I left him in the car.
Gaby?
Hey, Susan, what's up?
- Just came to say good-bye.
- Okay. All right. See ya.
Oh, no. I mean, this is it.
Tomorrow's moving day,
and it's gonna be crazy,
so I didn't want to rush
through our good-byes.
Oh, good for you. I'll
catch ya when I catch ya.
Hello? Hello? Damn it!
Oh! Susan! Uh...
I'm sorry. I'm just so
choked up about you leaving.
- I just couldn't deal with it.
- Oh!
Really?
You know who else is
gonna be devastated? Angie.
Angie Bolen?
Yes. She's totally broken up about this.
You've gotta say good-bye.
Seriously? I...I mean,
I like her and everything.
I just... we've had our problems.
Oh, just neighbor stuff.
Well, I tried to crush
her son with his car.
One of her favorite stories.
And then she attacked me with a bat.
She's Italian. That's love. Now come on.
You know, Angie once told me
that a good-bye doesn't mean anything
if it doesn't last ten minutes.
Really? I don't think
Angie and I have ever had
a conversation that lasted more than...
Gaby?
Okay. Uh...
It's getting late. Let's go.
Yeah, these aren't
gonna draw any attention.
Not as much as a bullet in
the head if you try to run.
It's my neighbor, Susan.
Someone really needs to thin this herd.
Get rid of her.
Susan. What's going on?
Uh... tomorrow's moving day.
I just came to say good-bye.
Okay... bye.
Don't you want my new address?
Relax, Ange. This will be
over before you know it.
It's okay, Danny.
I'm gonna get you out of here.
Oh!
Why are we stopping?
What's the range on this
thing? About 200 yards?
Yeah. Why?
Patrick, what are you doing?
When I woke up that morning 20 years ago,
and you were gone,
I was devastated.
I tried to forgive you, but I couldn't.
After all, you didn't just betray me.
You betrayed everything we believed in.
So I decided one day
I would find you...
And I would punish you.
And today is that day, my love.
Where's the bomb?
There's 30 seconds from the
time I push this detonator
till the explosion...
That's what you said, right?
- Tell me where the bomb is now!
- It's in your house.
And if you want to save our son,
I suggest you get moving.
- Come on. Hurry. I gotta help my mom.
- I'm trying!
Okay.
It's in the detonator.
You bitch.
Mom?
Oh, Gaby. We can't take
this. This is too much.
I insist.
Although I am gonna need $10 for parking.
So... this is good-bye.
Forever, right?
I mean, that's how this works?
Yeah.
You know what's funny?
Nick had to drag me here
kicking and screaming.
He told me it would be
a good place to blend in
because people wave at you
from behind their little picket fences,
but they would never get
involved. They don't care.
Well, thank God you proved him wrong.
Take care.
So we better hurry. Bus
is leaving in five minutes.
Yeah. We should give him his ticket.
This is a ticket to New York.
I thought the plan was to go to Atlanta.
That's our plan.
- No way.
- Listen to me.
I want to be with you guys.
And we wanna be with you,
but we have to stop being selfish.
She's right. It's time
we let you live your life.
You're gonna have so much fun in New York.
You get to be with Ana.
You can see grandma.
And you can finally stop running.
But I'll still get to see you
guys every once in a while.
Right? I mean, Patrick's dead.
The FBI is still looking for us.
I don't think I can do
this. I'm not ready for...
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
You are gonna be fine, okay?
Because you...
You have turned into one hell of a man.
Yeah.
If I am...
it's 'cause you were my father.
Mom?
Why is all of Orson's stuff gone?
He left me.
What? Why?
He feels I'm a hypocrite.
That's ridiculous.
No. He's right. I am.
Is there anything I can do?
There is.
You can give me your
permission to do something
I should have done a long time ago.
This is bad.
What if we don't say anything?
The nurse is dead. Nobody else knows.
The priest knows.
I don't suppose we could buy him off.
Just a suggestion.
If this leads to a
lawsuit, we have no defense.
This could ruin the hospital.
Jack, what's wrong?
I know one of these families.
They live two blocks
from me on Wisteria Lane.
Then maybe you're the
best person to tell them.
And how do I do that?
How do you tell parents the
child they've been raising...
The child they love...
isn't really theirs?
- Hey there. What's going on?
- Susan trying to sneak off without saying good-bye.
The more I thought about it,
the more I realized it's not a big deal.
I'm just moving across town.
I'm gonna see you all Friday for poker.
You better, 'cause if we don't
hear from you once a week,
- we will hunt you down and bring
you back. You know that, right?
- I do.
So who's renting your house?
Lee found a guy.
It's just not gonna seem right,
someone else in your house.
Yeah. Well, whoever the guy is,
he is very lucky, 'cause
he's about to get himself
three of the most wonderful neighbors
a person could ask for.
You know, sometimes when
you see people every day,
you forget to tell them
how much they mean to you
so for the record...
I think the three of
you are such good people.
And you've made me a better person,
and I thank you for that.
Hey, Susan, I hate to interrupt,
but we really gotta get going.
I should go check on Tom and the baby.
- I'm sure one or both will need to be fed.
- Go, go.
- I'll call you all in the morning.
- Okay.
Honey, what's wrong?
What Susan said...
It's not true. I'm not a good person.
Oh, that's silly. Of course you are.
No, I'm not. There's
something I need to tell you
I should have told you
years ago but I didn't.
You sound so serious. What is it?
It's the kind of thing that
could end our friendship.
Can we go talk?
Well... you ready?
Yeah.
Drive away slow, okay?
As they pulled away,
Susan looked out on the
street she loved so much...
A street where parents
could raise their children...
Where retirees could
enjoy their golden years...
Where good friends
could share horrible secrets...
Yes, Susan looked on this street
and vowed she would be back...
But as she did so,
she didn't notice the
car that passed her...
A car carrying Wisteria Lane's...
Newest resident.
So I have some paperwork
for you to sign over here,
and once we get this done,
I can give you the keys.
And I just know you're
really gonna like it here.
People are friendly, relatively quiet.
It's just... it's just
a lovely neighborhood.
Oh, I know the neighborhood very well.
The truth is, I used to live here.
Oh, well, then I guess everyone
will be surprised to see you again.
They absolutely will.