Previously on Desperate Housewives
Gaby learned a secret
Lee and I are trying to adopt a baby.
Mike made a commitment
but I can be a guy who
takes care of his family.
Lynette was warned.
I told Preston I want to
move up wedding to next week,
Next week?
A killer put everyone on edge
Can't believe she is dead
I gotta go home, My
mom was so freaked out.
It could be minished, if
she wants me to be around
So you're my brother?
Half-brother, to be precise.
Suspicioun was born
And what do we really know about Sam?
... should be to find
out everything I can.
Why shouldn't you? He's your brother.
And a very dangerous man
arrived on Wisteria lane.
Good neighbors--
They loan you cups of sugar...
They tell you why
your car won't start...
They even help you find your lost pets.
Good neighbors also come over
At the slightest hint of trouble...
Whether you want 'em there or not.
...being unreasonable! You know what?
I'm tired of fighting about this.
Okay, fine. Walk away.
It's what you always do.
Gaby, what are you doing?
I came to return this
magazine Lee lent me,
But you two were arguing, so...
So you decided it would
be fun to eavesdrop?
God, it's like you see into my soul,
And yet you don't judge. Thank you.
Oh, come on. Tell me what happened.
Our egg donor backed out.
Not again.
And the surrogate we hired will pull out
If the procedure isn't
done in the next month.
Well, can't you find another egg donor?
We could, if Lee wasn't so picky.
Why are you discussing this with her?
For God sakes, I was
eavesdropping. Catch up.
Okay, yeah, I'm picky.
We spent two years choosing a mattress.
I'm not just going to
get our child's d.N.A.
Out of the yellow pages.
If we lose the surrogate,
It could take months
to find another one.
Yeah, and then she'll drop
out for some ridiculous reason,
And I can't take any more of this!
You know, maybe we're not
supposed to be parents.
Don't talk like that!
Come on! Doesn't it seem like
The universe is trying to tell
us something? Why not take mine?
Take your what? My eggs.
I mean, I've got plenty,
And I hate to see you guys so unhappy.
So what the heck?
Good neighbors--they're
people who try to help others.
Bad neighbors are
people who make promises
They can't possibly keep.
The morning paper said
a young girl was missing.
It quoted her family,
Who said she had vanished
on her way to work.
It quoted her friends,
Who said she wasn't the
type to run away from home.
It quoted the police,
Who said they had very
little evidence to go on.
Sadly, people didn't pay much
attention to this bit of news.
No one thinks about evil
Until it shows up on their doorstep,
Which it soon would.
Oh, my God. Thief!
Hey! You!
Freeze! Whoa! Whoa!
Lady, put that thing down.
Oh, yeah? While I'm at it, why
don't I just hand you the keys?
Now hit the dirt! Relax.
I'm not stealing anything.
This is a repossession.
Do I look stupid to you? Fire! Fire!
What the hell are you doing?
People come quicker
when you yell "Fire."
Now I believe I told
you to hit the dirt!
Where's the fire?
Susan, you okay?
I'm fine. Just
call 9-1-1!
Hey, what's going on? This thief
is trying to steal your truck!
Hey. You're the guy who's four
months behind on his payments?
Yeah.
Stop, drop and roll!
Whoblems?
I was hoping business would
pick up before anybody found out.
But I guess that's no longer an option.
Mike, we talked about this.
I told you, I am willing to help.
And I told you, I'm not
taking my wife's money.
Well, enough with the macho pride.
I make a steady paycheck,
And I have all that money
from selling Karl's strip club.
No. I'm definitely not taking
your ex-husband's money.
Are we done here? Sure.
As long as you can explain
How you're going to
run a plumbing business
Without a truck.
I don't know. I'll figure it out.
And for the cover of the book,
I see you in an evening gown,
Sitting on a bale of hay,
ringing a dinner bell.
I love it. Such a sense of whimsy.
Well, if it isn't the dynamic duo.
How did your meeting
with the publisher go?
Fantastic.
Bruce loved the idea of a
nouvelle Southern cookbook.
And your brother came up
With the marketing slogan
in the room. Tell him, Sam.
"Mrs. Van De Kamp
Introduces you to upscale
down-home cuisine."
Catchy. I-I guess you
know all about marketing,
Having an mba and all.
I guess so.
Except, of course, you
don't actually have an mba.
What are you talking about?
I made a few calls,
checked a few records.
Turns out the golden
child never got his degree.
Is this true?
Yes. I'm a few classes short.
Is one of them ethics?
Andrew, please.
I don't understand.
It was the final semester.
We were about two months in
When the doctor told me
my mother was terminal.
I left school and brought her home
So she didn't have to
die in the hospital.
If you like,
I can save you a phone call
And bring in her death certificate.
That's okay.
The university let me
graduate with my class.
I should finish my
coursework next month.
But I'm sorry, Bree.
I should not have misrepresented myself.
Everyone steps over
the line now and then.
Let's all make an effort not to,
Shall we?
This woman is incompetent.
Why you bring me here?
Hey, you're the one who had to
come to a Russian bridal shop.
It was mistake.
Well... Look at the fun you're having
Chewing people out
in your native tongue.
Hey.
Sorry for the way she's
been talking to you.
Don't worry. You're not losing a son.
You are gaining a pain in the ass.
Tell me about it.
My son is marrying a
woman he barely knows.
He's making the biggest
mistake of his life,
And I am powerless to stop him.
If you like,
Maybe I get a little
sloppy with the pushpins.
Aw, you're sweet.
Irina? It's your phone.
If it's Preston, tell
him I be home soon.
Okay, your highness.
Bride's phone.
Irina...
Okay. Slow down. I...
I don't speak Russian.
Irina, it's some Russian guy,
and he doesn't sound happy.
Alexei...
Who was that?
Wrong number.
Wrong number? He asked for you by name.
If I wanted you to know,
I would say it in English.
Missus?
I can say it in English.
Hey. Double cappuccino, extra hot.
Need anything else?
Inspiration.
Sorry. We just have muffins.
What are you working on?
A novel.
I know--another guy in a
coffee shop writing a novel.
Just what the world needs.
No, I think it's cool. Mind
if I ask what it's about?
You really wanna know?
I do.
It started out as a love story,
But it's getting kind of dark.
This guy meets this girl,
Takes her from nothing,
Gives her life meaning.
Basically creates her.
Okay.
Then one day,
She just disappears...
Vanishes...
With another man.
Sucks for the guy.
And she takes his baby.
Damn. Well, she sounds like a bitch.
Sure does.
Anyhow, I'm up to the point
Where the guy who's been
looking for her for a long time
Finally tracks her down.
And that's where I'm kind of stuck.
What does he do?
Well, I don't know all the details,
But you said it was dark, right?
Yeah.
Seems to me the guy would kill her.
Funny. That was exactly
my first instinct, too.
No.
No? You asked my permission to
be an egg donor, and I said "No."
Oh, I wasn't asking
you. I was telling you.
Sorry. You can't do
this without my approval.
Those eggs are half mine.
How so? I'm your husband.
I own 50% of whatever
comes out of that uterus.
Oh! So you think you own my body.
I pay for the clothes it wears,
The massages it receives
And the implants it
will one day require.
If I don't own it, I'm at
least a major stockholder.
Which means I can stop you
From handing out your
eggs like party favors
To every childless gay
couple that wanders by.
You cannot stop me. I can do
whatever I want with my eggs.
And I can do whatever I want
with the credit cards I pay for.
For example, I can cut them up.
I don't care about credit cards.
I am trying to do something Noble here.
I'm helping these
people become a family.
You've hidden the cards, haven't you?
Damn straight.
Okay, I am begging you,
As your husband,
Please don't do this.
It'll be too weird having
your d.N.A. Living next door.
I don't care. My mind is made up.
I am going to help
Bob and Lee have a baby
So they can experience
the same love and joy
That we occasionally
have with our children.
So the Russian salesgirl
translated for me,
And you'll never guess
what irina said to the...
Angry guy on the phone.
Please don't make me guess.
She said, "Go ahead
and call the police."
You'll never find me."
And that's it?
How much more do you need?
She is a foreigner. She's
done something criminal.
Start your deportation now.
Ma'am, without proof
of criminal activity,
There's nothing I can do.
Can't you at least... Interrogate her?
Yes, and... If you wanna
slap her around a bit,
You'll get no complaints from me.
Look, Mrs. Scavo, we
are a government agency.
We can't investigate your
future daughter-in-law
Just because you don't think
she's good for your son.
Ah. It all makes sense now.
You're single, right?
Never had any kids?
Yeah. So?
You just don't get it.
Hi. Nice-looking family. Is
that your daughter-in-law?
Yeah.
You two get along?
Don't get me started.
Got a minute?
M.J., what are you
doin'? Clogging the sink.
What?
Daddy needs work.
Honey, that's sweet,
but daddy only gets paid
When other people
have plumbing problems.
So I should do this to
somebody else's sink?
No, honey.
That would be wrong.
Hi. I'm having a problem
with Mike and his male ego.
Long story short--
can I clog your drain?
So don't phone Mike until I get home.
Ugh. Okay, and when you
call him, sound desperate.
That way, he'll feel useful.
But don't call till Saturday.
He gets double time on weekends.
There's enough there for a tip,
But careful when you give it to him.
I don't want him thinking
anyone's doing him a favor.
Trust me, Bruce. After
they taste these recipes,
They will be onboard.
Just give me the chance to dazzle them.
Okay. Bye.
Problems?
Bruce got a little resistance
when he met with the sales team.
They fear Southern
cookbooks are a tad overdone.
So I suggested we have a little dinner
To let them sample the
recipes themselves. Excellent.
We have to really impress them.
Let's see if we can book
the private dining room
At the britannian hotel.
I'll take care of it.
But before I do, I have
something... Difficult to say.
Well, I hope it's not about
that silly mba business.
I think I know why Andrew
tried to discredit me yesterday.
He knew you had me auditing the books,
And he knew what I was gonna find.
What did you find?
Did you charge the donellys
for five cases of vodka?
Yeah. So?
According to our invoices,
Only four were delivered to their party.
And the rotary club luncheon was
charged for seven cases of wine,
And only six showed up. Why are
you even looking at this stuff?
And I seem to recall your
having a party that same weekend,
With lots of wine and lots of vodka.
Okay, yeah, I-I took some
leftover booze to my house
For a party. What's the big deal?
It wasn't leftover. You charged
the client for that liquor.
That's stealing. Is Sam the
one who told you about this?
We are not talking about Sam
right now. But we need to.
Can't you see the type of person he is?
Yes, he is the type of
person who leaves college
To care for his dying mother.
You are the type of person
who steals from clients.
Believe what you wanna believe,
But I'm not gonna listen to this.
Andrew.
Don't you walk away from me!
Can't you see how he's manipulating you?
How stupid can you be?
Apparently I'm stupid
enough to have trusted you.
Well, if I'm the problem,
why not just fire me?
I'm tempted. Don't push me.
Clear your things out
and turn in your keys.
Oh, hey, Tom.
Did irina and Preston say when
they'd be back from the mall?
Stop!
Stop what?
Not you. I'm teaching Parker to drive.
Okay. I'm planning to steal
irina's passport number.
Oh, God. What are you up to now?
I have a new best friend at immigration
Who's got a friend
at the Russian embassy
Who's agreed to initiate
a background search.
Lynette, this is getting out of hand.
That woman is hiding something,
and I am taking her down.
Da!
You buy me beautiful things,
and now I thank you. Ahh!
Come on.
We shouldn't be in here
with the door closed.
My mom gets a little freaked
out. Well, your mother is a prude.
That is what happens to
women when they grow old.
Now kiss me. Mmm.
Mmm! Oh, my God.
Who's that?
Your mom.
"Get home now.
"Trapped behind the closet door.
Preston and irina
are about to--"
Pull over. I gotta get home fast.
I can go fast.
Seriously, irina, my mom's in the house.
I know. Is what make it fun.
Honey maple short ribs
drizzled with manzanilla Sherry.
These are amazing.
Bruce's sales team will
be powerless to resist.
Well, you are really
focused on this dinner,
Which is amazing
considering what happened.
I mean... Firing your own son.
I've done worse things to Andrew.
We have a... Very
complicated relationship.
You'll see that the longer
you're at the company.
How? You fired him.
No, that's just our pattern.
He provokes me, and I push him away,
But we always come back together.
So... You're going to bring him back in?
Eventually.
But the stealing...
And the way he spoke to you, I...
Sam, he's my son.
Hey. Busy day, huh?
Yeah, busy week.
It's so funny.
I've had all this work
right here on the lane.
Well, that's good, right?
Especially since you
don't have your truck.
Uh-huh. Hey.
Guess what I found?
Oh! My earring.
Been looking all over for
that. Where'd you find it?
Gaby's bathtub drain.
Oh.
Ohh, of course.
Gaby and I went jogging, and, uh...
So my earring probably
got caught in--in her...
Sports bra, and when
she went to take a bath--
Hey, do you, uh, wanna have sex?
So Gaby's drain,
Angie's garbage disposal,
Lynette's
toilet--
I mean, the really dirty sex.
So now I have to return all that money.
No, you don't.
I...
Gave it to them.
You're saying everyone
on the street knows
I'm having financial trouble?
Well... I think they
already figured that out
When they saw your truck get repossessed
Out of our driveway.
This is humiliating, Susan.
I'm sorry, but it all
could've been prevented
If you'd just let me make a few
stupid payments on your truck.
I told you, I don't want your help.
This is my business, my problem.
You know, I don't
remember all those "Mys"
In our wedding vows.
It's supposed to be a partnership.
If you can't let me help you,
Maybe there's something
wrong with our marriage.
I'm not gonna listen to
this, all right? I'm tired.
I had a busy day wasting my time.
I'll sleep on the couch.
Danny?
You up there?
Hello?
Oh, jeez, Nick, you scared me.
Nothing. I just--
I just got home,
And I-I thought I heard a
noise. It--no, it's fine.
Just hurry home, okay?
To Gabrielle solis, the best neighbor
Two childless, upwardly mobile
gay guys could ever have. Mm.
Aw.
I got it. Hey!
No, no, no. That was purely ceremonial.
We don't want you drinking.
Why? Does it affect my fertility?
That, and you're kind of a sloppy drunk.
Fine. Let's talk babies.
So... What are you guys
hoping for--a boy or a girl?
I want a girl.
That way, we can put her
in baby beauty pageants.
Yeah, they're so cute in
their makeup and
rhinestone dresses. Right?
Really? You guys gonna do that?
Why not? Well, it's just I
kind of dabbled in that world,
And for me, it was a bit much.
Well, don't panic.
50% chance it's a boy.
Then it's makeup and
rhinestone vests. What?!
He's kidding.
Oh! He better be. There's
no way I'm allowing that.
Mm, now that I think about it,
I do hope we have a boy.
And why is that?
I already have two girls.
I'm so sick of buying dresses.
When he's old enough,
I'm gonna take him on the
biggest shopping spree ever.
Right.
I guess you can do that
when we come back to visit.
Visit? Where are you going? My
mother lives in upstate New York.
We thought we'd move closer to her
So the baby can be around family.
Really?
Is that a problem?
It just never occurred to me
That you guys would leave
and take my only son.
Gaby...
This child-- it'll
have your genes,
But it won't be yours.
You get that, right?
Of course.
I mean, it's the only
way it can work, right?
Come on. You ready?
Okay, no peeking.
You gonna beat me again this time?
Hey, guys.
What?
Mommy, why do you look so sad?
Well, I was just thinking
about what it would be like
If I couldn't see your face every day...
and it made me sad.
What's going on?
Come out of the kitchen.
I want you to spend some
time with these people.
Mingle. Have a drink.
I don't drink, Bruce. I'm
an alcoholic. One drink.
I'm not asking you to
swing from the chandelier.
Why are you so nervous?
I really put my neck on the
line for this book, Bree.
No one likes the idea. No one.
Oh, I should've stopped
at just one drink.
Look, they are gonna love the food.
I hope so,
Because if they don't, I don't see
How you're going to publish
another book of any kind.
Here you are.
Just put 'em on a little
plate. Yeah, that'll be fine.
Hop to, people. This is a big one.
Something wrong? What's this?
It's the Sherry we drizzle on the ribs.
This isn't Sherry. This is vinegar.
Vinegar?
Oh, my God.
It's ruined.
They're all ruined. It's disgusting!
The floor's not looking so great either.
Stop! We can't serve this food.
We've already taken
out most of the plates.
Well, don't just stand
there. Go get them back.
How can it be vinegar?
We tested the recipe last
night, and it was perfect,
And then I locked the
Sherry in the liquor
cabinet. Who had access?
Did you give Andrew's keys to
anyone after you fired him?
He never returned his key.
Oh, Bree.
They won't give the plates back.
The publisher guy's
giving a little speech,
And then they're gonna
eat. No, no, no, no.
I am not gonna lose my
cookbook career over this.
God.
Hand me that torch.
We're serving cobbler
in the parking lot!
I just made you real hot chocolate.
Don't I get a smile?
My son tried to ruin my career tonight.
I don't think I'll ever smile again.
Honestly,
I don't think Andrew had
anything to do with it.
You don't?
Mnh. Look at the planning
that went into it.
The vinegar had to be
substituted for the Sherry
After you'd selected the bottle
But before you'd left for the event.
And the ingredient had to be
something you wouldn't sample.
Come on. Andrew's not clever
enough to pull that off.
He can't even steal a case of
wine without getting caught.
Well, then who do you think did it?
Well, it'd have to be
somebody pretty smart...
At least smart enough to get an mba.
Sam? That's ridiculous.
Why would he want to hurt me?
Who said he wanted to hurt you?
Andrew's the one taking this fall.
No, that's not possible.
What does he stand to gain?
Hmm. What a good question.
Enjoy your chocolate.
Every once in a while,
I catch Susan looking
at me this certain way.
You know, I'm putting on
my shirt or mowing the lawn.
I'll turn my head,
And I'll catch her with
this look in her eyes,
And I know she's thinking
that she's lucky to have me.
So how can I tell her I'm dead broke?
How can I say, "I can't take your money,
"Because it won't begin to cover
The debts I've been racking
up for the last year"?
She thinks it's a
couple of truck payments.
She's got no idea.
This would really hurt her.
If she found out I kept this from her,
I don't think I'd ever see
that look from her again...
And I can't let that happen.
Tell me how much you need.
Double capp, extra hot, right?
Wow. Good memory.
I haven't seen you for a while.
I thought maybe you left town.
Oh, I'm not leaving
till I finish my book.
Oh, right, yeah. How's that goin'?
Did the guy kill her?
I tried to write it that way.
He went over there. She was alone.
He had the chance.
And what happened?
Just seemed too easy.
So you stuck again?
No.
I've got a better idea.
If you think about it,
The worst part of what she
did was taking the kid, right?
So I figure
The best way for him to get revenge...
Is to take something from her.
But what could he take that's
gonna be as bad as what she did?
The kid.
He's gonna take the kid, right?
That's what I'm thinking.
He did.
I feel awful.
The more he thought about it,
he just couldn't let me do this.
And let's face it, he does have a say.
It's completely understandable,
Gaby. It was a lot to ask.
So where's Lee?
I wanna talk to him, too.
He left.
Left?
After Carlos came over,
Lee and I got into yet another fight,
And...
We broke up.
Are you kidding me?
Lee says he can't go through it again.
I'm determined to have a child,
So...
Is there anything I can do?
Oh, right.
Sorry.
It's okay, Gaby. Like I
said, it was a lot to ask.
My left shoe is missing. We'll find it.
I can't get married in
one shoe. Just get dressed.
The wedding starts in half an hour.
Hey, maybe he should wear sneakers.
It'd be wild, like
he's too cool to care.
Or I could-- I just
help him keep looking.
There you go.
Lynette! Help me look
for Preston's shoe!
Lynette?
What are you doing?
I need your help. Preston
can't find his shoe.
I put it in the oven.
Why?
Because that woman at immigration
Never called me back,
And I am screwed.
Oh, honey. Come on.
Hiding a shoe isn't gonna
stop them from getting married.
I know. I just wanted a few more minutes
Before I had to tell my son
I'm not going to his wedding.
I will not be a hypocrite, Tom.
I know how you feel.
But if you think irina's got power now,
Just you wait until you don't
show up to your son's wedding.
Oh, I wish...
I wish... I went to church more often.
I could really use a
favor from the man upstairs
Right about now.
Mrs. Scavo?
You're not gonna believe what I found.
I'll see you Sunday morning.
You look beautiful.
Mm. Thank you.
I am guessing this one's much nicer
Than your first wedding dress, you know,
When you got married in Russia to...
Alexei kosokov?
Here in America
We actually get divorced
before we get married again,
Otherwise you spend
your honeymoon in jail.
Alexei told me
If I marry him, he
will give me good life.
But he didn't.
He never worked.
He treat me badly.
Now he won't sign the divorce papers
Unless I give him money.
Okay.
That explains alexei.
What about...
The guy in Italy...
Who pressed charges after you
cleaned out his bank account?
That guy was a pig.
Believe me, I earned every Penny.
We have a term in America for
women who get paid for sex,
And it's not
"Daughter-in-law."
You know why it doesn't bother me
That you don't like me?
Can't wait.
Because it really doesn't matter.
All that matters
Is that one hour from now,
I will have a ring on this finger,
And I will be
The most important person in his life.
So give Preston your little file.
I will explain it all away,
And he will believe every word.
He always does.
Preston.
Mom, do you mind?
I need to talk to irina.
Your father told me you
called off the wedding.
Obviously, I think you
are doing the right thing.
I know you hate me right now,
And I just want you to know
that I am okay with that.
I love you so much.
I would rather have you resent me
Or even cut me off completely
Than to allow you to make a mistake
That could ruin your life. So go ahead.
Hate me for as long as you want,
And when you are done,
I will be here waiting.
Try not to take too long,
'cause I miss you already.
Hey. Where you going?
Motel,
Till I get flight out
of this horrible place.
What? The scavos couldn't
even give you a lift?
That's harsh.
I want nothing from the scavos.
They're dead to me.
Lucky for you,
I am not a Scavo.
Sorry about the wedding.
It's Preston's loss, man.
I mean, he'll never get
someone as hot as you again.
I don't want to talk about it.
Sure. You know, I get that.
You know, if you wanna save money,
You could--you could
always skip the motel
And stay at my place.
I don't think so.
No, I promise,
no--no funny business.
I mean...
Unless you want some.
Yeah, I-I mean,
think of it as a--
As a transition relationship.
It'll help you get over Preston.
I-I have no problem
letting you use me--
Okay, enough.
I'm a little out of your
league, don't you think?
I mean, I didn't come to America
To end up with some
greasy-haired little boy.
What are you doing?!
Eddie?
We all know that evil exists.
The newspapers are filled with stories
About young girls who suddenly vanish.
But we don't pay attention
Because we're worried
about our marriages...
Concerned about our friendships...
Anxious about our employees.
Yes, we don't pay attention to evil
Because we think it will
never come to our house.
But it does.
Hey, Mrs. Scavo. I'm here
to pick up Porter for school.
And sometimes...
How you doin'?
Good.
We let it in.
Sync by kuniva
www.addic7ed.com