All right. I love you.
There, I said it.
Feelings were stated boldly.
I think it's time for me to give up on man.
A romantic suggestion was made.
Date chicks?
And a plan was hatched...
He wants to represent you.
Aah! they want you in
new york immediately.
To break up a romance...
This is a huge opportunity.
The best part is she is miles
away from the nearest bolen.
But young love couldn't be stopped.
Since she'd become a mother,
Gabrielle solis had
learned many things--
How to get gum off
a remote control...
How to rescue a doll
from the disposal...
And where to find
disappointing report cards.
Gabrielle had also learned
That no matter how
hard she tried...
Cereal again?
She couldn't please everyone.
Yes, another free meal you
didn't have to work for.
It's tough being 7.
Celia, get down here!
Ana used to make us bacon.
I miss her.
Yeah, well, she also used to
do the laundry and the windows,
So I miss her more.
Celia, the milk is poured!
Oh, I need cupcakes
for school today.
Today? How many?
Mom!
Three dozen.
Why didn't you tell
me this last night?
I forgot. We got any ham?
I need meat.
Babe, are you gonna pick up
my suit from the dry cleaners?
Yes, after I fold the laundry,
fry up some ham
And pull three dozen
cupcakes out of my ass!
Mom! what?!
My face itches.
What are those, mosquito bites?
Whoa. That looks like chicken pox.
No. No! no! no! I don't
have time for sick kids!
Forget the dry cleaning.
You gotta take her to the doctor.
Oh, god. What do you do for chicken pox?
I've never had ' of the house.
Why? You can't go
anywhere near her.
If you've haven't had them,
you're not immune.
In fact, you gotta get out of here.
Honey, celia is sick.
Chicken pox is dangerous
for adults. Go.
I have to do the laun
I will take care of the house.
Yes, gabrielle had learned
many things as a mother.
The most important...
See ya.
Was to get while the
getting was good.
Seduction--
Any soap opera fan will tell you,
It's an art best practiced...
Stop.
...On those who are vulnerable.
Hey there.
You hungry?
Oh, I am now.
What's that amazing smell?
Uh, cinnamon brioche french toast.
Oh, but I probably shouldn't.
You're such an amazing cook.
I'm already having trouble
fitting into my clothes.
Oh. Uh...
You need some maple syrup.
Oh, seriously,
you heated the syrup?
You're unbelievable.
You should eat it
while it's still...
Hot.
Look.
I just got syrup all over me.
I don't know what it is with me.
I just... Have to get dirty.
You...
Got some on your bra, too.
Oh.
I'll get it.
Please. It's wrong.
Then why does it feel so right?
Katherine? You up yet?
Oh, good. I was calling,
but you didn't hear me.
I think you feel
asleep with the tv on.
So what would you
like for breakfast?
Anything but french toast.
Oh, I don't think you'll
be here that long.
I got it.
I got the perfect
name for the baby.
Patricia.
Let me think about it.
No.
Wh--
Why not? It's a great name.
I told you, I want to honor my aunt.
We're naming her polly.
Polly?
Okay, you get a peg leg,
I'll get an eye patch,
And we'll carry her
around on our shoulders.
Morning, penny. Oh, hey, baby.
Mwah. Where are my pancakes?
Oh, sweetie, I've got
a lot going on today.
I'll make you
pancakes this weekend.
But I always get pan
That's... Right.
You do.
But...
We... Have... An even bigger treat
Planned for you this year. Yeah.
What?
Like I'm gonna tell ya
and ruin the big sprise!
How could you forget
her birthday? Me?
I'm pregnant. I forget
What's your excuse?
What's my surprise?
What the hell are we gonna do?
Cover me. I'm going in.
Birthday breakfasts...
Are for kids.
Now that you're 11,
I was planning to make you...
The best...
Birthday... Dinner ever,
With decorations...
Tons of presents...
Pin the tail on the...
You forgot my birthday.
Wow.
There was no covering that, babe.
You're twice the man he is.
What's raymundo gonna say
When he finds out tiffany's
sleeping with his brother?
Alas, you'll never know.
Oh, hey, mom. We-
-we were just taking a break.
So I gathered.
If you don't mind, tad, I'd like to
In private, tad.
Oh! so you want me to--
Be anyplace else but here, right.
Uh, so--so what's up?
There's a truck outside
With the flower arrangements we
ordered for the
All 100 of them.
Wait. But we only ordered ten.
That's what I said.
Then the delivery man
showed me this invoice.
At first I wasn't sure if
that was tad's signatur
But when I saw that his
name was misspelled...
I knew it was him.
Uh, would you like
me to talk to him?
No. I would like you
While I strike him with
a large wooden spoon.
Whatever. I-i'll take care of it.
What are you going to say to him?
Look, when--when orson
had his accident,
Did you or did you not
put me in charge? Yes,
but I am starting to
thinou're gonna have to learn
Look... I'm never gonna
figure this job out
Unless you let me make
mistakes and learn from them.
I realize that,
andrewour control issues,
Mom, I know you have
your control issues,
But when stuff happens,
you're gonna have to learn
To just relax and--and let me
clean up my own messes, okay?
Hey, where do you want all
these flower arrangements?
Oops.
No problem, tad.
As luck would have it,
we've got extra.
Mmm!
Roy, we've got guests.
You can watch your soap later.
Come on, roy.
Well, again, thank you for
inviting us over to brunch.
Everything looks delicious.
Yeah, it does, doesn't it?
Right, karen?
You know what I want.
When company comes over,
I get to use salt.
Roy's on a low-sodium diet.
"no sodium" is code for "
tastes like socks."
So sue me 'cause I don't
want you dropping dead.
Listen to you two.
You sound like a sweet,
old married couple.
So... Have you ever thought
Of making an honest
woman out of karen?
What are you doing
Oh. I just want them to
be as happy as we are.
Uh, we're happy.
Living in sin suits us just fine.
Is that how karen els?
Susan, why don't you,
uh, try this frittata?
Karen don't care about marrge.
Do you, pumpkin?
Here.
Have some re salt.
I alys figured yod say no.
So why don'tou grow
a ir and findut?
Are u serious?
Of coue she's seous.
Ne.
Mikegive me a hand, will y?
Oh, my god! This is so romantic.
Karen, will you...
Son of a bee.
There's the battery
to my hearing aid.
Okay, okay.
Karen... do you wanna marry me?
Golly, I don't know what to say.
This is all so sudden.
Answer. My knee hurts.
Would love to marry you, roy.
Yes!
@@@@@le of days,
Why'd she bring three suitcases?
She said most of her dresses
haven't had chicken pox either.
Oh!
That... was amazing.
I just took a nap in
the middle of the day.
Guess it's a little
different without kids, huh?
Oh, you kidding me?
I haven't taken a nap
since juanita crowned.
Okay, you just created a
visual that is Forbidden
inside these walls.
Try to watch that.
Here. You're just in time
for pre-dinner cosmos.
In a crystal glass?
Mm. Oh! Celia broke our
last one six months ago.
I've been drinking my cocktails
out of a scooby-doo sippy cup.
Mmm! I'm in heaven.
Mmm. So it's movie night.
Have you seen this?
Does it have a talking penguin
or a dog that plays basketball?
No, just gratuitous sex and
lots of violence. Yay! Art!
Ahh!
Uh-oh. Somebody's glass is empty.
That's also forbidden
inside these walls.
Oh!
I know I don't know you
guys that well, but...
I love you.
Oh, wow.
Are you okay? Oh, my god.
- Penny?
- All right, it's time for cake.
I got your favorite.
Chocolate?
I got your second favorite.
- Mom?
- Yes?
Uh, I have a date in half
an hour. Can I go now?
No, you cannot go.
Preston's in europe.
Parker's at band practice.
- You are representing all siblings.
- Mom--
Don't you feel bad we
forgot her birthday?
I didn't forget. I gave her
a present this morning.
So don't take it out on me that
you and dad failed as parents.
Oh. We used up all our
good parenting on you.
That's why you're so delightful.
Okay.
Here we go!
Hee-hee!
One, two, three--
Who's polly?
Oh, my god!
Erase, erase, erase.
Sweetie, I am so sorry.
You know, I don't
know if you know this,
But pregnant women get
a little scattered.
And then your dad and I were
talking about baby names,
And I got on the phone
with the bakery, and...
Which is clearly a terrible excuse,
And again, I am so sorry.
Let me fix this.
Hey! That just made it worse,
And how would you like a puppy?
Forget it.
But you haven't opened
your presents yet.
Come back...
Penny.
I know her name.
The central bank thursday
raised interest rates...
nick!
Yeah. What? What's going on?
Danny took off. Listen to this--
"Didn't want to wake you.
Went camping with eddie.
"Had to clear my head
about the whole ana thing.
P.S. Took my cell,
but doubt we'll have reception."
Good for him.
Are you crazy?
He's never been by himself.
He knows how to drink out of
a canteen and pee on a tree.
- I think he'll be fine.
- This isn't funny.
Look, should he have asked us?
Okay, yeah.
But I think it's healthy.
Hey, better hiking with eddie
Than alone in his room
with a bottle of pills.
I don't know.
He's 19. Eventually,
we gotta let him live a normal life.
He's never gonna
have a normal life.
None of us will.
I realize the mistake
was ours, mr. Tan,
But what am I supposed to do
With 90 extra floral arrangements?
Well, it will be your problem
If I stop doing business with you.
Yes. What can I do for you?
Actually, the question
is what can I do for you?
I'm sorry. Did we
have an appointment?
No, but I've been wanting to
meet you for such a long time,
And when I woke up this morning,
I told myself today is the day.
May I sit?
No, no. Not just yet.
What is it you want, mister...
Allen. Sam allen.
I've been following your career
for a while now, mrs. Hodge.
I've been to some
parties you've catered,
And I've got your cookbook,
I've read every interview
you've ever done,
and I think you're quite amazing.
How nice. Now let's skip to
the part where you assure me
That you're not some
deranged stalker.
Hardly. I want to work for you.
Doing what?
Anything. Everything.
I'm very busy, mr. Allen.
I worked as a sous-chef to put
myself through business school,
Where I graduated at
the top of my class.
I know my way around a
kitchen and a calculator.
And I'm not asking you to pay me
a lot of money, not yet anyway.
I want to learn your
business from the ground up,
And then I want to
help you expand it.
Really?
You're a woman who has something
to say about traditional values,
And I think our country's
ready to listen.
I am flattered...
But I'm also fully staffed,
And I honestly wouldn't know
how to use you. I'm sorry.
So am I.
In regard to the extra
floral arrangements,
You could donate them to a hospital
And record the loss as a
charitable contribution.
And if you split the
arrangements in half,
You could double the
amount you claim.
Just a thought.
Mr. Allen?
Now you can sit.
Hey. Where's your blushing bride?
Upstairs in the can.
What do you want?
Well, I thought I
would drop this off.
It's a bouquet I found.
Don't you think it'll
be perfect for karen?
Haven't you done
enough already? Huh?
We had a good thing going-
me and karen.
Now 'cause of you, we're gonna
get married and ruin it.
Getting married
isn't gonna ruin it.
It's gonna make it better.
No, it isn't. It's like salt.
What?
All my life,
I never cared about salt,
But when my doctor said I
couldn't have it anymore,
I started craving it.
Wait. Are, uh...
You telling me that...
You're gonna cheat on karen?
I go to a stretching
class at the center.
There's a lady with blue hair,
always sits in front of me.
Six months she's been there.
I never gave a crap about her.
But this morning,
48 hours after you told me
I had to propose to karen,
I'm looking at ol' blue hair,
And I'm smacking my lips.
Salt.
You're 80 years old, roy.
Infidelity is...
Dangerous.
My body's 80,
But inside, I'm still
a randy teenage boy.
Susan, I'm telling ya,
I have to kiss some other
women before I die.
Well, you can't, so forget it.
Just think about karen and
how much she loves you,
And if you do that,
I'm sure you'll be able to resist
Any inappropriate urges, okay?
Yeah, that's the stuff.
How is your wife
being molested funny?
It was just a kiss from
an 80-year-old man.
Well, it's too bad he
didn't grab my ass.
You'd be rolling on the floor.
What do you want me to do,
beat him up?
Take the tennis balls
off his walker?
Okay, forget about me.
What about what
he's doing to karen?
I mean, they're about
to get married,
And he has no intention
of being faithful.
Because he feels trapped.
And whose fault is that?
Don't point the mustard at me.
Susan, I was there.
You practically
forced him into this.
Okay. I made a mistake.
I didn't know that he was
some sort of jurassic gigolo.
I have to tell karen
about this right now.
No. You've meddled enough.
Well, I can't let her marry him,
knowing what I know.
Susan, he's having second thoughts.
I mean, come on, there's
not a married man on earth
Who didn't have second
thoughts before he got married.
Oh, really?
Well...
Co--I didn't mean...
Okay, I'm done.
Mwah. See ya,
boys! Thanks for driving!
Bye, gaby! Don't
forget to friend us!
Oh, I won't, fernando.
And good luck with
your pec implants.
All right, time for a nightcap.
Oh, nightcaps! I'd forgotten
all about nightcaps.
Oh, I miss the gay single life.
You know what? She deserves
the full experience.
We're gonna throw you a party.
Brilliant! I have mini
quiches in the freezer
And ten homos on speed dial.
It's done.
Oh! I'm so excited!
Invite those guys from tonight...
Except fernando.
He's prettier than me.
Hi. It's bob. * and lee
Leave a message.
Hey, guys. It's Carlos.
I'm looking for Gaby.
The doctor says the girls
aren't contagious anymore,
so she can come home now. Thanks.
Well, that's good news.
What?! That is horrible news.
My children are healthy. Damn it!
But you can go home now.
No, I'm not ready.
I'm just starting to remember
What it's like to be human again--
Sleeping in, not stepping on toys,
Eating at restaurants
that don't have a slide.
I have tasted freedom,
and I am not ready to give it up!
But what are you gonna tell carlos?
Oh, no. A stomach virus?
Yeah, when you called earlier,
i was throwing up.
Well, we don't want
the girls to catch it.
What's that noise?
My teeth are chattering.
Anyhow, I'll be home
as soon as I can.
Doctor says it's a 24-hour thing.
Don't forget the hangover.
Or 36-hour thing. Gotta go.
Start pourin'.
I said I was throwing up.
Don't want to be a liar.
I can hire whomever I want.
It's my company.
And I run it for you.
I should have been consulted.
Why are you being so
unpleasant about this?
I hired sam to help you.
I don't need his help.
I've got it under control.
Andrew, all I've seen lately
is evidence to the contrary,
And if you think I'm gonna stand by
While everything I've
built falls apart...
Sam. I thought you'd gone home.
Oh, I stayed late to
finish the inventory.
Well, aren't you industrious?
I also wanted to talk about tad.
Uh, what about him?
Every task I've given him
He's either botched
or failed to finish.
I think it's time
to cut our losses.
We're-- we're not firing tad.
Why not? He's a moron.
He's a good guy,
and--and I don't want you
Talking that way
about my employees.
Andrew, you have to admit,
He's more than a
little incompetent.
Give him a chance. He's just a kid.
You're having an affair with him,
aren't you?
Sam! How could you
say such a thing?
I think the more
pertinent question is
Why isn't andrew denying it?
Andrew, have you had sex with tad?
Just once. Uh...
Oh, my god.
Well, he came on to me.
It was late, and I'd been drinking.
That's your excuse?
Honestly, andrew,
I am so disappointed in you.
Oh, really? Y-you want
to play that card?
You're living with alex.
And you're married to orson.
Yeah, I know about karl mayer.
Hello, pot. I'm kettle.
It's nice to meet you.
I cannot believe you
would bring this up
in front of a stranger.
Yeah, you know me.
Hypocrisy just makes
me forget my manners.
Perhaps I should go.
Yes. But I want you back
here bright and early
Tomorrow morning to
help me fire tad.
Y--no. No. You--you-
you can't fire him.
Yes, I can.
In fact, I can fire anyone I want.
Taking off her bra,
I woke up.
What do you think that means?
Seems pretty straightforward.
But I'm not a lesbian.
You're getting ahead of yourself.
Maybe this dream isn't
even about robin.
Maybe it's about how
I've been so hurt by men
That women are the
only safe option left.
Why are you even thinking
about relationships at all,
With men or women?
You're still fragile.
Now when you're stronger,
Then we can talk about who
you might be attracted to.
But I'm not attracted to her.
That's what I'm saying.
Women my age don't
just wake up one day
With a whole new sexual identity.
This dream has got to
mean something else.
Well, what it tells me, clearly,
Is that you are being
distracted from your recovery.
So what am I supposed to do,
stop dreaming?
No.
But you might want to consider
Asking robin to find
another place to stay.
This lettering is so small.
I can hardly read the label.
All right, while you're deciding
Which one is dolphin-safe,
I'm gonna get some beer.
Hey! Mrs. Bolen!
I--do you shop here?
Where's danny? He said you
guys were going camping.
Oh, yeah.
No, but h--I--
it turned out I couldn't go,
So he just went... by himself.
You wanna get in line?
You wanna make me?
Spill it.
I'm sorry. He said he'd
call you when he got there.
Eddie. Hey, you guys back already?
So where is he really?
New york.
Danny went to find ana.
Hey. Hey.
Don't freak out. It's a big city.
What if he goes to
the old neighborhood?
Patrick is not going to find him.
He found us the last time.
Come on. I gotta go pack.
You're in early.
Oh, I couldn't sleep,
So I thought I'd review
our liability insurance,
But I'm having a little
trouble focusing.
Maybe some coffee
will perk you up. Mm.
Um, about what happened
yesterday, sam,
That, um, ugliness with andrew--
Driven, successful people like
you have complicated lives,
But the specifics are
none of my business.
My, um...
Relationship with andrew is,
uh, to say the least,
Complicated.
I'm sure andrew respects
and loves you very much.
I just worry that...
What?
Well, it's not unusual for
children in a family business
To have a sense of entitlement.
I hope you don't
mind me saying that.
No. Go ahead.
This must be so hard.
What do you do in this situation?
Keep coddling him,
hoping he'll change,
Or do you cut the apron
strings and trust
That all the hard work you've
done will allow him to thrive?
It's a good question.
You know what?
I've got everything
under control here.
Why don't you go back to the house
And catch up on your sleep?
But there's so much
work to be done.
Sure, but that's why you
hired me, isn't it--
To help you out? Thank you, sam.
You're very kind.
And, sam?
I'm very glad you're here.
Unh-unh!
Hey, bert. I'm looking for penny.
She didn't get off the bus.
That's 'cause she didn't get on.
I figured she went home
sick or something. What? No.
She didn't come home sick.
Where is she? Penny?
Mrs. Scavo?
Penny said to give you this.
She's running away.
Any ideas why she ran away?
Problems at home?
No. No, everything's fine.
Well, we did kind of
forget her birthday.
And... she put the wrong
name on her birthday cake.
Honey, could we please stick
To the facts that
pertain to the case?
How could you get your
daughter's name wrong?
Are you people
involved in narcotics?
No! No, I'm pregnant,
And it makes me very forgetful.
Surely you can understand that.
I'm not pregnant.
You're not gonna look for
our daughter, are you?
Aguilar.
Yeah, they're still here.
Oh, okay.
Your daughter's fine.
She tried to use
Your credit card to
check into a hotel.
Hey.
You mind if I come in?
Wow. Marble bath,
Flat screen,
$8 can of peanuts.
Nice.
Sweetie, I am so
sorry about the cake
And about forgetting your birthday.
I know you hate me right now,
and I don't blame you.
I don't hate you. I hate that.
Oh.
Because you're not gonna
be the baby anymore.
Oh. Penny.
Sweetie.
You're missing the
big picture here.
Preston's gone. Porter's next.
When this girl comes along,
we are poised
To take control of the
house with a 3-2 majority.
Do you know what that means?
Women get veto power over
what tv shows to watch,
What takeout to get.
Just think.
Think of a world where the
toilet seat is never up.
This is our time to take them down.
We're both gonna take them down!
Hey.
Oh.
I'm sorry I ran away.
We can go home now.
I have a better idea.
Since you already
paid for the room,
How about we order
hot fudge sundaes...
And spend the night?
Just... just us girls.
Yeah.
Okay.
You know, mom... hmm?
If you have two more girls,
we'll take the lead.
Let's just... order our sundaes.
So there I was at this huge party,
Flirting with this
middle eastern sheikh,
And out of nowhere...
He offers me a million
dollars to sleep with him.
So what did you do?
I slapped him.
Apparently in the right place,
'cause I walked out of
there with 20 grand.
Shh. Gaby, it's juanita.
Oh, excuse me, guys.
Gotta do the "Mommie
dearest" Thing.
Hi, sweetie. How was school?
What?
Oh, you scored a goal in soccer?
What? Wh--hang on, sweetie,
While I find a quiet place
so mommy can hear you.
Hang on, sweetie.
Okay, honey, mommy can...
H-hold on, sweetie.
Do the words "Wet paint"
Mean nothing to you?
Uh, juanita? Honey,
I have to call you back. I love you.
Sorry.
I didn't mean to. I...
Is this a...
A nursery? Yes.
We haven't told very
many people yet,
But... lee and I are
trying to adopt a baby.
Oh. I had no idea.
Yeah.
It's something we've
wanted for years.
Oh, okay.
Why?
I mean, you guys have
this amazing life.
Parties every night,
cosmos at 5:00.
You know all that goes
away when the baby comes.
And we can't wait.
Last month there was
this baby in ohio.
We got the call in the
middle of the night.
We were on a plane in the morning.
We got to the hospital,
and there she was--
A little girl.
We held that baby in our arms...
For two days.
And then we went out to buy a
car seat to bring her home,
And when we got back
to the hospital,
The... social worker was waiting
for us outside the nursery.
The mother had changed her mind.
I know how that feels.
I am so sorry, bob.
You may envy our life, gaby,
But... it's nothing
Compared to how we envy yours.
Hey, what are you doing?
The party's just getting started.
I know. It's just--juanita
scored her first goal in soccer,
And she wants to tell
me all about it, so...
Go.
Give them a kiss for me.
I will.
Knock, knock. Karen, are you home?
I'm in here.
Uh, listen.
I've been thinking
about your wedding,
And, well, I just want
to talk to you about...
What's wrong?
Nothing.
The doctor found a spot on my lung.
A spot?
He thinks it might be cancer.
She told you, huh?
Yeah.
It's gonna be okay.
She's getting a biopsy next week.
She's gonna lick this thing.
Cancer picked a fight
with the wrong broad.
Uh, so given the diagnosis,
Maybe it's not a good
time to get married.
Oh!
We're getting married,
Soon as we can.
But you said-- I know what I said.
All I could think about was
losing my independence,
Losing my freedom,
But after this happened,
Now I realize the worst
thing I could lose is her.
So...
You're willing...
To give up salt?
I'm willing to give up anything.
Oh, roy.
Ah-ah! Watch it, doll.
I told you I'm giving it up.
One kiss is all you get.
Oh, hey! You're still up.
Yeah, I... sort of needed to
talk to you about something.
Well, if it's me helping
with the bills...
I've got great news.
You got the job?
You're looking
At the downtown
grill's new hostess.
I start tomorrow.
Oh! Thank you for
loaning me your top.
The manager said I
looked very classy.
Oh. I can't tell you how
happy this makes me.
So... you wanna tell me your thing?
No, it's--it can wait.
Are you sure?
Yeah. Absolutely.
I'll get you a glass.
Aah!
Oh, my god! Oh.
Oh, my god. Oh.
Oh, your blouse.
I am so sorry. It's okay.
Wait. What are you doing?
I'm just gonna rinse it out.
No, no, no. Stop.
It's--it's--it's okay.
No, but it's gonna stain.
I'll send it to the dry cleaners.
Oh, but that is so expensive.
Here we go--
You have to leave.
What?
I need you to move out of my house.
Why?
It's--it's-- it's complicated.
Is this...
This what you wanted
to talk to me about?
Yeah.
Sorry if I did something wrong.
I have a friend I can go stay with,
So I'm just gonna go pack.
Robin.
You haven't done anything wrong.
I like you very much.
In fact...
Too much.
Lately I've started to
have feelings for you...
That I don't understand,
And it's confusing me.
You know what I'm saying?
I do...
'cause I'm having those
feelings for you, too.
You're right.
I should go.
Seduction is an art.
Subtle methods of coercion are used
To sway the susceptible.
And those who are determined
Will take their time
to get what they want.
And when the seduction
is successful,
Those who succumbed
ask themselves...
Was I seduced...
Or was this what I
wanted all along?
Sync by YYeTs.net
Transcript by Addic7ed.com