Previously on "Desperate Housewives"...
Old friends fought.
You knew that Julie was in trouble,
and you chose not to come to me.
New lovers lie.
Where did you get it, Bree?
She bought it? I'm assuming.
Uh, yes, at that little antique
store down on pearl street.
Sorry. We sell furniture.
She must have gotten it somewhere else.
And suspicion was born.
Do you know where Katherine was
the night that Julie was attacked?
Julie Mayer was having trouble sleeping.
You see, every time she closed her eyes,
she dreamt of her neighbor.
They met when she came to tutor his son.
Later, a chance encounter at a caf
led to hours of conversation.
He asked to see her again...
and again...
and again.
And the next thing Julie knew,
she was having an affair
with a married man.
But then, after a close call,
she came to her senses
and told the man it was over.
Unfortunately for Julie,
Some men can't take "no" for an answer.
Can I come in?
What, that's it? It's
that simple to you?
You have to leave now.
Come on. Let's just talk about this.
There is nothing to talk about! Just go!
Yes, there is! Just
come on. Talk to me! huh?
Lynette. Hi. What's up?
I'm just dropping off that band
candy your mom bought from Penny.
Everything okay?
Yeah, everything's fine.
Um... Mr. Bolen was just leaving. Right?
Yeah, I guess I was. Hey, Lynette.
Hey, Nick.
What was that about?
What do you mean?
Well, I don't mean to pry. It's just...
When I was walking up,
I heard you two arguing.
He's the guy.
The guy?
The guy I was... having the affair with.
No. No!
- Why did you tell me this?!
- You asked.
Why not lie?
I'm late for work.
I would've bought anything.
Look, don't freak out. It's over.
Not for me. Now I have to tell your mom!
No, you don't.
She was pissed when I didn't
tell her you might be pregnant.
If I don't tell her
about this,  I'm dead.
Come on, Lynette.
I am serious!
She already shot Katherine.
Now she's got a taste for blood.
There's no reason to tell her anything.
I broke it off weeks ago.
Then why was he here?
He wants me to take him back.
Threaten to tell his wife.
He doesn't care. He says he loves me.
Oh, honey, you're smart enough
to know that that's a lie.
Right?
I keep trying to get over him,
but then he comes over here
and he says all this stuff,
and I... I just get so confused.
Listen to me.
I will handle this.
Really?
And you... you won't tell my mom?
No, I won't.
Thank you.
That night, for the first time in weeks,
Julie Mayer would sleep well.
Unfortunately,
Lynette Scavo would not.
"The Fairview Homeschooling Workbook"
was created to help parents
teach their children.
It's colorful,
very entertaining,
a bit challenging
and guaranteed to make teaching fun.
Pick that up, or I will
knock you into next week!
I hate fractions!
I don't care! You still
have to learn them!
Why? Fractions are boring!
Okay. Fine.
Let me make it more interesting for you.
Say I take Mrs. Doolittle...
you favorite doll...
and I chop her into thirds.
I bury one third in the yard.
I put another third down
the garbage disposal.
How much of Mrs.
Doolittle do you have left?
You're not gonna hurt her, are you?
It depends on how you
answer the question!
Gaby! Can I see you for a sec?
- What is going on?
- I'm teaching math.
By threatening her toys?
Well, maybe teacher's
a little tired, okay?
It's not the only thing
I have to do around here.
I also have to cook and clean.
Okay, I hear you.
It isn't fair that
all this falls on you.
- I'll get you some help.
- Thank you.
We'll get a housekeeper.
What? No, no, no, I'd
rather have a tutor.
You'd rather scrubs toilets
than teach your daughter?
Well, at least the
toilets won't talk back.
Gaby, she just had to leave
her school and all her friends.
And now her mother's gonna abandon her,
- and leave her with some stranger? I don't think so.
- No, but...
No "but"s. Juanita needs you right now.
You're doing this.
Don't worry. Your doll's safe.
If I'm gonna chop anything off,
it's gonna be something of your daddy's!
So you're saying you
won't even talk to her?
No, we already interviewed Mrs. Mayfair.
That's when you thought
Danny Bolen had attacked Julie.
You treated her like a witness.
Now you need to treat
her like a suspect.
Look, miss, we're not trying
to dismiss your concerns,
but women don't commit
this kind of crime.
They tend to keep at a physical remove
from their victims...
vehicular assaults, poison.
Well, maybe Katherine was
thinking outside the box.
- Hey, did you get any mayo?
-Yeah.
Look, I was skeptical, too,
but she does have a motive.
- She hates Susan.
- Well, that's a motive to attack her.
Well, maybe Katherine saw
Julie taking out the garbage
and thought it was me.
She mistook you
for a 23-year-old?
I'm sorry, Mrs. Delfino, but, uh,
unless you've got actual evidence,
we're gonna keep assuming that
this is a random incident...
one that your daughter
thankfully survived.
Damn it! They forgot the pickle!
What is with this place?
Is there anyone here that understands
a woman can be a psycho killer, too?
Ah, maybe I can help.
You want me to take this one?
Have at it.
Thank you so much.
So how about I, uh,
take a look at your file?
I will swing by tomorrow,
- and I'll get your statement then.
- Great.
Well... It is nice to know that someone
Cares about justice More than pickles.
Come on, Mike.
Are you sure you want this case?
'Cause I've got a serial killer
here that might be more fun.
Nah, she and I go way back.
She doesn't remember
me now, but she will.
I wish you hadn't committed us to this.
Why? They're our neighbors,
and they've been asking us for weeks.
I'm not a fan of Angie Bolen.
She can be very forward.
I like her. She's earthy,
takes a real interest in people.
Yes. Last week, she asked
me how much my dress cost
and did I still get
visits from my Aunt Flo.
Well, I believe that's
a euphemism for...
I know what it means.
By the way, I stopped by
that antique store today...
the one where you said
you bought that brooch.
I thought I'd get you a replacement
since you gave yours to Susan.
But the owner said they
don't sell jewelry there.
Just furniture.
Well, that's odd.
I must've confused that store
with the jewelry shop on Maple Street.
Yes, I remember now.
That's where I bought it.
Hey, look who's here!
My goodness. Another course?
Well, my grandma Bombelli always said,
"If the men can still button their
pants, dinner ain't over yet."
Is her braciole amazing or what?
I have to admit, I've
never had this before.
And it is quite tasty.
Aw, thanks, hon. Hang on a sec.
You don't want to stain
that gorgeous blouse.
I'm actually a very neat eater.
Oh, hey, when Nick here
starts twirlin' his pasta,
nobody's safe.
I did get some friendly
fire from a meatball earlier.
I'm glad we're finally doing this.
You two are hard to pin down.
Well, we've been incredibly busy.
Oh, I'll bet, especially
since Katherine wigged out
and you had to give her the boot.
You know, if you need
someone to replace her,
you could a lot worse than Angie.
Oh?
Yeah, her grandma Bombelli had
the best restaurant in little Italy
and taught Angie everything she knew.
I mean...
If you're lookin' for help.
Well, if your food is all this good...
We're... not hiring.
Sorry.
Okay. It's just a thought.
You sure, Bree?
She said no.
No, I'm just sayin'... you
don't know what you're missin'.
Nick, she's had four courses.
She knows what she's missing.
Now zip it.
Don't bite my head off.
I'm just tryin' to help.
What, by embarrassing our guests?
Just ignore him, okay?
It was your idea to cook for her.
Thank you! Now they're gonna think
that I don't cook for people
unless I have an angle.
I am so sorry.
Now look at them. They're
wishin' they hadn't come.
- No! we're having a lovely time.
- No! we're thrilled to be here!
Perfect! Now you're
makin' our guests lie.
I'm gonna go stir the sauce.
I'll get more wine.
We're gonna need it.
Uh, just curious, how many more courses?
Three.
Orson, I never thought
I'd say this to you again,
but please... unbutton your pants.
Okay.
If you have half a cabbage,
and someone gives you a quarter cabbage,
how much cabbage do you have?
None, because I hate cabbages
and I wouldn't take 'em.
Fine. They're balloons.
There's no such thing as half a balloon.
Well, there is a such
thing as half an allowance,
which is what you're gonna get
if you don't start to focus.
Why can't I just use a calculator?
'Cause you have to know this stuff.
If not, you're gonna end up
scrubbing other people's toilets!
Sorry.
Look, if you finish this page,
we'll go get some ice cream.
- How's that sound?
- I don't want to have ice cream with you.
I'm gonna get some air.
Will you make sure she
doesn't move from the table?
What do you call this again?
Uh, foie gras mousse.
Mmm. Tastes so elegant.
Don't you think it's elegant?
It's okay.
Would you like to sample
something else, Mr. Vitale?
Some salmon en croute or
perhaps some coq au vin?
Got anything I can pronounce?
You don't need to pronounce it.
You just gotta wipe it off your shirt.
You wanna end up on a plate
next to the salmon, keep it up.
I... I'm sorry we wasted your time.
My husband doesn't understand
elegant food. He's an ignoramus.
Hey, this ignoramus is throwing you
an anniversary party for 500 people.
500, you say?
Let's, um, sit down
and figure something out
because I would really
love to cater this party.
Look, you seem like a nice lady.
It's just that our guests
are comin' in from the Bronx.
They don't know from fancy food.
It's more of a sausage and
peppers crowd. I'm sorry.
I could make you braciole.
You can do braciole?
Yes, and, uh...
gnocchi and tortelloni
and, uh, lasagna verde.
But none of that stuff's on your menu.
That's because they're family recipes
from... my grandmother Bombelli.
You're Italian? You don't look it.
Papa was Irish.
I may get my hair
from the o'rourke side,
but my stomach...
She's all bombelli.
If you give me this job,
I will feed your family my stracotto
till the men can't button their pants.
Now that's what we're
lookin' for. You're hired.
Ahh! I feel better.
All right, let's get back to it.
Hold it. You got all
these problems right?
You cheated, didn't you? Confess!
No, Ivana helped me.
- Who's Ivana?
- That's me.
We met when you handed
me this bucket and rag.
Oh. yeah. Right.
Sorry. Uh, you helped her?
I told her to look at fractions
like a big chocolate cake.
The bottom number is the whole thing,
and the top number
represents how many slices.
Well, I should've known cake would
make everything come into focus.
Math is my specialty.
I have a PHD in engineering
from the University of Bucharest.
But it means nothing in the
American job market. So...
Wow. A doctor.
Impressive.
Oh, the upstairs bathroom has a
bunch of hair stuck in the drain.
Can you take care of that?
Sure.
Mom, this next page doesn't
make sense. I need help.
Uh... doctor?
I'm thinking that drain can wait.
- Nick...
- Hey, Lynette! Perfect timing.
I was just thinking about
busting open a bottle of wine.
Well, actually, I'm
here to talk to Nick.
I was admiring your roses
and I was hoping you could
give me a few pointers.
Honey, you hear that?
People are asking us for gardening tips.
We are officially suburban.
Oh, so... wine?
- Uh... you go ahead.
- All right.
- Thanks,
though. - Mm-hmm.
So here's the key...
you, uh, you cut going away from the bud
- at a 45 degree angle...
- I know about you and Julie.
For God sakes, you're twice her age.
Okay, Lynette, this is
none of your business.
No offense.
None taken.
But you know who might
be offended? Her father.
If Karl finds out, he's
gonna come over here
and cut your buds off
at a 45 degree angle.
- Yeah, thanks for the warning.
- I mean it.
If you don't stop bothering
julie, you will be sorry.
Happy gardening.
Wait, hang on a second. Hang on. Hang...
Wait, Julie said I was bothering her?
Did she also tell you that
she started this whole thing?
She came after me.
All right, there are
two sides to every story.
Yeah, well, your side is married.
Look, I tried to resist.
She just wore me down,
talking about how she'd
never met anybody like me,
she never felt this way before.
She's been jerking me
around since the day we met.
I don't care! Just leave her alone.
Yeah, all right. all right, fine.
If I find out you told anyone about us
you're the one who's gonna be sorry.
So like I said, you
wanna water the roses
you know, a few times a week.
Don't get anything on the foliage.
That's how they get diseased. all right?
Hey, thanks, baby.
You okay?
I think I might know
who strangled julie.
Hey, good timing. I'm
putting dinner on the table.
I thought the housekeeper
was supposed to start today.
She did, and she's fantastic!
And her family escaped from Romania
with practically nothing.
Well, what were they
fleeing from, cleanliness?
Well, I... I didn't wanna just
throw work at her the first day.
We needed time to bond.
Okay, so when does she start
bonding with the dishwasher?
Daddy, look what I did!
Fractions! All right!
So mommy taught you how to do fractions.
Mommy didn't. Ivana...
Ivana take all the credit myself!
Can you believe her?
After all the work I've done...
let's go teach you some manners.
So the best I can figure,
the attack happened
around 11:30 that night.
Now people saw Katherine
leaving the wedding in the afternoon,
and no one saw her again
until the next morning.
So... you have to wonder.
Um... I am sorry
but aren't you gonna
write some of this down?
You totally don't remember me, do you?
Oh, my gosh!
No. sorry. uh, can I get a little help?
Denise. Denise Lapera.
Of course!
A little more help, please?
Fairview High.
I used to sit behind you in
Mr. Parsons' English class.
Oh, my God! I am such an idiot!
Denise Lapeera!
- Lapera.
Mr. Parsons.
"Pit-stain" Parsons.
Oh, gosh. I wonder what
ever happened to him.
Yeah, I actually arrested
him a few years back.
Twice. Drunk driving.
He got a little aggressive.
I had to use my taser.
Part of my was like
"zip! And that's for 'Beowulf'!"
That's good times.
Oh, good times.
And the good times just keep
rolling for you, huh, Susan?
I mean, look, you got a handsome husband
and two beautiful
children and a lovely home.
Oh. Well, how about
you, Detective lapeera?
- Lapera.
Uh, I, you know, you have
done very well for yourself.
Professionally, maybe.
But I'm living in my mother's basement.
I'm sorry.
- Uh, divorced?
- Never married.
Dating anyone?
No, but I did bowl a
179 the other night.
And you're a detective.
So back to Katherine.
Uh, is there, you know, anything else
That you would need
to know? No, I'm good.
I'll just head over
there now and nose around
and see if she has an alibi.
Oh, actually, uh,
Denise, one more thing.
Um, this is a very
tight-knit community,
and I'm afraid if Katherine
finds out that I'm the one
that accused her of this,
things could get ugly.
Aw, we wouldn't want that, would we?
Exactly, so maybe you could just say
it was an anonymous tip or something.
- Sure.
- Thanks.
- Oh, say hi to your mom.
- Yeah, we don't speak.
Oh, look. what a nice gift.
It's the least I could do to thank you
for that marvelous dinner.
Oh, please, we should be
thanking you for not walking out
when me and Nick started
screaming at each other.
Oh, it was just one course.
The rest of the meal
was extremely quiet.
God, you are so tactful.
You think you can teach me some of that?
And take away that earthy
charm? I wouldn't think of it.
Listen, Angie, I have this friend
coming to town next
week, and I would love
to serve her that
dinner you made for us,
if you don't mind sharing your recipes.
Oh, gee, I would love to
help, but grandma bombelli
was real strict about not
sharing the family recipes.
Please?
This friend just loves
good italian food.
Take her to Piccolino.
Their food is good.
Um... this friend...
she doesn't really go
to restaurants anymore,
not since the fire.
People stare, so...
Oh, my God. that's awful. you know what?
Grandma would want this
woman to eat well. Hold on.
Okay, we got the gnocchi, lasagna verde,
the tortelloni, the braciole,
the stracotto, arancini
and the polenta cake.
But... I'm making a big exception here,
so promise you won't
go passing these around.
Trust me. I will treat these
recipes as if they were my own.
She has been over there
a long time, hasn't she?
Man, are there enough photos
of you in this yearbook?
- Wow. Do you still have this cheerleading outfit?
- Mike!
I just thought if you put it on,
it might jog your memory.
Looking at Denise's
photo might do the trick.
Hey, here she is. Yikes.
Hair in the '80s... what
were you girls thinking?
Oh, my God. Moose.
Too much mousse, if you ask me.
No, the animal. That was her nickname.
- Oh, God. Oh, God.
- What's wrong?
This is moose Lapera.
She was the only girl that
hated me in high school.
Why?
I may have mentioned to Beth Porter
that... she had a laugh like a moose.
You gave her the nickname?
No, I just made that comparison.
Beth is the one that got
the entire school to go...
whenever she walked by.
And she hates you because of that?
Well, and also... I
kinda stole her boyfriend.
"Kind of"?
She spent all senior year
in love with Mark Malone,
and they went on, like, one date,
and mark noticed me and
dumped moose to ask me out.
So the guy came after
you. Wasn't your fault.
Clearly you were never
a high school girl.
Moose was convinced that
I stole Mark from her,
just like Katherine is
convinced that I... oh, my God!
I sent her over there.
It's like a meeting of
the "I hate Susan" club!
What am I gonna do?
This was a long time ago.
Nobody holds a grudge that long.
Hey, maybe you're right. Look at this.
I think she might be
arresting Katherine right now.
That is a perp walk.
She is taking Katherine on a perp walk.
Looks more like a perp hug.
What is going on?
What... what is she doing?
I think she's showing us how long
someone can hold her grudge.
Juanita, I was thinking,
after you and Ivana
finish your schoolwork,
would you like to go
see a movie with me...
just the two of us.
Cool! Can we have
junior mints for dinner?
Wouldn't be a movie if you
weren't throwing up candy
on the ride home.
Hi. Can I help you?
Hola. I'm Christina.
From happy housekeeper?
Oh! Oh, there must be some mistake.
Uh, our maid is Ivana.
I request Ivana. Where's Ivana?
My english not so good.
It's okay. It's our new cleaning lady.
Gracias por venir.
Would you excuse us
one moment? Un momento.
What do you mean, new cleaning lady?
Where's Ivana?
I called the agency and had
them send over someone else.
Well... why?
Because Ivana sucked,
and not in that good vacuum sort of way.
Hey, cut her some slack. She's Romanian.
Okay, when your people are
being chased into Argentina
by angry cossacks,
maybe a sparkling toilet
isn't that important.
Argentina?
How about you stick to fractions,
and I'll teach Juanita geography?
Good bye
Gracias.
So how do you feel about
teaching math to 7-year-olds?
My english...
Not so good.
Yeah, I know.
Knock, knock!
Angie, what are you doing here?
Oh, your shortbread was so good,
I made you a batch
of my pignoli cookies.
How incredibly thoughtful of you.
Hey, I smell marinara.
You cooking my food for your friend?
Yes, and I am way behind, so...
Oh! Well, let me help you, then! Wow.
You sure got a lot of sauce here.
Lot of potatoes, too.
This is all for three people?
Well, with food like yours,
who wouldn't want leftovers?
"Vitale anniversary party
- arancino, gnocchi, braciole."
You were stealing my
recipes for a catering job.
I wanted to serve foie gras.
The client demanded pasta.
So you come running to
me with some sob story
about a burn victim who can
only be healed by manicott'?
I admit that was a bit tacky.
I lit a candle for that woman!
If you think about it,
it was a huge compliment.
And the compliment is
that my food is good
enough for your business
but I'm not.
I would never say you
weren't good enough.
Of course you wouldn't. You're tactful.
But you know what? I'm
not, which is why I can say
that you're a two-faced,
condescending bitch
who will never make a nickel
off my dead grandma's braciole!
But enjoy the cookies!
- That's insane.
- I know this is hard for you.
It's impossible. It
couldn't have been Nick.
How can you be so sure? It was dark.
You told the police you
couldn't see who attacked you.
This doesn't make any
sense. He loves me.
Exactly, and you broke up with him.
Honey, this is something
we have to consider.
Well, I can't consider
it, okay? I just can't.
Julie... we watched you grow up.
You're like a daughter to us.
We can't stand by and do nothing.
So you're gonna talk to the police
no matter what I say.
I think we have to.
It just couldn't be him.
You. What are you doing here?
The agency gave me this address.
Please, Ivana, I need you to come back.
Your husband told the agency
that I am a lousy housekeeper.
You never told him
what I was really doing.
The agency almost fired
me. You have to leave.
Oh, no, no, no! Wait! Wait!
- I need you!
- Juanita needs you.
See? She needs you.
She has a test tomorrow,
and when I teach her, one
of us ends up in tears.
Don't make me teach my baby.
I'm sorry. I have floors to scrub.
Forget scrubbing.
Ivana, you have a gift.
Share it with the world,
starting with my daughter.
What about the floor?
You missed a spot.
Got a minute?
This really isn't a good time.
Ooh. Gnocchi.
Tasty.
Don't patronize me.
Angie's are light as air.
Mine are like little shot puts.
Well, perhaps this will cheer you up.
I went to that jewelry store on Maple
and look what I found.
- You like it?
- I told you, I don't have time for this.
You know, it's odd. I asked
them about the first brooch,
but they said...
Oh, for God sakes, Orson,
would you just stop it?!
I have told you again and
again I want a divorce.
Do you think you can change
my mind with trinkets?
I don't want jewelry. I
don't want romantic gestures.
I want out! Now would
you please leave me alone?
Or for God sakes, I swear
I'll throw something at you!
Just not one of the gnocchi.
Those things could put a man's eye out.
Sorry I'm late!
I had to take down some geezer
in the ten items or less line.
Ivana, you should probably split
before Carlos gets ho... oh, my!
Yeah, I got off work early,
so I let our cleaning woman go home.
Juanita, good job. Let's
knock off early today.
Okay, daddy.
Do you hear that? I
think Celia fell down.
Gaby.
I'm sorry.
I asked you for help.
I asked for a tutor, and you said no.
Because you're her mother.
You should be able to set
aside a few hours each day
- to teach your own daughter.
- And I will teach her.
There's so many things
I'm gonna teach her...
how to dress, how to put on makeup.
I'll even show her how to
get a boy to notice her.
That's stuff I know. And
we're gonna have so much fun.
But fractions and grammar and history...
it's just not my
thing, and she knows it.
And then she gets frustrated
because I'm frustrated.
And it's ruining our relationship.
Come on, Gaby. Let's not exaggerate.
Carlos, she turned me down
when I asked to take her for ice cream.
I know. I know.
Some moms are made to homeschool,
and I'm just not one of them.
Okay.
I get it. hmm?
We will figure something else out.
You won't have to
homeschool her anymore.
Oh. Thank you, Carlos.
You're welcome.
Can I keep the housekeeper?
Absolutely not.
I know. I know.
- May I come in, please?
- What now?
Um... I just...
Came to say I'm sorry.
What I did was wrong,
and those names you called me were harsh
but regrettably accurate.
I don't know if you'd even
consider working for me now,
but if you would, I would be honored
to have you in my kitchen.
Well, well, well. You must
be drowning over there.
All right, I'm drowning.
And you want me to save you.
Please.
First, tell me this.
Why don't you like me?
I like you.
I find you colorful and...
Oh, enough with the tact.
Fine. I...
You make me uncomfortable.
I don't know how to respond
when someone is as candid as you are.
You say whatever pops in your mind.
You fight with your husband
in front of guests...
Oh, well, not everyone's marriage
is as perfect as yours, Nancy Reagan.
My marriage is not perfect.
Oh, come on.
Orson and I barely speak
to each other anymore.
We haven't shared a bed in three months.
Seriously?
Well, I never would've guessed.
That's the point.
Our problems are personal.
We don't share them with the world.
But you can't seem to
keep anything to yourself.
What?
Trust me, honey.
If there's one thing I know how to do,
it's keep things to myself.
Well... there we are.
You think I'm vulgar.
Oh, excuse me. Candid.
And I think you're a tight ass.
But you need help, and I need a job,
so... let's get cookin'.
You mean it?
Thank you, Angie.
You're a lifesaver.
So... no sex for three months.
What do you do, sit on the dryer?
Okay, now you're just goading me.
One ham on wheat, extra mayo.
Corned beef, lean,
and of course, an entire jar of pickles.
What's this about?
Honestly, uh, I don't
think this new detective
is up to the job,
and I need a couple of seasoned pros
with old school savvy...
Oh, hello, Susan.
Denise.
Why don't you call me
"Moose"? You know you want to.
- Moose?
Denise, I'm glad I ran into you.
I... I came down here to apologize.
No, you came down here to
get me kicked off the case.
Okay. One more thing to apologize for.
So look, um, I really am
sorry about Mark Malone,
but that was ages ago,
and that guy had "loser"
written all over him.
Hmm. He's the CEO of Malone Enterprises
with a 6-bedroom home
overlooking the lake.
Okay. The point is,
I'd hate for our history
to cloud your judgment
in this case.
You think I'm behaving unprofessionally.
Well...
when you were leaving
Katherine's house the other day,
you two did look... pretty chummy.
Oh, well, it turns out
we have a lot in common.
We both had boyfriends stolen by you.
I did not steal Mike.
Katherine just thinks that I did,
which is why I'm betting
she strangled Julie.
Yeah, well, she couldn't have,
because she was on the phone
all night with her daughter,
- and the phone records confirm it.
- Are you sure?
I know how to do my job, Susan.
In fact, I've discovered
some interesting facts
while investigating this case.
Is it true
that on the evening of September 16th
at approximately 11:45,
you shot Katherine Mayfair?
What? That was an accident.
And you not reporting it was a crime.
Okay, um, let's not blow
this out of proportion.
I hurt you,
but you've gotta get past
this. You can't keep blaming me
for the way that your life turned out.
It's just... it's gonna make
you bitter and miserable,
like Katherine.
You need closure, Denise.
You have the right to be happy.
And you have the right
to remain silent.
In you go!
Hey, Susan, you know
what this is called?
Closure.
The Julie Mayer assault?
We're not on that case anymore.
Detective Lapera's handling that.
Why?
Well, we have some new
information to report.
The detective is out
on a call at the moment.
This needs to be checked out right away.
What needs to be checked out right away?
Did you guys ever talk to Nick Bolen?
The dad of the kid we arrested.
Yeah, yeah, we talked to him.
I'm guessing he didn't
mention that he and Julie
were having an affair.
She broke it off right
before she was attacked.
No kiddin'.
Hey, babe. What's up?
Good news. I am a working girl.
Bree asked me to join her company.
Yeah? Hey, that's great.
Hey, you're still gonna
cook for me, right?
Are you kidding? You're my guinea pig.
Mwah. Congrats.
Oh, and there was something
else I needed to tell you.
Oh, right, right, right. Cops called.
They wanted to know where you were
the night that Julie
Mayer was strangled.
What?
Why would they be asking about me?
I guess because you were
having an affair with her?
Look, I don't know what they told you.
They didn't tell me anything.
I've known for weeks.
Ange...
don't. Don't embarrass
yourself... or me.
You did a stupid thing.
But I know you can't go anywhere,
and you know I can't go anywhere.
So we're gonna have to get past this.
I'm so sorry.
I've put you through a
lot, so you get this one.
But that's it.
You know I never attacked her.
And that is why I lied and told the cops
you were with me the entire night.
So we're okay?
Now we're okay.
The truth is,
there's only so much
we can learn from books.
They can't tell you how
to make your wife happy.
They can't tell you how to
appreciate your neighbor.
They can't tell you
if that man across the
street is dangerous.
No, the only way to truly
learn is from your mistakes.
Of course, if those
mistakes land you in jail,
it might be nice to have a book
to pass the time.
corrected by chamallow35
www.addic7ed.com