Previously on...
A marriage was on the mend.
I would like to recapture
what we once had.
Gaby and carlos
Discovered a secret.
you are gettin' sloppy!
And if people start
pokin' around, we're done.
And susan made a request.
You're asking if i'm okay with
letting a stripp
The first thing you need to know
About robin gallagher
Was that everyone
liked to look at her.
They would stare at her legs...
And her breasts...
And her hair.
And once they were done,
People would begin to ask...
Who is this?
this is my friend robin.
Hello there.
mike had to work today,
So i thought i'd bring her
as my plus one. hello there.
You already said that.
I wanted her to know i meant it.
It's really good to have you
back on the lane, katherine.
It's great to be back.
i didn't know
What to expect at first.
i have wondered how everyone
Would feel about me,
if they were really ready
To welcome me back.
i guess there's always
That fear that people
are going to reject you.
Do i smell appetizers? i know i do.
Hello, susan!
Who's your new friend?
Robin, this is carlos,
tom, roy and orson.
Hope you got all that,
'cause there's gonna be a quiz later.
Oh, god.
So, robin, welcome
to my humble abode.
Thank you.
It's so suburban.
I've never been in a place where
the ceilings were so tall.
Fascinating. just fascinating.
You live in the city?
I did, but i'll be living
with susan for a while.
I just moved in today.
Susan, let's get you a drink.
Oh, no, that's okay.
i'll wait till--oh!
So...
So how did you meet susan?
So... you want to tell
us about your new friend
Or, uh, should i say "roommate"?
She was down on her luck and
she needed a place to stay.
Plus, i feel responsible,
Because i told her to give up her
job. what was wro a stripper?
Well... we probably don't need
to let the guys in on this,
But... robin was-- that's wild!
So you used to be a stripper?
Yes...
Everyone liked to look
at robin gallagher...
But not everyone
liked what they saw.
Later,
While the men of wisteria
lane were trying the shrimp,
Their wives were trying
to control themselves.
You moved a stripper
into the neighborhood?
What were you thinking?
you guys aren't
even taking the
timethere pooling togeth
Our husbands are in
there pooling together
Their dollar bills.
what more do we need to
know? i just met rob
she's a stripper?
Did she mention that
Did she have to?
Look, i am just trying to
help her get back on her feet.
I bet that'd be a nice change for
her. she is livi
If anybody should be worried,
it'd be me,
And i am not threatened
by her at all.
Really?
Yes. she's a nice girl.
Yeah, nice, blonde, and you can
bounce a quarte
I'm telling you, she's trouble.
here's a good thing--
She can't bring any more crazy
to this street than i did.
Let's give her a chance. i agree.
Robin's probably had a
tough life, and she needs
our help. well,
i'm allassionate about it...
But i have teenage boys at home.
The last thing i need
next door is a stripper.
Hey, mrs. scavo. we're
picking up parker for school.
Please come in.
i'll get him for you.
So you ever gonna get back
to folding the laundry?
Well, i thought i'd treat myself
And wash the breakfast
dishes first.
Well, you started this.
don't you think you should finish?
Well, since you're so
passionate about it...
Knock yourself out.
Okay, you just went
From jerk to adorable real quick.
Happy anniversary.
Oh! mm. mm.
It's the ring!
Oh, you went back to
that antique shop.
Yep. Oh, thank you! mwah. mm.
Wait till you see your present.
You can unwrap it tonight
when the kids are asleep.
Or how about after
they leave for school?
Okay. Hey, why are
they still up there
And why can't i hear them?
Hey, boys.
What's going on?
Uh, we're late for school.
Oh! Oh, hey, lynette.
Hi. the next time
you take a shower,
Do you think you could
close your blinds?
I have a 16-year-old son,
and he has friends.
Oh, no.
Oh, yes. you may have
retired from the strip club,
But you're still doing
seven shows a week. i mean,
at least they didn't hav Right?
This is a nice community.
You have a responsibility
to the neighbors,
Especially the ones
with innocent children.
Well, they're not all so innocent.
Excuse me?
Yesterday that son of yours
Asked me if i would
have sex with him.
Parker?
My parker?
Red hair, skinny,
Still-sleeps-in-a-bed-shaped-
like-a-racecar parker?
Of course i said no.
Then he offered me cash.
Come in.
Have a seat.
What's up?
Something wrong?
We hoped it would be another year
Before we had the
parent-son conversation
Where we tell you not to offer
your neighbor money for sex.
But...
Oh, crap. she told?
Yeah.
You might want to pick a more
discreet stripper next time.
What were you thinking?
We raised you better than that.
didn't we? yeah, we did.
We did. so... what do you
have to say for yourself?
I just really, really, really...
Needed to have sex.
Three "reallys.
" well, in that case,
Here's a $20.
go back and try again.
You are a 16-year-old boy.
We understand your hormones are
holding your brain hostage,
But why would you think you
would need to pay for sex?
Because i'm the only
one of my friends
Who hasn't lost his virginity. oh.
first of all, we've
And trust me, "pimples," "braces"
And "beam me up,
scotty" are not gettin' any.
Girls don't look at me that way.
It's never gonna happen.
Knock it off!
You are a great kid!
You don't need to pay for it.
In a few years,
When you're emotionally ready,
You'll meet the right girl,
And you will have tons of sex.
After you're married.
Okay, dad.
Sorry.
Nice job. Thank you.
You think he bought it?
Bought what?
You know.
Guys always pay for
sex in some way--
I mean, dinner, flowers...
Antique rings.
Whoa. whoa.
You think that's the only
reason we're having sex tonight?
Of course not.
it's our anniversary.
It's a given,
like turkey on thanksgiving.
Although i am hoping
That the ring gets me an
upgrade from missionary.
Forget about upgrades.
you just got bumped off the flight.
Honey, wh-- why are
you getting so upset?
Because i didn't know i was married
To such a cynical lug nut.
Wait. are we really not
gonna have sex tonight?
Don't worry, tom.
In a few years,
when you're emotionally ready,
You're gonna have tons of sex.
Come on!
So you really like that ring?
Yep.
Did you read the inscription?
"to my darling--"
We're not having sex, tom.
Oh, come on. why not?
Because i am still
upset by what you said.
Do you really think women
only sleep with men
If they buy them things?
No. i think supermodels sleep
with 80-year-old millionaires
Because they love to hear stories
About when bread
was 5 cents a loaf.
Well, i'm not a model,
and you're no millionaire,
So i'm thinking you
owe me an apology.
You and i went to marley's tavern
On our first two dates,
And i could barely get
past a good night kiss.
But third time out, i dropped
200 bucks at la rive gauche,
And bam! you finally put out.
Finally made love.
Listen, you idiot!
I did not "put out" because you
bought me an exed about you.
I did it because you showed up
for the date with a lightbulb
To replace the one
that had burned out
In the hallway to my
apartment. remember?
Oh. you said i didn't live
in the best neighborhood.
And i was worried about you.
Bingo. i was ready to do
you right then and there.
Really?
That's all it takes?
Me showing you i care?
'cause that's easy.
And now it's time for
your anniversary present.
Hey, robin.
Remember the other day
When i told you this was
a nice neighborhood?
I forgot to warn you--
There's this one bitch
that lives right nearby,
And that would be me.
Look, i understand.
An ex-stripper moving next door
will freak some people out.
No. seriously, i'm sorry.
Apology accepted.
Oh, and, uh, by the way...
Oh. yeah?
The next time you're
giving it to your husband
With the lights on,
could you draw the drapes?
And roy offered to
take me to the park.
Oh. well, isn't that lovely?
Do you wanna watch a movie? well,
i guess i'll read...
I guess we could watch a movie.
No. no, no. if you
want to read, go ahead.
Good night.
If you need anything,
just ring the bell. i'm...
Right upstairs.
I-i'm sure i'll be fine.
Knock, knock.
Robin. come on in.
Can i ask you a favor? sure.
Susan and mike have
been so good to me.
I wanna do something nice for them,
and i thought,
Hey, maybe i should
bake them a cake.
Oh, that's very thoughtful.
Well, feel free to use
whatever you need.
Thank you.
So what do i need?
Robin, what exactly do
you know about cakes?
Well, i know that if
you're gonna hide in one
For more than an hour,
The air holes have
got to be pretty big.
All right, then.
It looks like i will be
teaching you how to make a cake.
Oh, yay! you rock, bree!
I rock.
Now the key to success
Is following the recipe exactly.
The secret to baking is precision.
Got it. you're my hero.
What are you doing?
making you my screensaver.
Oh, that's sweet.
You're replacing my cat.
he's eating noodles.
Let's just do this.
Okay. Go get yourself an apron.
That is, like, the coolest
cake i've ever seen.
Raspberry mocha.
Orson's favorite.
I talked to him at the party.
he's nice.
It must be tough having
him in a wheelchair.
It's been challenging.
Well, they say you can
get through anything
If you have a solid marriage.
Yes, well...
Oh. i'm sorry.
i didn't mean to pry.
It's fine.
Let's just say before his
accident there were issues,
And now we're trying to put
the pieces back together.
Well, that's good for you.
So what's the piece you can't find?
Ah! now you are prying.
What?
We did make a cake together.
Look, my grandmother always said
That if you wanna
save your marriage,
There's only one room to do it in.
The bedroom.
Yeah, i got that.
It's not about sex.
It's about... closeness.
We've lost our intimacy.
Oh. honey.
Sex is how men get intimate.
Well, i'm not even
sure he's capable.
Oh, it doesn't matter.
His brain still works.
And he can see you.
he can feel you touch him.
He can hear what you say to him.
You know, i had this
regular customer--
92 years old, in a wheelchair.
I used to have to push the
oxygen tank out of the way
To give him a lap dance.
I don't know if he's
even interested.
Well, here's the thing.
Neither of us knows for sure,
But only one of us can find out.
Hello, dear.
How was the bar mitzvah?
a boy became a man,
and a rabbi blesseof this piece.
Same old, same old.
how was your day?
Oh, i've been passing
the time reading.
Well, i suppose i should
get out of these clothes.
Oh! peter tchaikovsky.
god bless you.
Yes. i never tire of this piece.
It's extraordinary-
so moving, so...
Sensual.
Don't you wanna do that upstairs?
You know, near the hamper.
Actually, i'd rather do it...
Right... Here.
Why are you walking like that?
Why do you think?
I'm not sure.
You're trying to make me feel
better about being paralyzed?
Guess again, big boy.
Well, if you're having a stroke,
we're gonna make
I do believe it's getting...
Hot in here.
Are you all right?
Yeah. just a second.
my earring's caught.
Enjoy the music.
Oh, let me help.
No, no, no. i'm good.
stay there. i'm coming over.
No, orson, i've got it.
I'm sorry. i'm sorry.
I told you i didn't need any help!
Well, in my defense,
that wasn't entirely clear.
Forget it. this was stupid.
What was that?
What do you think?
! it was a lap dance!
That was a lap dance?
I was trying to arouse you.
You are aware i'm in wheelchair?
well, i thought
You still might be interested
in that sort of thing. i am!
Well, you certainly
don't act like it.
After the accident,
I just never thought you
would ever consider...
Oh, orson.
Things will be awkward at first,
But we can work on it.
You're my husband.
I wanna be close to you.
I wanna share your bed again,
even if it means
Just holding your hand
before you fall asleep.
Come here.
Is this all right?
Let's see--
I've got tchaikovsky on the stereo,
My wife in my arms.
She and danny spent the
whole day together.
What's left to say?
This is out of control.
let's forbid ana to talk to him.
Yeah, forbid two teenagers-
that always works.
Besides, what would we say--
We overheard his parents talking
and we think they're evil?
What do you think the bolens did?
i don't know,
But you don't go on the run for
not paying your cable bill.
They've been cagey ever
since they moved in.
And nick doesn't work.
how do they have money?
Maybe they're drug
dealers or gun runners.
Whatever they are, i don't want
ana anywhere nem
She won't break up with him.
she will if we make her.
I told you that won't work.
We need to come up with
a carrot, not a stick.
Ana.
Privacy, please.
I've got big news.
for me or for you?
You! oh.
I just got a call from my
good friend luke rayfield.
I was a struggling
model in new york
When he was a
struggling photographer.
Well, mostly i was his beard
for all his family functions.
There was this one time-
is the part about me coming up?
Oh, yeah.
Anyway, luke now has his
own modeling agency,
And he's always looking
for new talent,
So i sent him your picture.
Wait for it! wait for it.
He wants to represent you.
You may now begin screaming. aah!
Oh, i have to call danny!
Oh, well, you know what?
danny can wait.
We need to go buy you
some new luggage.
They want you in new
york immediately.
Now? but, uh, don't i have
to finish high school?
World war ii--germany lost.
korean war--korea lost.
Vietnam war--we lost.
happy graduation.
What's wrong?
I-i don't think i can go just yet.
Why not?
Danny and i have a plan.
We're going to new york
together when i graduate.
After everything
i've done for her...
"danny and i are moving to new york
"after i graduate. we're in love!
Pour me some more wine before
i throw up. what's wrong?
Oh, gaby got her niece a foot in
the door for a m
And she's turning it down.
ooh, bad call.
I used to take ballet,
and i was pretty good at it, too.
And one time, this instructor
from a big ballet company
Saw me perform, and--oh,
long story short,
Two days later they
offered me a job.
What happened?
Bobby butterfield happened.
A boy. not just a boy.
The boy.
Oh, i was crazy about him,
Thought it was gonna last forever.
So i passed on the job.
And two months later,
he dumped me for louise mcmullen.
And then a month after that,
i got into a car accident,
Messed up my knee,
And then it was good-bye, tutu.
hello ta-tas.
That is fantastic!
Did we just hear the same story?
You have got to tell
that story to ana.
Putting off your dreams
And then having your life
spiral down the crapper?
It couldn't be more perfect.
Well, i-i guess i
could talk to ana,
If you think it would help her.
Great. and don't be afraid
to turn on the waterworks.
Nothin' sells pathetic
like stripper tears.
Maybe it would help
If i started taping you
So you could hear
what it is you say.
Don't be discouraged
If luke starts you off
with catalogue work.
Just try to get your
face in the shot.
A little tough to do
with a lawn mower,
I was texting you.
oh, i was just coming over.
Ooh. taking a trip?
I'm... sure you two have
a lot to talk about.
So i'll just take
these inside for you.
Bye, danny.
What do you need luggage for?
I was just about to come
over and tell you right now.
When did this happen?
i just found out, okay?
Ana, i thought we were
supposed to go together.
Why can't you wait?
this is a huge opportunity.
You should be saying,
"great, ana. go for it."
If you can't support me,
Then maybe we shouldn't
even be together.
Hey! hey, robin!
Oh, hi. what's up?
I've been meaning to thank you.
You little speech to ana
worked like a charm.
I just took her to
the airport. great.
Mm-hmm. so, uh,
why was she fighting
with danny bol, flowers...
They were breaking up.
They were dating?
Yeah. that's the whole reason
i wanted you to talk to her,
To convince her she was
screwing up her life,
So i could ship her off to new york
And get her away from danny.
You didn't tell me that.
So i don't like being used. oh,
don't get upset need to talk.
Ana's gone. danny's
out of the picture.
I owe ya big time.
Danny.
Hey, i think we need to talk.
Sorry. it's really not a good time.
Actually, this is exactly the time.
I just talked to luke.
Ana has settled into her dorm,
She's got all her classes lined up,
And he's taking her new
head shots tomorrow.
And the best part is,
She is miles away from
the nearest bolen.
Oh, perfect timing.
Something smells good.
Thank you.
Just putting on the finishing
touches before we eat.
Oh, you spoil me. mm.
Mm! what's wrong?
Is it your back again?
Yeah. i spent all day
working in a crawl space.
Aw. i'll call the chiropractor
first thing in the morning.
No need for that. i can fix it.
Come here. ow!
Oh, wait! wait! wait! wait!
what are you doin'?
At double d's, the girls were
constantly throwingo make dinner.
From sliding down that pole.
they all came to see me.
Now just relax,
and one, two, three.
There. how do you feel?
Oh, my god. it's gone.
The pain's gone.
Wow! uh, thank you, robin.
I-i was just gonna
give him a scotch
And make him sleep the guest room.
Seriously, you really fixed me up.
Thanks. oh, please.
After all you guys have done for
me, it's the lent out again.
I'm home!
In here!
No fast food tonight!
fire up the...
Microwave.
Hey. my back went out again.
Robin tried cracking it,
but it just didn't go deep enough.
This is the way the
buddhist monks do it.
It's the only way to get
through all that muscle.
Is there a problem, babe?
No. no problem.
It looks like you're in good hands.
Or... feet.
So i'll just, uh, go make dinner.
Happy trails!
How does that feel?
Oh! yeah, yeah, do that! do that!
Can you handle a little more?
oh! give me all you got.
So i, uh, ran into
janice white today.
Says her husband is sick.
Oh, wow, you're really stiff.
Okay, let me try something else.
Oh,you're the boss.
Apparently, it's bacterial,
And he's, uh, bloating like a pig.
I'm gonna grab it and pull.
Go for it!
And there's a lot of diarrhea!
Oh, yes! ohh! yes!
Ohh, yes!
This is incredible.
Those monks really know
what they're doing.
Oh, yeah.
When do they find time to pray?
Hey! i'm on my way to school.
The faculty volunteered to make
sandwiches for the homeless.
Okay, well, i'll,
uh, see you later.
What's the matter?
I, uh, re-piped an entire house.
even my hair hurts.
Aw, you poor thing.
you want the heating pad?
No. no, i'll be okay.
Well, i won't be gone long.
feel better.
I'll just have robin crack
my back when she gets home.
Or i could stay here and do it.
What about the homeless?
Please. they've gone
this long without food.
What's another ten minutes?
Susan, do you have a problem
with robin working on me?
Of course not.
But she's not here,
and you're in pain.
So why don't you let
me take a shot at it?
A shot at it? we're
talking about my spine.
Mike, robin didn't exactly
go to medical school
Between lap dances.
I saw what she did.
i can do the same thing.
Okay. here we go.
Ow? no "ow." that's
exactly what robin did.
No, she didn't yank it.
It's my arm,
not an emergency brake.
Shh. just take a deep breath.
The key is relaxation. okay.
One... two...
You know, if you hadn't
moved when i said "three"...
Just go.
Oh, my god, susan.
is mike gonna be all right?
Can i see him? sure, sweetie.
Just don't climb on the bed.
Look, why didn't you wait for me?
I would've taken care of
mike's back, no problem.
Well, i wanted to do it myself.
Oh. okay. hmm.
I'm lying. i didn't wanna do it.
I just really wanted
you not to do it.
I don't understand.
God, i've been trying really
hard to be cool about all this.
But when i walked in and i
saw you all over mike...
When--when i was cracking his back?
I was just trying to help.
While you wearing next to nothing
And straddling my husband.
How was i supposed to react?
you used to be a stripper.
Oh, don't cry. why are you crying?
Strippers are supposed to be tough.
Stop calling me that.
Yes, i was a stripper.
But you know what?
You were the only person who
never treated me like one,
Until now. oh.
And i'm really sorry if i
crossed the line with mike.
You know, i guess after working
nine years in the club,
I just don't know where
the line is anymore.
Uh, it's...
I-i overreacted.
Maybe i should move out.
No. robin, you don't
have to do that.
I want us to be friends
for a very long time.
So, yes, i do.
Hello.
Hi. susan asked me to bring
you some of your mail.
Oh, thank you.
I'm robin. we met at your party.
Yeah, i remember.
How's it going?
Oh! i take it you heard
about my little vacation
At fairview behavioral.
Yes. i heard.
Well, to be honest,
It's been hard,
Especially coming back
to this big, empty house.
Not to mention the
subtle glances i get
From people judging me.
But you know what i say?
to hell with them.
Thank you.
I'll see you.
Oh, hey, and if this
house gets too lonely,
I'm looking for a room to rent.
I mean, mike and susan are great,
But it's gettin' a little
crowded over there.
Okay, i'll keep it in mind.
Mm, for what it's worth,
It might take the heat off of you.
No one judges the woman
from the looney bin
When there's a stripper next door.
This is great.
I haven't had a female
roommate since...
After college.
Let's hear it for girl power!
You know, we should go out and
have a drink to celebrate.
Oh, i don't know.
My therapist says i should
get out more, but...
Even being over at gaby's
house the other day, it's...
It's just hard.
Yeah, i get that.
So what was it like being
in a mental hospital?
You know...
As much fun as one would expect.
I only ask 'cause of my mom.
She used to use me
as a punching bag,
And i always dreamed about
having her committed.
I'm sorry.
Oh. no, it was only
when she was drunk.
It was her way of coping
With my dad cheating
on her all the time.
I remember wishing that he was ugly
So other women wouldn't want him.
But he looked like clint eastwood.
Anyway, mom had to take
out her anger somewhere,
And i was an easier target
than a 6'4" trucker.
Actually...
It was pretty bad at the hospital.
People always say it's the
screaming that gets to you.
But at least screaming means
you're alive, you know?
What i couldn't take
Were the people with
the blank stares.
There was this one woman
Who sat frozen in
the garden all day,
Whispering the words to
"old macdonald had a farm"
Over and over and over.
The doctors ever take
offense when she got to
"here a quack, there a quack,
everywhere a quack-quack"?
You know what?
If there were ever two people
Who deserved a night
out drinking...
It's us.
Okay... mm-hmm?
Quid pro quo. mm?
I told you what it was like
to go to bed in restraints,
So i think it's only fair
That you tell me what it
was like being a stripper.
Ooh. it was brutal.
If i had a dollar for every
guy that slapped me on my butt
Just 'cause he felt like it...
Come to think of it, i do.
Excuse me. uh,
my friend and i were wondering
If you'd like to
join us at our table.
No, thank you.
it's girls night out.
Two beautiful women in a bar.
can't blame a guy for asking.
Uh, we're over there if
you decide to go coed.
Is it bad that i wanna
go sit with them?
You do? yeah!
It's been a while since a guy
that cute has flirted with me.
You know what? let's do it.
Really?
Yes. you look way too hot
to waste it on just me.
Shall we? mm!
Come on. you've
gotta have a secret.
Nope. it's shampoo and conditioner.
Well, it looks amazing.
You should be on the
cover of hair magazines.
What is it you said you do?
i didn't,
Her own catering company.
oh, well, thinking about it.
Cooking's a passion of mine.
But a lot has to happen before
i start my own business.
I know. you're a model. no.
Oh. uh... dental hygienist? no.
Oh, i know. you're a
flight attendant. mnh-mnh.
You may as well tell me,
Or i'm just gonna keep
guessing all night.
She's a stripper, okay?
Ex-stripper. i'm sorry.
Oh, hey, why are you apologizing?
we love strippers.
Yeah. they're like
angels of mercy...
That show their boobs.
We should probably get going.
W-what are you talking about?
we haven't even danced yet.
Oh, i don't really
feel like dancing,
Although i can't speak
for katherine here.
Well, it's just,
i wanna dance with you.
You're not attracted to
someone who's classy, witty,
Not to mention
breathtakingly beautiful?
No offense to your friend,
but you're more my type.
Oh. well, in that case,
I guess i'll just keep
her all to myself.
Night, guys.
God...
The look on their faces...
oh, i know.
It was the perfect combo
of "i am so turned on"
And "i am so going home alone."
You should remember that
The next time you want
to get out of a bad date.
Oh, no, i don't think so.
Those two pigs confirmed
What i've been thinking
for a while now--
I think it's time for
me to give up on men.
Mm. amen, sister.
It's official.
my dating days are over.
I mean, you don't have
to take it that far.
You could always just do what i did
And explore other options.
What do you mean?
Cast a wider net?
Expand the pool?
Date chicks?
So you're... yep.
Card-carrying.
I thought that kiss
felt awfully convincing.
Well, i mean, i dated guys
for a long time and...
I just never really
felt a connection.
And then i started stripping,
And i was surrounded by all
these confident, sexy women,
And i realized,
"robin, sweetie, you have been
barking up the wrong tree.
Yeah, i think i got the right tree.
Just sick of barking.
Well, suit yourself.
Uh, you're okay with this, right?
I mean, it's not gonna
affect anything with us?
I-i don't see why it would.
Okay.
Hey, robin. what are you up to?
Just out for a walk.
it's such a nice day.
Yeah, it is. so how do you
like the neighborhood?
Is everyone treatin' you okay?
i guess so.
No one's giving you any guff
about about being a stripper,
Are they? oh, no.
I just wanna make sure,
'cause trust me, i've been there.
Way back when, i was sorta
in the sex trade myself.
Oh, yeah.
I used to model women's
foundation garments
For sears, roebuck.
These breasts put
me through college.
They're real, by the way.
They look real.
Yeah.
Anyway, i'm glad that people
are treating you nice.
You know what the best part is?
They actually see me.
See you?
I spent a lot of years
Working in a place where people
stared at me all night long.
But no one ever really... saw me.
You know what i mean?
I do.
And when i first got here,
I thought it was gonna
be the same thing. but...
I get the feeling your neighbors
See past all the stuff that
people usually look at.
It makes me feel really good.
I'm glad.
Robin gallagher was right.
The people she had
met on wisteria lane
Had really looked at her,
And they had seen her
sense of morality,
Her loyal heart...
Her surprising insight,
Her forgiving nature.
Some people had even taken notice
Of her incredible beauty...
And they were surprised to discover
They liked what they saw.
Sync by YYeTs.net