A proposal was made...
Your niece came to my restaurant,
asked me for a hostessing job.
I'm sorry.
Another was broken.
Oh, Katherine, you don't have to...
Mike, please.
A secret was kept...
Carlos is gonna find out
about this thing eventually.
By then, I will have proved I
can do the job, pregnant or not.
She's still unconscious.
I'd like to run some tests.
Another revealed...
Julie's pregnant.
Bree Van De Kamp was having an affair.
And whenever her lover called...
She needed an excuse to leave work early.
I'm off to the jeweler's.
Gotta get my pearls restrung.
I'm off to the salon.
Gotta keep this red hair red.
I have to visit my aunt in the hospital.
She has shingles.
But on this particular day,
Bree was surprised to find
her work had been done for her.
Morning!
Katherine, it's barely 9:00.
How long have you been cooking?
Oh, I don't know. Since 3:00? 4:00?
You don't need to do
this whole luncheon by yourself.
Well, I don't mind.
When I'm happy, I have all this excess energy.
Gotta channel it somewhere.
Oh, you must be pretty darn happy.
Any particular reason?
Isn't it obvious?
I'm in love.
That's wonderful!
Why didn't you tell me
you were seeing someone?
You know what? It doesn't matter.
The main thing is
you're finally over Mike.
I'm not over Mike.
You're not?
No, silly. Who'd you think
I was in love with?
But Mike just married Susan.
Oh, honey. Their first marriage
went down in flames.
This one's gonna crash even faster.
They're not even sleeping together.
What makes you say that?
Last night,
the light in their upstairs
den was on at 3:00 a.m.
That doesn't mean anything.
Maybe Susan wanted to
read without waking him.
No. Mike made a mistake and he knows it.
He's just waiting for Julie to feel better,
and then he'll dump Susan
and beg me to take him back.
So... grab an apron. We
still have dessert to make.
I'm thinking tarte tatin.
It's Mike's favorite.
We'll make an extra one for him.
Poor Bree.
She wanted to help her friend.
But she didn't have time
to deal with Katherine's imaginary lover...
I have a teeth cleaning,
so I won't be able to help you.
Not when she had a real one.
You wouldn't know it to look at him,
but that nice man
who delivers your mail
hits his wife.
You'd never guess by her smile,
but that nice woman
across the street
embezzles from her boss.
And that attractive couple
who jogs by every morning?
Well, they like their cocaine.
The sad truth is,
we don't know our friends and neighbors
nearly as well as we think we do.
Even the people we love...
keep secrets.
Need coffee.
Mmm.
Well, this isn't helping you get your coffee.
Whatever. It's wakin' me up.
Hey, bud. Hey, what are you still doin' home?
I thought you had a morning class.
Actually, I'm thinking
about quitting school.
What?
Yeah. I thought I might get a job.
Danny, our family's been in
this country five generations.
It's time one of us got a diploma.
Okay, what's going on?
Talk to me.
No one talks to me at school,
no one sits near me,
and everybody thinks I'm
the perv who attacked Julie.
Look, this is a temporary thing.
The police are gonna catch this guy,
and everyone will know you are innocent.
Yeah, but meanwhile,
I'm the campus freak.
Baby, do me a favor.
Let's talk about this later.
If you go to school today,
we'll figure something out
when you get home, okay?
Okay.
Why you being so nice to him?
There is no way we are
lettin' him drop out of school.
I know that,
but we have to be careful here.
You know Danny...
when he gets unhappy, he gets sloppy,
says all sorts of things he shouldn't.
Okay.
So now all we've gotta do
is figure out how to make a teenager happy.
Damn it!
What's the matter?
Oh. Nothing fits.
My breasts have gotten huge.
Oh, yeah. I hate it when that happens.
Every time I'm pregnant...
second trimester like clockwork. Bam!
Why are you smiling?
Why do you think?
"The Supremes" are back.
What did I tell you about naming
them after musical groups?
I know.
It's just that "benny and the jets"
are so happy to see 'em.
This is serious.
I have to hide these things at work
so Carlos doesn't find out I'm pregnant.
What am I gonna do with you guys?
I got some ideas.
Hey, hey, I got a meeting.
Wait, but... but... but... but they're
only like this for two weeks
until they get all sore,
and you give me that "don't touch me" look.
Okay. Goodbye, Tom.
Oh, come on. No, Lynette,
come on. Call in sick.
Kids get snow days.
We could call it a boob day.
Okay, it is way too early
for the "don't touch me" look.
So I waited around all morning, Carlos,
for that repairman that you told
me to call, and he never showed.
No, I'm not done. I'm sharing my day with you.
Then your children took my $300 perfume
and gave their dolls a bath.
Yes, I spent $300 on perfume.
But you're missing the point!
Oh, really? You don't like it when I yell?
Well, how about this?
I have taken care of your
demon spawn children
for 12 hours.
My shift is over.
So, you, uh, having fun
working at the restaurant?
I'm having fun working with you.
Oh! Look who's here.
Hi, Gabrielle.
I was talking to her.
So... I thought I was gonna pick you up.
John offered to give me a ride.
And I appreciated the company.
Okay, time to go inside.
Someone's got homework.
Bye.
Night.
You remember homework, John...
that thing that kids in
high school have to do?
I remember it. I think you used
to help me with mine.
What are you doing with her, John?
I take care of my employees.
Really? Do you drive
the busboys home, too?
I will pick her up from now on.
Come on.
Hey there.
How's she doing?
Much better.
The doctor says the swelling
in her brain has subsided
and she could come to at any moment.
Well, that's terrific.
Mm. Julie, you should see the
flowers Andrew brought you.
They're gorgeous.
It's the least I could do.
Julie knows how I feel
about her. Don't you, Jules?
I love that you two have
stayed friends all these years.
Yeah, well, we... ke kind of lost touch
when she was in med school,
but... but ever since she quit...
I mean, we talk all the time.
She quit med school?
I... I thought she told you.
It was six months ago.
She's been out of school for six months?
You are so lucky you're in a coma right now.
What has she been doing all this time?
She didn't know what she
wanted to do with her life,
so while she was deciding,
she got herself a job...
Waiting tables.
Did you just say "waiting tables"?
I thought she...
Told me?
Yeah, no, she didn't.(Forced laugh)
This is unreal.
Yesterday, I found out Julie
thought she was pregnant.
And now I'm finding out that
my daughter the surgeon
is actually my daughter the... waitress.
I'm gonna need a moment.
Take your time.
I'll... I'll just... wait!
The guy.
What guy?
Julie was seeing some guy.
You two talk all the time.
What do you know?
Now would be an excellent time
to wake up and help me.
Andrew, who is he?
He may be the one that attacked her.
All I know is there was a guy,
but i... I... I don't know his name.
Oh, please.
Why would she tell you she was
seeing someone and not say who?
Because he's married.
What you got there?
Mints.
Mints?
Mints that are...
"Ribbed for her pleasure"?!
Yeah, we found a whole box
of them under ana's bed.
Ana!
Can I have one before dinner?
No! No, you can't eat these!
These aren't mints.
They're... balloons.
Yay!
Grownup balloons.
Do you and daddy play with them?
If we did, you and I wouldn't
be having this conversation.
Nice knock.
What are these?
Well, those are condoms.
You see, when a boy and a
girl like each other...
Shut it. Juanita and Celia
found these under your bed.
Okay, I want a lock on my door.
I've got news for you.
That is not where the lock is gonna go.
This is really none of your business.
Sorry. 17 plus condoms?
Totally my business.
What's the story? Are you
sleeping with John Rowland?
Aunt Gaby, he's my boss.
Ah! And the oscar goes to...
not you.
Okay, fine.
But we haven't done anything...
Yet.
"Yet"? Why is there a "yet"? I love him.
Did you hear me? I said I love him.
I heard you. I was swallowing vomit.
You and John... not gonna happen.
What is it about John
that gets you so crazy?
He was just your gardener.
I'm not crazy! And
this conversation is over.
I promised the girls
They could fill these with water
and drop them off the roof.
Come on, kids. Let's go!
Hey, Porter. Can I talk to you?
Hey, Mrs. Bolen.
Uh, sorry. I've gotta go
pick up Penny from school.
Whoa!
This'll just take a minute.
Okay.
So, uh, this Friday night,
what do you say you help me
throw Danny a little party at our place?
A party?
Yeah. He needs to make some friends.
He's a little shy,
and this whole thing with Julie has not helped.
Okay, here's the thing.
Danny and I don't hang out.
We don't have that much in common.
Well... Danny likes money.
Do you like money?
Sure.
See? You do have something in common.
Are you bribing me?
No. This is to pay for the party.
And, of course, if there's a little left over...
Oh.
And I almost forgot.
You can't have a party without beer.
Okay, is this a trick?
Is my mother hiding in the bushes
to see if I take the bait?
I just want him to have a good time.
So make sure you invite
some nice people,
maybe a couple of cute girls.
Anything for my good friend Danny.
All right, how about this one?
It's a lovely 4-tier cake with pink fondant.
Hmm.
Okay.
Well, after showing you 43 cake designs,
I've learned that "hmm" means "no."
But you're getting married in two days,
so unless you wanna shove wedding jell-O
into each other's faces, you
really need to make a decision.
Oh, I'm sorry. We just want
everything to be perfect and...
Ooh!
What's this one?
Oh, this must be a new design
by my partner Katherine.
You like it?
I love it.
Wonderful.
Now... what flavor do you want?
I would suggest
a classic white cake
with raspberry genoise.
Hmm.
Hey, Carlos, notice anything
different about Lynette?
What are you talking about?
Check her out in this photo from
the Christmas party last year.
Before...
after.
Whoa.
Lynette got implants.
Definitely. And look at those puppies.
Wait a minute.
Aren't you gay?
You can't ask me that.
Well, if you're not,
I'm gonna have to punch you in the face
for checking out my married friend.
So gay!
Judy-Liza-Barbra gay!
Proud member since '89!
So for the third quarter,
net income increased
by 20% compared to...
What are you looking at?
Sorry, Lynette. I just...
I know.
You know what?
Your little secret.
Oh, God, you know about the twins?
Well, I mean, yeah. I have eyes.
Okay, first of all, this was not planned.
It wasn't?
God, no! Tom and I went out to dinner,
he got me drunk, and
the next thing I knew...
Ah.
So Tom's responsible for all this.
Well... who else?
God, you are such a good wife.
I wish you'd talk to Gaby,
get her to jump on the bandwagon.
Doesn't Gaby already have her hands full
with the two she's got?
Mnh, they're okay. I always
thought we could do better.
What?!
You know, Gaby really looks up to you.
If she knew you got a boob
job, she might consider it.
Boob job?
Sorry. Breast enhancement.
Just give her the name of your doctor.
He did great work.
Oh! Oh.
Oh, now I...
O... okay. Got it.
Sure.
By the way, let this be a lesson to you.
Don't try to hide things from me.
I'm a little too sharp for that.
Okay.
Susan?
Here.
Hey, I, uh, just got called on a job.
It's just a busted water main,
so I should be back by...
Whoa.
What happened here?
I came across Julie's journal.
Okay.
She never says his name.
Whose name?
The married man she's been seeing.
She doesn't use his name.
She just uses the initial... "D."
Why would she use a code
in her own journal?
Oh, because she's afraid
her mom might come across it?
Okay, I know that I am invading her privacy.
I mean, screw it. This is an emergency.
I bet this D. is the sick bastard who...
Hey.
Shh.
And you know the worst part?
I read this and...
it's like it was written by a stranger.
I mean, who is this girl?
She dropped out of med school,
she leaves her full scholarship to wait tables,
And then when she came back,
she started an affair
with a married man.
I don't know that Julie.
I mean, what is going on with her?
Hello?
Really?
You can ask her yourself. She's awake.
Dr. Hill? How is she? Can I see her?
Yeah, just so you know,
she doesn't remember anything
about being attacked.
She's very tired and needs her rest,
so just sit with her, okay?
No questions.
Of course.
I'll just... sit.
Oh, Julie.
It is so good to see you awake.
Hey, mom.
Oh, how are you feeling?
Oh, wait. I forgot.
Doctor said no questions.
So.. I'm just gonna sit here
and... look at you.
Thanks.
I'm really tired.
Oh. Well, you just sleep, baby.
Just so you know, you're not pregnant.
What?
Well, Lynette said you
were scared you might be.
But you're not, so...
Yay!
She shouldn't have told you that.
Oh. Now I've upset you. I'm sorry.
Uh, just ignore me and you sleep.
Okay.
If you want,
I could tell your boyfriend
that you're better.
My boyfriend?
Well, I knew you thought
that you were pregnant,
and I don't see you going
the turkey baster route,
so I just assumed
that you had a boyfriend.
I could call him for you.
Ugh, mom.
Unless you think he strangled you
because he's married.
I don't want to talk about this now.
Then we won't.
I'm not even here. You just rest.
How can I rest
when you come in here
with all these questions?
Have I asked you one single question?
I mean, besides that one?
I think you should go.
Julie, please. I am your mom.
There is not a thing
that you can't tell me.
I know, and I'm telling you to go.
Okay.
I miss you, too.
A peach nightgown. Why?
Karl, we are not doing this
on the phone again!
If you can't sleep, take a pill.
Mm.
Katherine, I'm glad you're here.
We, uh, really need to talk.
If it's about ordering the tents
for the Henderson reunion,
already done.
I saw you at Mike and Susan's last night.
You were spying on me?
I am not the spy in this story.
Okay, you saw me.
Want to know what I saw?
Susan went to bed early,
and Mike watched a ball game.
Does that sound like a marriage to you?
That sounds exactly like a marriage.
All I know is,
it was really nice to watch
a ball game with Mike again.
Through a window!
Katherine, you are losing your grip here.
Mike loves Susan. He is
not coming back to you.
And if you can't accept that,
then you really need to get some help.
You just cannot stand
to see me happy, can you?
Okay, I realize you're upset... because
you know that once I get Mike back,
I am gonna have more in my
life than just work.
And I'm not gonna be able
to do your job for you.
Excuse me?
You're never here anymore, Bree.
You're always so busy these days.
But you're never too busy
to take bows for the food that I cooked,
and I am tired of carrying you!
Okay, well, that's gonna stop right now
because I am putting you
on sick leave for three weeks,
effective immediately.
I'm not sick.
Yes, you are.
Now go.
You've got some admirers out there.
Oh?
Yeah, as you walked by,
I heard one of them say, "check
out the rack on that one."
Aw. Can I do the honors and call security?
No, and here's why.
They're the Bertollini brothers.
They've got a $200 million pension fund
they're looking for somebody to run.
Why are you telling this to "the rack"?
Just listen. We take them to dinner,
they admire the girls
up close and personal,
then we close the deal.
And then they leave the money
on the dresser, right?
What, you're mad?
Yeah., of course I'm mad.
You can't use my breasts as bait.
Where do you get this attitude?
Come on. You don't buy
Christmas ornaments
unless you're gonna
hang 'em on a tree.
Okay, bad metaphor.
My point is, why would you get those things
if you don't want people looking at them?
I guess...
I...
I wouldn't have.
Okay.
When do we do this?
Tonight.
And if it makes you feel any better,
buy yourself a new dress...
on the company.
A man just gave me a credit
card because of my boobs.
That makes me feel less like a hooker.
John.
Hey, Gaby. What's up?
If my niece has her way, her skirt.
Excuse me?
You pulled out the old John Rowland charm,
and now Ana has fallen for you.
So she has a little crush. I think it's sweet.
No, no, no.
"Sweet" would be doodling
your name in her notebook.
Ana bought condoms in
what looked like a valu-pack.
Wow. I had no idea she was that serious.
I mean, I was only flirting with her... a little.
Well, she's 17,
so you're also flirting
with an orange jumpsuit.
You're pretty worked up about this.
You should be, too.
If you lay one finger on Ana,
Carlos will knock every tooth
out of your mouth,
which will make you pretty
darn popular in prison.
Look, I'm not really into Ana.
Okay, I was flirting with her
to see if you still cared.
And obviously, you do.
No, I don't.
Really?
Uh, if you weren't jealous,
then why'd you forbid me
to drive Ana home?
Because I remember
what you could accomplish
in a parked car.
Look, I think about those days a lot, Gaby.
I mean, I was just a kid.
You know, I had to mow lawns for a living,
and I couldn't offer you
anything but... but sex.
But now I can offer you so much more.
W... what are you talking about?
I have a lot of money now, Gaby.
You know, and... and you're stuck in a house
with two kids and a husband
who's never home.
And when I saw you again,
with macaroni and cheese on your t-shirt,
I said to myself, "what a shame.
"You know, this gorgeous woman
should be sipping champagne on a yacht."
So... what, you're gonna rescue me?
Tell me you're not unhappy.
I'm not.
Why don't I believe you?
Ana, wait!
Carlos?
He isn't home yet.
Ana, we have to talk.
You knew that I liked him.
How could you do this?
Okay, what you saw wasn't
what you thought it was.
Oh, did you slip,
and your tongue accidentally
fell into John's mouth?
I didn't kiss John! John kissed me!
And no tongues were involved!
Yeah, well, you have
your version. I have mine.
We'll see which one uncle Carlos believes.
Okay, Ana, I'm gonna
tell you something.
Ten years ago,
John Rowland and I...
had an affair.
Your uncle Carlos knows about it.
A lot of people got hurt.
But we survived it.
I have no more feelings for John.
But today I found out
he still has feelings for me.
I saw you staring at this the other day.
I didn't understand it then.
Now I do.
Ana...
I was staring at a memory.
Yes.
And sometimes when I'm
having a rough day,
I think about what might have been.
But trust me, I would never go back.
Look, Ana, I love your uncle Carlos,
and we have a wonderful life together.
Please, do not do anything
that's gonna hurt him.
Hey, guys.
Finally got home early.
Hi. Ohh.
Mmm. Wo what's new?
I was just telling aunt Gaby...
that I wanna quit my job.
Anyway, I have homework.
Mom?
I found this on my bed.
You like it? Yeah. What's the occasion?
The party. I want you to look good.
You didn't have to do that.
Why not? I wanted to buy
something nice for my son.
Besides, it made me feel less guilty
about buying this for me.
Cute, huh?
Yeah.
Wait till you see it on me.
Are you ever gonna get
that thing taken care of?
What, the scar?
Mnh. I don't even see it anymore.
They can get rid of those things
these days, mom.
- Yeah, but that costs money.
So?
We have to be careful
about money. You know that.
I don't see dad being careful.
He bought a new set of golf clubs.
Danny, listen to me.
After the explosion, I was in bad shape.
You father took real good care of me.
He hung in there.
He's a good man. Don't you forget that.
One day, I'm gonna make a lot of money,
and we're gonna get that scar fixed.
Oh, honey.
And don't worry.
Whatever happens,
I'm gonna take care of you.
Whoa. Check out the dress. It's fantastic.
What'd it cost?
My dignity.
Worth every penny.
Aren't you going to check your jacket?
Well, it's a little chilly in here.
Lynette, it's not chilly.
And even if it was, that's more
of a reason to lose the jacket.
Hmm?
Come on. It's just for one night.
Fine.
I will check this for you. Go meet the guys.
And there he is now.
Hey, I was just telling these guys about...
Hey, could I talk to you for a sec, dad?
What are you doing?
What, I can't talk to people?
A lot of people are here,
but you pick a couple 20-year-old girls?
Danny, come on. I'm saying hello
to a couple of your friends.
Yeah, well, don't.
You know, I've been gettin' this
vibe from you for a while now,
and I don't think I deserve it.
Oh, I think you do.
You do? Why is that?
Because I know.
You know what, son?
Jeez, Nick! What the hell?!
What do you gotta crash
every party in the world?
I bet you want him the hell out of here.
I'm on it. Have fun, baby. Come on.
Hi, sweetheart.
Hey!
Hooker's home.
How did it go?
It was bizarre.
From the moment I walked in
with the girls here,
I got smiles, winks. Men pulled out my chair.
The busboy filled my water glass
every two minutes.
And the Bertollini brothers,
who seem to think our proposal
was written on my cleavage,
were putty in my hands.
They signed the deal on the spot!
That's great!
Congratulations.
Yeah.
So why are men so obsessed
with these things?
I don't know what to say, honey.
I mean, some guys, uh,
are just breast men.
"Some guys," huh?
Me? I appreciate all
aspects of the female...
I'm up here, Tom.
Come on.
Come on, I've seen pictures
of your old girlfriends.
Just admit it.
Okay. My name it Tom Scavo,
and I like big breasts.
But you married me.
Man, I stepped right
into that one, didn't I?
So let me ask you. You ever
feel like you compromised?
Yeah.
Okay, I'm giving you
one chance to start over.
No, no, no, no. I...
I need you to not be perfect.
Why?
Because I'm not perfect.
I'm not... rich.
I'm not brilliant.
I'm not movie star handsome.
If you didn't have this one flaw,
I would spend every moment
of every day wondering,
what the heck is she doing with me?
You may not be brilliant,
but you can tiptoe through a minefield
better than anyone I know.
Well done.
Mwah.
Mmm.
Hi.
I tried to wait up, but today was just too much.
What happened?
Well, the repairman finally showed up,
but he didn't have the
right part so he left again.
Then Celia hid my car keys
so I couldn't take her to the dentist.
Then she forgot where she put them.
I told them both
they'd be sorry when their father got home,
except you didn't... until now.
I'm sorry, Gaby.
It's okay.
It's kind of funny when you think about it.
What?
My life.
It just seems so small sometimes.
I spend my days
thinking about detergent and groceries...
or how I'm gonna get the spot
out of the upholstery.
It's not at all
the life I thought I'd choose for myself.
But some days,
I look up,
and I realize I'm happy.
I'm honest to God
happy with my life.
Anyway, I just thought
you might like to know that.
Can I help you with that?
Katherine.
You're supposed to be on sick leave.
I'm better. Really.
Now what can I do?
I don't want to fight.
Neither do I.
I've lost so much these past few weeks.
My job and your friendship... it's...
it's all I have left, and I can't lose those.
Oh, honey.
So... are we friends again?
Of course.
I've just been worried
about you, that's all.
But if you say you're better,
then.... I believe you.
Good, because I really, really am.
What the hell is that?
Oh, that's the cake.
No, that's my cake.
Yes. The bride saw your
design and just loved it.
No, it's my cake...
the one I designed for my wedding...
mine and Mike's.
Oh.
Well, aren't you glad we
found a good use for it?
I watched another bride marry my fiance.
I am not going to watch
another bride eat my cake.
Well, no one says you have to watch, dear.
Katherine, I know you're upset,
but don't you dare take it out on that cake!
It's mine. And if I can't have it, nobody will.
Katherine, don't you touch that cake!
Aah!
Somebody help!
Oh!
Stop that woman!
It's mine!
...  to be my lawfully wedded
wife and one true love.
I promise to cherish, honor and protect you,
and to love you more each day
than I did the day before.
You may now kiss the bride.
Katherine, no!
Hi.
Hey.
Good to see you out of bed.
I'm sorry about yesterday.
So... have you remembered
anything else about the attack?
Nothing.
Uh, Julie,
you know, everybody wants
to see the guy who did this
off the streets, but the police
don't have much to go on.
So... if they could talk to this...
Man that you were seeing...
Mom.
Maybe they could cross him off the list.
He didn't do it.
And I'm not seeing him anymore, okay?
I broke it off.
You broke it off?
Well, that's a motive right there.
At least let them question him.
If he's innocent, he has nothing to lose.
Except for his family when they find out.
So now you're concerned about his family.
What did you say?
You heard me, Julie.
For God sake, what were you
thinking, dating a married man?
Don't do this.
I am your mother. I love you.
I have spent the last five days sitting there,
not sleeping, not eating.
Don't shut me out.
I was lonely. Okay?
He was nice.
It... it just happened.
I don't see how.
This is not something you would do.
Well, guess what?
I'm not perfect anymore.
That perfect daughter you remember
who was always there
when you needed her,
who held everything together
when you were falling apart?
She's grown up, and she's
going to make mistakes.
You wanna make mistakes? Fine.
Dye your hair, drop out
of school. I don't care.
I never expected you to be perfect,
but I didn't raise you
to do something this stupid.
You know what an affair like this can do.
You saw it firsthand.
Morning. Katherine?
Where do you think you're going?
To the test kitchen.
We need to start prep on
the Berman bar mitzvah.
Yesterday, you nearly destroyed
my company's reputation.
Today you're worried about prep work?
I don't want to talk about yesterday.
It won't happen again.
That's right, because you're fired.
I'm sorry, but I see no other way
to get you realize how serious this is.
You have got to give up
this obsession with Mike
before it ruins your life.
I need to work. It's all
that's keeping me going.
You need help, counseling.
I'm telling you this as your friend.
You are not my friend.
Yes, I am.
That's why I'm taking such a firm hand.
Your only job now is to get better.
Katherine...
I'm gonna need you to give me your keys.
There ya go.
A souvenir of our... friendship.
You wouldn't think of it to look at her,
but the lady next door is
having a nervous breakdown.
You'd never guess by her smile,
but the wife of your uncle
once betrayed his trust.
And that daughter you adore...
Well, she's having an affair
with a married man.
The sad truth is,
we don't know our friends and neighbors
nearly as well as we think we do.
Even the people we trust most...
keep secrets.
Hey, Julie.
It's Dominic.
I miss you.
Done by mosito1001 - corrected by chamallow35
www.addic7ed.com