Previously on...
Carlos' niece arrived.
We want you to be part of this family,
but you will obey our rules.
Lynette and Tom got big news.
We're gonna have another baby.
Twins.
You would actually send your wife to prison?
My wife... no. My ex-wife... you bet.
Orson resorted to blackmail.
I think you're the most fascinating woman
that I have ever met.
And Karl made his move.
Katherine's marriage to Mike...
That woman I was with, tell her I had to go.
It's an emergency.
Was put on hold.
You guys are in danger. Get out of that car.
Get away from Dave.
and when the dust settled, wedding bells rang
for someone.
The veil was made from the finest silk.
The garter was trimmed with handmade lace.
The shoes were designed
by the top couturier in Milan.
You see,
the bride wanted only the best for her wedding day
because she was about to marry
the best man in the world...
for the second time.
How do you feel?
Like the worst person in the world.
Don't do this to yourself.
Katherine is never gonna forgive me for this.
Mom, this is your day.
You and Mike were meant to be together.
Wish me luck.
Then by the power vested in me,
I now pronounce you
Husband and wife.
You may kiss the bride.
Yes, the bride wanted
the best wedding money could buy.
But as she left the altar,
it suddenly occurred to her...
Sorry I'm late. Did I miss anything?
She should've spent more on security.
It's not hard to find sin in the suburbs.
Just look behind closed doors.
That's where you'll find your neighbors
cheating on their taxes...
and drinking too much vodka...
and stealing their father's magazines.
Yes, the suburbs are filled with sinners,
some of who occasionally... repent.
We can't do this.
It's adultery.
Luckily, we're both adults.
Mmm. Stop! I'm married.
Yes, to a man who's blackmailing you.
Don't you think making love
to your divorce lawyer
would be a nifty way to get back at him?
Mmm.
Oh, Karl. No. No!
No.
What now?
If I'm gonna break a commandment,
I don't want it to be for a quickie on this couch.
Who said quickie? I've got
40 minutes before my 10:00.
And thou shalt get sweaty.
I wanna do this. I do. But not here.
I need to feel special.
But you are special.
Are you saying
You've never made love to
another woman on this couch?
Not a special woman.
Okay. All right.
I get it. I get it.
I want this to be nice for you. I'll find us a hotel.
Call me later when you've set something up.
Done.
Ahem.
And just so we're clear, this visit was not billable.
Morning. I'm late for school.
I don't have time for breakfast.
At least take a muffin.
Thank you, Uncle Carlos.
Kind of warm for a sweatshirt, isn't it?
Oh, it gets really cold in the classroom.
Mm. Stop.
Lift it up.
Gaby.
Girls who spend an hour on makeup
do not wear baggy sweatshirts. Lift it.
Well, that oughta heat up the classroom.
Go and change.
Gaby, what is your problem?
All the girls in my class dress like this.
That's why your school nurse is an obstetrician.
Wear something else.
Fine. I'll borrow one of your tops.
It might be exciting
for it to go someplace
besides the supermarket.
Oh, snap!
Hey, you I can hit.
Do you see what I have to put up with?
It was just a shirt.
Yeah?
And when she came home past
curfew, it was just 40 minutes.
And when she took money
from my purse, it was just $5.
Why do you always make excuses for her?
She's had a sad life.
Her mom's in jail. Her dad walked out.
Yeah, yeah, she's one dead dog
away from a country song.
I don't care.
Well...
Maybe she would calm down
if she felt a little more secure here.
I'm not signing those papers.
We need to be her legal guardians.
And look after her for the next two years? No.
Until I see a change in her behavior,
I'm keeping all my options open.
Is this better?
Yes. Very nice. Thank you.
Stop.
Mmm. What do I smell?
Despair. Mortality. Paralyzing fear.
Oh. I thought it was waffles.
Do you realize that when
these twins finish high school,
I'll be in my 60s?
No.
No, you'll be in your, uh...
Huh.
At their graduation,
I will be the crazy old lady
with oatmeal on her chin.
Look, I know this wasn't planned,
but we... we can do this.
I mean, we had a lot of fun
raising the first four kids.
But we were done, Tom.
We were across the finish line.
No more diapers.
No more strained carrots.
No more reading stupid "goodnight, moon"!
Lynette...
And with Preston going to Europe,
we even had one moving out!
We will never be done
if we birth two every time one moves out!
That's just math!
Eight and half months to go.
Yay.
Are you all right?
You know what's funny?
I was never able to picture us old together,
sitting on the porch, gray hair.
I tried,
But I could never see it.
I'm sorry.
Oh, Katherine, you don't have to...
Mike, please.
I don't need another reminder of you.
So... how'd it go? How was she?
She was... Okay.
"Okay"? What does that mean?
I mean, did you tell her everything?
Did you tell her we're getting married?
Yeah. I think she's trying to take the high road.
The high road? Um, as in,
"I wish you and Susan the best"?
Or the high road as in, "when I cut Susan's brake line,
she'll careen off the high road"?
Well, she knows it's over, and she's dealing with it.
Mm, that must have been really hard for you.
Yeah, it was.
Mm.
But now that she knows, it'll be
easier when you talk to her.
Me talk to her?
Uh, why? Why? Why?
I... you're the one who was dating her,
I'm... I just... I don't...
I think we're good now.
Honey, you're gonna have
to deal with her at some point.
Fine. Yes, I will. I will.
Um, just, uh, not today, 'cause
today Julie's coming home
and, uh... you know, I wanna get her settled in.
So... what about tomorrow?
Ooh, that's not good either,
'cause Julie and I are gonna
pick out my wedding dress.
You live right across the street from her.
You can't avoid her for the next 50 years.
Well, not 50.
Just till she's too old to throw things.
Don't worry about it.
I think Katherine's really gonna surprise you.
All of the windows are triple pane energy efficient.
Oh, and I should mention the hardwood floors were
completely redone recently. Black walnut.
It's nice.
So do you have any questions for me?
Nah, I think you pretty much got it covered.
Really? Check me out!
I'm... I'm new at this. I just got
my broker's license last week.
Congratulations.
It's a pretty nice house for your first listing.
I got really lucky. The woman who handled
the properties in the neighborhood...
she slammed her car into a pole
and got fried by a power line.
Like I said, congrats.
Uh, Mrs. Bolen's been awfully quiet.
So what do you think?
Me? I'm thinkin' you're full of crap.
I'm sorry?
Well, the fact that we can afford this place
says to something is wrong with it.
So, uh, start talkin'.
Mold? Termites? Leaky roof?
Honestly, I have told you everything that I know.
Sure, you could play it like that.
But if we do buy this place
and it turns into a money pit,
I'm gonna need to take my anger out on someone.
Like maybe the realtor who made a big deal
out of telling us he lives right across the street?
Okay, well, I don't know
that this is actually considered a flaw,
but a while ago, uh, the lady who was living here...
she was apparently going
through kind of a tough time,
and long story short, she committed suicide.
Shot herself...
in... in the head.
In this room.
That's it?
Well, yeah.
We'll take it.
Really? Oh, that is so... that is...
Okay, I'll just... I'll just get the paperwork.
It's a nice place.
I think we could be happy here.
Right, Danny?
Why are you asking me?
I didn't want to move here.
Oh, honey.
Whose fault was that?
Julie! Look at you!
Oh, Angie, these are incredible.
what do you call 'em again?
Pizzelles. Come on, eat up. I made six dozen.
My grandmother's recipes
were always for 30 people.
Trust me, she'd fatten you four up in a week.
These go straight to your ass.
Hmm.
Okay. I'm sorry. Do you guys not say "ass"?
Sure, we do.
Come on, Bree. Show her.
So, uh, Susan tells me
that your son is about to start college.
Mm-hmm. We're just dealing with some paperwork,
but he should be startin' sometime next week.
Oh, I thought he was already in class.
Uh, he asked julie to tutor him in math.
Really?
Oh, that must be Katherine.
I'll get it.
Katherine? Y... you didn't say
Katherine was coming.
She's just dropping something off.
What's the matter? You've seen
her since this Mike thing.
Oh, yeah... sorta.
Your voice just got very high.
You have talked to her, haven't you?
I'm... going to.
I've just been so busy with all the wedding plans.
Yeah, I wouldn't open with that.
Hi.
I'm just dropping off the menu
for the Davenport anniversary party.
You finished that? Already?
It's three months away.
Well, I have a lot of free time on my hands these days.
Hello, Susan.
Oh!
Hi, Katherine.
How... how are you doing?
Haven't seen you in a while.
Well, I've been...
using the back door a lot more lately.
Katherine, your buttons...
Oh!
I don't know where my head is anymore.
Whoa. Was it just me or was that
the most awkward moment ever?
You bet your sweet ass it was.
Hon, could you get me
a glass of water, please?
You got it.
Thanks.
It's our first.
Yeah, I got that.
How about you?
Four at home, two on the way.
Oh, big family. You're so blessed.
I just can't imagine anything
better than being a mommy.
Really?
I mean, I know it's a lot of work,
but luckily my husband
plans to be really hands-on.
Yeah. That's not gonna happen.
Pardon?
Oh, he'll be there at first,
maybe even change a diaper or two
until the novelty wears off.
But those 4:00 a.m. Feedin
he said he'd help out with? Forget it.
Oh, you don't know my Johnny. He's different.
Does he have boobs?
No.
Then you're the only bar in town.
That baby can scream into a bullhorn,
and Johnny won budge.
Okay.
Thanks.
I'm not done.
You see this?
You'll never wear a bikini again.
But you've had four kids, and you look good.
You haven't seen me naked.
My stomach looks like spanish stucco.
And my breasts resemble
two balloons you'd find behind the couch
a week after the party.
You know, most women say
this is the greatest experience of their life.
Most women are liars.
My mother was liar, and her mother was a liar,
and your mother is a liar.
It's a lie every generation
tells the next
so they can get grandchildren.
Please stop talking to me.
No, you need to hear this.
You have to be prepared.
Your children will hit you and steal from your purse.
Your husband will begin to buy your birthday presents
at the car wash.
And the kicker,for the rest of your life,
there will be so many moments when you feel lonely,
but you will never be alone.
They were out of water.
Is juice okay?
Hormones. Get used to it.
I cannot believe we are finally going to do this.
You're not an easy woman to pin down,
but I sure am going to enjoy trying.
What?
This is not what I was expecting.
Hey, I think I look pretty good for my age.
Not you, Karl. The room.
It's filthy and hideous.
Well, I took you to a nice hotel last week,
and we had to leave 'cause you saw someone you knew.
Who we gonna run into here?
Well, certainly not a cleaning lady.
Okay, so it's a little dusty.
But trust me, once I get started, you'll never even notice.
My God, those sheets! What's wrong with them?
They're discolored, threadbare
and reek of industrial bleach.
You give me five minutes, they'll reek of us.
Karl, I'm not gonna lie on that revolting sheet,
wondering how many junkies have died on it.
What do you want me to do about it?
Ooh, egyptian cotton!
These are pretty, aren't they?
Great. Love 'em. Let's go.
It doesn't help when you say
that about every single set.
Bree, an hour ago, I was half-naked.
Now I'm sheet shopping.
Forgive me if I'm an easy sell.
I'm just not sure this color will match the carpet.
Well, get 'em in blue.
I'll tell you what they'll match then.
Fine. I'll take these.
Now we just need to stop for some flowers.
Flowers?
I just want this affair to be nice.
You know, you don't want this affair to be nice.
You don't want it at all.
Don't be silly. Of course I do.
You may think you do,
but I've been chasing you for two weeks,
and you've down nothing but throw up roadblocks.
"Not tonight." "Not this hotel." "Not those sheets."
Karl, if you think I've been
leading you on, you're wrong.
Bree, it's not your fault. It's just who you are.
You're a good girl who never breaks the rules
no matter how miserable it makes her.
I thought a little Karl time
might brighten your day.
But there's not much I can do for someone
who would rather be good than happy.
Can I help you?
I've got a delivery for Susan Mayer,
but she's not home.
Do you mind signing for her?
Oh. That must be her gown.
Of course I'll take it.
We do things like this for each other all the time.
In fact, just last month,
she took in something of mine.
Oh, God.
Oh, God. Oh, God. Oh, God.
Um, Katherine, it's me.
I... I've just come over to pick up my...
Hello, Susan.
Okay, I did not see that coming.
It's just so beautiful.
I couldn't resist.
Well...
thank you for taking such good care of it.
But I should probably go now,
so if you just wanna slip it off and...
Oh, wait. I have to check on my sauce.
Sauce?
Mmm!
Doesn't that smell good?
It smells done.
Why don't you step away from the pot?
Oh, no. The secret is you have to keep stirring.
You know,
I really love this fabric.
It feels so expensive.
It is.
That's why they had it all protected
With that acid-free tissue paper
and plastic garment bag.
Huh.
Maybe...
I should give you some of this sauce to take to Mike.
He used to love my sauce.
Of course,
He used to love me, too.
Okay, enough with the sauce.
I want my dress back now.
Of course. I'm sorry. Can you please unzip me?
Mm.
It really is a beautiful dress.
Katherine was actually wearing the dress?
Yes! Stop blocking my light.
Keep blotting.
Ugh! Mom, relax. We got all the sauce.
No, I still see flecks of red.
It's your third wedding.
An all-white dress is gonna be a stretch anyway.
Do me a favor.
Save the "my mom's a slut" jokes for the toast.
You think I should go talk to her again?
What? Why?
Well, she's obviously hurting more than I thought.
Excuse me, she kidnapped my wedding dress
and held a pot of sauce to its head!
How could you possibly defend her?
I'm not defending her. I'm just
a little concerned. Aren't you?
No! I mean... yes, I was.
But at this point, I'm a little sick of her.
Do you know that when I told
people that I'm getting married,
no one says congratulations.
They all say, "oh, my God. Is Katherine okay?
How's Katherine?"
Does no one remember that you were with me first?
She stole my leftovers. Does nobody remember that?
Did she just refer to me as leftovers?
My point is that I didn't do anything wrong.
You and I have a child,
and I am just tired of feeling like the other woman.
Scary part is, of the two women you could marry,
that's the stable one.
Thanks for taking me to the store.
I promised Roy I'd make him meatloaf.
Oh, I think it's sweet
that you found a male companion
at this stage in your life.
Roy's no companion. The man has seen Paris.
That's right. I'm back in the saddle.
It started one night
when roy asked
if my bathtub was big enough for two...
Hey! You want me to crash the car? 'Cause I will.
Hey, Aunt Gaby.
Need your car washed?
Oh! I'm Aunt Gaby now?
Let me guess. You want something.
Well, there is a party tomorrow night...
Really?!
Okay, you can go.
Seriously?
Well, if you can make an effort around here,
then I guess I can, too. Just be home by 10:00.
Yeah, that's the thing.
The party doesn't start till 11:00.
What kind of party starts at 11:00?
This new dance club is opening downtown,
and it is, like, the hottest thing ever.
Everybody's going. Not everybody.
It's a school night, and you know the rules.
But thank you for washing the car.
Well, she's quite the charmer.
Do you see what I'm dealing with?
I mean, Carlos and I basically took her off the street.
You'd think she'd be grateful.
But every day is a battle.
I don't know how to get through to her.
Teenage girls... they're the best
reason for not having kids.
Thank God Roy had a vasecTomy.
So based on the data given for this population,
and using the standard deviation formula,
what do you think this variable is?
Would you like to go to a movie sometime?
It's not like it would be a date or anything.
We're friends, right?
Friends go to movies all the time.
I don't know if you know that.
Did you know that?
I did know that.
Okay.
Really?
That's great.
Hey, Julie. Nice to see you again.
Danny, do me a favor and
take the trash out, will ya?
Uh... can I do it a little later?
Uh, yeah. Yeah, you could,
but I think you're gonna do it right now.
Hey, thanks for doing that.
Doing what?
Not shooting him down.
I know he's probably not your type.
No, I like him. He's nice.
Well, yeah, yeah, but, uh...
clearly not in your league.
I'm sorry you have to work late, sweetie.
Don't worry about us. Everything is fine here.
Good night, Ana.
Oh! Sorry.
Ana paid me $5.
Ooh! Hey, muscles. I need a lift.
Ooh! Hey! Hands! Hands! Hands!
Um, excuse me!
Sorry to interrupt. But can I
have your attention, please?
Hello?
Okay. Hi. My niece is somewhere in this building.
She's got brown hair, gold leggings, a cream top...
which she took from my closet.
So if you could just look around and point her out...
No, hey, hey, this is important, okay? She's only 16.
And she came here even though
she knew she wasn't supposed to.
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Either you find my niece,
or I will call the cops with their drug-sniffing dogs.
Found her over here!
Here she is!
Stop. Put me down.
Somebody...
Get your hands off me. Let me down.
God, what are you doing?
Ugh.
Thank you, everybody.
Put the music back on.
I told you not to mess with me.
I cannot keep doing this, ana.
Or what? You're gonna throw me out?
Fine.
You'd actually be doing me a favor.
I can take care of myself.
You're 16. How exactly are you gonna make money?
I'm... I'm gonna be a model.
A model?
Yeah.
You know, people tell me that I'm pretty enough.
I... will just... I'll go to Paris or New York,
and I'll get discovered.
And I will be rich and famous,
and no one will ever tell me what to do again.
And you really think it's
that easy to become a model?
It was for you.
What, you left home when you were only 15.
No, I left because I had to.
My stepfather was...
Not a nice man.
My mother didn't care about me.
My father left when I was 3,
and my mother's been in and
out of prison ever since.
I can beat you at this game.
This is not a game, Ana! This is your life.
You can't scare me, all right?
And I don't stay where I'm not wanted.
Oh, don't give me that.
We feed you. We put a roof over your head.
And you're also keeping all your options open.
Yeah.
I heard.
Oh, good, you're back.
The girls haven't made a peep.
Gaby?
No more options.
I am now officially your guardian.
So... what?
I'm supposed to hug you now?
No, you're not gonna want to hug me,
because from here on out,
I am gonna be watching you like a hawk.
I wanna know where you are
going, who you are going with,
and when you are coming home.
And I'm gonna keep you from ruining that life
you are so anxious to start living.
You are so mean.
Yeah.
And I wish...
I wish...
Someone had been this mean
to me when I was your age.
Danny, look, it's complicated.
No, it's really simple, Julie.
You only care about yourself.
Please let me explain!
Go to hell.
Katherine said you were here.
And I thought, since you were already in church,
we might see the pastor
and schedule some counseling sessions.
I don't need counseling, Orson. I need a divorce.
Don't tell me we don't need counseling.
You've been sleeping in the guest
room for weeks. It's not right.
I agree, and if you had
an ounce of chivalry, you'd
have given me the master.
You might think that withholding sex
will make me give up on us.
But I can be very patient.
You do realize in prison,
I went three whole years without any sex.
No, but thank you for clearing up a question
I never quite knew how to ask.
Bree, eight years ago,
we stood at an altar like this,
and we made a vow before God to love each other.
Do you think I haven't struggled with this?
I've struggled with this in ways
you can't even begin to imagine.
Then let me help you.
I can make you happy again.
How? By blackmailing me?
I'm not your wife anymore, Orson. I'm your captive.
Don't you feel any remorse at all over that?
Of course I do,
but sometimes guilt
is a small price to pay for happiness.
There it is. Baby number one.
Oh, my God. It was so worth
cutting class to hear this.
And... there's number two.
Good, strong heartbeats.
Isn't that great, Lynette?
Yeah. Terrific.
I'll...
Get the nurse, have her come clean you up.
Thank you.
So what's with you?
What?
That was an amazing moment,
and you just sat there
like y... you didn't even care.
I'm just tired.
Look, I know this has been a shock,
and I'm trying to give you time,
but it's been three months.
When are you gonna start
getting excited about our kids?
What?
I don't love them.
Lynette.
Please. Don't look at me that way.
If I can't talk to you about this,
then I am in big trouble.
You're just upset because... this wasn't planned.
None of them were planned,
but I loved each of our kids
the moment I knew they were coming.
It's different this time.
I don't love these babies.
Stop saying that.
When you hold them in your arms,
you will care about these kids
just as much as the others.
Okay.
I think I left something in the car. I'll see you inside.
Bree.
Orson will drink too much today,
like he always does at weddings. He'll be asleep by 9:00.
Meet me at the Shangrila Motel at 9:30.
And you won't bail on me again?
I booked the room last night.
I've already changed the sheets
and cleaned the bathroom.
Kiss me.
What happened to the good girl?
She decided guilt's
a small price to pay for happiness.
Ahh.
Frankly, I think it looked better on me.
Katherine.
What are you doing here?
You may have noticed that
I've been out of sorts lately,
and I just couldn't understand why.
I mean, sure, I was dumped by the love of my life,
but it was more than that.
And then it hit me.
My friend...
who was sort of responsible
for my world imploding...
never bothered to cross the street
to see how I was doing.
Didn't have the...
decency to apologize.
I am very, very...
No, not here. Out there.
In the hallway?
In your ceremony.
Everybody in town knows you humiliated me.
I think I deserve a public apology.
In the middle of my wedding?
I found the perfect spot, right here.
After the reading of ecclesiastes
and right before "we've only just begun."
I am not doing that.
Yes, you will,
or I will create a scene so ugly
your guests will still be talking about it
On your golden anniversary.
Okay.
But I am not happy about this.
Aw. Try to smile anyway.
Nobody likes a grumpy bride.
Why don't we just get this over with?
Would you mind getting my gloves?
They're in the garment bag.
Aah!
I'm sorry.
It's just until after the ceremony.
Susan!
And from this day forward,
you shall be each other's home.
You shall be each other's sanctuary.
Susan, let me out!
With this ring,
I thee wed.
Aah!
Sorry I'm late. Did I miss anything?
What the hell? What are you doing here?
Susan knows.
Look, I don't know what you want,
but I'm asking you nicely to leave.
And if you don't, so help me God,
I will drag you out of this church myself.
I'm sorry. I...
I... I just wanted...
I'll go.
Katherine, wait.
Uh... Oh.
Uh... hello, everybody.
I just wanna say something.
Oh, we don't need this on the video.
Um...
when Mike asked me to marry him...
again,
it was one of the happiest days of my life.
But for someone else,
it was the day her whole world fell apart.
And I have to admit, I...
I didn't care.
In that moment, I was a selfish person,
and I chose my happiness.
But I want you all to know
That I am truly sorry
for changing her path.
And I hope
That Katherine Mayfair finds happiness
and can find it in her heart to forgive me...
and be my friend again.
I hope that helped.
Honestly...
It didn't.
Where the hell is Danny?
He left the wedding two hours
ago and he's not in his room.
He'll be home soon.
You know, what has gotten into that kid?
He's staying out late, pickin' fights with girls in public.
He knows better than that.
He's a teenager.
Well, go look for him.
We can't afford to make waves here.
Everyone has to think we are nice, normal people.
Yeah.
It's not hard to find sin in the suburbs.
Just look behind closed doors,
And you'll find your neighbors
Cheating on their husbands....
Resenting their children...
Plotting against their friends.
But as much as we like to talk about
The sinful things people do...
We forget there is a difference between sin...
and evil.
Sadly, there's always someone willing to come along
and remind us.
Transcript by addic7ed.com
Sync by honeybunny - corrected by chamallow35
www.addic7ed.com