Previously on Desperate Housewives...
In the wake of a tragedy,
a daughter was safe...
You saved her life.
We owe you everything.
Orson was changed...
There's a good chance
your husband's paralyzed.
An unborn twin was gone...
We lost the baby...
but the other baby is fine.
- And an ex-husband...
- Karl didn't make it.
- Oh, my God.
-... was dead.
A month after the death of Karl Mayer,
his family assembled for
the reading of his will.
To each, Karl left
something to remember him by.
To his great aunt,
he left a grand piano.
To his favorite cousin,
he left gold cuff links.
To his beloved daughter,
he left cash and securities.
But Karl Mayer left
his most extraordinary possession of all
to someone who wasn't expecting a thing.
"and finally, to my
ex-wife, Susan Mayer..."
Hey, that's me.
Oh, I.. I.. I was just
here to support my daughter.
Seriously, I've been
playing Hangman on my phone.
You were saying?
"To my dearest Susie Q.
Who endured my infidelities
far longer than she should have,
years of cheating,
betrayals almost from the
day we were married..."
Can we just skip to the
part where I get stuff?
Oh, don't look at me like
that. You got the piano.
"While I was never good
at hiding my affairs of the flesh,
I'm ashamed to say that
I was more successful
- at concealing some of my financial affairs."
- What does that mean?
I think dad hid money from
you when you were married.
Well, it's not money, exactly.
It seems your ex-husband
was part owner in a business.
He was having affairs, ran a law firm
and he owned a secret business?
Glad you're finally
getting a little rest.
Now he specifically asks
that you keep an open mind.
It's very successful.
Well, if it's so successful,
why do I need to keep an open mind?
Yes, Karl Mayer left his ex-wife
something to remember him by...
Not that there was any
chance she would forget him.
All kinds of men go to
the Double D gentlemen's club.
Frat boys looking for a thrill...
Soldiers looking to get lucky...
CEOs looking to close a deal.
Yes, all kinds of men go to Double D's,
which can be very upsetting
to all kinds of women.
Susan Mayer?
Jimbo Rooney, co-owner of Double D's.
Uh, look, I was real sad to
hear about Karl's passing.
He was a good man,
and he cared about each and
every one of these dancers.
Oh, I'm sure.
Karl was always a big
supporter of the arts.
Uh, so who do I speak to
about selling my share
of herpes on parade?
Are you sure you want to do that?
Now business has been real good lately,
especially since we started
topless karaoke Tuesdays.
Well, as lucrative an
enterprise as that seems...
Take a look around. Have a drink.
And then if you want to sell,
you have your lawyer call me.
Oh. Look at that.
You made the o's in "Rooney" into boobs.
Lovely.
You like that?
Wait till you see my
partner Vic's business card.
He took the "v" and he made it into a...
Got it. I think I'd
really like that drink now.
Oh, um, thanks.
But I... I'm not here for the show.
I just found out that
I own half this place.
Oh, no kidding. Well, nice to meet you.
I'm Jennifer Morelli, but
at 10:00, I'm "Destiny".
Oh, well, I'm Susan Delfino.
At 10:00, I am in a flannel nightgown.
Hey, we have a Delfino
that comes in here.
Really?
Well, it's a pretty common name.
- I think he's a plumber.
- Really?
Well, maybe there's another
plumber with that last name.
Mike... that's it. Mike Delfino.
Tall guy, brown hair, nice smile?
Big busted nose?
Oh, I don't think so.
Well, wait till the
next time you see him.
A TV? You guys didn't have to do that.
Yes, we absolutely did.
We have a family rule...
You saved our daughter from
being squashed by a plane,
you get a 60-inch plasma.
- and a faux leather remote caddy.
- Oh, thanks.
- This is very generous.
- Please. We could never make up for what you did.
Or for how I behaved toward
you the past couple of weeks.
- I was such a bitch.
- Oh, we both said things.
Yeah, but I said a lot
worse, a lot louder.
Yeah, you did.
By the way, I talked to human resources,
and they are fine with
continuing to pay you
- until the baby is born and for six weeks after that.
- Carlos, that's amazing.
So will Terrence fill
in until I get back?
- Actually, no. He took the job in Miami.
- So who's gonna take up the slack?
Well, I'll put in extra
hours, work weekends.
Don't worry about it.
You focus on that baby.
- Really? I don't want to have this fall on you.
- Carlos, we gotta get going.
We've got Juanita's
interview at Oakridge.
- Oh, right. Lynette, do not worry. I got your back.
- But I feel so guilty
taking your money and
leaving you in the lurch.
Hey, I got a crazy idea.
What if I fill in for Lynette?
Oh, honey, they're in a
hurry. No time for jokes.
I'm serious. I... I've done her job...
or pretty damn similar...
when I was in advertising.
I could step in for her until
she gets back on her feet.
Oh, but that's putting
Carlos in an awkward position.
- I think it's a great idea.
- Me, too.
No. No, I think it's a
great idea, in theory,
but it's just... it's
such a complicated job.
You don't think I can handle it?
No. No, I think you'd be wonderful.
- Great, it's settled then. Tom, you start tomorrow.
- There you go, Lynette.
Now you have nothing
to feel guilty about.
Right. Right.
Well, thanks again for the TV.
You guys have been way too generous.
You made scones. My favorite.
I know. Take as many as you like.
So... what did you want to see me about?
- Well, I wanted to give you this donation for the building fund.
- Oh.
And I also have some
things in the garage
for the rummage sale,
and I am also available
to run the next Sunday
school pancake breakfast.
Oh, good heavens.
Bree, what a wonderful
display of Christian charity.
I just want to do my part.
Does this have anything
to do with the plane crash?
In a manner of speaking.
Do you want to talk about it?
I can't. It would change
how you feel about me.
Bree, I've known you for years.
I don't think that's possible.
I had an affair.
Are you okay?
Um, before you confess a sin that big,
just try to wait till I've swallowed.
Oh.
Who was the affair with?
Karl Mayer.
He was killed in the plane crash...
The same one that injured Orson.
You must feel terribly
guilty about this.
I can't eat. I can't sleep.
That's why I wanted
you to come over here.
I have to do something
to make this right.
Well, seems to me the first
step is for you and Orson
to get into our marriage
outreach program.
Oh, it's too late for that.
We're about to get a divorce.
Yes, but this was before Orson
was in a wheelchair, right?
Well, yes.
I think you know what you need
to do to atone for this sin.
I think you knew it before
I walked in the door.
You want me to bring Orson
home and take care of him?
It's just that I'm not sure
that I love him anymore.
Bree...
There's a quote I've always loved.
"You cannot make yourself feel
something that you do not feel,
but you can make yourself do right
in spite of your feelings."
I don't remember that from the bible.
It's from Pearl Buck.
I am allowed to read
other books, you know.
Bree, no matter what
you feel about Orson,
if you don't help him now,
you won't be able to live with yourself.
Fine.
I'll tell Orson tomorrow,
and I'll bring him home.
Good.
Mmm!
I think you've had enough.
- Julie! Hold up.
- Hey. What's going on?
Eddie's doing stand-up
at the Chuckle Zone
on open Mike night.
Stand-up? As in comedy?
Well, people are always
telling me how funny I am,
so I decided to give the
people what they want.
Don't miss out. I got this
whole riff about airline food.
It's gonna kill.
Hey, Porter! Hold up!
When people tell him he's
funny, doesn't he realize
- they're being funny?
- Tell me you're going. I can't be the only one there.
I'll... I'll try. I, uh,
I actually gotta pack.
My dad left me some money,
- so I'm going back east to see my cousins.
- For how long?
Until they catch the
guy who attacked me,
I just don't feel safe here.
- I get that.
- Hmm.
I've been wanting to ask you something.
I... I heard you were in the hospital
because of an overdose.
You didn't do that
Because of...
I was dealing with a lot of stuff...
problems with my parents
having to move again.
I got really lonely.
And yeah, I guess you were part of it.
I'm better now.
Good.
Life has its low points, and
we just have to deal with them.
Speaking of which,
How do we get out of this?
Well, your timing is impeccable,
because it just so happens that
we have an opening right on.
Yes, we heard, and we're so excited.
Everyone knows that this is
the best private school in town.
It says here that you have
been homeschooling Juanita.
How's that been going?
It's been so rewarding spending
time with my little angel.
It breaks my heart to see it end.
Anyway, here's her
lunch. It's all packed.
And we'll pick her up at 4:00.
Uh, wait... wait just a second.
There are a few other families
on the waiting list before you.
Oh, there are?
Yes, but Susan Delfino gave you
such a glowing recommendation.
And to be quite frank,
We could use a little more
diversity in this school.
It's been quite a long time
since we've had a little
girl of Mexican descent.
Ah, well, we are very
proud of our heritage...
but Juanita can stand on her own merits.
- She's very bright.
- And I know I'm biased,
but I do think she's
a budding young genius.
I'm Mexican?
Honey, what did you just say?
He called me Mexican.
You are Mexican, honey. You know that.
Since when? I thought we were American.
Yes, but our ancestors came from Mexico.
Really? So we're like those people
who sell oranges on
the side of the road?
You're busy. We should go.
Thank you so very much for your time.
And, uh, again, we really
want to join you here
and help you with that diversity
thing, so just let us know.
- Just say it.
- I don't even know what that means.
Just say it!
Adios, senior.
This is fine.
Thank you.
Thank you for agreeing to see me.
I called a few times, but
you, uh, didn't pick up.
I had no idea.
My phone was in my pants
pocket, and I had it on vibrate.
And as you may have noticed, I...
So how's rehab?
Painful.
Well, the doctor says
with a lot of hard work,
you maybe be able to walk again someday.
Yes, they're very upbeat and optimistic.
I want to run them over with this chair.
So...
why are you here?
Well, I know we've been
through a lot lately,
but I decided it would be
best for you to come home
so I can take care of you.
Yes, I'd rather be cared for
by a flatulent helper monkey.
- Orson, I know you're angry, but I'm still your wife.
- Well, apparently we have
very different definitions
of the word "wife."
- I am proceeding with the divorce.
- I don't understand.
Three weeks ago you were
begging me for another chance.
What happened?
Karl Mayer happened.
I could forgive you
if you betrayed me with
anyone remotely admirable,
but you chose
the most contemptible
man I have ever known.
No, Bree,
I do not need you.
I'm having a ramp built at the house,
and I've turned the downstairs
study into your bedroom.
You're coming home where you belong,
and that's all there is to it.
You can start forgiving me,
and I'll start forgiving you.
I suggest you start first.
I don't understand. How could
you not know you're Mexican?
We eat Mexican food all the time.
We eat Chinese food, too.
Does that mean I'm Chinese?
No, that just means your
mother hates to cook.
Well, apparently, we have to
spell everything out for you.
- You do know you're a girl, right?
- Gaby.
What? Half the women in
your family have mustaches.
It could be very confusing.
Juanita, go inside and
play with your sister.
And while you're at it,
tell her she's Mexican, too!
I can't believe it.
We had that school right in our hands.
- How could we let it get away?
- The bigger question is how did we let our daughter
- grow up thinking she's white?
- Hey, Mr. and Mrs. Solis.
Hey, Parker.
Hey. Sorry I'm late.
I had to pick up some lumber
to build that ramp for Orson.
Oh, what a good person you are.
Hey, I need to pay
the paperboy tomorrow.
- Do you have any cash?
- I think I have a $20 on me.
Wouldn't you rather...
stick it in here?
Couldn't we just leave
it in the mailbox,
- like we usually do?
- Oh, I just thought
that's the way you do
it down at Double D's.
- Double D's?
- Yeah, turns out Karl was a part owner
and left me his share.
By the way,
"Destiny" says hello.
Okay. I see where
you're going with this.
Do you, Mike Delfino?
That's what she calls you, you know.
Because that's my name.
No one hanging from a
pole should know your name.
Susan, that place is one of my accounts.
I'm their plumber.
And that's it?
- You go there just to do the plumbing and nothing else?
- Well...
Liar! Destiny said you had
a beer there the other night.
Okay.
Sometimes when I finish
the job, I'll have a beer.
And you never look at the girls?
It's... it's... it's
completely innocent.
I... I... I don't buy that.
I want to see the "completely
innocent" look you have
when Destiny shakes her
tassels in your face.
Okay, so I've gone to a strip club.
Are we gonna laugh about this,
or you gonna make it a thing?
- Well, I am leaning towards "thing."
- Fine. If it bothers you that much,
next time I finish a job
there, I'll come right home.
Oh, you don't have to worry,
because you will not be working
there anymore. I forbid it.
You forbid it?
What kind of marriage is this?
The kind where the husband
wants to look at strippers
and the wife forbids it.
Susan, I love you.
I have never cheated
on you and I never will.
But you're not gonna tell
me what I can or can't do.
Let me get this straight...
You forbid Mike from
going to a strip club?
I know it was a little heavy-handed,
- but I just can't stand those places.
- Oh, what's the big whoop?
Carlos takes clients to
the strip club all the time.
I've been to one... the ass menagerie.
It was my brother's bachelor party.
This stripper named
Cinnamon gave me a lap dance.
Luckily, if I squinted just enough,
she looked like a young Ricky Schroder.
See, this is the reason
men go to those places...
- So they can fantasize. We all do it.
- You fantasize about other men when you're with Carlos?
Honey, Carlos has been
so many different men,
I'm actually surprised when I
open my eyes and it's Carlos.
Want to know who I fantasize about?
No, not necessarily.
Anyone want more wine?
Tom Scavo.
Wine now.
4th of July barbecue.
Those tan shorts.
Oh, I am there right now. Ooh!
Okay, could we please get
back to the issue at hand?
Look, bottom line is
you cannot forbid a man
to go to strip clubs.
And don't expect him to
understand why it bothers you.
That's just the way they are. Right?
Sorry. I was just
imagining Ricky Schroder...
wearing Tom Scavo's shorts.
Are you sure you want to
just give away your CDs?
The more you take, the
less I have to pack.
- In fact, is there anything else you want?
- Anything?
Okay. How about... Danny Bolen?
Uh, he's not really mine to give.
Come on. He's totally into you,
which is a complete mystery to me.
You know what? I think
I'm just gonna keep my CDs.
Okay, I... I didn't mean it like that.
It's just you don't seem interested,
- and I have sent every signal I can think of.
- Why are you so hung up on Danny?
Hello. He's hot.
Okay, here's the thing...
Danny's in kind of a
fragile place right now.
He really doesn't need
to get his heart broken.
I'm not gonna snag him
just to toss him aside.
I don't use people, Julie.
Okay, I used some people.
But I wouldn't use him.
Are you sure?
Yeah. I think we have a lot in common,
and if he'd just spend a little
time with me, he'd realize that.
You like stand-up comedy?
Yeah.
Too bad. We're gonna go see Eddie.
- Hey, honey.
- Hey.
Sorry I'm late.
How was work?
Crazy.
I had three conference calls
and a 2-hour client
meeting with Gary Danner.
- Oh.
- Mm. How was your day?
Even crazier.
I peed twice in every
bathroom in the house.
What's that?
Oh, little matching outfits for
the twins that people gave us.
I thought I'd give them to charity.
I ran into the Petersons today.
They just heard, wanted
to see how you were.
Mm.
So Gary Danner...
He's a prickly S.O.B.
Tell me about it.
Check out this proposal
I worked up for him.
Hmm.
What do you mean, "hmm"?
I'm glad you showed this
to me. I know Danner.
- And trust me, you do not want to go down this road.
- Why not?
- Don't worry. I can fix it. Where's
a pen? - Wait, honey, a-actually...
I showed it to Danner
today. He loved it.
Gary Danner liked this?
No, he loved it,
But not as much as
Carlos. He told me it was
the best written proposal
he has ever seen, bar none.
What's for dinner?
Meat loaf.
Mmm.
What's wrong?
Nothing. It's j... well,
that's quite a compliment.
- Yeah.
- Not to mention a bit of a slam on the work that I did.
Honey, he's just encouraging me.
- I don't think he was thinking about you at all.
- Oh. Okay.
By the way, this meat loaf...
The best I have ever tasted.
- Bar none?
- Hmm?
Just eat.
Wow. It's coming along beautifully.
Thanks. So, uh, when's
Orson coming home?
Oh, uh, it's still a bit up in the air.
But I guess now would be
a good time to call him
And let him know we're almost ready.
Uh, yes. Orson Hodge's room, please.
Would you stop hammering for a moment?
He checked out?
But that's impossible.
Where would he have gone?
- Mike, please.
- It's not me.
Never mind. I think I found him.
Oh, boy. The fat's in the fire now.
What is going on here?
The husband you're
divorcing has found new digs.
Before you jump down my throat...
Roy and I are on fixed incomes.
You can't blame us for
taking in a boarder,
especially one who can't
get to the second story.
That's our naked floor.
What are you doing here?
Enjoying my new home.
It's rather quaint,
once you get used to the smell
of denture cream and scotch.
Oh, don't mind me.
Just making sure you don't
slap a guy in a wheelchair.
So how are you planning
to pay your rent?
Well, I'm a bit
cash-strapped at the moment.
But karen knows I'm good for it.
Yeah, once he gets
his divorce settlement,
he's writing me a big, fat check.
So how long are we
talking? A month, two?
There will be no divorce, and
if he tries to file for one,
there will be delays,
motions and appeals.
It could take years for
him to ever see a dime.
Your wife loves you. Go home.
Bree, stop right now. Do you hear me?
So am I taking down the ramp?
Leave it.
You'll need it soon enough.
Almost home, dear.
Mike, call the police. My
wife is holding me hostage!
We've all been there, big guy.
Lynette.
I had an appointment with
my O.B. around the corner,
- and I just thought I'd stop by and say hi.
- Oh.
I also wanted to thank you
for being so nice to
tom, our little temp.
- How's he doing?
- He's amazing.
It's okay, Carlos. You
can tell me the truth.
He's knocking my socks off.
Everybody is so impressed.
Well, good.
Good, good, good.
I'm so proud of him.
But when I drop this kid,
Tom's out on his ass, right?
Excuse me?
I love him and I'm glad
he's doing well here,
but this is my job.
At some point, I'm gonna want it back.
And I say that as the
woman who dove in front
of a spinning propeller
to save your child's life.
Of course this is your job.
And you can have it
back any time you want.
Well, that's all I needed to hear.
It's just that I was
under the impression
you were planning to stay
at home with your baby.
And why would you be
under that impression?
That's what Tom said.
What exactly did tom say?
Lynette, I really don't want
to get in the middle of this.
Carlos, I saved a member of your family.
It doesn't mean I can't
take another one out.
And... and... and you can train a dog
to do almost anything,
but you can't do, um,
you can't do with cats and... cats.
And did you ever try
to get a cat to fetch?
They're like, you
know, they won't do it.
Stupid cats. Am I right, people?
Well... well, hey, you
guys have been great.
Good night.
Give it up for Eddie Orlofsky
Come on, folks!
Yeah! Whoo!
So, what do you think?
I never realized there were
so many differences
between dogs and cats.
That's why I'm the comic, babe.
I'm off to get my free drink.
Porter,
I left my jacket in
the car. Walk me out?
Jacket? It's hot as hell in here.
Ooh. Now I feel a chill.
Mm-hmm.
Um... I gotta use the bathroom.
Okay, what is your problem?
Excuse me?
Whenever we're alone together,
you find some reason to bail.
Why aren't you into me?
Ana, there's not a lot
of room to be into you.
Because of how much you're into you.
You did not just call me conceited.
Chill. It's not like I
asked you to spell it.
I'm not stupid, and I am definitely
not the attention whore at this table.
I heard about your little
stunt with the pills.
Okay, that was mean.
I'm sorry that I said that.
Don't be sorry.
You're right.
I like the blunt Ana
more than the cute Ana.
So...
you think I'm cute?
You're home. Perfect timing.
Margaritas. What's the occasion?
We're getting drunk, Mexican style.
Principal Hobson just called,
and Juanita got accepted to Oakridge.
Seriously?
I am free from homeschooling.
No more fighting, no more threats,
and no more parent-teacher
conferences with you.
Mmm.
Ahh. Come on. Start guzzlin'.
Uh, I don't think she should go.
- Huh?
- I've been thinking about it all day.
Let's keep her in public school.
- We can't. She was expelled.
- I made some calls.
Jefferson elementary can take her.
That's way out in my pleasant.
Yeah, and there's a
lot of Latino families
- that live in that area.
- So what?
We have a much better school
right here in our backyard.
I'm not schlepping way over there
just so she can be with those people.
"those" people? Don't
you mean our people?
Our people are the rich
private school people.
Oh, my God. I know exactly
what is going on here.
What? You are ashamed of being Mexican.
- Oh, that's insane.
- No, it totally makes sense.
All of our friends are white.
You didn't want me to
teach the girls Spanish.
Because I don't understand it,
and I didn't want you guys
plotting behind my back.
And when we bought this house,
and I said we would be the only
Mexicans in the neighborhood,
do you remember what you said?
- "Fine by me."
- You're right. It's my fault.
I should have told the realtor,
"forget square footage and central air.
Find us something next
door to a Mariachi bar."
Deny it all you want. You
are a self-hating Mexican.
Oh, yeah, well, you're
a self-wiping Mexican.
What does that mean?
Hey, you.
Traffic was insane.
Is there any dinner left?
I haven't eaten since lunch.
Everything okay?
I talked to Carlos today.
About what?
He was under the impression
that when I have this baby,
I'll be staying home with her.
Where would he get a
crazy idea like that?
I told him.
Wow! You're not even denying it?
I thought it might be
in your best interest.
Seriously?
You know how much that job means to me.
You know how much I hate
being a stay-at-home Mom.
How could you think
I'd be okay with this?
Because we lost a baby.
Honey, I thought you might
want to stay home with this one,
because she's all the more
precious, given what happened.
Oh.
So that's how I'm supposed to feel.
I don't know how you feel Lynette,
because you never talk about it.
It's been a month. Every
time I try to bring it up,
- you just... you change the subject.
- Because I'm dealing with it.
Well, shouldn't we be
dealing with it together?
You want to talk about this?
- Yes!
- Fine! We lost a kid we'll never meet him.
We'll spend the rest of
our lives looking at one,
always wondering why there aren't two.
How can saying this out loud be helpful?
You're right. It's not.
You win.
After you have the baby,
go back to your job.
Thank you.
You want me to fix you something?
I'm not... I'm not hungry anymore.
Now remember, fellas,
these ladies don't work for free.
Hey, Rooney.
Oh, hey, Mike. Long time no see.
Yeah, I got the call about
your John being backed up.
What? No, our bathrooms
are working just fine.
That's weird. Some woman called
and said it was an emergency.
I'm sorry, man. I... I
don't know what to tell you.
All right, it's time to introduce
our newest double D doll...
Miss Fix-it!
What the hell?
Susan!
Mike! What are you doing here?
What the hell are you doing?
Oh, well, since I'm one of the owners,
I figured I should
really learn the business,
from my bottom up.
Hey, you mind?
I'm trying to make a deposit here.
- Hey!
- Will you come down from there right now?
Why? They're just looking.
It's completely innocent.
Right?
Hey, pal. Sit down.
I didn't come here to
see the back of your head.
This is not funny.
Oh, I can't talk.
I've got a room full of
Neanderthals to entertain.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. What are you doing?
Just giving people what they want.
Don't you dare. Susan, I'm serious.
I want you off of that stage right now.
Wait. Are you forbidding
me from doing something?
I thought we didn't have
that kind of marriage.
Very cute. If I have to, I will
carry you out of here myself.
Oh, what exactly is the problem, Mike?
Oh!
Okay. I get it.
I will never come back here.
Aw! Come on!
Let's go home, Mrs. Fix-it.
Wait. Wait. Forgot my tips!
What are you looking at?
Nothing. Just some old photos.
I didn't know you had these.
We couldn't afford frames,
so my dad would put these
on the wall with tape.
Is that you?
Yeah. I was about 5.
- You're cute.
- Hmm.
But that toolshed's seen better days.
That was our house.
Wow.
It's funny.
I'm smiling in all of
these photos, but...
I hated that town.
Everybody was so poor.
Everybody was Mexican.
Back then I thought
they were the same thing.
And even though I was only
5, I knew I wanted out.
And you can call it
self-loathing, Carlos,
but I just...
don't want my kids to ever
know I lived like that.
That's your dad.
Yeah.
He was so strong.
I would run to meet him
when he'd come home from
working in the factories,
and he'd lift me up on his shoulders.
I loved that.
I bet he did, too.
I used to ask him, "Papa,
why do you work so much?"
And he would say,
"so one day we can live
in a beautiful house."
But we never did.
But you do now.
Your father had dreams, Gaby,
but they were for you,
and he sacrificed a lot to get you here.
Whatever our children achieve in life,
it's because of dreams that started
on the shoulders of a
proud, strong, Mexican man.
That is why I want our kids
to know where they came from.
I want that, too.
So, um...
How do your physical
therapists think you're doing?
Do they think you're making progress?
Orson, it's been three days.
You're gonna have to
talk to me sometime.
I know why you're doing this, Bree.
Reverend Sykes stopped by
to check on my progress.
He was very proud of himself
for convincing you to
take me on as charity work.
It's not charity work.
When I had that affair,
I didn't just betray you.
I betrayed my faith as well.
So please, you have to let
me help you or I am gonna...
Or you won't get into heaven?
Didn't realize how
much this means to you.
I guess I can find a way to be happy.
Thank you so much, Orson.
I am gonna take such good care of you.
By the way, my soup is cold.
Oh.
Well, mine is hot.
You can have this.
Oh, while you're up, could
you get me a glass of wine?
Yes, of course.
And perhaps for dessert,
some of your delicious Crme brule.
Orson, that takes over
an hour to prepare. I...
Well, I would do it myself, but...
Oh, and we're out of vanilla beans.
You might have to run to the store.
The act itself is quite simple...
You strip away the outer layer
and reveal what's underneath.
Of course,
sometimes the results
can be quite surprising.
If you strip away the
veneer of happy domesticity,
you may find grief.
If you strip away that facade of wealth,
you may find self-loathing.
If you strip away the
veil of helplessness,
you may find cruelty.
Yes, stripping can be
a dangerous pastime.
But for a lucky few,
it can also be...
a lot of fun.
corrected by chamallow35
www.addic7ed.com