Previously on...
He's in your band.
- This is too dangerous.
There were victims
of both violence
and hard times.
- We're sort of broke.
I thought Scavo's was doing well.
- When times get tough,
people do without things
like pizza.
And beneficiaries...
The deal closed. I got the bonus.
- and good work...
and perseverance.
Congratulations on your new job.
Congratulations on getting me
out of your office.
It's not hard
to spot a mother
who works outside the home.
Just look for someone
who dresses in a hurry...
eats her breakfast
while rushing to her car...
and applies her makeup
as she drives away.
But the surest way
to spot a mother
who works outside the home?
Just look for a child...
- M.J., why aren't you dressed?
We're gonna be late
for our first day of school.
who gets sick
at the worst possible moment.
Hey, guys. How you doing?
He's sick. I'm late.
- Thanks for helping.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. I gotta work.
- So do I,
and it's my first day
at a new job. I win.
What...
Look, I'd really like
to help you out...
and spend some time
with my best bud, but, uh,
Ms. Nelson's septic tank
is expecting me at 9:00.
You're a plumber. Ms. Nelson
is not expecting you on time.
In fact, if you show up before
dinner, she'll turn cartwheels.
I'm a teacher.
It's different.
Wait, I thought you were
just a teacher's assistant.
Well...
Listen to me.
The whole reason I went back to
work is so we could both afford
to give M.J. The things
we felt he needed.
Now I'm doing my part.
It's time you do yours.
I'll reschedule Ms. Nelson.
I gotta go.
You get lots of rest and drink
plenty of fluids, okay?
You never left me
when I'm sick before.
Oh, I know, Honey.
But mommy has a job now.
Come on. We talked about this.
You understand, right?
Don't be sad.
I am gonna pick you both up
at 6:00.
Yes, it's not hard
to spot a mother
who works outside the home.
Just look for a woman
who leaves her house
every morning
feeling incredibly guilty.
It begins just after sundown,
after a long day at the office,
exhausted people
start coming home.
Some are met by faithful pets...
Some are welcomed
with dry martinis.
Others are greeted
with dinner on the table.
Then there are those
who return
from a long day at work...
only to discover...
unpleasant surprises.
Oh! Good. You got my note.
Come on in.
Okay, Sure.
Uh, where's M.J.?
Here I am, Mommy.
Oh, hey, baby. How's my boy?
I missed you so much.
Are you feeling better?
Yeah.
Katherine made me soup
and read me a story
and showed me
how to play blackjack.
What are
you gonna remember?
Always double down
on a pair of aces.
That's cute.
Where's Mike?
Plumbing emergency.
Ms. Nelson's toilet
began erupting,
and I wasn't busy, so...
Uh-huh.
Well, uh, thank you very much
for helping us out.
Come on, M.J.
It's time to go.
thank you.
We already thanked her,
buddy.
Let's not
make her uncomfortable.
Thank you
for having us over.
We are so honored
to be the first guests
in your new home.
Your stunning new home.
I can't believe this.
The theme of my first place
was Early American beanbag.
Well, it's all Andrew.
He's the one with the taste.
Please.
Uh, he's running late.
Um, do you know why?
Ah, he's cleaning up
a little mess.
Someone didn't know
you couldn't serve
bacon-wrapped shrimp puffs
at a Bar Mitzvah.
I knew. I just thought
if they'd tasted mine,
they might change the rules.
So would you like something
to nibble on before dinner?
Is that cut crystal?
It's exquisite.
Andrew again.
He's got expensive taste.
Thank God he brings in
the big bucks.
He does?
Well, he does now, ever since
you gave him that raise.
That is a delicious snack.
Did you make this?
Uh, yeah. It's just...
party mix.
Oh.
You gave Andrew a raise?
- A tiny salary bump.
"Tiny" is not the word for
your extraordinary generosity.
Oh, look!
There's pretzels and cereal.
I can see why
they call it "party mix."
It's like a party in a bowl.
When you say "extraordinary"--
He's exaggerating.
They're children.
It just looks like
a lot of money to them.
My God!
Is this a... '96 Latour?
I know. Andrew bought
a case of it at a wine auction
to celebrate that huge raise.
Once you've had
a few glasses of this,
you're not going to remember
this evening at all.
We'll see.
Boy,
dinner without the kids...
It's nice to eat without
having macaroni thrown at you.
Yes.
Well, we, uh, we really
wanted to find a way
to thank you both.
- Thank us for what?
Saving our marriage.
Please. It was our pleasure.
How did we do that again?
Well, Bradley had been
working around the clock,
and I was feeling neglected.
But things are different
now that he has Carlos.
We have never felt closer.
And, Gaby, I know I've been
relying on Carlos a lot.
I-I hope it's not a problem, his
being away from home so much.
Oh, I'll be
more willing to forgive
once his bonus check comes in.
- And the only person
more excited than Gaby
about that bonus is her jeweler.
Brad, don't.
It's been such a nice night.
He's gonna hear it tomorrow anyway.
Hear what?
Look, I'm sorry,
but we're forgoing bonuses
this year.
Can I get anyone dessert?
Beat it. What?
It's the economy.
Um, our C.F.O. feels we need
to do some belt tightening.
But do you know how much
overtime Carlos has pulled?
How many trips he's taken?
He's killed himself.
For God sakes,
don't do this to my jeweler.
But, Gaby, no one's getting
a bonus, not even Brad.
So this was his bonus? A salad
and a stuffed chicken breast?
Look, hopefully next year
will be better.
We're ready for dessert now.
Wrap up ten lobsters to go.
Ahem.
Tom?
Come here.
We haven't had a customer
in about a half an hour,
so maybe we should just...
close up early.
No. I got an idea.
Hey, everybody, hey,
take off your aprons
and come sit near the window.
What is this?
- It's called psychology.
Come on! Hey! Guys...
Nobody wants to eat
in an empty restaurant, right?
So, guys, this is
what we are gonna do.
As soon as you see
someone go by,
you laugh, act like
you're having a great time.
It'll draw them in.
So now we have
pretend customers?
Gee, let's think
of something to do
with all the pretend money
we're gonna make.
Trust me. This is gonna work.
Okay, hey, you guys,
you're a group
of old high school buddies.
You haven't seen each other
since the big game.
And you two--
you're on a hot date, okay?
All right.
Hey, look! There's somebody!
Laugh! Have a great time.
Awesome. Just like that.
Okay...
As much as I love
Tommy Scavo's improv theater,
we need to face some facts here.
- It's a slump.
We--we--we--we'll ride it out.
We've done it before.
We--
- It's not a slump.
In this economy, people aren't
eating out as much.
Between that
and Porter's legal bills
and paying Bree back,
we are about a week away
from going bankrupt.
Honey, please, have a little faith.
I did, for seven years.
Now I'm gonna be a realist,
and I need you to be one, too.
Okay, I understand.
You're worried. I am, too.
But we can make it.
We just have to be creative.
But--
if we sell this place now,
We can escape with some dignity
and maybe even some money.
But if we keep on going
like we are,
We're gonna lose everything.
No!
No.
I am not going out
like this.
I am not gonna be
a failure.
Please tell me they just saw a customer.
So with all the calories
we just burned,
I say we deserve a huge lunch
at a fancy restaurant.
You do like to live well, Honey.
Well, why not? Life is brief
and mostly sucks.
Gotta grab
all the good you can
while you're
on this side of the dirt.
That was very poetic.
But sure,
we'll go any place you want.
Mmm! That was easy.
Well, since I'm on a roll,
how about this?
Let's go away this weekend--
pick a five-star hotel with
a great spa and just live it up.
I don't know about that.
I've got a lot of stuff
I need to do.
Oh, come on.
Big fluffy robes,
long massages.
Do you hear that?
That buzzing.
Uh... No, I don't hear anything.
Oh, maybe it--it's--
- Shh! Shh!
I hear it up here sometimes.
What the hell is it?
Hey, you know what?
I kind of like that hotel idea.
Really?
Yeah. You were right.
Life is brief.
Why don't you go call the travel
agent and see what's available?
You know, you're kinda sexy
when you buckle.
I'm gonna call right now.
Dr. Heller?
Listen, I got your latest text,
but you know,
it's been a few weeks now,
and people are freaking out
about you being gone so long.
So now there's a staff meeting
on the 15th,
and if you're not back by then,
I'm just gonna
have to tell people
that I don't know where you are.
So will you please just call me?
Hey, Mike. How's it going?
Well, so far, I've broken off
three of these stupid
plastic sprinkler heads.
But other than that, I'm great.
Well, good.
Look, I was coming over to ask,
what would you and Katherine
think about going camping?
Oh, man, I love camping. When?
Well, my schedule
gets busy on the 15th,
so it would have to be
before then.
I don't know, this weekend?
- Oh, I'm definitely up for it.
Uh, I'm not sure
if Katherine will be.
Well, if she doesn't go,
then Edie won't go, and...
Well, I guess if Katherine
knows another girl's coming,
maybe I can convince her.
Good. Tell her the menfolk
will do all the hard work--
Build the fires,
dig the latrines.
Hey, I wouldn't mention
that, uh, latrine part
until we're actually
at the campsite.
That's a good point.
I'll, uh, dig my gear out
tonight. It's gonna be fun.
Yeah.
This is gonna be fun.
My, that's a beautiful pen
Is it a Montblanc?
Uh, yeah. Yeah, I've always wanted one.
- Ah.
Well, I guess you can afford it
now with your new raise.
Oh, you heard about that?
- I sure did.
Well, the Chamber of
Commerce just called.
They've added 40 people
to their guest list.
Damn it.
I only planned for a hundred.
W-we're gonna need tables.
- Relax. They always pull this crap.
So I called the rental company
and had 'em put a few extras
on the truck. We'll be fine.
Oh, thank God.
- But you know what?
We can tell the Chamber people
That because it was
so last-minute,
we had to bump our fee by 30%.
- I like the way you think.
Ohh. What would we do
without him?
Hmm, yes. He's worth
every penny you pay him.
By the way...
how many pennies is that?
I'm not discussing
Andrew's salary with you.
It's none of your business.
You're right. It's not.
So... How much?
Andrew moved into a new home.
I simply gave him
a cost of living increase.
The cost of living in a home
with silver pens
and rare French wines?
Honey, please don't do this.
Oh, my God.
Is he making more than me?
Orson, drop it.
I am not telling you
how much Andrew makes.
I'd be happy to give you
that information, sir.
Am I speaking
to the account holder?
No, I'm her...
business partner.
Very well. Account number?
Yes. Um, 8-5-9-7-3.
Name on the account?
Van de Kamp's
old-fashioned foods.
And the password?
Password?
For security purses.
Um...
Oh. Yes. Of course.
It's, um...
Uh, you know...
Uh, it's--it's completely
slipped my mind.
It's the name
of her childhood pet.
Oh. Right.
Uh...
Fluffy.
Nope. That's not it.
Fido?
No.
Spot? Rover?
Mittens?
Sorry, sir.
Uh, Marmaduke.
Old Yeller.
I cannot give out
you information
without the password,
which you obviously don't know.
Then ask me
a different question.
How about her date of birth?
Her social security number?
Good-bye, sir.
How about
her real hair color?
Trust me, it's not
what you think it is.
If you're looking to get fed,
it's gonna be a while.
No, Dad called a family meeting.
Yeah, Mom, he said
it's about the restaurant.
Oh, boy. I think I know
what this is about.
Listen, kids,
things have been tough
down at the restaurant,
and i think your dad
has finally decided to sell it.
Wow.
I know.
Is he gonna be okay?
I don't know. That's why we all
have to be really supportive.
Are you with me?
Hey, guys.
Good. You're all here.
I love you, Daddy.
Not yet.
So... I wanted to talk
to you all about our pizzeria.
Just know we're 100% behind you.
That means a lot,
'cause this was
a really rough day for me.
I had to let
all our employees go.
So starting tomorrow...
you kids are my new waitstaff.
Tom, what the hell
are you talking about?
I got it all worked out.
You and I will handle the days,
and the kids will join us after
school and on the weekends.
Um, at the risk
of sounding spoiled... no.
Come on! It'll be fantastic.
We'll love working together.
Why? We don't even like
living together.
Look,
labor is our number one cost.
If we can eliminate it, we'll
start making a profit again.
What, you're not even
gonna pay us?
I'm 9! Is that even legal?
I think so.
But just to be safe,
you're now 15. Happy birthday!
Mom, please do something.
I ought maybe
after our conversation today,
you'd realize
it's time to pack it in.
I have got to do this. I can't
walk away from that place
until I have done everything
that I can possibly think of.
But having the kids work there?
- You said that you were behind me 100%.
Really?
That doesn't sound like me.
Lynette...
Okay. Fine.
Kids, we are going
to support your father
by working
in his restaurant.
You've got to be kidding me.
Just so you know,
30 years from now,
when you and Dad are old and feeble--
- You're putting us
in the cheapest nursing home
you can find.
Yeah, I got it.
Mrs. Solis,
I didn't realize you were here.
I've got your bracelet
I polished
and ready for a night
on the town.
Oh, put it on
and have a good time.
Turns out I'm not gonna be
able to afford it right now...
unless you can help me out
on the price.
What did you have in mind?
You give it to me,
and then call your insurance
and say it was stolen?
I didn't think so.
I'm really sorry about
the bracelet, Mrs. Solis.
Perhaps I can show you something
a bit less expensive.
Maybe some, uh, earrings--
- Oh, will you excuse me a minute?
Ah!
Carlos! Get in Here!
I got a real shockeroo
for you!
You are not gonna
believe this!
Brad! Hi.
Uh, what's going on?
He just stopped by
with great news.
I'm getting that bonus
after all.
Really?
Well, I went to our C.F.O.,
And I told him
it just didn't seem fair
that my right-hand man
should go unrewarded.
Isn't that great?
What kind of guy does that?
Oh, I think I know the kind.
So, Brad...
What sort of bonus
are we looking at?
How does 20 grand sound?
Like a great jumping off point.
Gaby.
Oh, honey, you heard Maria
the other night.
Your hard work is what's
brought them so much closer.
Pay no attention to my wife.
20 grand is a fantastic bonus.
You know, now that I hear
the number out loud,
it does seem a little low,
after all you've done.
25 is probably more fair.
Oh, Brad. Come on.
Saving a marriage?
You can't put price on that...
at least not a small one.
Gaby, will you knock it off?
You're being rude.
You're right. I'm sorry.
It's just--I really wanted
to buy this bracelet I saw today
downtown in this little jewelry shop.
You know the place, honey.
It's right next to the,
um...
Lexington hotel.
30!
$30,000.
Are you sure?
Yes! You deserve it.
You both do.
I don't know what to say.
You're the only one
getting a bonus,
so what I think
might be best is
if we all agreed
not to say anything.
Do we all agree?
Absolutely.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I'll leave you two to business.
All this negotiating just
goes right over my head.
Ha!
Thunder McFadden.
What a hoot.
What's that?
Oh, it's my porn name.
Friend sent me an e-mail.
You take the name
of your childhood pet
and the street you grew up on,
and voilà!
That's the name you'd use
if you were a porn star.
So I'm Thunder McFadden.
My buddy here is
Snoop Windemere.
Mm.
Hey, who would you be?
Orson, I'm preparing
a buffet for 200.
I don't have time to explore
my hypothetical career
in the adult film industry.
Fine.
But you should know that's
why people find you so rigid,
because you can never
just let go and have fun.
Coco Saugatuck. Happy now?
Sure am.
Thanks, hon.
Of course it could just
easily be Munchy Cedarhurst.
What?
Or Taffy Swallow.
We moved around lot
and had three dogs.
Bree, focus.
It has to be your favorite pet.
Like if I asked you,
"what's your childhood pet?"
This is the one you'd say.
- Well, I didn't really have a favorite.
I loved them all equally.
Oh, please. If Coco,
Taffy and Munchy were
in a burning building and
you could only save one...
Orson, why are
you being so morbid?
No. I-I just want
to know your porn name.
Okay, fine.
If I had to pick a favorite,
I guess it would be Munchy.
She was a bit rambunctious.
Father sent her to a farm
so she'd have room to run.
I cried for weeks and weeks.
Munchy, huh? This was fun.
All right, that's
a large mushroom pepperoni pizza
and two salads.
I'll get that started.
Tom, I got
need a large--
Large pep/mush at table nine.
I'm way ahead of you.
Thanks. And do you have
the calzones for table three?
Oh, crap.
Setie, I need two dinner salads.
What's the matter?
Parker said the only
reason you had me make salads
is because
it's a job for babies.
Well, clearly, that's not true
because you're not a baby.
You're 15, remember?
- Also, I can't find my band-aid.
Okay, you fill water glasses.
I'll make the salads.
Hey, Mom?
- Yeah?
This is for table five.
Oh, thanks.
Yeah.
Uh... you didn't give them
enough change.
Yeah, I know.
I figured this out.
You can short people 1%,
and they won't even notice.
If they got a buzz on, 3%.
Okay, you make the salads.
I'll handle the register.
Dude, back off.
That's my table.
Not anymore. You can take
the 4-top of old farts.
No way. I--
- What's going on?
He took my table.
So? Take another one.
What's the difference?
Well, since I'm the only one
here who can wait on that table
without knocking over a glass
with my pants,
how about I take it?
You handle the cash register.
You bus tables. Go on.
Well, look at this.
Everybody's happy.
Things are running smoothly.
Don't worry. I'm not gonna say,
"I told you so."
Hey. Katherine said
you wanted to talk to me.
Yeah. Come on in.
You know, you could have
just called.
You don't have to use her
as an intermediary.
Really? I thought
we were using Katherine
for all sorts of things--
sending messages,
raising our kid.
I don't see
what the big deal is.
I have to work,
and she has some free time.
It's better for everybody.
Well, it's not better for me,
especially when
I'm not even told about it.
Fine. Here I am telling you.
I have to work Friday,
so Katherine will be
picking M.J. up from school.
No.
What do you mean, "no"?
Let me remind you,
I have custody on Fridays.
Hey, thanks.
Let me remind you
that the reason
I agreed to custody is
so our son could spend time
with his father.
You have a problem with Katherine?
No, she's a peach,
but she's not the one
that dragged me to court
to hammer out
some custody agreement.
Now if you'd like,
we can go back,
and the judge can explain to you
the difference between
you and your girlfriend.
Okay, you listen to me.
Mommy?
Are you guys fighting?
No, sweetie.
We are just trying to figure out
what is best for you.
Aren't we?
I'll see you Friday, buddy.
Looks like I'll be
picking you up from school.
Andrew makes twice as much as me?
Who told you that?
A little bird
or should I say
a little dog named Munchy?
That's why you wanted to know
the names of my pets?
Orson Hodge,
you are shameful.
What's shameful is
how much you're paying him.
Andrew has been with me
since I launched the company.
He runs every aspect
of the business.
He deserves what he's making.
But I am your husband,
for crying out loud.
Yes, Orson, we're all aware
of how you got the job.
You know
what the real travesty is?
I'm more educated
than the lot of you.
I went to grad school. I'm a dentist.
- No, you were a dentist.
Now you're a caterer,
and you're paid fairly
based on your expertise
and contribution.
Oh, this is not about money,
Bree. It's about value.
And you're saying I'm worthless.
No, I'm just saying
you're worth... less.
I'm sorry, Honey.
I'm just being honest.
Very well.
Oh, since we're being honest,
Munchy didn't go to any farm.
That's what parents
tell their kids
When they just had their pets
gassed.
Hey.
Hi. You got a minute? I have
a really big favor to ask you.
Uh, sure.
I need
a little detective work done.
It's about Bradley.
So...
What's going on?
I'm gonna buy a golf club.
A baseball bat would be cheaper.
Maybe I should let you finish.
See, I don't know anything
about golf clubs,
But I know Carlos does,
so I was hoping you guys
could snoop around
and find out
what kind of driver Brad wants.
Oh, it's a gift.
Sure, yeah.
We'd love to help out.
So what's the occasion?
- No occasion.
I just want to thank him
for being a wonderful husband.
Well, don't spend to much.
Why don't you
just get him a card?
So our marriage counselor said
we should get each other
little gifts now and then
to keep things spontaneous.
Oh, you're in counseling.
That's great.
We were, but we stopped.
We don't need it anymore.
Are you sure about that?
- Yeah. Brad and I are solid.
Well, ice is solid, too,
until it cracks and you're
drowning in freezing water.
I'd stay in counseling
if I were you.
Gaby, I'm home! Can you come
in here for a minute?
Brad gives me a huge bonus
and you repay him
by telling his wife that
they need marriage counseling?
I'm sorry. I think they do.
Their marriage is
none of your business.
Besides, I think they're
a very happy couple.
Who? Him and Maria
or him and the blonde I
saw him kissing yesterday?
What? No way!
Yeah. And Brad saw me.
Why do you think
your bonus jumped
from a stuffed chicken breast
to 30 grand in a day?
Oh, my God.
This is illegal.
I'm getting a bonus no one else
is getting based on blackmail.
You're welcome.
I can't believe you did this.
Well, thank God
you came to your senses.
All right, let's get in there
and tell her.
No, we can't tell her. We'd have
to give the money back.
Don't we have a moral
responsibility to tell her?
It's like you said--
Their marriage is
none of our business.
He's the one who's cheating.
If we say anything,
it'll just make things worse.
We're the good guys here,
Carlos.
Really? 'cause it sure
doesn't feel like it.
It's open.
Susan, you got our message.
Yes, and imagine my surprise,
'cause the last time
I talked to Mike,
he promised me he was
picking up M.J. from school.
Oh, Mrs. Nelson had
another plumbing emergency.
Apparently this
new oat bran diet she's on--
I don't need the details.
I had a long day.
I just want to pick up my kid.
Mommy, we had paninis
for dinner. You want one?
No, thank you. Let's go.
But we were gonna make brownies
for dessert.
But we can make brownies
at home.
The box kind? Katherine says
those aren't real brownies.
Except when your mommy
makes them with love.
Good save.
Let's go.
Susan?
Look,
I know you were surprised
to find M.J. here again today,
But I really was trying
to do you a favor.
Well, I don't need you
to do me any favors.
What I need is for everyone
to just stick to the plan.
Monday, Wednesday, Friday--
Mike watches his son.
He doesn't pawn him off
on his girlfriend.
I had a really fun time.
Big group coming in. It is
now officially Saturday night.
Finally.
Oh, great. They're kids.
1 plate of spaghetti and
15 baskets of free bread.
Stop being such a downer.
We're finally making a go
of this place.
All you want to do is complain.
We're taking a break. N-not now.
- We just got a big party.
Good luck with that.
We're outta here.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
What's going on here?
Those kids go our school.
- And you know who that big guy is?
Kevin McDermott. The guy
called me "Jesus" for a year
'cause I wore sandals one day.
If he sees me wearing this,
I'll never hear the end of it.
Fine. Don't wear that apron. That's...
- No, I'm not waiting
on a kid who's gonna make fun
of me on Monday morning.
It's humiliating enough
having to work here.
Humiliating?
Guys, easy.
- No, you're-- you're not humiliated
when you use the money
that we make here
to buy your clothes.
- Tom, it's fine. I'll take the table.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Your mother can't wait
on this whole restaurant by herself.
- Well, then you do it.
Porter, I'm your father
and your boss,
and I'm telling you right now
to go take that table.
Or what, you're gonna fire me?
Go for it.
You think this is a joke?
This is my life!
Tom!
- You worry about being embarrassed?
I have put everything I
have into this restaurant!
All right, that's enough!
Let go of him! Let go of him!
Let go of him!
Guys?
I just sat a 12-top.
Who's taking it?
I will.
I started getting our accounts
in order.
If we're gonna sell
this place,
We should probably know exactly
how much it's worth.
I think this can all wait
until morning.
Don't you?
Hey. I just booked us
into the Brunswick Inn
For this weekend.
Great.
Prepare to be pampered!
Oh, shoot.
This weekend isn't gonna work.
Mike really wants us
to do that camping trip
that we've
been talking about.
Camping? Have you met me?
I figured
you were gonna say that.
I just can't blow him off.
This is the only weekend
that works for him.
Then you're on your own.
Have fun wiping with leaves.
- Oh, Edie?
Please don't tell Katherine
that you're not coming.
All right?
Mike really wants her there,
and if she hears that you're
not going, she won't either.
Will you take me
to the Brunswick Inn
next weekend?
Yes.
Then I won't say a word
to Katherine.
Hey.
When did you two get here?
Just a minute ago.
They said they have
something personal
they want to talk to us about.
Oh, really? What is it?
We're pregnant.
Oh, wow.
Yay!
I know. We are so happy.
But that's not all.
See, even though
we've only known each other
for a short time,
your friendship
has meant a lot to us,
which is why Maria feels strongly
that you should be
the baby's godparents.
Do you hear that, Carlos?
Godparents.
Yay!
You are such good people,
so kindhearted and decent,
and that is
the kind of influence
that we want in our baby's life.
How could we say no?
Oh!
Oh. I see you got your bracelet
after all.
Oh, yeah.
Uh, but I'm not enjoying it
as much as I thought I would.
Ok, watching a movie.
You are one lucky boy.
I'm gonna take
a quick shower.
Try not to get any crumbs
on the couch.
What's wrong?
It's peanut butter,
no crusts--
your favorite.
I want a panini.
I don't know
how to make paninis.
It's just turkey and cheese.
Do we have any provolone?
No, we do not have
any provolone.
Can we borrow some
from Katherine?
Absolutely not.
In this house, we do not eat
pretentious cheeses.
We eat
honest American peanut butter.
Now watch your movie,
and I'll be back in a minute.
Will you make me a panini?
Uh, well, sure, sweetie.
Does your mommy know you're here?
Hey, sweetie.
How was your sandwich?
M.J.?
M.J., Honey, where are you?
M.J., where are you?!
M.J.!
What is he doing here?
He wanted panini,
said you knew.
M.J., go wait
outside on the porch.
I need to talk to Katherine.
You can take the sandwich.
Look, he showed up
on my doorstep.
He seemed hungry.
You think I don't feed my kid?
Okay, well, maybe he just
wanted to come see me.
Yeah, 'cause you make it
like Disneyland over here,
with your paninis
and your blackjack.
You're trying
to do everything you can
to make him think that
you're the other mommy.
What?
You're trying to get your hooks
deeper into Mike
by showing him how
much his son loves you.
Susan, I am being nice
to the child of the man I'm dating.
How does that make me evil?
- No, not evil. Devious.
Well, you know,
I hate to tell you,
but your big plan is
not gonna work,
'cause from now on, M.J. is
either at my house or Mike's.
He is no longer allowed to be here.
- Yeah, uh, that's gonna be tricky.
Well, that's the way it's gonna
be, whether you like it or not.
No, it's gonna be tricky
because Mike's moving in here.
What?
First of the month,
he's giving up his place
and moving in with me.
So M.J. is going to be
spending a lot of time here,
whether you like it or not.
Orson, I'm glad you're here.
I was doing a recount
of the goblets
for the Hopkins
wedding reception,
and we're short by about 30...
- Oh.
So I have to run over
to the supplier
and pick up the rest.
Could you hold down the fort for me?
Sure. No problem.
Thanks.
Hey, you know, Andrew? It
never would have occurred to me
to do a recount of the goblets.
Bree's lucky to have
someone as conscientious
as you working here.
Wow.
Thank you, Orson.
That--
that means a lot to me.
It begins just after sunrise.
After a good night's sleep,
people leave their homes
to go to work.
They do this
so they can provide
a better life
for their families...
afford to buy nice things...
and have a reason
to get up in the morning.
And when their exhausting work
is done,
people come back home again...
and some
begin counting the days...
till their next vacation.
Subtitles by LeapinLar
www.tvsubtitles.net