Previously on...
Lives change in five years.
Some families grow,
while others grow apart.
So I thought I'd bring him back
sunday around 6:00 or so. Fine.
And we find ways... it's
not really a good time.
To ease the pain.
Yes, in five years...
Edie, is that really
you? I have a husband now.
Many things change.
You're required to
check in once a month.
It was a condition of your release.
All in all,
Susan mayer's boyfriend knew
he had a lot goingor him.
He was romantic...
Had a nice smile...
And was consistently thoughtful.
Yes, jackson braddock had
many wonderful attributes.
Sadly...
A sense of timing wasn't one of them.
Hello.
Can I help you?
I guess you could
tell susan I'm here.
Okay. Uh... who are you?
Oh, I'm mike... the ex-Husband.
I, uh, I take it you're...
Jackson.
I'm, uh...
Susan's, uh...
Friend?
Friend. That's right.
Wow. Could this be any more awkward?
Well, your robe's open... so yeah.
Well, you be the judge.
I don't know, man.
It--It's pretty good.
Well, I got the feeling that...
Hey, your ex-Husband is...
Mike! Uh, what's going on?
I was just returning
m.J.'S video game.
He left it at my house.
Oh. Thanks. So I
guess you met jackson.
Yeah. Nice legs.
Oh, clearly this is not
How I would've wanted
the two of you to meet.
He's--He's
really a nice guy.
Yeah, well, just to
make sure, I'm gonna need
To hang with him a
little bit, check him out.
Oh, I don't know
that that's necessary.
If he's sleeping in the
same house as my son,
I think it is.
Oh, well, first off, um, m.J.
Was at a sleepover last night.
And, in fact, jackson
and he haven't even met,
So, uh, there's really no
need for you to be hanging...
Or checking.
Oh, just... tell jackson I'll
pick him up here tomorrow night.
Hey, hold on.
You don't get to just decide
these things by yourself.
You remember how nice I was
about our custody agreement?
I can haul you back to court tomorrow
If I'm not 100% satisfied
with who you expose my son to.
Got it?
Uh, I'm sorry.
It's so not how I wanted to
meet your ex for the first time.
Well, when you meet
him for the second time,
You can tell him that.
He's picking you up here
tomorrow night. What?
I'll explain over breakfast.
Did you get the paper?
And that is w jackson
braddock realized
He needed better timing...
Who are you?
And a longer robe.
If there is one thing everyone in
suburbia can appreciate... oh, hey!
It's a good neighbor.
You know, the kind that helps
With the last bag of groceries...
Or brings over misplaced mail...
Or offers to mow your lawn.
Yes, everyone appreciates
a good neighbor.
You are so sweet to do this.
I just know how tricky
these bulbs can be.
And no one knew this
bette than dave williams,
Who was determined to be
The best neighbor steria
lane had ever seen...
Assuming, of course,
His wife didn't get in the way.
What's going on?
Packing our bags.
Karen mccluskey insulted me again,
And I can't put up with it anymore.
All right, what did she
say to you this time?
Nothing. It doesn't matter. We are
moving. Adults don't pack up and move
Because of some
good-Natured teasing.
She said that my breasts were
a triumph oferman engineering.
You call that good-Natured?
Come on. She's a cranky old lady.
It's not just her. It's all of them.
I mean, it's been five
years. I have changed.
But the people on
this street don't care.
To them, I will always be a joke.
I'm sorry you had a bad day.
Please don't use your
motivational voice.
I really hate that.
You're upset and you're tired.
Why don't you take a nice hot shower,
And I'll makus some lunch?
Does that sound good?
I just never understood it.
We--We could've gone and lived
in any city in this country.
Why did you insist on living here?
'Cause we can be happy here.
You just need to give it some time.
And I promise,
I'll personally see to it
That people start treating
you with a little more respect.
You didn't answer my question.
Didn't I?
Carlos, we got invited to
michelle downing's party!
I'm gonna have to buy
something nice to--Aah!
Gaby, I'm giving a massage.
I can see that.
I can see a
lot of things--
Things that can never be unseen.
Uh, sorry. I guess the
towel must've rode up.
Carlos? Kitchen. Now.
I know you don't like
it when I work down here,
But he couldn't get up the stairs.
He's got a bum hip. He's
also missing a testicle.
Carlos, how much more of
this am I supposed to take?
Okay, okay, maybe I could
set up my table in the garage.
No! That's only part of the problem.
Have you checked our
bank balance lately?
Gaby, I am not taking
the country club job.
Why not? You'd be
massaging rich people.
They tip better and they tend to
Flake less. Yeah, but
I like working here
I get to spend lots of
time with you and the kids.
Carlos, I don't need to
spend lots of time with you.
And frankly, the kids
are on the fence. Gaby!
Bottom line, I miss our
life. I miss shopping.
All I have to look forward to
Is the occasional
invitation to a fancy party.
And I can't even afford
a dress to go to it.
Carlos, please, I am begging you.
Fine. I'll-- I will take the job.
Thank you.
Sorry.
Ah, no.
Unh-Unh. Come on.
I really don't think mike's
gonna care what shirt I wear.
Well, I do.
We need a shirt that says,
"I'm a responsible citizen,"
Not "my favorite clothing
store also sells bongs."
Are you dissing my sense of style?
Absolutely.
Put this on.
Now...
Let's talk about acceptable
topics of conversation.
You like sports, right?
Yeah. I'm a huge socr
fan. No, you're not.
You like football--
American football.
Specifically the colts. Okay.
And here are some other
things you can talk about--
Cars, barbue, fishing.
How about fire? Mike like talk fire?
Jackson, please take this seriously.
I am. I'm just--I'm not gonna
pretend to be somebody I'm not.
If he doesn't like
me, wh's he gonna do?
He could take me to court,
And the judge can make me
choose between you and my son.
And I'm sorry. You will lose.
Peyton manning
Is the greatest
quarterback who ever lived.
Thank you.
Now go shave. You look like a hobo.
Got a sec?
Not really.
So I assume you know about
what happened to jimmy conrado.
I guess.
Your friend gets busted
for dealing drugs at school,
And all you have to
say is, "I guess"?
He's not my friend.
- What are you talking about?
You were on the same
little league team.
Yeah, like a million
years ago. Anything else?
No.
Not really.
Parker.
Can I ask you something,
just between us?
Does porter hang out
with jimmy conrado?
I don't know. I could check out his
Friends list on
silverfizz. His what on what
It's like myspace.
You have a web page.
It shows your hobbies,
your favorite music,
And you can talk to people.
Really? Can anyone talk to him?
Yeah. He just has to invite you.
And, uh...
How would somebody make that happen?
Now it's just a mock-Up,
But this is what the book
is going to look like.
Mom, that's fantastic.
Good call on the font.
Thank you, dear.
Orson, what do you think?
Well, I think it's strange
To see my wife billed
as "mrs. Van de kamp."
Well, you knew what
the book was gonna be
Called. Yes, but it's
differen actually seeing it
I mean, is it too late
to go with "mrs. Hodge"?
My company, which I formed
when we were separated,
Is called mrs. Van
de kamp's catering.
It's how I'm known. Oh, in fairview.
But this book will be national.
I mean, it's your chance
to rebrand yourself.
Is there something
wrong with "hodge"?
I think I just heard the
milk go bad. I should check.
Orson, I adore you,
But your name... our
name-- It has no music.
"Van de kamp" trips off the tongue.
"Hodge" sounds like the
noise a plunger makes.
That's preposterous.
Listen...
Van de kamp.
Hodge.
Also, she's got a radio
interview wednesday,
And they're already promoting
her as mrs. Van de kamp.
See? The ship has already sailed.
Oh, don't be hurt. It's
my professional name.
In this house, I will
always be mrs. Hodge.
Now... would it help if mrs. Hodge
Cooked you your favorite
pot roast tonight?
Yes, I guess it would help.
Uh, meeting with your publicist?
Oh, right. Um,
tomorrow for sure, then.
Van de kamp. Hmm.
Hodge.
Here you go. Oh, thank you.
Toby, get off my
chair. You know better.
So what's on your mind?
It's Edie.
You said something to her yesterday
That hurt her feelings.
That thing about her breasts?
Come on. That was a joke.
Perhaps, but it upset her so much
That she suggested we
leave wisteria lane.
I can't have that, mrs. M.
Hey, this is what Edie and
I do. We tease each other.
I say she's easier to get
into than community college.
She says my face looks like a knee.
It's fun.
Still... I would consider
it a personal favor
If you'd apologize to her.
You know, make her
feel accepted and loved.
No.
No?
If Edie wants to change the
way we talk to each other,
She's gotta ask me personally.
And I think you've got a lot of gall
Making me feel like
I did something wrong
When you don't even know me.
Oh... I know you,
Better than you think.
Oh, really?
For starters,
You talk to your cat
like it's a person.
When I knocked on your door,
you immediately invited me in.
Doesn't take a genius to
see that you're lonely.
I'm thinking you had people
in your life at one time...
People who cared about you.
But somethg happened to them.
Some probably died. The rest, well...
They just don't come
around much anymore.
Why do you think that is?
I know you, mrs. Mccluskey.
And it seems to me
That a woman le you
would like to keep
The few friends that she has left.
I think you'd better go.
Thanks for tonight.
And, uh, before I
forget, the colts suck.
Oh, here's what sucks--
Watching a zero-Zero game
With no cheerleaders, soccer boy.
You guys were insulting each other.
That's good, right?
Yeah, we had a blast
Really? Yeah.
In fact, we're getting together
wednesday night at o'brien's,
Which he claims has the best
bacon potato skins in town.
Potato skins at o'brien's?
You've made his inner circle!
This is fantastic!
Thank you. Mmm. Mmm.
Ah, you can think of
A more creative way
to thank me than that.
Nice.
Yeah?
Yeah. Mmm.
You've never done that before.
Wait.
Why are you doing that now?
I don't know. Don't you like it?
Yeah. But how did you
know I would like it?
Oh, my god.
What?
Mike told you about the
ear thing, didn't he?
No.
So you just happened
To stumble across my secret turn-On
The same night that you
and mike became b.F.F.S?
But aren't we losing sight
of the fact that you like it?
This is... I mean, I'm just...
I have been violated.
Oh, honey,
come on--
Don't touch me! Or my ears!
My ears are dead to you.
It just slipped out. We were
talking about how girls--
They--They all like
different things, right?
And I-I was talking about
this girl in high school,
How she liked to do
it with her shoes on,
And--And mike talked about the
lobe nibble. He has a name for it?
Okay.
That's it. You and mike
are not hanging out anymore.
And this little
Wednesday "potato skins
and susan sex tips night"?
I forbid it.
Did mike mention he likes
having his toes sucked?
Oops! That just slipped out. Hmm.
Gaby...
Bree! What's up?
Well, um, michelle downing
asked me to speak to you.
I don't know if you heard,
But I'm catering her
birthday party-- I
Heard. I can't wait.
Ooh, I was gonna ask you
Should I wear the navy blue chanel
Or the red sleeveless
dress? You can't come.
Sorry.
I just had to rip the band-Aid off.
What? She's disinviting me?
It's not personal.
You know how carlos
just started at the club?
Well, her guests are all members,
And she thinks they
might find it awkward
Socializing with...
Staff.
She called us "staff"?
Oh, gaby, it's just one
party. I'll save you some cake.
No! It's not just one party!
It's the kickoff to
the whole social season.
If people see we're
off michelle's list,
Then we'll be off everyone's.
And then it's gonna be
the start of our slow slide
From gowns and galas to
flip-Flops and keggers!
Okay, if carlos working
at the club is the problem,
Then tell her he just quit.
Oh, hon, I don't
think that's gonna fly.
He's already rubbed too many members.
What's happened to my life?
We used to have help.
Now we are the help!
What are you doing?
I am just...
Talking to porter on silverfizz.
Who is saraj from
macarthur high school?
Me.
I'm 16 and cute.
I like graphic novels and
tokyo police club. Oh, my god.
You--You're pretending
to be somebody else?
Our brooding son has a classmate
Who got arrested for selling drugs.
I really think the end
justifies the means here.
Okay, we'll address your major
ethical breach in a moment.
What did you find out?
Well, the good news is
He really doesn't hang
out with jimmy conrado.
But I am a little
worried about anita47,
Who told him cherry fruit
pops are an aphrodisiac.
Okay, great, you know who
he hangs around with now.
You got what you came
for. Time to stop.
You're probably right. It's just...
Did you know porter writes poetry?
Serious? Yeah.
Our porter,
The kid who communicates
with grunts and shrugs,
Writes this...
Beautiful, heart-Wrenching poetry.
Maybe one day he'll share it with you
Instead of your fantasy alter ego.
Until then, shut it off.
Okay, okay.
You're right.
I luvs me some walt whitman!
Emlly dickinson kicks
walt whitman's ass!!
Yeah, if you're into spinster poetry.
Oh, really?
Is your girlfrend into poetry,too?
Don't have one.There's a girl I
lile.But we haven't gotten to that yet.
Aw. That's sweet.
Girls love romance.Send her a
poem.She won't know what hit her.
Still talking to poetry girl?
Bite me.
Dude, she didn't put up her photo.
5 bucks says she looks
like she came out of an egg.
Whatever.
Toby?
Toby! Where are you?
Toby!
Everything all right, mrs. M.?
It's toby. I can't find him.
Oh, no. How did he get out?
The living room window
was open, which is bizarre
Because I don't remember opening it.
Can you help me find him?
Have you given any more thought
about apologizing to Edie?
She's still pretty down in the dumps.
I've kind of been busy.
Of course you have. It's just that...
Well, since I'm about to
help you find your cat,
It sure would be nice if you
could help me out with Edie.
Doesn't that seem fair to you?
I guess.
Here.
Thank you.
Okay. Toby!
Toby! Come here, boy!
Toby!
So they'll finish with the
news, do a quick traffic update,
And then we're on the air.
Uh, do you need anything?
No, I'm good. How do I look?
We're on the radio.
Oh. I'm a little bit nervous.
This is my first national interview.
And I am a huge fan
of your cookbooks.
Well, I've heard
good things about you.
I understand you're catering
Michelle downing's
birthday dinner tonight.
Oh, you know michelle?
Yes, and I'll be there.
I can't wait to see what you dish up.
Okay, now I'm terrified.
Here we go.
Good afternoon.
I'm linda flanagan, and
this is "gourmet americana."
If you've been to
fairview's best parties,
Then you've probably tasted
the mouthwatering food
Dished up by my first
guest, bree van de kamp.
Now she's about to
publish her first book,
"Mrs. Van de kamp's
old-Fashioned cooking."
Welcome, bree.
Hi, linda.
Tell me. Why "old-Fashioned"?
Well, I think a lot of people
miss the way life used to be--
Back when women had
more time to cook.
It's always been important to me
To have the family gather
around the table every night
For hot, lovingly prepared meals.
So you're a traditional kinda gal.
Is there a mr. Van de kamp?
No.
Uh, mr. Van de kamp is deceased. Oh.
But in regards to my husband,
I should make one
thing very clear--
His passing had nothing
to do with my cooking.
Is that my yeats book?
I love his poetry.
Yeah. I'm borrowing it for school.
This is the kind of poetry
that melts a girl's heart.
So romantic.
Oh! Here's
a great one--
"The lover tells of
the rose in his heart."
My first boyfriend gave me this poem.
I was a junior in-- Mom, I'm--I'm
running late. Can I have the book back?
Oh. Sorry.
Enjoy!
Katherine, it is not too
late to change tonight's menu.
If linda flanagan likes my food,
She might give me a
quote for the book jacket.
I have to knock her socks off,
And I am not betting
the farm on haddock.
Argue with me all you like.
I just bought 40 pounds of pork,
so get your tushie over here.
Orson! Did you get my
message about linda flanagan?
Yes, I heard.
Isn't it amazing?
Mm. Almost as amazing as
my on-Air death notice.
What?
"So, bree, do you have a husband?"
"Nope. Used to. He croaked." She
didn't ask if I had a husband.
She asked if there
was a mr. Van de kamp,
And there's clearly not.
Well, there's a mrhodge.
Would it have killed
you to have mentioned me?
And waste valuable airtime?
The show was about my cookbook,
Not about my tortured
marital history.
That's not what this is about.
It's because I went
to jail, isn't it?
Orson, I have 6 hours to
prepare a meal for 80 people.
We're not having this discussion now.
Just admit it. You're ashamed of me.
Should I be proud?
Do you want me to go
on the radio and boast
That my husband served time
for running someone over?
I went to jail because you told me
It was the only way
you'd take me back.
And because it was
the right thing to do.
I just didn't know then
That I would be a
public figure someday.
But I am. I have a name now.
And luckily for you, it's not mine.
Orson, please don't be hurt.
I am under so much pressure
and so terrified I'll fail
That I don't even know what
I'm saying half the time.
Just let me get through this.
As soon as the plates go out tonight,
I will come home and cook
you that pot roast I promised.
Okay?
Okay. Hmm.
It's just
that... I--
Chives! How could I forget chives?
Hey, susan, it's me.
Listen, I'm not gonna be
able to make dinner tonight.
My college roommate's in town,
And this is the only
night we can get together.
Oh. Is his name mike delfino?
Did you room together
at liars' college?
Um, I know it's last-Minute,
and I'm really sorry,
But I stilwanna see you.
So how about I drop by later?
Call me if that's a problem.
Yeah, you'll drop by later...
With potato skins on your breath,
You miserable two-Timer!
What's wrong, mom?
Nothing.
Just, the answering
machine lied to mommy.
I finally found a poem as beautiful
as you. You're all I think about.
"The lover tells of the rose in
his heart" by william butler yeats.
Oh, crap on things.
Crap on what things?
Porter sent me a sex poem.
What? Why?
He may be in love with me.
Why would he be in love with you?
Okay... remember how you told me
I should stop talking to him online?
Well, of course, I didn't,
And I sort of told
him I liked his poetry.
You told a teenage boy
that you liked his poetry?
Jeez, lynette! Why not
just flash him a boob?
Shh! He'll hear you. So
what are you gonna do?
Are you gonna tell him the
truth now, or are you gonna
Wait until after he kills
me and blinds himself?
Calm down. I'm gonna
break it off in an e-Mail.
Oh, great. Just like
that? That'll kill him.
I know that you have only
been the receiving end
Of break-up letters, but
I've actually written a few,
And I know how to let him down easy.
"Dear porter,
"I really like you,
But I wanna see other offspring."
Go away.
You know, I'm kinda surprised
We still made michelle's
list this year,
What with me working at the club.
Oh, don't be silly, carlos.
We're still on everyone's list.
Now let's go. Okay.
Gaby, are we in the banquet hall?
What's all the noise?
Oh, it's just the caterers
Putting glasses and
silverware on the tables.
They make some racket, huh?
But the decorations are stunning.
Especially that waterfall effect.
Gaby? Bree!
Shouldn't you be in the kitchen?
Don't move, honey. The
press is taking your photo.
What are you doing here? You were
disinvited. I got it all figured out.
We duck inside, make sure we're
seen by all the right people--
Except mrs.
Downing--
And then after about
20 minutes, we cut out.
Well, I know nothing.
Just keep me out of it.
What is carlosoing?
Where is he? Where is who?
Like you don't
know-- Jackson.
Well, he's not here.
Really? Whose is this?
I... d--I don't
know. Some guy's.
"I... I don't know"?
Well, I hope that "some guy"
Doesn't mind this.
No, susan, really, I wouldn't...
Lady, what are you doing to my beer?
We're not married anymore,
So I don't have to protect you.
I am... so sorry.
Miss?
Um... could you just...
Please take good care of my friend?
Jackson canceled on me.
He said you weren't
comfortable with us hanging out.
He said that? And I
think I said, "meow."
I am such a jackass.
So why don't you want us hanging out?
Well, I was pretty ticked off
That you told jackson
about the ear thing.
Oh, god. The second I said
that, I wished I hadn't.
I-I'm really sorry.
Apology accepted.
So if I promise to behave,
can we still hang out?
'Cause I really think
it'd be good for m.J.,
Just seeing that we're all friends.
I don't...
What?
I'm just not comfortable
With you and jackson
getting that close.
Okay.
It's just...
I don't want him to see
me through your eyes.
How exactly do you think I see you?
Well, those last few months
we were together, I...
The things I said to
you, the way I acted...
I mean, I'm not proud
of the person I became.
That was a bad time, susan.
We're not those people anymore.
And if you could see
yourself through my eyes,
You'd know you got
nothing to worry about.
Could you please
take care of this guy?
He's my friend, too.
Boy, am I glad to see you.
Where you been?
Out, uh, doing some thinking.
And I've decided that I may
have gone a little overboard
About you and mike.
In fact, I think it's cool if
you wanna hang out with my ex.
Hey, susie q.!
Just shakin' the dew off the lily.
And speaking of,
That paint job in the
guest can is nice. Kudos.
What are you doing here?
Well, julie needed me to cosign
some insurance stuff for her,
And I guess I lost track of time
talking to crunchy granola here.
Plumber to housepainter
in one move, susie?
Don't get dizzy climbin'
that social ladder.
Can you leave, please? Just think...
If I'd been a roofer, we might
still be together. Sigh. Get out.
See ya around, hacky sack.
So... any more exes
I should know about?
Don't you just love
michelle's parties?
Oh, they are fun. Mm-Hmm.
But I enjoy my intimate
lunches with michelle even more.
We have intimate lunches. We're
friends. Well, you simply must come
To the charity auction at
ted's gallery next weekend.
Really? We'd love to.
Gaby!
Well, it's the caterer!
Everything is fabulous.
But would you be a dear and get me
some more wine? I would be happy to.
I just want to make sure
it's the kind you like.
You're still here?
Dinner is about to be served.
Whose seats are you in? The bowmans.
I found out mrs. Bowman is
home with the flu. Score!
Oh, will you unclench? It'll be fine.
No, no, no, no, no. These are
my seats. This is my mother.
That was mr. Bowman, wasn't it?
Yes, and I'm pretty sure
That elderly woman
with him was his mother!
What kind of man leaves
his sick wife at home
To go party with mommy?!
- You can fix this.
Just tell them that
you're at the wrong tabl
And then slip out
the side door. Right.
Yes, sir, he has absolutely no--
That was the matre d', wasn't it?
Yes, and he appears to be checking
the guest list. Which we're not on.
Okay, you can fix this.
Just explain you're
going to a different party
Here at the club and
that you got confused.
Mrs. Downing never
has to know. Right.
You need to leave! Out.
That's mrs. Downing.
How am I gonna fix this?
At this point, I would just run
off screaming into the night.
Thank you. Mm-Hmm.
Get your hands off me.
Gaby! Gaby!
Poor blind bastard.
I'll meet him outside.
What? Hi, Edie.
I just wanted to say I feel
awful about what I said to you.
You know, that crack
I made the other day?
Okay.
That's nice of you.
Are you all right?
Actually, no. My cat's missing.
Toby? Mm-Hmm.
Since when? It's been two days,
and he's never been out this long.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I'm sure he's fine.
Yeah. Well...
Could you tell dave...
Tell him I apologized? And,
uh, you and I are good, huh?
I guess I could.
Why do you want him--
Oh, just tell him, please.
I cannot believe you
pulled a stunt like that.
What?
I was just trying to salvage
what's left of our social life.
Now just let it go
And start thinking about
where we're gonna move.
This is not a joke, gaby.
I work with these people.
I have to show my face
tomorrow. It's humiliating.
You wanna know what's humiliating?
Waking up one day
And finding out you're invisible.
Now it's official.
I've lost everything.
Everything?
First our money, then my figure,
Now the last shreds
of our social standing.
We haven't lost a thing
Except the chance to hobnob
with a bunch of unhappy snobs.
What do you mean, they're unhappy?
They're rich! They
have jewels and cooks.
They use "winter" as a verb.
I rub them, gaby,
And there is nothing
That a blind masseur
doesn't hear about.
Trust me.
They are every bit
as miserable as I was
When I was out there
chasing that stuff.
We have lost nothing that matters.
We have a home, we have each other,
We have work that supports us,
And we have two beautiful
little girls that...
Love us more than ice cream.
I've never been happier in my life.
Are you serious?
Yes,
And the only thing that
would make me happier
Is forou to realize
how good we've got it.
"I have never talked
to such a wonderful guy,
But I should've told you I'm
already seeing somebody..."
Blah, blah, blah...
"Continue to trust your heart,
and your dreams will follow."
Wow, lynette.
Best dear john letter ever.
Uh... thanks.
Except you might
wanna change that part
Where you signed it "love,
mom." What? No I didn't.
Yeah, you did...
Right there.
You sent it?!
Oh, my god! Oh, my god!
Oh, my god! Oh, my god! Oh, my god!
Why didn't you say something?! I did!
You said it was great.
Way to bury the lead, tom!
Tom, don't you dare! Hey,
One of needs to live to
take care of the other one
Hey.
Mind if I join you?
Okay, I know what I did...
Was unforgivable.
And I am not trying to make excuses,
But...
We used to talk all the time,
And then one day it just stopped,
And it killed me.
I felt like I lost you.
And then I was saraj,
and I had you back,
And we were talking again,
and you were telling me thin.
I wasn't telling you anything.
I was telling her.
Okay.
Well, for what it's worth,
I loved our conversations,
And I'm... going to miss them.
Me, too.
Orson, you're still up.
Oh, I wish you could've been there.
Linda flanagan loved my food.
She said I was "god's
gift to the table"
And that I could quote
her on the book jacket.
Are you all right?
I'm hungry.
It's after midnight.
Haven't you eaten?
I was waiting for you. You
said you'd make me pot roast.
I am so sorry. I-I
lost all track of time,
And linda had so many
questions about the food.
I'll make you that pot
roast tomorrow, okay? No.
I want it now.
Now?
You promised.
Orson, I've been cooking all day.
I... I'm so tired,
I can barely stand up.
You really want me to
make you a pot roast now?
You promised.
Toby!
Where in the world
did you come from, huh?
Yes, everyone appreciates
a good neighbor...
You know, the kind that helps
you with the groceries...
But doesn't ask, "why
is your son so moody?"
The type that delivers misplaced mail
But doesn't point out your
wife seems discontented...
The sort that offers
to mow your lawn...
But doesn't mention
your husband seems cold.
But if you're not
sure the man next door
Is as nice as he would
have you believe...
Now why would you bring me flowers?
'Cause you've got a computer,
And I need to find out some
stuff about Edie's husband.
Do everything you can to
get to know him better.