Eli Scruggs
was the handiest
of all handymen.
You could ask any
of his customers,
and they would tell you,
there was nothing
he couldn't fix.
Whether it was a broken vase...
a leaky pipe...
or a shaky banister,
Eli always knew
how to get the job done.
But sadly,
the man who had fixed
so many things
for the residents
of Wisteria Lane
was now about
to break their hearts.
Eli Scruggs,
get down from there!
Mrs. McCluskey.
Just found this note
in my mailbox.
Says you're retiring?
What the hell?
Yes, ma'am. It's true.
Now why would you want to do
something stupid like that?
My doc says
I got a bum ticker,
have to take it easy
from now on.
Well, once I'm done fixing
Mrs. Mayer's shingles,
I'm on a plane to Waikiki.
- Well, this is very annoying.
Who's gonna fix my water heater
when it breaks?
Oh, I met this young guy
named Toby.
Very bright, just turned 30.
He'll take care of you.
Ah, damn it, Eli!
I am not comfortable
with strangers in my house.
Took me ten years to trust you.
- I know.
Most of those guys leave tools
and nails all over the place.
You never leave a mess.
Thank you, ma'am.
Have you told everyone else
you're leaving?
I left copies of that same note
in everybody's mailbox.
Well, that's not right.
After all these years, people
will want to say good-bye,
and... you know, maybe throw you
a party or somethin'.
Oh, no. I prefer to go quietly,
if you know what I mean.
I don't want a big fuss.
Well, I'll miss you, Eli.
There will never be
another one like you.
With that Eli Scruggs
climbed his ladder
for the very last time.
And once he had finished
making his last repair,
Eli Scruggs--
quietly, with no fuss--
had a heart attack and died.
And most importantly...
without leaving a mess.
It took an hour
for someone to finally notice
the body laying atop
Susan Mayer's roof.
Aah!
It was
less than ten minutes later
that the neighbors
began arriving,
each determined to get a look
at the various paramedics
and policemen
who were all frantically
trying to figure out
exactly how
to bring the body down.
And it took two days
for my friends to realize
this tragedy
had affected them...
We're ready! Come on.
more than
they were willing to admit.
Hey, Gaby, did you remember
to get change?
'Cause when I cash in my chips,
I don't want to hear you say,
"all I've got is $50s."
- Speaking of cashing in your chips,
anyone know when Eli's funeral is?
- Oh, I think it's Saturday.
I wonder how many people
are gonna show up.
Mrs. McCluskey was saying
he didn't have much family.
Poor Eli. We should make sure
he's got flowers at his funeral.
I'm in.
- How much are we talking?
I don't know.
What do you think, Gaby?
Gaby?
Wow! Jimmy Choo!
Oh, Carlos!
These aren't even
in the states yet.
What's the catch?
What are you talking about?
You never buy me a present
unless I'm mad
or about to be mad.
And I don't think I am,
so why am I about to be?
I have to go to Cleveland tomorrow.
- Carlos!
They're begging me.
The merger's going south.
You just got home!
With shoes.
Don't leave me here.
I'm going out of my mind.
Everyone is so boring
and suburban.
And how many
freakin' honor students
can that school have?
Can we please not argue
in front of the handyman?
He has a name.
What's your name?
Eli Scruggs.
You hear that, Carlos?
You've brought me to a place
where people are named
"Eli Scruggs."
Fine.
I'll give up my job...
and everything
that comes with it.
Not the Jimmy Choos.
They're the only friends
I've got.
Thought so.
I'm going to pack.
You know,
it's none of my business...
You're right. It's not.
But the ladies
in this neighborhood
are actually pretty nice.
- Yeah. They came by, brought muffins.
One of 'em
wants her basket back.
That'd be Bree.
Anyhow,
she and the other ladies, uh,
play poker every week.
If you'd like,
I could talk to 'em,
see if they'll let you
host a game.
Hi. We're, um...
the neighborhood.
Gabrielle invited us
to play poker.
So... is she in?
Mrs. Solis
will be right down.
She likes to make
an entrance.
What does that mean,
"an entrance"?
Hello there.
Welcome to my home.
Oh.
That's what it means.
So I said, "pumpkin"--
That's what I call
Jon Bon Jovi--
I said, "pumpkin, even if
I could steer a yacht,
I'm certainly not about to do it
in 5-inch heels."
True story.
Well, you've certainly had
quite a glamorous life.
Well, it was before my husband
moved me here to East Nowhere.
Seriously, I don't know
how you girls do it.
Do what?
- Get out of bed in the morning.
I've only lived here a month,
and I want
to put a gun to my head.
You know what I mean?
No, we don't.
There are no good
nightclubs, no theater.
What do you do for a good time?
Well, we watch the kids
play soccer.
And the school drama department
puts on some really great shows.
And then there's church,
of course.
Church.
Oh, you're serious.
Look, I know it's quiet here,
but I think you'll find
there's a real charm
to Fairview.
No, no, it's cute. It's cute.
I get that.
It's just...
I was a top-tier fashion model,
and I guess I'm just gonna
have to get used to the fact
that the best part of my life
is behind me.
Good-bye doing vodka shots
with Kate Moss,
and hello
to sipping international coffee
with you girls.
Full house.
Yes?
Hello. Is Mrs. Solis here?
Oh, I got it. I got it.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Ma'am, here's the bill
for fixing your sink.
Okay. Thank you.
By the way...
You made quite an impression
at the poker game.
Really?
Oh, yeah. The ladies
can't stop talking about you.
Aw. Well, I'm sure
it was kind of exciting
for them to have a star
in their midst.
Uh, let me think...
did they say "star"?
I heard, uh, "stuck-up,"
"obnoxious," "bitch."
What?!
You know, I went out on a limb
to get you into that game,
and then you go in there
acting like
you're better than they are.
Oh, my clothes
said that, not me.
Well, did you ask them anything
about their lives?
Why would they want
to talk about their lives?
Their lives are boring.
Well, you know what's
gonna be really boring?
You sitting here alone in this
big house without any friends.
If I were you,
I'd drop the attitude.
Learn to like
your neighbors.
Well,
thanks for the advice.
You wanna add that
to your bill?
No. It's on the house.
I brought muffins.
That's so nice.
We were just...
Playing poker,
and I wasn't invited.
I know. I get it.
I just wanted
to tell you guys
I know I made
a horrible first impression.
Now you know why
models don't usually talk.
Because we say a lot
of stupid, patronizing things.
What I should've said was...
my husband's never home.
I miss the city.
I miss my life.
I'm lonely all the time...
and I could
really use some friends.
Anyway, here.
Now that's how
you make an entrance.
Gaby?
I'm sorry. What?
We're getting a wreath
for Eli's funeral. Are you in?
Actually, why don't you
let me pay for it?
It can still be from all of us.
- No, you don't have to do that.
I sort of do.
Now let's play some poker.
All right,
time for my luck to change.
This hand is for Eli.
Hmm. Next hand is for Eli.
You know, if we're gonna
have a get-together
after the funeral, we should
start thinking about food.
And by "we" and "food,"
you mean Bree, right?
I thought that was clear.
I'd be happy to.
Any special requests?
How about we pick something
from your cookbook?
Great. Gaby,
do you have your copy?
I'll go get it.
You use my cookbook
to balance your table?
Oh, it's only temporary.
Juanita needed
her coloring book back.
Oh.
- All right.
Watch out, ladies.
I'm sorry if the frittata
is a bit dry.
Are you kidding? It's great.
You should give Linette the recipe.
- Yes, 'cause that's what
women in their eighth month
really crave--more stove time.
Mine is so erratic.
I'm not even sure what the
real temperature is.
Of course,
if a certain doctor
would loosen the purse strings...
- We're not getting a new stove.
If you would just take on
a few more patients,
we could afford it.
Well, if I'm not supporting
you adequately, my dear,
by all means, feel free
to do something about it.
Such as?
Well, you could maybe...
I don't know, get a job?
I have a job.
I'm a homemaker.
And a damn good one.
So to make this,
you--you just s-sauté
some ham and some onions--
It's not happening, Tom.
I just sometimes think
maybe you would appreciate
the value of a dollar more
if you had to work
outside the home.
And I think you would appreciate
my value more if, for once,
you had to cook your own food
and wash your own clothes.
Lynette makes me sew my own buttons.
- I'll sew anything you want
if you just stop
getting me pregnant.
I want a new stove, Rex,
and if I need to get a job
to pay for it, so be it.
If you're
looking for a stove,
we've got one
that's hardly ever been used.
I wish I could say the same
for my uterus.
Oh, yeah. I ruined the brunch.
Hey, how's it looking
under there, Eli?
Is it gonna cost me
an arm and a leg?
Nah. A few fingers, maybe.
Honey, my stomach's growling.
When's dinner?
Oh, we're having leftovers.
You can heat them up yourself
if you want.
Since when
do we have leftovers?
Since I started
writing my own cookbook.
Remember how you told me
I should start making
my own money?
Well, I've been going through
all my old recipes,
and I've got
this great idea
for a real home-style American cookbook.
- You're not serious?
Why wouldn't I be?
People are always
complimenting me on my cooking.
You're great, but come on.
Every bored housewife
who pulls off a decent lasagna
thinks she can
write a cookbook.
You think I'm just like
every other housewife?
No. No, no, no. That's not what
I'm saying. It's just that...
what do you really know?
I'll learn. And I want it to be
more than just a cookbook.
I want to talk
about traditional values
and give helpful hints
about homemaking.
Look, look,
this is my fault.
You know, I-I was
ribbing you the other day
about getting a job,
but you took it seriously.
If you really want a new stove,
I'll get you a stove.
Now can you stop
this foolishness
and make me something to eat
that isn't leftovers?
Mrs. Van de Kamp?
I fixed your banister.
Should be fine now.
I'll just go.
You can pay me whenever.
I know this is
a rough time for you.
Thanks, Eli.
By the way,
the service for Mr. V.
was really nice.
You were there?
I sat
in the back of the church.
I wanted to say good-bye
to Mr. V.
So uh...
have you thought about
what you're gonna do now?
You mean, with my life?
I don't know.
Mrs. V...
I've been meaning to give this
to you for a while now...
but I, uh,
could never find
the right moment.
I kept it for you, just in case
you might need it someday.
Hope you don't mind.
Oh, I gotta tell you.
I made your Cajun meatloaf.
Whoo!
That may be
my favorite meal ever.
I can't believe
you saved this.
Ah.
Of course,
I'm not really in the mood
to write a cookbook
right now.
Well...
maybe one day you will be.
Hey, Bree, I know what
you can make for the wake--
that flaky-breaded-shrimp
thing.
Thanks, but I know
exactly what I'm gonna make.
Dave, it was a nice trip,
but I gotta tell you,
I don't know why we spent all
that money going to the Bahamas.
If we're not gonna
leave the hotel room,
then why not just cover
ourselves in suntan lotion
and have sex here?
You just got a message
from Mrs. McCluskey.
Oh?
She said your handyman died.
Eli?
Oh, my God.
He was
working on Susan's roof
and dropped dead
of a heart attack.
Can you believe that?
No, no, no. You are not
going to the gym again.
You said we were gonna
have afternoon sex.
We'll do it when I get back.
You say that
every time, Umberto,
And then you're too tired.
Maybe I wouldn't be
if you weren't so clingy.
Clingy?
We haven't had sex
in two weeks.
It's like I'm 15 again.
Not us. You.
Your libido
is out of control.
Umberto--
Look, you've got
a drawerful of toys. Use 'em.
Oh!
Ahem.
Oh! Eli! I-I forgot
you were in there.
Yeah. I'm done fixing
your faucet.
Actually, I was done
ten minutes ago,
but I was afraid to come out.
- I'm sorry you heard all of that.
The good news is,
while I was in there,
I re-grouted your tub...
free of charge.
Wait a second.
What do you think
of my ass?
Sorry?
My ass--
on a scale from one to ten.
Well, I-I-I, uh...
ticktock.
Ten. It's a ten.
And the boobs?
Perky and firm?
You've named them?
Oh, come on, Eli.
My husband
won't have sex with me.
I just need to make sure
it's not... me.
It's not you.
Are you sure?
Trust me. I used
to work in construction.
My buddies would've
gone crazy for you--
cat calls, uh,
nasty gestures.
"Hey, you,
with the sweater meats!
"If you ever need
any work done, call me!
'Cause I got the perfect tool
for the job!"
Y-you get the drift.
Yeah. I do.
That was insulting
and demeaning.
Oh.
Thank you so much.
Miss Britt?
The door was wide open.
I got the paint. You
want to check the color?
Eh.
Is everything okay?
Things are great.
You want some wine?
We're celebrating.
What's the occasion?
I am no longer married
to a gay guy.
Umberto was gay?
So you wasted your time
installing that light
in the closet,
because...
he went flying out of there.
At least you know now
it wasn't you.
Wasn't it?
He said
that being married to me
was what convinced him
that he liked men.
Oh.
You could imagine what a
boost to the ego that was.
Come on.
You had a gay guy sleeping
with you for two years,
and those guys are pretty hard to land.
No. No, trust me.
No need to be sad.
You're a knockout.
No, I-I-I need
this hand back.
It's hard to be a handyman
without a-a hand.
Mm.
Miss Britt,
what are you doing?
You put the mirror
over my bed.
You know
exactly what I'm doing.
Are you sure about this? I don't
want to take advantage of you.
Oh,
I'm sure you'll be gentle.
Anyway,
I guess they're
burying him on Saturday.
Obviously, you want to go.
Yeah.
I do.
Oh,
leave that black dress out.
I'll get it dry-cleaned
for the funeral.
A little sexy for a funeral,
isn't it?
Oh, I don't think Eli would mind.
Mom?
That's Penny.
I'll be right back.
Mom!
Hey, sweetie.
What's up?
You said you would
help me with my math.
We're dividing fractions.
Oh. I wish you'd caught me
two Chardonnays ago.
Mom, you promised.
I know, but mommy's
still planning Eli's memorial.
Start without me.
I'll be there
in a little while.
Oh, my gosh.
Lynette, are you okay?
The doctor just called.
I'm pregnant.
This is fantastic!
You--
Yeah. Whoop-dee-doo.
Honey, you don't sound
too happy about this.
I was planning
to go back to work.
What? What a--
what are you talking about?
I had it in the back
of my mind for a while,
and then yesterday, I got a ph--
- Hold it.
Sorry. I was having trouble
paying attention.
Jeffrey Cuevas is retiring
in September.
I am the perfect person
to step into his job,
and that is exactly when
Parker starts kindergarten.
The timing is like a dream.
But what about our dream
of having a-a little girl?
This could be our chance.
Oh, please. You know it's gonna
be a boy. It's always a boy.
It's just gonna pee
in my face
and hide dead things
in my shoes.
I am doing this, Tom.
I am going after this job.
But who's gonna take care of the kids?
Well, I was hoping you could
cut back on your hours at work.
I can't do that.
I have a career.
You did not just say that.
No, I-I didn't. I didn't.
Tom, I cannot just
stay at home wiping noses.
I need it for my sanity,
and I need you
to back me up.
Oh!
Mom?
Well, the kids are up.
They're gonna want
their breakfast.
And I'm gonna back you up
by, uh, making it for 'em.
My hero.
Jeff Cuevas is fantastic,
but I know I could take his
department to a whole new level.
What the hell is that?
Oh, my water broke.
Take the overnight bag
out to the car.
Oh, three weeks.
That's a little soon, but, uh,
sure, I could make that work.
For God sakes, Lynette,
we gotta go to the hospital.
- In a minute. I'm
trying to lock this job down.
What kind of
perks are we talking about here?
Okay, you're having
contractions. That's it. You--
I swear,
if you touch this phone,
I will have this baby right here
and then beat you with it!
You're insane.
We have to go.
Could you hold on
one second?
We agreed
I could go back to work
after I gave birth.
- After, Lynette, not during!
I'm sorry.
Is there any way we could finish
this conversation tomorrow?
Oh!
L-l-later in the day
works better for me, too.
Well, thank you very much.
Bye.
- Hey. Whew! I got the job.
Congratulations.
The baby's arm is sticking out.
Why don't you high-five it?
Tom, I am in pain.
Do you mind?
Oh.
You'll see, Tom.
I know.
People say that you... ooh!
You can't have it all,
but I know we can.
Oh, Mr. Swenson, I can't
tell you how excited I am.
Maybe you could schedule
a staff meeting
so I could hit the ground
running on Monday.
No, no.
No, it can't be Friday,
because, remember, we agreed
that we would start next week?
So again, thank you so much
for this opportunity.
Mrs. Scavo?
Yeah?
I think you might have
forgotten somethin'.
Could you hold on a second?
Oh, my God.
She's fine.
I was on the phone.
I was talking to my new boss, and I...
- She was only in there for a minute.
But it's 85 degrees outside.
I've never done this before.
You got a lot on your mind--
three kids and a newborn,
it sounds like new job.
Yeah, I do.
Yeah. It's a lot to handle.
There you go.
Mm.
I should probably get back
to Susan's windows.
Uh, you take care.
Lynette,
are you still there?
Lynette?
Hello?
Are you still there?
Hey. You coming back in?
No.
I'm gonna go help my daughter
with her homework.
Ugh.
Yard sale!
Oh! Good. You're here.
How are you, Eli?
Fine. You?
Great. Yeah, I haven't worn
these Jeans in a while,
and I found 20 bucks
in the pocket.
Don't you just love
when that happens?
Also, Karl left me
for his secretary,
so I need you
to change these locks.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Oh, thanks, but don't be.
Just hurry.
Karl said he was coming by
to get some of his stuff,
and I want this place
to be a fortress by then.
You're doing all right,
though?
Oh, well, on one hand,
I got dumped for a pair
of headlights named Brandy.
On the other, I reported
Karl's credit cards stolen,
and I cut the pockets
out of all of his pants.
So a little from column "a,"
a little from column "b."
Oh. Sorry.
Well, if it's any consolation,
redheads are nuts.
What do you mean?
That she'll make his life
a living hell.
It sounds like
what he deserves.
Brandy's not a redhead.
She's blonde.
So, uh, you maybe want to go
with a dead bolt this time?
What... do... you... know
I saw him around town
a couple times with a redhead.
Uh, people in the neighborhood
were talking.
I-I thought you knew.
I didn't.
Would you feel any better
knowing that, uh,
she's kinda chubby?
Just leave!
But what--
but what about the locks?
I-i-if Karl's coming...
Change the locks, then leave.
Okay,
but I really am sorry--
Change the locks,
don't talk to me, then leave.
Susan?
Susan, did you call me?
I couldn't really understand
the message.
Oh, wow.
You want me
to come back later?
Are you all right?
No. Of course you're not.
I heard you and Mike
are getting divorced.
I'm sorry.
Probably not
what you want to hear,
but I thought
you were a great couple.
Thanks.
Sweet.
Do you--maybe you remember
what you wanted me to do?
Locks.
Change the locks. Got it.
Let me go see what I got
out in the truck.
Susan...
I don't know much
about love.
I... I dabbled in it
once or twice,
but it always seemed
more trouble than it was worth.
I told myself
I wasn't missing much.
But watching you
all these years,
how...
how hard you've tried, how...
how hurt you've been,
but you still...
keep getting back up,
you dust yourself off,
then you try again.
Maybe I am...
missing something.
Maybe...
maybe it is worth it.
And, um, I'm sure
it's not gonna help
for you to hear
tell you this,
but you're damn heroic
to me.
You are.
Yeah.
Hey. Just dropping these off.
I finally got 'em cut.
Tell Jackson
I'm sorry it took me so long.
Actually, um...
Jackson and I split up.
Wow. I'm sorry.
Am I sorry?
Oh, yeah.
He's a great guy.
I just, uh,
want to be alone right now.
Well, good for you.
Oh, hey.
- Mm?
As long as you're here,
I think there's a loose shingle
on my roof.
Do you think maybe
you could fix it for me?
Oh, I'd be happy to.
But just so you know,
it'll be the last thing I ever
fix for you. I'm retiring.
What?
Today's my last day.
You can't retire.
I break too many things.
I know. You paid for the trip
to Hawaii I'm gonna take.
No, it's the right move.
Be happy for me.
Hey, I am happy for you.
It's just, uh...
this is gonna sound crazy.
What?
Um, I think you have been
the most consistent
male relationship in my life.
You're so stable and reliable,
and I just...
always thought
you'd be around.
Which is funny, because I don't
really know anything about you.
Well, how about this--
I fix your shingle,
and when I'm done, you can
ask me anything you want.
Great.
I will go to the store right now
and get some wine
so we can toast
your retirement.
I like that. Perfect way
to end my time on Wisteria Lane.
Oh, yes.
What kind do you like--
red or white?
Either one. Just make sure
it's a screw top.
Eli Scruggs was buried
on a Saturday...
and all the people that Eli
had helped over the years
came to pay
their last respects.
But one person was missing--
someone who had changed
Eli's life...
in a way he never forgot.
Hope I'm not interrupting
your day.
Not at all. Can I help you?
I was hoping I could help you.
I'm a handyman.
Just moved into town.
Looking for work.
Sorry. I, um, I don't have
anything that needs fixing.
Well, if you ever do,
uh, here's my card.
"Eli Scruggs."
What a distinctive name.
People do seem to remember it.
So if any of your friends,
uh, need help,
I can do pretty much anything.
- I don't know. Um...
If you have a extra card or two,
I-I could hand them out.
Oh,
I'd really appreciate that.
Oh.
Anyway...
thank you for your time.
I have a broken vase.
I'm sorry?
I-I was, uh,
dusting the other day
and knocked it off the bureau,
like an idiot.
Anyway, I saved the pieces.
If you could glue it
back together for me,
I'd really appreciate it.
Oh, ma'am,
you don't have to do that.
Mr. Scruggs,
I need my vase fixed.
It means a lot to me.
Now you're not gonna
make me beg, are you?
No, ma'am, I'm not.
Good.
Come on in.
Mr. Young?
Oh. Didn't mean to disturb you.
Your front door was wide open.
Oh.
Eli, I-I don't have any work
for you today.
I'm just here to drop off
that handle you wanted.
Finally found one that matched.
Want me to install it?
Not today.
Okay.
I'll just be going then.
Eli, wait.
What?
Do you remember this?
Oh, right.
This is the very first
thing you ever fixed for me.
Yeah, that must have been what,
uh, two years ago?
Yeah.
I just that glue really held, huh?
- Yeah.
I want you to have it.
What?
Why?
I've just been
doing some thinking
about the people I know,
the ones who've walked
into my life
and made it better than it was before...
- Oh.
People like you.
Anyway, I've--I've--
I've never said "thank you."
Oh, no, I'm--I'm the one
who should thank you.
You--you introduced me
to all your friends.
My business
couldn't be better.
I'm so glad.
Yeah.
Anyway, I, uh,
I want you to have this.
Mrs. Young...
Are you all right?
Everything's fine.
Are you sure?
You should go now.
So I look in the window,
and there's blood everywhere--
all over the walls and the ceiling...
- Oh!
Not to mention,
her hardwood floors,
which she just had installed
last week.
I don't know
what she was thinking.
I just wish there had been
some warning,
some sign that she would do
such a thing.
Eli Scruggs sat in his truck
for almost an hour,
devastated that he had done
nothing to save me.
He then made a quiet vow
to God--
From that moment forward,
he would do what he could
to help people,
to help them fix their lives.
And for the rest of his life,
that's exactly what he did.
That was a lovely service.
Eli would've liked it.
Hell of a turnout.
- Who knew he had so many friends?
I'm not surprised.
He was a good man.
I can't help feeling
there's more we could have done
to honor him.
Well, let's just make sure
we remember him.
Eli would have said that's more
than most people get.
And he would have
been right...
As usual.
Wait.
I wanted to fix something
for Eli for a change.
And somewhere,
in a place reserved
for the very best of us,
Eli Scruggs smiled
and said, "thank you."
Subtitles by LeapinLar