Previously on...
a call was made.
Sweetie, where are you?
I don't wanna tell you.
And if porter doesn't show up for
court, we're gonna lose our restaurant!
A guy threatens to kill your son,
and that's what you're worried about?
And as one love affair
blossomed, another...
you were married before?
She's dead.
I want you out of my house.
Withered on the vine.
Mike delfino has to pay
for taking you away from me.
I want him to lose what I lost.
it had been a long
journey for david williams,
and though it began years ago,
he remembered every step of it...
walking outside his front door to find
a policeman with news of a car crash...
running into the hospital only to be
told his wife and daughter had died...
no! No! Let go of me!
being dragged into a psychiatric
facility after his mental breakdown...
no!
Strolling into a hotel
weeks after being released
and bumping into a beautiful blonde...
marcng down the aisle with a
woman who, as it turned out,
once lived on the same street with
the man who had killed his family.
But his bride was now unhappy,
and dave williams was worried that his
dream of revenge had been destroyed.
Luckily for dave, fate was about
to take some steps of its own.
Hey, dave! What's going on?
Edie and I had a fight.
I take it you're giving
her time to calm down?
No, I think I'm looking for a place to
stay while she's looking for a lawyer.
Oh, man, I...
wanna say something helpful,
but all I got is "that sucks."
That it does.
So where are you headed?
Oh, it's such a nice night, I thought
I'd walk to at motel on the interstate.
Might as well enjoy the stars
while my life falls apart.
it's getting late, and so, uh...
hey, why don't you stay with me?
Really? I, uh...
I wouldn't want to impose.
Dave, you saved my life.
I owe ya.
Well, now that you
mention it, I guess you do.
come on in.
And just like that, dave's
dream of revenge was salvaged...
lead the way, roomie.
And he started to feel his
long journey would soon be over.
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ßÇÈâÈâ
Desperate
Housewives Season04 Episode12
At 9:02 the next morning...
edie williams began calling her friends to let
them know something humiliating had happened to her.
By 9:06, her friends
had begun to arrive,
just so they could
hear the juicy details.
So he was married before.
You don't kick a man out for that.
no. but you do for never mentioning it.
And especially when I
laid out mentire past.
Emphasis on the word "laid."
Exactly. Gaby gets it.
Well, maybe they were only together a short
time, and she didn't mean anything to him.
I doubt it, since he walks
around muttering to her ghost.
You know what would lift your spirits?
We should all do a spa weekend.
Yeah! Let's do that.
Oh, I appreciate the offer, but I think
I'm better off gettinlost in my work.
Well, maybe I can help you.
Think you can rent my house out?
What?
Jackson got a teaching job at
the college in riverton, and...
I'm going with him.
Uh, wait, you're moving?
I know it's sudden, but I
feel really good about this.
And it's only two hours away, so it'll
still be like we're practically next door.
I am so happy for you,
but we're gonna miss you.
Oh, don't worry about
us. Jackson is so great.
You are making the right choice.
Absolutely. Come here, you!
I can't believe you're leaving.
When you're done here,
you wanna come do my lawn?
Well, I figure since mike's letting me
crash here, it's the least I could do.
Well, that's very nice... and brave.
- Mike takes a lot of pride in his yard.
- Yeah.
Look at his roses.
Every time I walk by here,
I just want to steal one.
- Here, let me cut you one.
- Oh, no. Couldn'T.
He wouldn't like that.
Hey, you. What's up?
Not much. Got a call from dylan.
Hehusband's traveling more for his business, and
she doesn't have anybody to help her with the baby.
She's trying to pushe
to move out to baltimore.
So, uh, what'd you say?
Oh, just that I'd think about it.
What do you think I should do?
Well, she really needs your help.
I guess you should help her.
Well, I don't know that
she need it. Honestly?
I think she's just lonely.
of course... it would
be nice to be closer.
But is that a good enough reason
to uproot my whole life here?
What do you think?
I'm not sure. It's up to you.
I know. I just... thought
you might have an opinion.
oh, shoot. I'm, uh, expecting
a call from a supplier.
I'll, uh, I'll talk to you later.
on second thought, I'm sure
he won't even notice it's gone.
Of will require an updated irrigation
system, which I'm happy to take care of.
Bree, you bought us a house. We
can't let you do all this, too.
Nonsense! It's a small price to pay
to make your home more beautiful.
- I insist.
-yes!
It's gonna be here tomorrow.
Orson, take it easy!
impossible.
Soon, I, the grillmaster, will
christen a brand-new barbecue.
You're pretty excited about a grill.
Oh, it's so much more
than that, young man.
This is the prairiefire turbo.
It's 122,000 btus of charbroiling power.
Look out, cattle!
You think you're excited? Just imagine
the salesman who overcharged you.
Well, bree, I got a very good deal.
He only thinks he got a good deal because the
salesman threw in one of those "kiss the cook" hats.
And the temperature-sensing
rbecue fork.
- Well, that sounds good.
- Yeah.
Don't encourage him!
Orson is a horrible negotiator.
He's never met a sticker
price he didn't like.
- Oh, no, bree,
that's-- - it's true.
There's a reason the local car dealers send
you a fruit basket every christmas. W hush.
bree, could you please not do that?
Do... do what?
It's just...
when you talk to your husband that
way, it really pushes a button for me.
My mom used to do that, and it, uh...
drove my dad away.
I think he was tired
of being emasculated.
Did I mention it has a
rear-mounted rotisserie rack?
what exactly are you saying, alex?
I'm saying, if you're gonna be rude to your
husband, could you just not do it in front of me?
So rotisserie, huh?
Yeah. Good for chicken,
rolled roasts, legs of lamb.
This thing is so advanced, I
could obably use it to make soup.
I'm sorry. Daddy has to work.
Carlos, what is going on?
You're gonna miss your plane.
They're upset. They're
not used to me being away.
Oh, for god sakes, girls. It's
not like he's going off to war.
He's gonna be back tomorrow.
Why can't daddy work here?
Because daddy has a new job
that's gonna make us lots of money.
We don't need lots of money.
Hey, what did I say about
that kind of language?
Look, gis...
Daddy's gonna be home
tomorrow in time for dinner.
You can call me whenever youant. Okay?
And the best part is you get to
spend a whole day with just mommy!
heoh, llo, mr. Fishmanan.
I'm coming in. Watch the wheels.
Boy, you just had to
put a rug here, huh?
Uh, is everything okay?
It's about your damn son.
- Porter?
- How the hell do I know?
He's got red hair and he's got a face you just
wanna slap, and he's driving my sister crazy!
What are you talking about?
The retirement home.
Your kid has been staying
in your mom's room.
What?
Muriel thought he was just visiting,
but he's been there for a week.
Now the rules clearly state...
no visiting after dark.
Tom, I know where porter is.
He's hiding at my mother'S.
Oh, hiding, my ass. He's not
hiding. He's living there.
He even stole my sister's orange juice.
I'll take re of it. Thank you.
Call bob. Tell him we can
make the hearing tomorrow.
Nobodyan sleep there because he's
got that tv blaring all night long.
Look, tom, I can't
talk now. Just call bob.
I'm going over there now. Okay. Bye.
parker, I'm gonna be back in an hour.
Mr. Fishman, thank you so much.
well, don't just stand there.
Make me a sandwich!
Uh, one more thing. Could you see
about having the basement cleared out?
Yeah, e last time we went down there,
it was filled with mildewed boxes.
Oh, I'll take care of that.
There's nothing worse than
having old junk around.
Edie!
Case in point.
edie?
edie! Do you not hear me?
Yeah, I heard you.
Why do you think I kept walking?
Looks like the mailman switched
our mail again. Do you have mine?
Yep. T's in my garbag come by
and grab it at your convenience.
What is wrong with you?
I asked everyone over this morning because I had
this huge thing to share about kicking my husband out,
and you prance in with your, "me and
jackson are moving to a fairy castle."
I'm sorry.
I thought we gave your latest breakup
the three seconds of shock it deserved.
Get the hell out of here.
Gladly.
- what have you done?
- nothing. It's locked.
do you have a key?
In my purse.
Which I left in the kitchen.
Does anyone know you're here?
No.
- Help!Get me out of here!
- Somebody help me!
juanita, it's time for your bath.
I'm watching my movie.
You've seen it a hundred times.
She loses her shoe, the prince
finds it--end of story. Let's go.
I'll go when I'm ready.
- hey, it's not finished!
- It is for you. Now move!
Juanita solis, I am not kidding.
Okay. That does it. Juanita.
If you think I'm not gonna drag you
to the throom, you are sadly mistaken!
You're never gonna make it.
Oh, yes, I will.
My rage is fueling me in
ways you can't imagine.
what's wrong?
My rage just needs to catch its breath.
okay. Okay.
I am willing to forget this entire incident
if you just go jump in that bathtub right now.
What do you say?
I am gonna scrub that smug
look right off your face.
Oh, my back!
where is he?
I'm sorry. Have we met?
wait...
you're the girl who stuck
me here three years ago.
You come by every christmas
and look at yo watch
while I unwrap the socks you
bought me on the drive over.
Do you know what's going on with
porter? The fire? The arrest?
Yes. I read the newspapers.
Everybody's ying for
that poor kid's blood.
No, no. We have this great lawyer.
He thinks he can get
the case thrown out.
Oh, really? I didn't realize that.
porter! Come out from under the bed!
Mommy is here to take care of you!
Just like she took care of me.
Okay. I know you're mad.
I know we have a lot
to hash out between us.
But don't take your hate
for me out on your grandson.
Now where is he?
He's safe.
I heard muriel fishman
rat me out to her brother,
so I-I made sure that
porter cleared out.
Mom... this is wrong. Please.
Sucks to feel powerless,
doesn't it, lynette?
Please, help!
Please!
I'm getng a really unpleasant picture
of what u're like in the ol' sackarooni.
Face it, mer. We're stuck.
Gotta get out.
I'm supposed to be
meeting the moving company.
what?
Keep talking about how you're going
to move away and be with jackson.
I ar stupidi makes time go faster.
So now me wanting to be with
the man I love is stupid?
And needy and pathetic
and... kinda hilarious.
But there's one thing it's not, mayer.
That's "unexpected."
What are you getting at?
Have you ever in your
life been without a man?
- Of course I have.
- When?
I don't know. I'm not sure.
What are you doing?
- making a calendar.
- Edie...
oh, come on. We've got nothing but time,
and I assume you don't wanna make out, so...
first boyfriend?
Todd shaffer. I was 14.
And why did you and hot toddy break up?
He dumped me during math class.
And how long did it take you
to start dating somebody else?
This is a stupid
exercise.I refuse to--
- when was it?
- Lunch. It was lunch.
You know, I'm feeling
a bit randy tonight.
What do you say we make a little love?
Well, we've got 15 minutes
till the news is on. Why not?
I still can't get over the
way alex behaved this morning.
"Emasculating." I' never
heard such nonsense.
Don't you think so?
Well, I thought the matter in which
alex made his point was inappropriate.
But?
Well, I wouldn't say it was nonsense.
You can be a little tough sometimes.
"Tough"? That's not a word I
would use to describe myself.
Nobody blames you, bree. You run a
business. You have to be formidable.
Sometimes, if that frame of mind
carries over into your personal life,
it's only to be expected.
I don't think I do that.
I know you don'T.
It's not worth getting upset about.
Andrew and I are used to it, and I'm sure
in time, alex will get used to it, too.
Now... on to more pleasant things.
Even though it's my turn, I
don't mind if you're on top.
I think we forgot one.
Didn't you date somebody after
you stole karl away from me?
Ron. Dr. Ron.
- Are we done?
- Yep.
Here it is--the history
of your love life.
Proof that you can't
be happy without a man.
This is not proof of anything.
Seven boyfriends through high
school and college-- only...
41 days single.
What does that tell you?
My grades sucked?
It's a cry for help, mayer.
and it doesn't get much better into
the many decades of your adulthood.
Hey, I was single for several
months after karl and after mike.
But that wasn't of your
choosing. They dumped you.
I know. It's hard to look in the mirror.
Have you ever looked
in your mirror, edie?
You're famous for the number
of men you've conquered.
- Thank you.
- It's not a compliment, you tramp!
Okay, i am not gonna take relationship
tips from a woman who has hooked up with...
what is it? Over a thousand men?
Okay, that's tE.I enjoyed the '80s
but the difference is, I go
after men because I want them.
You go after them because you need them.
That is not much of a distinction.
Yes, it is.
You have holes in your heart that can
only be filled by a pair of trousers.
Face it, mayer. You're weak.
porter wasn't there, and she
won't tell me where he is.
did you tell her that
he could end up in jail?
Of course I did.
Lynette, you're really upset.
Just hang up and come home.
She's so angry at me.
She's never gonna tell us where he is.
lynette? Lynette?
uh, we need to find lynette scavo.
Let me check.
This is all my fault.
She was so worked up
when she left my room.
I'm not finding a lynette scavo.
Oh, my god. Does that mean she's dead?
No. No.
It means she outsmarted her mom.
Oh, my god, porter,
we missed you so much.
I-I don't understand. I
thought you were in an accident.
No, sweetie. I was driving home last
night, talking with your dad on the phone,
and two cars in front
of me had an accident.
And I thought, damn, that could be me.
And then I thought, that could be me.
You scared the hell out of me.
We are sorry, but we had to get you
back. You've gotta be in court by 5:00.
I don't want to go to jail.
Porter, listen to me.
Bob talked to the judge.
He thinks he can get
them to drop the charges.
I don't know if I should believe you.
You're gonna have to.
- Okay.
- great. Come on. Let's go.
That was a rotten
thing you did, lynette.
I thought you were dead.
Yeah, well, what can I tell
ya? I learned from the best.
celia! Juanita!
I am not gonna ask you again
to pick up these clothes!
You've got till the count of three!
One... two... three!
You can hear me, right?
yeah!
All right, that's it!
I'm calling your father!
You are gonna get it now!
He is gonna tear into you!
It is gonna be a bloodbath!
hey, babe. What's up?
- It's your children. They've run amok.
- What?
Now that you've gone back to
work, they won't listen to me.
They know you're not in the next room,
ready to drop the hammer. Help me!
How? I'm in a meeting.
O-okay. I'm gonna put you on speer,
and I want you to rip 'em a new one.
I'm with clients. I
don't have time for this.
- But-- -
I gotta go!
Carlos? Carlos!
I think he hung up, mommy.
Can you bring us a lemonade?
hi, mike.
- Hey, sorry I'm late.
- Where's katherine?
Ah, headache. She ses her regrets.
you mind if I grab a beer?
Uh, yeah. In the test kitchen.
Uh, beer sounds good. I think
I'll grab one, too. Excuse me.
So... katherine not feeling well, huh?
Yeah. Yeah, I think she also
might be a little miffed with me.
this about baltimore?
it's not that I want her
to go, 'cause I don'T.
They why don't you tell her?
I don't wanna be the guy that comes between her
and her daughter, not to mention a grandchild.
I thought this was
because... I don't know.
Maybe you're still
hung up on your ex-wife.
Susan? No. No, that's over.
You sure?
And most guys I talk to, they say
they only really fall in love once.
And even if it doesn't work, they spend the rest of
their lives thinking about the one that they lost.
I always wondered if that's
how you felt about susan.
Why would you wonder
about something like that?
Oh, I don't know. You're
my friend. I care about you.
well, no.
In fact, dave, I think I might
be falling in love with katherine.
Did you just use the "l" word?
See, I-I didn't realize
it was that serious.
Ll, to be honest, it didn't really
hit me until she said she might leave.
Where are our guests?
The food's gonna get cold.
Oh, I'll go find them.
And bring some steak sauce.
Oh, you're not gonna need
any sauce with these babies.
They are seasoned to perfection.
bring it.
Well, there's no sense
in waiting. Dig in.
Oh, dear. Are they overcooked?
No, they're well-done.
That's the way I like them.
Bree, what do you think?
Oh, I really couldn't say.
You couldn't say if
your meat is overcooked?
No. I wouldn't want to upset anyone.
Well, don't rrY. You won't upset me.
I don't think she was referring to you.
Well, it's just that grilling
is suca manly pastime.
If I suggested that orson somehow
failed to produce the perfect steak,
you might see it as another
example emasculation.
I see. You're not gonna
let that go, are you?
Well, for all I know, telling orson his steak
tastes like charcoal might be deballing him.
You know, bree, you can make
your point and still be nice.
You know what else would be nice, alex?
Showing gratitude when people
have been generous with you.
Don't listen to her,
alex. She's not mad at you.
She's mad at me... and the meat.
Gratitude? What do you mean by that?
I mean I bought you a house.
You'd think you'd show
me a little respect.
seriously? You're bringing up the house?
Well, why not? It was a fairly
grand gesture on my part.
Yes, and one that apparently
comes with strings.
If by "strings," you mean I won't let you
be rude to me in my own house, then yes.
You know wha I think I'm going to
have to decline your grand gesture.
Keep the hse.
What's wrong?
Orson burnt the steaks.
Susan, how can you tell
if pickles have botulism?
Ah, what the hell? I shoot
this stuff into my forehead.
Forget it. I'd rather
starv for a day or two.
By then, you'll be dead, and I can use
your remains as a source of protein.
Oh, come on. That was funny.
You know... maybe i do feel
incomplete without a man.
But I... wouldn't trade places with
you for anything. You wanna know why?
No, but I'm trapped,
so knock yourself out.
It's the way you are with
men-- they're like tissues.
You use one and then toss it awa
and then you're on to the next one.
At least I'm looking for something al.
so you think this happy ending
crap that you believe in is real?
Please. I know what men are really like.
Really?
Well, when I was 16, my dad had an affair
with this woman who had a 10-year-old daughter.
And one day, he told my mom and
me that he was leaving us for them.
Oh, my god.
No talking.
A week later, he comes to
the house to get his stuff,
and my mom didn't want to see
him, so we went to the movies.
Now I had this, uh,
horse figurine collection.
Plastic, glass, ceramic--
hundreds of them.
Anyway, we come back from the movies,
and my dad had taken all his stuff.
So... I go into my bedroom,
and something seems different.
And then I realize all
of mhorses were gone.
My mom called my dad and
screamed and all he said was,
I was too old for th and that his girlfriend's
daughter would appreciate them more.
can you believe that? What a fungus.
oh, god. Are you crying?
it's just... now I get it.
Get what?
All these years, I
have judged you, and...
it is not your fault. Oh, come here.
you are the way you are
because of your father.
Edie, what the hell?
Don't psychoanalyze me, you simp!
I was just trying to tell
you how selfish men are.
And I was just trying to be nice and give
you a free pass for being such a big slut!
Edie!
Okay, girls. Pick up your toys and
put 'em in the basket before dinner.
Dinner's not for two hours.
I've had enough of your
crap. Now pick up these toys!
No!
Okay, juanita. What is going on
here? Why are you being so difficult?
When daddy asks you to do
something, you just do it.
That's because I love daddy mo.
Fine.
everything okay, mrs. Solis?
Yeah. just my kids.
They really know how push my buttons.
Oh, yeah. I got a couple
monsters at home, too.
The key is, you gotta
be the bigger monster.
Well, unfortunately,
they're not afraid of me.
Ooh, that's bad. Fear is the
foundation of all good parenting.
You gotta practice your big voice.
finish that broccoli now!
you see how that works?
Yeah. It's very effective.
well...
hey, you got an extra 15 minutes?
do it! Faster! Faster! Faster!
I wanna see this place sparkle!
Mommy...
it's out of my hands, girls.
Word got out that you were
disobeying, and they sent reggie over.
Who sent reggie over?
Well, I know how much
you love him, but...
it was your daddy.
Enough chatter. Ke moving!
when they're done, you
want me to make them vacuum?
- If you wouldn't mind.
- Nah.
Gues
- aw, come on, edie. I said I was sorry.
- Guess
July?
Wrong. March!
Man, you're bad at this.
Guess.
oh, hey, mrs. Williams. I
didn't know you were down here.
Oh, thank god! We've been
locked in here all night.
Really? Good thing I came by
to check the rat traps then.
I'm glad I forgot about those until now.
uh, mayer?
I, uh, would appreciate it if you
wouldn't talk about what we talked about.
I wasn't planning to.
Good, because I'll deny it if you do.
I won'T.
And... I'll kill you.
Good-bye, edie.
oh, I'll bring your mail
over when I get home.
Thks.
Hey, mom.
I just came by to tell you that the judge
threw out porter's case for lack of evidence.
Isn't that great?
Mom...
I did not put you in here to punish you.
I didn't have a choice.
- You had a choice.
- No, I didn'T.
From the moment glen died,
u were out of control.
It's true you lost all
that money in vegas.
You started drinking again.
D how many times did I go to your condo,
only to finyou asleep on the sofa
with a cigarette in your mouth?
No, I won't apologize
for bringing you here.
I did it because I love you.
Then why don't you come visit me?
It's not a very pleasant experience.
So I yell a little.
So I toss a few curse
words your way. Big deal!
Last time I came, you
threw pudding at me.
I'm an angry old woman,
lynette! What do you expect?
Here's a thought--
stop being angry.
How?
I can't make a friend in this place without having
them drop dead of a stroke five minutes later.
I-I feel like hell. Every time I
look in the mirror, I wanna scream.
My anger is all I've got left, baby.
If I let go of that,
it's over. I know it.
The ball game will be over.
The ball game is going to end
whether you like it or not.
I would like to be here with you
for whatever time you have left.
But for that to happen,
things have to change.
Would you come visit me more often?
At least twice a week, and
sometimes I'd bring the kids.
I'd like that. You know,
they turned out really good.
How'd you learn how
to be such a good mom?
I have no idea.
Well, now that you're here, why don't
you stay, and we can talk a while?
I--and get my flask
out of the drawer.
Hey, I can't be nice, forgiving
and sober all at the same time.
- Daddy!
- daddy!
Missed you guys.
You're really helping
mommy, huh? That's great.
The scary man told us we had to.
We don't even know the guy.
He left a flier in our mailbox.
You left him do your parenting?
Hey, you're the one who
told me to get creative.
This wasn't what I meant!
Easy for you to say.
They told me they love you more than me.
And when I was running things,
they said they loved you more.
Really?
So don't get your feelings hurt, and stop
asking strangers to discipline our kids.
Well, I wouldn't have
to if you would do it.
so you want me to go twork all
day, go out on business trips,
and what little time I have here with the
girls, you want me to spend screaming at them?
Just for the first 15 minutes
after you walk in the door.
Then it's carlos time.
Forget it! This was the arrangement
you wanted. You made me take this job.
I just wanted us to have a normal life.
Well, guess what, sweetie?
Dad's unhappy at work.
Mom's home with the
screaming kids. You got one.
Oh, good. You're back.
Can we talk?
If it's about work, yes.
If it's about what happened
at the barbecue, no.
Fine.Then as my employee,
I authorize a 5-minute break so we
can talk about my son's boyfriend
and his absurd
overreaction this afternoon.
Th's it. I'm out of here.
Andrew, please. You were there.
Alex started the whole thing.
You need to tell him
to stop criticizing me.
I'm--I'm not getting
in the middle of this.
If you have a problem
with alex, you tell him.
I tried. He won't listen to me.
Don't you mean obey?
He's not your son. He's not your
husband. He's not your employee.
Not everyone has to listen to you.
I'll--I'll do
this tomorrow.
I got the flowers.
They were from you, right?
Oh, yeah.
I just have a minute, and I don't want
to get into a whole thing with you.
This won't take long.
I don't want to fight anymore.
Please, just take the house.
I don't know how else to say this.
What happened yesterday
is gonna happen again.
It's not gonna be the last time
we fight, 'cause that's who we are.
Let's not make it worse by
living on top of each other.
Alex...
I'm gonna tell you something I haven't told
anybody-- not orson, not andrew, just you.
I know that I've changed since my business
took off, but I didn't want to admit it.
I've watched myself become
selfish, impatient, rude.
I was never thtype to suffer fools gladly,
but now I seem to find fools everywhere.
And I don't want to be that way.
I need someone who isn't
afraid to speak out,
to call me out when I cross those lines,
and I would love it if
you would be that person.
Did my mother-in-law just give
me permission to criticize her?
Yes, I did.
I'm a lucky guy.
Edie.
Listen, um...
I'm not happy about you lying to me,
but I think what we have is real, A...
I'm not ready to throw it away.
Really?
And don't tell anyone, but
I'm at the point in my life
where I could use a happy ending.
I'll get my stuff.
hello?
Jackson, hi. Do you have a sec?
Sure. Is something wrong?
Uh, no, nothing's wrong. Just...
we need to talk about this move.
At 5:15 that afternoon,
edie williams began calling
her friends to inform them
that her husband had come home.
Sadly, she never got
through to any of them.
gabrielle never picked up.
She was too busy watching her children
being told they had to obey their mother...
and trying not to smile.
Lynette wasn't home when edie called.
she was with her mother, laughing and
sharing stories about the old days...
and enjoying every minute of it.
Bree was outside showing her
future son-in-law color samples
for the home she had bought him...
and smiling politely
when they disagreed.
And susan-- well,
she didn't answer
because she was sittinin her
favorite chair with a cup of tea...
learning to enjoy, for
the first time in her life,
what it was like to be alone.