Previously on...
Porter's affair...
Your son loves me, and i love him.
Escalated into violence.
- Hey,warren.
- Yeah?
I don't care what it takes. You're dead.
But the full extent of
Dave's rage was realized...
Fire!
During the battle of the bands.
Mike!
And out of the tragedy came a hero.
Hang in there.
I'm not done with you yet.
Something awful happened
to gabrielle solis...
And she was reminded of this every
time she looked in a mirror...
Every time she glanced
at an old photo...
And every time she walked past a man.
Yes,gabrielle knew
she had lost her looks.
But she tried her best to
look on the bright side.
After all,what woman
needs to be beautiful...
When her husband is blind?
Hi,sweetie.
How's our patient?
Well,he took a pretty nasty
fall in the fire last night.
But,uh,the c.t.scan shows
no bleeding or swelling.
That's it? No concussion?
Actually,there is something.
Please tell me it's not my hearing.
I'm already down to four senses.
The scan revealed a tiny bone fragment that
may be putting pressure on the optic nerves.
And,what,you're afraid it's
gonna impair his vision?
I'm sorry. You were saying?
The bone fragment might be a remnant
from your injury five years ago.
Due to its small size, the
original scan might have missed it.
Mm,five years. Can't we just leave it?
Actually,there is a chance if we remove that
bone fragment, you could regain your sight.
- Are you serious?
- That's fantastic!
I'm not promising a slam dunk here.
I'm just saying it's possible.
Doc,two days ago,i spread
moisturizer on a cracker.
I'd kill for "possible."
I've spoken with ted daniels.
He's the best eye surgeon in the state.
He says he could fit you in
for surgery in about a month.
Oh,my god.
If this works, i'll finally be able to
see my little girls and my gorgeous wife.
This is unbelievable! Thank you.
Doctor, thank you very much.
Yes,gabrielle solis knew
she had lost her beauty.
She also knew the time
had come to get it back.
www.SUBTITULOS.es
-DIFUNDE LA PALABRA-
www.SERIES.es
*TU COMUNIDAD DE SERIES*
Desperate Housewives 5x09
"Me and My Town"
TRAGEDY IN NIGHTCLUB
There was a fire in
the town of fairview,
And those who had been injured came to
recover at fairview memorial hospital.
INTENSIVE CARE UNIT
By morning, their burns
had been bandaged...
Their broken bones had been set.
And their wounds had begun healing.
Yes,everyone was well on
their way to recovery...
Except for the man who
had started the fire.
You see,hissuffering was just beginning.
- Sorry.
- That's all right.
- Are you Dave williams?
- Yeah.
I'm detective collins. This is
detective lyons. You have a moment?
Why?
We wanted to talk to you about
the fire at the white horse bar.
We've been interviewing everyone
who was there last night.
We were told by an...
Orson hodge that you were onstage
with the band when theire broke out.
Yeah. We had just started when...
Suddenly the curtains went up.
Everything happened
really fast after that.
That's okay. We know how
hard this has got to be.
So... Have they figured
out how the fire started?
We know it was arson.
Really?
It's looking like the point of origin
was the storage room off the back hallway.
And there was a body in there,too.
And you think that's the
person who started the fire?
No,we don't think so.
But this guy was pretty badly burned,
so it'll take us a while to identify him.
Anyway,if you,uh, remember
anything you think we should know,
Give a call at that
number there. All right?
Dave williams...
Aren't you the one who went back
in and saved that delfino guy?
Yeah.
You're an honest to god hero.
You should be real proud of yourself.
If you say so.
I would've come sooner,
but i burnt the first batch,
And i wasn't sure you'd
appreciate the irony.
I'm so hungry, i wouldn't have noticed.
Hey,can i get a kiss from my cookie?
Mike!
What if someone sees us?
What if they do?
You haven't told Susan we're dating yet.
I'm waiting for the right time.
Her friendship's very important to
me, and i want to ease her into this.
Okay. I get it.
See ya.
Just walk out slowly.
Give me something to live for.
Susan.
How's jackson?
Uh,he's fine, just getting
some stitches. How's...
Wait,who are you here to see?
You know... Everybody.
So many people in the
neighborhood were hurt in the fire.
I just thought it would be
nice to bring them... Gifts.
Crap! I didn't get anyone gifts.
But ididgive blood, so i'll just
remind everybody that i did that.
How you feeling? I just gave blood.
Uh,i'm fine,just a
little smoke inhalation.
How's jackson doing?
Oh,fine. He just needs some stitches.
Ooh,those cookies look
delicious. Where'd you get 'em?
A friend. Have one.
Oh,i shouldn't. They're yours.
You know you want to.
Well,i did just give blood.
Attractive.
Mm,i hate macadamia nuts.
You think they're white chocolate chips
until it's too late. Stupid hawaii.
Who made 'em?
Like i said, a friend.
Yeah. But what friend?
Wait. Is this a woman friend?
Um,don't you wanna throw
that macadamia nut away?
When i'm done. Don't change the
subject. Are you seeing someone?
Why doyoucare?
I care because you mean a lot to me,
And it makes me feel good knowing that
two people have found love and happiness.
So what's her name? Who am i happy for?
Susan,i'm not tellingou.
Why not?
Because she wants to tell you herself.
So... I know her?
Whoa,i think my meds just kicked in.
I don't know what i'm saying.
You're dating a friend of mine?
Don't be angry.
i'm not,but now you have
to tell me who she is.
Fine.
Have it your way.
Oh,if he ever needs a transfusion, you
are not allowed to give him my blood.
Hello,dr. Cominis.
How's my husband doing?
Well,the x-rays indicate
there was no concussion,
So i think we're gonna
release him today.
Wonderful. The house was
too quiet without him.
You'll have to wait to talk to him.
He's been in a lot of pain, so we
gave him something to help him sleep.
Oh,that's all right. I can wait.
Mmm,he looks so peaceful.
Goodness. I'm sure if orson were
awake, he'd apologize for that.
Has he always snored?
Occasionally, but
never quite this--
robustly.
Well,the injury to his
septum might've made it worse.
But it can be corrected with
a simple surgical procedure.
Well,if it's so simple,
what are we waiting for?
It'll take a few weeks to schedule.
So... Soon as he wakes
up, you can take him home.
Well... At least the house
won't be quiet anymore.
I ran into katherine.
She said you wanted to
see me about something.
Right. What was it?
Oh,yeah. Thanks for saving my life.
Yeah,well... We all did
what we had to do,right?
And you went back in for jackson.
Yeah,but i ended up
passed out on the floor,
Which,technically,makes
me an idiot and you a hero.
Yeah,people keep saying that.
I don't... Feel like one.
Well,i would've been dead without you.
So... How about free plumbing
for the rest of your life?
That sounds fair.
Seriously,you've,uh, you gotta
let me do something to thank you.
Well,ever since my brother
died,i haven't had a...
Really good friend.
Think you could handle that job?
I think i could.
The stitches are in. I'll need
to see you again in a few days.
Would you like some pills for the pain?
Nah,stitches never
bother me. I'll be fine.
Great. Then let me get another
bandage,and we'll be done.
Thank you.
Mr. And mrs. Scavo?
Can we ask you a few follow-up
questions about the fire?
We already told you
everything we can remember.
This will only take a moment.
It's come to our attention
that the owner of the club
And your son got into a fight
minutes before the fire broke out.
Now did you witness that?
I saw a grown man beating
up on my teenage boy.
What else do you want to know?
During the altercation, did your
son threaten to kill mr. Schilling?
No.
Really?
Well... I was right there,detective.
My son said no such thing.
You sure?
Absolutely.
Thank you for your time.
Maybe i'm being a little paranoid here,
But i sort of got the feeling
that you were lying to the police.
Lynette,please, tell me that porter
did not threaten to kill mr. Schilling.
Got the bandage.
You might wanna go ahead and
give him those pain pills,doc.
He's gonna need 'em.
I don't understand.
Carlos might get his sight
back. You should be thrilled.
Oh,i know. It's just...
He's been through so much these past
five years, and he's never complained.
I just think he deserves to open his eyes to a
wife who doesn't tuck her boobs into her pants.
Oh,Gaby,please. Most women
would kill to look like you.
But i'm not most women.
I was an international fashion model,
and that's how carlos remembers me.
You are still beautiful.
So you've gained a
little weight. Who hasn't?
Don't go by me. I have
a weird metabolism.
Hey there!
I just heard the good news about carlos!
What's wrong?
Gaby thinks that carlos isn't gonna find
her attractive after he gets his sight back.
Yeah,that was my first thought,too.
- Edie!
- Oh,it's okay,it's okay. Let her talk.
At least she's being honest.
It's the kind of support and
friendship i need right now.
Fine. You're a pig.
Thank you.
God,what am i gonna do?
Well... You're gonna stop whining,for
one. You got a month,right?
That's pley of time to go on
a diet and start exercising.
By the time carlos gets his eyesight
back, you are gonna be looking hot...
Or hot-ish.
Really? I mean,do you
think i could pull this off?
Of course, even though i still think
you're beautiful just the way you are.
You gonna start that crap again?
I don't believe it.
Tom,i was 6 feet away.
Porter looked warren
schilling in the eye and said,
"you're dead.I don't care
what it takes. You're dead."
That doesn't prove a thing.
And--and--and i'm
sure he didn't mean it.
Maybe he didn't.
But ten minutes later,
that nightclub was on fire.
No. No!
I know porter. He wouldn't commit
arson just to get back at someone.
What about rick's restaurant?
Porter and his brother burned that down.
That was five years ago.
I mean,they--they were
trying to protectus.
They--they--nobody
got hurt.
The building was empty.
Yes,thattime, the building was empty.
This isinsane.
Lynette,are you actually telling
me that our son is a murderer?
I'm lling you i heard him
threaten warren schilling.
I don't know what happened next.
What if somebody saw him?
What if he left behind evidence?
What are we gonna do?
We're going to protect our son.
Even if he killed six people?
Okay.
Oh,boy!
Who knew healthy food
could look so tasty?
Okay,dig in.
What's wrong?
It smells like the beach that
time they wouldn't let us swim.
It's a recipe i got
from a diet magazine.
It's--it's fish
and broccoli.
Fish?
Yes. Not all fish is
shaped like a stick.
Now i know you're not used
to it,but give it a try.
You're gonna love it.
Yummy.
It's still in your mouth.
See? Delicious!
I want macaroni.
Hey,i'm not a short-order cook.
I don't have time to make
different meals for everyone.
It comes in a box. It's not that hard.
Okay,look.Mommy needs
to lose a few pounds,
and it's not easy eating healthy
with you two in front of me,
Scarfing down all the good stuff.
So what do you say? You want to
help mommy be beautiful again?
No.
You got a lot of nerve.
Part of the reason i'm on this diet is because
carrying you 2 brats for 18 months made mommy fat!
And you with the
head-- you ruined me!
So this is how it's gonna go down.
You're gonna eat fish with mommy
and you're gonna like it. Got it?
Thank you.
A spokesman from fairview memorial hospital
says this latest death raises the total to seven.
- Oh,come on. You're watching that again? - Authorities
estimate there may have been as many as 100--
Sorry.
Are you okay?
I just...
This fire--i still can't
believe it really happened.
I mean,they just said another
person died this afternoon.
That makes... Seven.
Well,if it makes you feel any better,
they think they know who did it.
Who?
Well,it's just a rumor, but i hear
they're looking at porter scavo.
Porter? Why would they think it's him?
I don't know. I guess there was a fight
between him and the guy who owns the club.
You know,i've known that kid since he was 6
years old, and i always thought he was trouble.
And trust me,i'm areallygood
judge of character.
You slept on the couch?
Why? It's so uncomfortable.
Yes,it is. Sit down. We need to talk.
What's wrong?
Orson,dear, because of the way your nose
was broken during the fire, you now snore.
Oh,didn't i snore before?
Good point. Snoring is too mild
a word for what you're doing.
Imagine a terrified
elephant summoning his herd.
You know,Bree, i can't help but
take issue with your sarcastic tone.
Snoring is not something
that i can help.
Not exactly true.
The doctor said there's
a very simple procedure--
Procedure?
Very routine and-- and
practically outpatient.
You mean surgery? No way.
I had an uncle who died during
an "outpatient procedure."
He went in for a broken wrist. They
put him under. He never woke up.
You don't have an uncle!
Fine. He was more of a family friend.
No,the point is, he's still dead, and
i am not having unnecessary surgery.
This is absolutely necessary.
I am going through a
very stressful time.
I have interviews,that cooking
demonstration at the mall.
If i don't get my rest,it could
affect the launch of my book.
Well, that's very reasonable.
Youget to be a best-selling author.
Iget to b an organ donor.
Orson,if we can't share a bed, it's going
to hurt the intimacy of our marriage.
My death will have the same effect.
Oh,orson, i can't help but take
issue with yoursarcastictone.
I hear you're getting discharged today.
Are you going back home?
Home? Hmm,let's see...
Two cracked ribs, black eye...
Nope,got everything i need from there.
I'm sure you heard about
the nightclub burning down.
Yeah,i heard.
Your husband's blaming porter.
What?
Porter would never do anything li that.
What's this?
I'm helping you help me.
This way,you get to start a new life,
And i get to not have you around
while my son is going through all this.
What if i'm not ready to leave?
Well,then you can face statutory
rape charges without the money.
Your call.
I'll pick you up tonight.
I'll give you a ride to the bus station.
You can count it then.
Hey,do you wanna take a walk?
I need a little girlfriend time.
I've got something in the oven,
but you can come in if you want.
So... What's on your mind?
Well... It's about Mike.
- Mike?
- Yeah.
Can you imagine how upset i was when i
discovered he's dating a friend of mine?
Oh,Susan,i'm
so--
it's gotta be lisa wallace.
So shocked at lisa! How dare she?
You know,she has wanted to get
her hooks into Mike for years.
Every time she would have us over for a
barbecue, she always wore something booby.
Well,in lisa's defense, maybe
she thinks you're over Mike,
Which is something i've
heard you say more than once.
Well,it doesn't matter.
She's my friend.
She should've co to me
and discussed it first.
Well,you're not always available.
And besides...Maybe...
lisa was waiting to see
if this thing had a future.
All things we can discuss when i
knock her teeth out with a pool cue.
You know,it's sad when
you can't trust a friend.
Or maybe the lesson here is that she
wasn't really a friend to begin with then.
What's wrong?
Susan,i swear i was gonna tell y.
It's fine. It's... Fine.
I just didn't think it
would be such a big deal.
I mean, you're seeing jackson now.
Yes,i am. You're perfectly right.
And i've been so lonely lately.
Well,now you're not.
I know you're mad at me. Would you
just please yell at me or something?
Oh,damn it. I should've
listened to Bree.
- Bree?
- Yes. She told me weeks ago i should've told you.
- So Bree knew?
- Yes.
Okay. Well,have a nice day.
So... We're okay then?
You knew about katherine and Mike?
Oh,god,Susan. Can't this
wait till after my nap?
Why didn't you tell me?
I didn't think it was my place.
I thought katherine should tell you.
Well,she didn't.
I'm sorry.
Uh,not good enough.
Y-you had a million chances to
say something and you didn't.
That is just the same
as lying to my face.
You know,i always thought that the one
thing i could depend on you for was honesty.
What happened to that?
You want honesty? Fine.
You didn't want to divorce Mike.
You hit a really bad patch after the
accident, but you never stopped loving him.
And why would you?
Your relationship didn't
have a natural end.
So face it. You're not mad
at me or Mike or katherine.
You're mad at yourself for
letting your marriage fall apart.
What am i supposed to do?
Either tell Mike how
you feel or move on,
Because that's what he's trying to
do, and it's not fair to stop him.
You need to make a decision, Susan.
And i need to get back to my nap.
I know ****not to get our hopes up...
But i can't help it. My hopes
are up. I am gonna see again!
I knew it. Ou're excited,too.
I can hear it in your voice.
Hi,dr. Bach! How are you?
Hi,mrs. Solis.
Hey,doc! We are still
reeling over the good news.
Well,i have even better news.
Dr. Daniels just had a cancellation.
He can fit you in next friday.
Friday?
But you said it would
be at least a month.
I mean,that's so soon.
So? Friday's great.
Okay,i didn't wanna have to say this, but
you should never have surgery on a friday.
The surgeons are thinking about
the weekend. They're all distracted.
Next thing you know,you come out of the
o.r.still blind and missing your right leg.
Why are you talking like this?
Also,the surgery is very expensive.
We need time to figure out
how we're gonna pay for it.
How about using our insurance?
That only covers 85%.
And we arebroke.
You know what? The hospital has a foundation
to help people in this exact situation.
No. We don't accept charity.
What? Wealwaysaccept charity!
Well,i have turned over a new leaf.
I'm sorry about the timing,
carlos,but it is what it is.
Gaby,we are doing this
friday. Now drop it.
So you say this guy's good, huh,doc?
Dr. Daniels is one of the
top guys in the country.
That's what i like to hear.
Bree...
Pleaselet me sleep in my bed.
No.
I promise not to snore.
And--and if i do, i will go down to
the sofa and stay as long as you say.
And how exactly are
you gonna stop snoring?
Well,i read somewhere that
chamomile tea helps prevent it.
That doesn sound right.
Well,it's worth a try, right?
Look,i'll-- i'll
brew you a cup,too.
Whatever.
There you go. Drink that up.
All right,but i think i'll
be too tired to finish it.
That pill i took really kicked in fast.
You took a pill? When did you do that?
When you were downstairs.
Uh,oh,well, then you shouldn't drink
this, because the chamomile actually,uh,
Counteracts the effect
of the sleeping pill.
Since when have you become
such an expert on chamomile?
Well,the point is, we shouldn't risk it.
Fine. I just know i
need my sleep tonight.
That's it.
We'll finish that thought Tomorrow.
I,um,don't suppose you'd tell
porter something for me,would you?
I know this is probably the last
thing you want to hear, but...
Idolove your son.
He was very sweet to me.
Kindness has always...
Been a weakness of mine.
Good luck.
Anne?
When the baby comes,
you don't contact porter.
You can contact Tom or me, and we'll
do what we can for you from a distance.
Understood?
There's no baby. Never was.
Hello?
I just got a call from the
lady at the department store.
She said that mom's late.
Late for what?
For the cooking demonstration.
That's today?
Yeah. It was supposed
to start ten minutes ago.
Look,i'm in mt.Pleasant right
now buying some end tables
so you're gonna have to get her there.
Orson?
Bree,honey? Wake up. It's 9:15.
9:15? 9:15. I'm supposed
to be at the mall.
Did i forget to set the alarm?
We need to get dressed.
I'll get you some clothes.
I'm so thirsty.
Well,i'll bring you some juice.
That's all right. I'll
just drink this tea.
Bree.
What?
On second thought, you need coffee.
Almost there.
All right,coffee time.
Enough coffee. It's not
working,anyway. It must be decaf.
No,it's a triple espresso.
I just don't understand
why i feel so loopy.
Very mysterious.
Look,Bree,all you gotta do
is whip up a few pancakes,
Hand out some advance copies of
your book, and we're outta here.
Do you think you can handle that?
Of course i can.
You are such a nervous nellie,rex.
Oh,and here's the lady who's gonna teach us
how to make her traditional buckwheat pancakes--
Bree van de kamp.
Thank you for joining us.
Thank you for having
me to your lovely home.
Bree,um,your book is about so much
more than just recipes,isn't it?
Yes,my book is about food and families
and how food brings families together
when they make food.
It's mothers teaching
daughters how to cook.
So i'm gonna cook
pancakes with my daughter,
Only she's not here 'cause
she grew up and stole my baby.
So... Who wants to be my daughter?
Hello?
It's me. I just wanted to tell you...
I've been thinking about it, and,um,
i'm okay with you dating Mike.
You are? You don't hate me?
No... And i think it's great.
Oh,Susan,thank you. I was so worried.
I just... I didn't know what
i'd do if i lost you as a friend.
Well,you haven't.
Just... Treat him well,
okay? He's a really good guy.
I will.
Hey,um,i was just about
to make a cappuccino.
You wanna come over?
No,thanks. I'm really busy.
I have a lot of things to do today.
Another time though,okay?
Bye.
Just call me back,okay?
I really need to talk to you.
Who's that?
Nobody. Just a kid at school.
I lent him my bus pass.
Listen,we need to talk.
What's up?
I have to ask you something, and it is
very important that you tell me the truth.
Okay.
Did you set that fire at the nightclub?
Before you answer, let
me say that if you did,
I promise,your father and i will stand behind you
and try and find some way out of this nightmare.
But if you lie to me, d i
find out later that you...
Killed... Those people...
Well,i will love you.That
will never change,
but i won't believe in
you anymore, and if i...
Don't believe in
you... I can't help you.
We have to tell each other
the truth from here on out.
Mom... I don't know who set
the fire, but it wasn't me.
Of course it wasn't. Of course.
Then we're gonna be okay, as
long as you keep telling thtruth.
Everything's gonna be fine.
Mom?
There is one thing i lied about.
What?
When you walked in, i was
leaving a message for anne.
She hasn't returned my calls, and
the hospital said she checked out.
Do you have any idea where she is?
No. Sweetie,i don't.
You know what i'm really excited about?
Christmas lights.
I might be able to see christmas
lights again and holiday derations.
Man,i really miss that stuff.
Yeah,well,let's keep
Our fingers crossed.
You okay?
Yeah. It's my hamstring.
I've just been working out.
You want me to rub it?
No,no,you rest.
You're gonna have
surgery in a couple days.
I know. I can't wait.
You know,carlos, i know you're really excited
to see christmas decorations again, but...
I just want you to
be prepared because...
Well,so of those lights
may have lost their luster.
So should we buy new decorations?
No,i'm talking aboutme.
Imay have lost my luster.
Come on. I'm always gonna find
you beautiful. I told you that.
Yeah,that's when you thought
you were gonna be blind forever.
But if this operation works, i just
don't want you to be disappointed.
Oh,come here.
Did i ever tell you when i
knew i was gonna marry you?
First time you saw me on the runway.
No,that's when i knew i
was gonna sleep with you.
No,i knew i was gonna marry you the night
we went to that restaurant on third street.
Mmm,i remember that place.
You wore a white linen sundress.
And you ordered this
giant plate of ribs.
And you ate them with such gusto,
up to your elbows in barbecue sauce,
Meat hanging from your teeth
and grease in your hair.
And when it was all over, i
pointed out what a mess you were.
Well,you pulled out your
mirror, took a look at yourself
and just let out this huge,Happy,
totally unrestrained laugh.
The room completely filled with it...
And i thought to myself, nowthatis a
sound i'd like to hear the rest of my life.
That's why i proposed to you, and
it had nothing to do with your looks.
You know when i decided i
wanted to be with you forever?
No. When?
About two seconds ago.
Up until then, it was
pretty touch-and-go.
♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪♪
well,my husband has agreed to
the procedure you suggested.
Oh,the one to alleviate his snoring?
Yes,that's the one.
So anytime you wanna get in there and
start hacking away, he's ready for you.
Aren't you,love?
Yes,dear.
Well,how is two weeks from friday?
Well,fridays are when orson plays golf.
So friday's perfect. Right,orson?
Right... Dear.
I'm sorry,mr. Hodge. I'm sensing you're
a bit apprehensive about the surgery.
Oh,he's not apprehensive.
He's terrified.
And i don't care, because
he owes me one-- A big one.
Don't you,darling?
I sure do.
I'm sorry. What's going on here?
Are you married, dr. Cominis?
No,but i just moved in with someone.
Well,over time,you'll learn that there's
a balance of power in relationships,
And if your beloved ever pulls
a nasty trick on you, like say,
Drugging you into a stupor, then
the balance of power shifts to you,
And then you can demand they prove
their love by,say,undergoing surgery.
Do you understand?
Not really.
You will.
Come along,orson.
Hey,hon,listen, can you
promise me something?
Tell me we'll never grow into one of those insane
couples that just lives to make each other crazy.
Well,no worries there.
You already make me crazy.
Oh,hey,guess what? I,uh,i picked
up our new end tables today.
Yeah,hurry home. I want you to see 'em.
If you walk through
fairview memorial hospital,
You will encounter all sorts of
people doing their best to recover.
It might be a husband licking his
wounds after a marital battle...
Or two parents rallying
from an attack of doubt.
It might be a wife who's been
cured of low self-esteem...
Or a pair of lovers who find
honesty to be the best medicine.
Sadly,you will alsoind some poor
souls afflicted with a condition
they will never recover from.
Detectives,i heard you were
still here, interviewing people,
and i have...Something to tell you.
Okay.
The night of the fire...
I was back by the storage room.
Yes?
And i saw somebody come out--
a kid who lives on my block.
His name is porter scavo.
You asked me to tell you if
i remembered anything, and...
I remembered that.
www.SUBTITULOS.es
-DIFUNDE LA PALABRA-
WE'LL TAKE THE HIT AND WE'LL
GO FORWARD. IT'S JUST MONEY.
IT'S NOT JUST MONEY.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
HEY. COME ON. WE'RE UP.
OKAY, LOOK...
YOU KNOW HOW YOU'RE ALWAYS SAYING
I KNOW WHAT TO DO IN A CRISIS?
YEAH.
HERE'S WHAT WE'RE GONNA DO.
YOU--NO QUESTIONS.
YOU--YOU'RE PORTER NOW.
LET'S GO IN.
COME ON. COME ON.
YOU LIKE IT?
IT'S BEAUTIFUL. WHERE'D IT COME FROM?
I BOUGHT IT TODAY. IT'S YOURS.
WHAT?
WE CAN'T AFFORD THIS.
I SOLD THE BASEBALL.
YOU NEVER TOLD ME
THINGS HAD GOTTEN SO BAD.
YOU WERE BLIND AND DEPRESSED.
I DIDN'T WANNA ADD TO IT.
THANK YOU FOR TAKING
SUCH GOOD CARE OF US.
I PLAN ON SPENDING THE REST OF
MY LIFE MAKING IT UP TO YOU.
MM.
FIRST THING TOMORROW I'M SELLING MY WATCH
SO I CAN BUY YOU SOME NEW
SHOES TO GO WITH THAT DRESS.
YOU SHOULD KNOW THAT WATCH IS A KNOCKOFF.
I SOLD THE RL ONE TWO YEARS
AGO TO GET THE ROOF FIXED.
SO HOW IS KATHERINE'S FOOT?
WELL, SHE'S KINDA GOT A PSYCHEDELIC TOENAIL,
BUT SHE'LL BE FINE...
WHICH DOESN'EXCUSE WHAT YOU DID, MISTER.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
SWEETIE, IF YOU'RE WORRIED
THAT I DON'T LIKE YOUR DADDY SPENDING
TIME WITH KATHERINE, DON'T BE.
I THINK IT'S GREAT.
BUT THEY CAN'T BE TOGETHER.
WHY NOT?
'CAUSE YOU AND MOMMY ARE
GETTING BACK TOGETHER.
WHAT?
THAT'S WHAT MOMMY SAID.
UM... HEY, I'VE GOT AN IDEA.
WHY DON'T YOU GO MAKE A GET
WELL CARD FOR KATHERINE'S FOOT?
- OKAY.
- GOOD.
I CAN TOTALLY EXPLAIN THIS. I SWEAR.
I'M LISTENING.
IT WAS--I DON'T KNOW, UH, ABOUT
A MONTH AFTER YOU MOVED OUT.
IT WAS BEDTIME.
I WAS TRYING TO READ TO HIM,
BUT HE ONLY WANTED YOU.
AND HE WAS CRYING SO HARD,
AND HE KEPT ASKING ME
IF YOU WERE EVER COMING BACK,
AND SO I FINALLY...
SAID MAYBE YOU WOULD.
I JUST DIDN'T WANT HIM TO BE SO SAD.
- OH, SUSAN.
- I DIDN'T EVEN THINK HE'D REMEMBERED IT.
OF COURSE HE REMEMBERS IT.
HOW COULD YOU SAY THAT TO HIM?
BECAUSE WE HAVE NEVER SAID IT.>
WHAT?
WE'VE NEVER LOOKED EACH OTHER IN THE EYE
AND SAID THAT THERE IS NO CHANCE
WE ARE EVER GETTING BACK TOGETHER.
O-OKAY.
MAYBE WE HAVEN'T, BUT WE MOVED ON.
DID WE?
SUSAN, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU'RE WITH JACKSON NOW.
I'M WITH KATHERINE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I DON'T KNOW. I...
YOU DON'T EVER THINK ABOUT IT?
I'VE GOTTA GO CHECK ON KATHERINE.
IT'S AN AWFUL THING TO LIVE IN DARKNESS,
UNABLE TO SEE WHAT OTHERS TAKE FOR GRANTED.
BUT IF WE ARE LUCKY,
THE DARKNESS LIFTS
AND WE CAN FINALLY SEE THE SECRET
SACRIFICES MADE BY OUR WIVES...
THE SURPRISING PROGRESS
MADE BY OUR MOTHERS...
OR THE UNINTENDED CONSEQUENCES
OF OUR OWN ACTIONS.
BUT THERE ARE THOSE
WHO PREFER THE DARKNESS,
BECAUSE THERE, THEY SEE
ONLY WHAT THEY CHOOSE TO SEE.
I KNOW IT MUST SEEM LIKE
I'VE FORGOTTEN AUT YOU,
BUT YOU HAVE TO KNOW,
I THINK ABOUT YOU EVERY DAY.
I LIVE FOR YOU, JUST LIKE ALWAYS.
BUT I HAVE A PLAN,
SO I HOPE YOU CAN WAIT A LITTLE LONGER.
I'LL BE WITH YOU SOON,
BUT FIRST MIKE DELFINO HAS TO
PAY FOR TAKING YOU AWAY FR ME,
AND I NEED JUST THE RIGHT MOMENT TO DO IT.
HE DESTROYED WHAT I LOVED THE MOST,
AND I WANT HIM TO FEEL THAT HURT.
I WANT HIM TO LOSE WHAT I LOST.
welcome to www.1000fr.com