??
±¾×öä»½ö¹©ñ§ï°½»á÷£¬ñï½ûóãóúéìòµóãí¾
When her first husband died,
bree thought she was rid
of her mother-in-law.
danielle got pregnant,
and bree got creative.
soon this whole charade
will completely unravel,
and we will be humiliated.
carlos and gaby's affair
turned dangerous...
if she pulled something
like that on me,
that guy wouldn't be around
for long.
and an old neighbor returned.
i didn't want poor aunt lily
to spend her final days
in a nursing home.
that is so kind of you.
(mary alice)
mrs. lillian sims
returned to wisteria lane
on a saturday.
as she emerged
from the ambulance,
it occurred to her
the neighborhood looked
exactly as she had left it.
she then decided
she should have
painted her house blue.
moments later,
she wondered if she would
see her husband in heaven.
these are just
some of the thoughts
that go through
an old woman's mind
when she comes home to die.
now if you need anything,
you just ring this little bell,
and i'll come running.
i'm sorry
to be so much trouble.
well, the good news is,
i-i won't be a burden
much longer.
oh, don't say that.
the doctors say
there's a good chance
that you'll be with us
for a very long time.
i know what's happening to me,
katherine.
you don't need to lie.
aunt lily...
mm.
what does it feel like?
dying, i mean.
it's not that bad.
i feel lucky.
when you know
time is running out,
you--you get a chance
to reflect on your life.
i-i really did try
to live a good one.
you did more than try.
god is going to welcome you
with open arms.
i'm not so sure.
oh, why would you say that?
i keep thinking
about dylan...
what we did,
what we covered up.
we did what we had to.
we should have told someone.
we couldn't. you know that.
it--it was a mistake,
and it's not too late
to rectify it.
your life may be over,
but that does not
give you the right
to go around
destroying the lives of others.
i can't go to my grave
with this on my conscience.
please!
we have to tell that girl
what happened in this room.
absolutely not.
as her guilt over the past
began to mount,
it occurred to lillian
death couldn't come
quickly enough.
this thought
occurred to her niece as well.
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
æ¬ãû µún¼¾µún¼¯
-=ææàãðü×öä»×é=-
·­òë£º¸öèëid
ð£♪ô£º¸öèëid
ê±¼äöá£ºuranus êø»¤ììê¹
there were a lot of things
bob hunter disliked
about living in the city,
and the thing he hated most
were the pests--
the rats
that lurked in the alleys...
the flies
that swarmed the garbage...
the bugs
that invaded his co-op.
i have tried it your way...
finally, bob informed
his significant other
it was time...
to leave the city.
so they moved to suburbia,
which they quickly discovered
had a few pests...
hey, neighbor!
of its own.
oh, we haven't
gotten a chance to meet.
i'm susan. i live next door.
oh! (chuckles) jeez.
hi. hi, i'm lee.
uh, i-i just wanted
to say hi.
you know,
i saw the movers taking in
some of your furniture,
and i just have to say
you and your wife
have gorgeous taste.
(chuckling)
need some help?
yeah,
like you wouldn't believe.
um, i'm susan.
i live next door.
oh, hi. i'm lee's partner bob.
oh, you're partners.
what kind of business?
you know, whatever it is,
just don't let
the neighborhood association
hear that you
work out of your house.
they're so not cool.
actually, we're life partners.
oh.
oh! (gasps)
oh, that's super!
(both laughing nervously)
yeah, i've seen a lot of cable,
so i get it.
(laughs) you're just great.
(chuckles) thank you.
i-i hope we can live up
to your stereotype.
ow.
don't mind him.
he's just a little cranky
from, uh, all the fresh air.
do not apologize for me.
lee, you're the one who said
moving here
would be better for raphael.
oh. so there's, uh...
there's three of you.
(laughs)
well, that must be...
cozy.
yes. we're gay mormons.
Susan, uh...
that's raphael.
oh. (laughs)
raphael is your dog,
of course.
you know, 'cause you folks
can't have kids.
i mean, uh, i mean,
of course you can have kids,
um, you--you know,
because times have changed,
and now you're allowed.
um...
what a... nice dog.
i should go.
nice to meet you.
hey, stop by any time, susan--
ow! what are you doing?
what are you doing?
well...
yes?
i have a delivery
for danielle van de kamp.
can i get you
to sign here, please?
is that for us?
no, it's for danielle.
there you are.
thank you.
that's odd. who would
send her a scooter?
i knew it!
phyllis--rex's mother.
ever since he died,
she's been trying to buy
the children's affection.
wow. well,
it's a honey of a bike.
i'm sure danielle
will appreciate the thought.
well,
i'm not giving it to her.
can you think of a worse present
for a pregnant girl?
well, i'm not knocked up.
let me have it.
you know how i feel about
2-wheeled motorized vehicles.
they're too dangerous.
we'll donate it to the church.
what?!
reverend sikes said
they're looking for items
for the raffle.
so we're just gonna??
well, it's better than
you breaking your neck on it.
mom, you know how much
i want a scooter. come on.
you heard your mother.
we're donating it to the church.
of course, we need to make sure
it's in good working order
before we do that.
(starts engine)
not without a helmet.
this blows. are we gonna
let her do this to us?
absolutely not.
if we win that raffle,
we're keeping it.
hey.
it is nice
to hear you humming again.
well, it's amazing what
a week without chemo can do.
yeah. when does
the last round start?
next month,
so i have some time
before i start feeling
like total crap again.
and i was hoping we could
put that time to good use.
are you sure?
i mean, the doctor said
it could be months
before you get your mojo back.
well, it's back.
and since when
do you question the mojo?
you're right.
you're right. forgive me.
okay,
so here are your options.
"a," we could go romantic,
play soft music,
light some candles,
or "b," go straight
to the--whoa!
(kisses)
god, it's so been so long.
i hope i remember
how to do this.
well, it's just like riding
a bike. you never forget.
now start pedaling.
hey. mmm.
hey. what are you doing?
ooh, sorry.
i just messed up your hair.
i'm just trying to fix it.
ow!
sorry. al-almost got it.
hey! (laughs)
whoa. hey.
screw it.(laughs)
what--what are you doing?
oh, i ripped it this morning.
it's been itching
the hell out of me...
and this is much better.
are you sure you wanna
take that off, honey?
i mean, won't you be cold?
no, i'm good. mwah!
♪♪
what??
late???
♪♪♪
♪♪
(susan) come on, bree.
you have to let us do this.
uh, it's a lovely thought,
but i really don't want
a baby shower.
well, i bought you
an expensive gift,
and i'm not giving it to you
unless there's a party
with people who can see
how generous i am.
(orson) bree, watch this!
orson, i said be careful!
(sighs)
i just think it's tacky
to have a baby shower
when it's not your first baby.
well, i don't see the problem
with it... hint, hint.
yeah, and showers aren't just
about presents. they're fun.
and we can play games,
like "how big is mummy's tummy?"
excuse me?
yeah, we get a ball of yarn,
and we each cut a piece
that we think is just big enough
to fit around your stomach,
and the one closest
wins a prize.
i really don't want
a shower.
(orson) look! look at me!
orson, just five more minutes!
that's all you're getting!
i tell you what. why don't we
just skip the shower,
and after the baby's born,
i'll have a christening party?
what do you say?
(grunts) i'm okay! (laughs)
i'm fine.
oh, dear god.
excuse me, ladies.
i-i couldn't help overhearing
you--you talking
about my mom's shower.
i-i think i could be
of a little assistance here.
why do you have to take
our new neighbors cookie bars?
oh, look, i made
a terrible first impression,
so i thought i'd make them
some of my home-baked goodness.
(scoffs) but you didn't
bake any goodness.
you just warmed up the goodness
i bought at the store.
well, yeah. i don't bake.
catch up.
you know, not all neighbors
have to be friends.
why don't you just
let it go?
mike, they live
15 feet from us.
if we have a fire,
i wanna be sure
that they like us enough
to call 9-1-1.
ah, that's the real reason.
you can't stand it when
somebody doesn't like you.
well, maybe.
well, maybe bob and lee just
like to keep to themselves.
that's fine,
and once they like me,
they can keep to themselves
all they damn well please.
hi. i wanted to bring you
a "welcome to
the neighborhood" present.
you should try one while they're
still warm from the oven.
that was really nice. thank you.
oh, are there nuts in them?
nuts?
yeah.
gee, let me think.
nope, no nuts.
are you sure?
'cause i'm highly allergic.
half a pecan could kill me.
i'm not seeing any nuts.
okay, you made them,
so did you or did you not
put nuts in them?
okay, here's the thing.
i'm a really crappy baker.
to give you something
that i made myself
would be like an insult, so--
so--so--so you bought them,
and--and then you heated them up
in attempt to make your gesture
seem more thoughtful
than, in fact, it was.
hey, i would've made them myself
if i knew how.
honestly,
i'm a good neighbor.
(laughs) yeah, well, neighbor,
why don't you take
your store-bought, warmed-up,
possibly poisonous cookie bars
and give them to someone
more likely to survive
your generosity?
do you like wine?
no, no, so please don't bring me
a bottle from your vineyard.
this rip is pretty big.
it'll take about a week.
a week?
all right.
you'll hurry if you can?
honey, it's okay.
you look cute in a scarf.
i'm upset
'cause that salesgirl
just walked away
with my sex life.
what?
after two months
of puking my guts out,
last night
i was finally in the mood,
but tom--not so much.
apparently, my bald head is
a big turnoff for him. (scoffs)
why'd you take your wig off?
it was itchy.
okay, not smart.
gaby, i am his wife.
he's supposed to love me--
not my body, me...
my--my soul.
why can't he make love
to my soul?
interesting.
question--when was the last time
you were in the bar
and heard a guy
turn to his friend and say,
"hey, check out the soul
on that girl"?
what are you saying?
i'm saying men are visual.
hell, i have a whole closet
full of costumes.
you need to give tom
something to look at,
something spicy, like...
gaby, i'm not a redhead.
but you could be,
which brings me
to my second point--
men like variety.
tonight you're a redhead.
(laughs)
tomorrow... you are...
(imitates swedish accent)
helga, the sexy milkmaid.
(normal voice) or...
(deeper voice)
amber, the lonely runaway.
(normal voice) or...
jeff, the friendly guy
from work.
what? i don't know
what tom is into.
claude, you know
i don't like it when you "hmm."
edie...
how long have you had this?
had what?
i don't have anything.
i'm just here
for my 5,000-mile checkup.
well, you know that bullet
you've managed to dodge
all these years?
which one?
the clap? the herp?
the syph?!
crabs?
relax. i'll boil
all the sheets and towels,
and then we'll use
this special shampoo,
and in three days,
the crotch carnival
packs up and leaves town.
oh, man.
how did this happen?
don't give me that look.
i know exactly how i got 'em.
i used the tanning bed
right after mimsy porter,
that skank.
(sniffs) ew, it smells like
burnt licorice.
well, come in the bathroom,
and i'll show you
how to use this.
(metal bristling)
i think
i can figure that out.
you know, the good news is we're
in a committed relationship.
otherwise, we'd have to make
that call of shame
to everyone we've been with.
(sighs deeply)
(victor)
...you've heard me make before,
but something i feel
very, very strongly about.
for me,
it's a very simple formula.
more development leads
to an increased tax base,
which helps build schools
for our children.
around the country, the needs
of children are being...
(whispering)
what are you doing here?
i need to talk to you.
can't you just call me?
this is not something that
you wanna hear on the phone.
(victor)
...and not follow this trend.
(whispers indistinctly)
and we will put education
where it belongs--
at the top of the list.
ew! how did you get those?
how do you think? edie.
you are still
sleeping with edie?
well, you're still sleeping
with victor, aren't you?
yeah, if i didn't, he would
think something is going on.
what is your excuse
for doing it with edie?
she wants to,
and i'm a guy.
ow!
this is serious, okay?
if victor wakes up
with a zoo in his pants,
there's gonna be hell to pay.
you don't have to tell me.
if he finds out about us,
i'm the one that's gonna
wind up in a landfill.
okay, just don't panic, okay?
we're gonna get the salve
or the ointment
or whatever it is you put down
there, and we're gonna be fine.
we'r're screwed.
yeah.
(lynette)
tom? the kids are asleep.
are you coming to bed
anytime soon?
yeah, i just gotta pick
a new running back
for my fantasy football team.
that's too bad.
i had a little fantasy thing
planned of my own.
whoa. lynette...
lynette's not here right now.
i'm brandy,
the slutty cheerleader.
this is all very romantic,
gaby,
but i still have
four building proposals to read
before tomorrow.
that's nurse gaby to you.
nurse gaby?
am i sick?
well, the doctor says
you need to relax,
and i know
just how to relax you.
wow.
it smells like licorice.
it's a blend
of 36 essential oils,
anise root and fennel.
do you like it?
it smells
a little medicine-y.
that's the fennel.
(chuckles)
it's stinging a little.
that's the tension...
(whispers)
leaving your body.
it's really stinging.
and we can rinse it off...
in three to five minutes.
but before we do that...
what the hell is that?
you know, for a guy getting
rubbed down by a hot nurse,
you ask a lot of questions.
sorry.
oh, come on, uncle frank.
what's the point
of having a gay uncle
if you're not gonna help me
make friends with these guys?
oh.
uh, mom said
that the whole family knew.
um, okay. gotta go. love you.
(beep)
what's going on?
oh, i found raphael
wandering in the street.
i went to take him back,
but bob and lee aren't home,
so i'm just gonna
give him a little treat
and put him back
in their yard.
bup, bup, bup! wait a second.
what?
leave him with me.
i need to score some points
with those guys,
and being a dog-rescuing hero
could be just the ticket.
so what, you're just gonna keep
him here until they come back?
uh-huh. maybe a little longer.
how long?
well, long enough
for them to worry.
you know, the more they worry,
the more i'm a hero. get it?
i get that you're insane.
i'm not, i'm not.
now get some mud.
i wanna dirty him up so he looks
like he's been through hell.
okay, in you go.
here, let me help you
with those.
oh, that's all right.
i've got them, mr. knievel.
oh, boy. you're never gonna
let me live this down, are you?
nope.
i thought the same thing.
it seems to me that you
should go to the doctor again.
(all) surprise!
uh,guys... what did i tell you?
you said "no shower." but look around--men.
so technically,it's a party, not a shower. mwah.
andrew told us that you only said no... (kisses)
'cause you didn't want to impose.
oh! (laughs) so you're responsible?
yeah,well,i-i know you said not to make a big fuss,
but,hey,you earned it.
(gabrielle) well,don't just stand there. come in.
we have lots of food and fun and surprises.
(under breath) yeah,all kinds of surprises.
(woman,singsong voice) where is she?
bree!
phyllis!
i,uh,helped with the invitations,too.
i can't tell you how touched i was to be included,
especially after my many conciliatory gestures
were so coldly rebuffed.
i have been awful.
i wouldn't blame you if you stormed out right now.
nonsense.
i'm here to celebrate our renewed friendship...
and your baby.
or should i say babies?
you know, it's often a sign of twins
when a mother's face gets all plump like yours.
oh,um...
i,uh, bet you wouldn't mind
if i broke my neck on that scooter now.
i'm off to the bank.
aunt lily just took a pill, so she's down for the afternoon.
okay. have fun.
is your mother gone?
yeah. do you need her?
no,no. (sets down bell)
this is what i wanted.
i thought you took a sleeping pill.
i pretended to so she'd leave us alone.
aunt lily,what's going on?
i have to tell you something.
first,you should know that what happened...
(gulps) it was nobody's fault.
what do you mean, "what happened"?
you don't remember living on this street before,do you?
no. (panting)
well... there's a reason for that.
(katherine) dylan?
mom,i thought you left.
i forgot my checkbook.
could you go down and find it for me? sure.
you really should get your rest.
hey. hi.
hi. got your wig back,huh? yeah. mm-hmm. good as new.
listen,i thought we could put the kids to bed early tonight,
if you know what i mean.
i do,and i'm up for that.
fantastic.
i hope brandy won't get stuck late
at cheerleading practice.
oh,about brandy...
bad news.
what? what--what happened?
well,penny wanted to play beauty school with the wig,
and,well,let's just say she's got no future as a stylist.
(chuckles) bad haircut,huh?
oh.
sounds like brandy might get awful mad about that.
brandy's history,tom. let her go.
(lee in distance) raphael!
come here! raphael!
come home,boy! (clapping hands)
raphael?!
lee? is something wrong? raphael got out.
i-i don't know what happened. i think he jumped the fence.
oh. well,would you like me to help you look for him?
seriously? what a--what about your party?
oh. (chuckles) it's just a baby shower...
that i'm throwing... for my best friend.
i can't--i can't ask you to leave that. that's--
oh,please. what are neighbors for?
raphael?!
here,puppy!
i see you've taken down all the pictures of rex.
well,i'm,uh,sorry if that offends you,phyllis,
but i didn't want orson to feel uncomfortable in his new home.
i see.
you're trying to be considerate of your husband's feelings.
well,i'm glad that you're at least trying to get it right
the second time around.
still,it must be awfully hard on danielle and andrew
to have their father's face banished from their own home.
he wasn't banished.
by the way...
where--where's danielle?
she's,uh, at boarding school...
in switzerland.
switzerland?! is it asking too much
to be told what continent my granddaughter is on?!
you are keeping my grandchildren from me,
and i don't know why.
i'm going to mingle.
every time i start a chat, you walk away.
i mean,if you don't want to talk to me,
why did you invite me?
it's a surprise party, you daft woman!
what makes you think i had a hand in the guest list?
so... you don't want me here?
oh,for god sakes,phyllis,
it's not as if we got along when rex was alive.
what did i ever do to you
but try to treat you like a daughter?
i even gave you my mother's sable coat.
you hated your mother. but i loved that coat.
then i'll give it back to you.
no,you keep it
as a reminder of how hard i tried
to make you like me.
grandma, are you leaving already?
i'm sorry,dear,
but your mother has made it impossible for me to stay.
where does she keep my sable coat?
probably in her bedroom closet.
where is she going?
she asked me where your fur coat was.
and--and you told her?!
oh,crap.
i guess you won't be needing the breast pump i bought you.
hey! so,can i take these?
(chuckles) so... danielle is having a baby.
yes,and for the sake of her reputation,
we've agreed to pretend that it's mine.
i just hope that
those swiss doctors know what they're doing.
she's not in switzerland.
she's at the sisters of hope convent.
look,phyllis,i'm sorry. i know this is upsetting.
actually,i'm thrilled.
i'm going to be a great-grandma.
well,um... (chuckles)
technically,yes.
what do you mean, "tecically"?
we're saying that the baby is mine and orson's,
and if you hover around like a grandmother,
people will be suspicious.
you're not keeping this baby from me,
not if you don't want me to tell those people downstairs
whose child it really is.
you wouldn't. think of danielle!
i wish you had.
if you'd raised her properly,
she wouldn't be pregnant without ahusband.
you think i don't know i'm a failure as a parent?
that's why this child means so much to me.
it's my second chance.
well,i hope the second time around that you take my advice.
i always said that you were too strict with those kids.
parenting tips from you? that's rich.
i was a wonderful mother to rex. then why did he always avoid you?
why were you barely ever here?
because of you! he knew you hated me.
oh,he was happy to let you think that,
but he was the one who dreaded your visits.
(whispers) oh.
oh. (gasps) phyllis,wait!
excuse me,everyone, but i have something to say.
what--what is it,grandma?
i...
i have to go,
and i just wanted to say how nice it was
to see you all again after so much time.
good-bye.
(lowered voice) thank you for the gift.
you know,bree,
you're not the only one who would like a second chance.
nothing,huh? no. no,he's lost.
and he doesn't know this neighborhood.
there's no way he's gonna find his way home.
oh,he will. come on. you gotta keep believing.
oh,crap! bob's home. (scoffs) what am i gonna tell him?
don't. we'll just keep looking.
i have a feeling we're gonna find that cute little guy.
you--you are so nice to do this,
i mean,especially after the way i acted when we first--
you know what? don't worry about it.
i'm gonna go inside and get us some water,
and then we're gonna just keep looking. okay.
lee! i can't find raphael. you seen him anywhere?
oh,bob,prom--promise you won't hate me.
what are you talking about? what happened? raphael got out.
he got out? yeah.
he doesn't know the neighborhood. i know he doesn't know the neighborhood.
what are you talking about? i know--i don't--
how are you looking for him? well,susan,she-- she's getting water.
oh,wait, he's right there.
oh! oh,my god!
what was our dog doing in your garage?
i have no idea.
what?
(lowered voice) did you get a chance
to,uh, napalm the jungle yet?
yep. and?
all quiet on the southern front.
gaby,we have got to be more careful.
absolutely.
it's kind of exciting, though.
what is? playing with fire,
almost getting burned but not quite.
don't be thinking like that.
if victor catches us, he'll kill us both.
(whispers) that's what's so exciting.
hi.
oh,my--excuse me.
mmm,that's,um...
an interesting cologne you're wearing.
my wife gave it to me.
it's got,uh, anise root,fennel.
what,you like it?
yeah,it's just,um...
i don't know... weirdly familiar.
crab cake?
uh,yeah. thanks.
crab cake? oh,thank you.
crab cake?
thank you.
kids are asleep.
i'm not.
whatcha got back there? just a little present.
say hello to brandy's even sluttier sister...
candy.
what are you doing?
well, i just--i just thought
since we had so much fun last night,
maybe we can have a little more fun.
and that's only possible
when you're pretending i'm someone else?
well, you have to pretend,too.
what?
this... (scoffs)
is me,tom, not brandy or candy.
it's just your wife,lynette. am i not enough for you?
what are you getting so mad for?
the first wig was your idea.
yeah,because i'm bald.
and i know that that's a big old turnoff,
but,you know, i can't help it.
i have cancer.
yes,i know. i hear about it all the time.
can you blame me for wanting to escape every once in a while?
escape from me,you mean? yes!
you know why last night was so much fun?
because i got to make love to someone who wasn't sick.
look,i know,i know,i'm not supposed to say this stuff.
i have to be the heroic husband who listens
and holds you when you cry and never cries himself.
but this affects me,too.
well... i know that.
you do? yeah.
how?
since this whole thing began,
have you ever once asked me how i'm doing?
oh... my god.
i haven't,have i?
i am one of those...
whiny,self-involved sick people.
i didn't say that.
no,i am. it's been months,
and i have barely thought about what you're going through.
it's okay. you're going through something--
will you stop being so heroic?!
i'm a cancer bitch!
what?
i'm not gonna argue with you.
(laughing) you suck.
well...
i guess i could give candy a whirl.
are the kids really asleep?
'cause i think she might be a screamer.
actually, if we're gonna pretend...
how about tonight
i'm not a hero
and you are not a cancer patient?
we'll just be tom and lynette,
see what happens.
oh,i'd like that.
how's bob's suit?
ruined. oh. what if we take it to my cleaners?
susan,that paint's not coming out... (whimpers)
so we're buying him a new suit...
for 2,000 bucks.
(gasps) $2,000?
well,according to lee, it's a dolce.
i don't know what that means, but he said it six times. that's crazy.
no,what's crazy is i'm about to buy
the most expensive suit of my life,
and i'll never wear it.
oh. i just wanted them to like me.
well,they don't.
lee said that six times,too.
there must be some way i can apologize to them.
we can't afford any more of your apologies.
i know. uh,maybe if i-- damn it,susan, let it go,okay?
i asked you to before,and you didn't,and look what happened.
so i'll ask you again. just let it go.
mike,wait. we should talk about this.
i'm going to bed.
i've gotta work tomorrow. i'm buying a suit.
grandma!
what are you doing here? you needn't be embarrassed, dear.
your mother's told me everything.
it's great to see you. (chuckles)
i hate this place. it's like baby jail.
oh. well,that's what i've come to talk to you about.
perhaps it's time for you to leave.
(lily,raspy voice) dylan?
is that you?
we have--have to talk.
hey.
i'm glad you're home.
i wanted to talk to you about aunt lily.
what about her?
it was so weird. she called me into her room this afternoon.
she started saying she knew why
i didn't remember living on this street before.
oh,sweetie.
your aunt lily is fading fast.
half the time,she doesn't know what she's saying.
was that her?
no,i just checked on her. she's sleeping.
you know,you have that recital in two weeks.
shouldn't you be practicing?
(panting) dylan.
please!
pests--
they come in all shapes and sizes
and disrupt our lives in a variety of ways.
at first, they're merely annoying,
and we do our best to ignore them.
home in my own bed....
but if we don't take them seriously,
they can become quite dangerous.
for some,
death seems to be the easiest solution.
but the problem with pests
is that what they leave behind...
is just as dangerous.
ææàãðü×öä»×é
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
»♪ó­¼óèë