Previously On...
Lynette Dallied
With Temptation...
Are You Sleeping
With My Wife?
Carlos Struggled
With His New Life...
I Am Poor, And I Am Blind,
And There Is Nothing About That
That Is Your Type.
Bree Found Herself
With A New Rival...
Bree, That Is, Like,
The Best Pie You've Ever Made.
This Is Not My Pie.
Okay, You Caught Me.
It's Mine.
And Susan Made The Best
Of Having Houseguests.
Oh, And, Listen,
Bob And Lee Introduced U
To This Wonderful Contractor,
So We Won't Be Imposing
For Long.
Imposing? Who's Imposing?
You Can Stay
As Long As You Want.
In A Corridor
Of The Greenwood
Rehabilitation Center
Is A Sign.
It's There To Remind Patients
To Be Honest About The Past.
But Orson Hodge
Did Not Notice It.
He Was Too Busy
Thinking Of S Past,
Or At Least The Part Of It
He Shared With Mike Delfino.
Orson Thought
Of The Night They Met-
The Night His Mother...
Had Murdered His Mistress.
He Thought
Of The Next Timehey Met
And How Mike
Began To Recognize Him.
He Thought Of His Mother's Fear
Mike Would Remember Too Much
And Her Demand That Orson
Stop This From Happening.
He Thought Of How He Agonized,
But In The End,
Had Still...
Done The Unthinkable.
Orsothen Started To Think
About The Message
He Had Received From Mike,
Asking Him To Visit.
The Thought
Was Crossing Orson's Mind
That Mike Had
Remembered Something-
Something Dangerous,
When Suddenly...
Orson. Come On In.
The Time For Thinking
Was Over.
So I-I See Ty Have
A Tennis Court Here.
Must Be Nice To Get Out
And Whack
A Few Balls Around, Huh?
Why Don't You Sit Down?
It Might Make This Easier.
I've Been Trying
To Figure Out All Day
Just How
I Was Gonna Do This.
Do What, Mike?
Since I've Come Here, I've Had
A Lot Of Time To Think.
Things Are...
Becoming Clearer.
I'm Starting To Put
Some Things Togeth.
Oh?
Well, Good For You.
No, Not Really, Orson.
When You Hurt People,
You Gotta Be Accountable.
There's No Way Around It.
So I Have To Ask You...
Do You Think
You Can Forge Me?
What?
When I Asked You To Write
A Prescription For Pain Pills,
It... All I Could Think About
Was Getting My Next Fix.
The Fact That You Could Have
Lost Your License,
Your Business-All That
Never Even Entered My Head.
And I Am... Really Sorry.
Oh.
Of Course.
No Need To Apologize.
Wow. I-I Feel
A Million Times Better.
You Know, One Thing
I've Learned Here-
If You Don't Get This Stuff
Off Your Chest,
It'll Eat You Alive.
As He Left,
Orson Thought Only
Of His Good Fortune And Relief,
Ignoring Completely
The Feelings Of Guilt And Shame
That Were Rising Within Him.
That Was The Sad Thing
About Orson Hodge...
He Had No Idea
Just How Sick He Reay Was.
From The Moment His Doctors
Had Told Him He Was Blind,
Carlos Solis Had Worried
About Only One Thing-
That The People In His Life
Would Come To See Him
As A Burden.
But As It Turned Out,
His Friends Didn't Mind
Driving Him To The Store.
His Neighbors Didn't Mind
Helping Retrieve His Mail.
The Paper Boy Didn't Mind
Helping Him Find
His Morning Paper.
In Truth,
Everyone On Wisteria Lane
Was More Than Willing
To Help Caos
Adjust To Fe As A Blind Man-
Everyone, That Is...
But His Wife,
Who Was
Quickly Starting To Feel
She Was The One
With The Handicap.
"And In A Surprise Move,
The Spurs Announced A Trade
That Will Send
Perennial All-Star To The... "
Oh, Jeez, Gaby.
I Asked You To Please Fish Out
All The Little Carrot Squares.
I Did.
Well, I Think You Missed Some.
Could You Get 'Em Out,
Please?
There You Go. All Gone.
Did You Just Use Your Hand?
Of Course Not. I Us A Spoon.
I'm Sorry
That I'm Such A Handful.
I Really Am Trying To Do
The Best That I Can.
I Know You Are, Babe.
And I Know It's Hard,
And I'm Gonna Try To Be
More Sensitive To Your Needs.
Now Hurry Up And Finish.
I Have To Go To The Store.
Could I Go, Too?
I'm Bored.
Oh, Please, Carlos.
I Have A Million Errands To Run,
And I'd Do It
A Lot Faster Without You.
Plus I'm Having Lunch
With The Girls First.
Oh, Okay.
Mm. Gaby, Another Carrot.
Just Eat Them.
Carrots Are Good For Your...
Sorry I'm Late. Blind Husband.
You Know The Drill.
Oh, Gaby,
I'm So Glad You're Here.
I Was Just About To Tell
Everyone To Keep An Eye Out
For Their Invitation
To The Founder's Ball.
I'm Sorry.
What Is The Founder's Ball?
You All Seem So Excited.
It's A Black-Tie Fund-Raiser
That Bree Organizes Every Year.
It's A Lot Of Work, Exhausting
And Completely Worth It.
Especially When You Get Your
Big Moment In The Spotlight.
Bree Gets To Present An Award
To Somebody Who's Done Something
Extraordinary For The Community.
Ooh, I Say We Nominate The Woman
Who Gives Edie Her Bikini Wax.
Ha Ha Ha Ha.
So, Bree,
I've Planned A Few Events
Myself Back In Chicago.
Small Potatoes Compared
To This, I'm Sure,
But If You Could Use Me,
I'd Love To Help.
That Would Be Lovely.
It Would?
Yes, Of Course.
Why Wouldn't It?
Nobody? Okay, I'm Going In.
Because You Two Would Kill
Each Other... Literally.
It'll Start
With Hair Pullg
And End With Detectives
Taking Our Statements.
Remember The Pie Thing?
"Remember The Pie Thing"-
Tibetan Monks
Remember The Pie Thing.
I Acknowledge That Katherine
And I Have Had Our Differences,
But We Have All Been
Through A Lot Recently.
And I Would Hope
That It Taught Us
To Put Our Differences Aside
And Be Friends,
Because That's
What's Most Important.
I Faced Cancer And A Tornado,
But I'm Running From This.
Hi.
Oh, My God. Rick.
How Are You?
Great, Actually.
We're Great.
Well, You Look Great.
Mm.
Oh. Hey, Tom.
Look Who's Here-Rick.
I See That.
Table For One?
Uh, No, Thanks.
I Just Wanted To Come By
And Bring You Guys...
It's Barolo.
I Just Got Back
From Italy.
Oh, Well, That's Nice.
Thank You.
Ah, What's The Occasion? Or Are
You Just Being A Good Guy?
I Can't Get Anything
Past You, Huh, Tom?
Well, I...
I've Got Some Work To Do.
Yeah, Well, You Know,
I Wanted To Come Here
And Tell You Guys In Person.
I'm Opening My Own Place.
Uh, You Must Have Seen It.
That's You?
On The Corner?
Yeah, I Looked Everywhere,
I Swear.
But, Uh,
It Was The Best Location.
I'll Bet.
Okay, Look, People Like
To Eat In Fairview.
There's Plenty Of Business
For Both Of Us.
Hey, I Remember You!
You Ck To Working Here
Now? Oh, No. Sorry.
Too Bad.
That Osso Buco Of Yours Was-
Really Something.
Well, I Got It On The Menu
At My New Place On The Corner.
Come Check Us Out.
See? Room For Everyone.
Oh! Orson, You Scared Me.
Why Are You Sitting
Down Here In The Dark?
And Aren't You
A Little Cold?
I Had To Do Something.
Then You Came Down Here And You
Couldn't Remember What It Was.
That Happens
To Me All The Time.
Well, The Baby Is Insisting
That I Eat The Last Piece
Of Bree's Triple-Chocolate Cake.
If You Want, We Could-
Oh, My God. You're Naked!
In My Kitchen Where I Eat.
Okay,
I Don't Hear You Leaving.
I Had To Do Something.
Pajamas-That's Something
You Could Do.
Okay, You're Right.
You're A Guest In My House-
A Completely Naked Guest
In My House.
I Should Leave.
Hey.
You Were Supposed
To Be Home At 8:00
To Help Me Wrangle The Kids
For Bath Time.
It's-It's Almost 11:00.
Sorry.
So Where Were You?
You Were Stewing,
Weren't You?
Come On.
You're Upset About Rick.
Look.
I'm Not Gonna Deny
I Was Ticked Off When I Saw Him.
But I'm Over It.
I'm Taking This
As A Challenge.
We Are Gonna Up Our Game.
Oh, Yeah? Yep. You
Know What I Did Tonight?
I Worked On Our Menu.
We Are Gonna Start Making
Our Own Osso Buco.
I Got A Recipe
That Is Gonna Kick His Ass.
So You're Really Okay
With This?
Yeah, I'm Great.
Look At How Cute You Are.
Oh?
It's Growing Back Fast, Huh?
Yeah, It's Back.
Morning, Susan.
Oh. Good Morning.
Love What You're Wearing.
Oh,
I Hope This Isn't Decaf.
Got A Big Day Ahead Of Me.
All Right. We Don't Need
To Talk About It.
Just Promise Me
It Won't Happen Again.
What Won't Happen Again?
Orson, You Were Naked
In This Kitchen Last Night.
I Was Not.
You Most Certainly Were.
Good Morning.
What's Going On?
Well, Susan Claims She Saw Me Last
Night Au Naturel. It Wasn't A Claim.
He Was Sitting Rht Here
Without A Stitch Of Clothing On,
And I Couldn't Have Cake.
Oh, I Think I Know
What's Going On.
Somebody Had
A Naughty Dream.
Susan, I'm Blushing.
No, No, No, No. No,
I Did Not Have A Sex Dream.
Susan,
It's Perfectly Understandable.
Mike's Away.
You're Feeling A Little Lonely.
Naturally,
You'd Project Those Feelings
Onto The Nearest Available
Sex Machine.
Oh!
You Are Such A Scamp.
I Know When I'm Dreaming,
And This Really Happened.
Why Else Wou I Be Sponging
Butt Prints Off My Sol?
You Know, Susan, Sometimes
I Climb Into A Warm Bath
With A Romance Novel.
Just A Thought.
You Wanna Give Me
A Hand With This?
Lynette!
Gaby, Since When Do You Come
To Price Warehouse?
I'm Poor Now. Remember?
I Have To Mingle
With The Unwashed Masses.
What Are You Doing Here?
Oh, I've Been Unwashed
For Years.
This Place Is Huge!
Would It Kill Them
To Have Valet Parking?
Gaby, People Don't Come Here
For The Amenities.
They Come Because
Toilet Paper's 3 Cents A Ton.
Look At All
These Handicapped Spots.
I Mean, What A Waste.
Take That Guy Selling Oranges,
Put Him In A Vest,
Stick Him Under An Umbrella,
And Bam!
You Got Valet Parking.
I Don't Know Why Poor People
Refuse To Better Themselves.
Yeah,
We're Crazy That Way.
I Don't Know Why
You're Complaining
About Handicapped Spaces.
Doesn't Carlos Have One
Of Those Blue Placards?
No, I Think You Have
To Have A Wheelchair
To Get One Of Those.
No, I'm Pretty Sure
The Blind Qualify, Too.
Mom, Can I Take Some
Of These Cookies Up To Julie?
Why Don't You Offer Some
To Our Guest First?
Oh, No, Thank You. We Have
So Much Ground To Cover.
Now Let's Move On
To The Flowers.
Uh, Last Year,
We Went With A Cascade
Of Pink And White Roses.
There It Is.
Exquisite.
Well, Easy Enough.
Let's Just Do That
Again, Then.
Next?
Well...
If You Have
A Different Idea,
I Would Love
To Hear That, Too.
Well, I Was Thinking
It Might Be Nice To Do
Something More Unusual.
What About An Arrangement
Of Purple Lisianthus
With A Spray
Of Dark Berries?
It's Interesting. I Can't
Really Picture That, Though.
Well, Let Me Help You.
I Keep Scrapbooks, Too.
My Mom And Mrs. Hodge Are Still
Talking About That Ball Thing.
She Wants Me To Be A Part
Of The Founder's Court
Or Whatever They Call It.
Like I Want To Put On
A Stupid White Dress
And Greet People All Night.
I Know. It's So Pathetic.
By The Way, I'm Doing It.
Seriously? Why?
Because I Did It Last Year,
And It's Actually Kind Of
Hilarious And Great.
It Is! It Doesn't Sound
Great. It Sounds Beyond Lame.
I Don't Want This To Come Off
The Wrong Way,
But You're A Buzz Kill.
Julie!
Okay, You Spend All Of Your Time
Cooped Up In Here Alone,
Obsessing Over
Some Mysterious Thing
That Maybe Happened To
Your Real Dad Or Maybe Didn't.
Look, I'm Not Saying
Don't Obsess.
I'm Just Saying Maybe
You Could Spare Some Time
To Have A Little Fun
With Your Friend, Too.
So This Founder's Thing-
It'll Be Fun?
Uh, These Were
The Centerpieces
From The Vanover Medical Center
Benefit.
The Donors Were Blown Away.
Well, They're Certainly...
Assertive.
My Only Fear Is-
I Know. I Know.
Fairview Is A Bit More
Provinci Compared To Chicago,
But I Think You'll Find
The People Here
Have A Lot More Taste
Than You Give Them Credit For.
Well, Perhaps I Could Try
Something New.
Let's Go
With The Lisianthus.
Look At You! Pronouncing It
Right The Very First Time.
Isn't Learning Fun?
Mrs. Scavo?
Uh, Yes.
Is Your Husband Home?
We're Investigating An Incident
Involving Vandalism.
Vandalism?
Porter! Preston!
Get Over Here!
No, Ma'am. This Incident
Occurred Two Nights Ago
Near Your Pizzeria.
Someone Threw A Brick Through
A Window Of A New Restaurant-
A Place Called Rick's?
What?
We're Asking Everybody
Who Works In The Area
If They Saw Anything Suspicious.
I Didn't Go Into Work That Night.
I Did, But, Um,
I Didn't See Anything.
What Time Did It Happen? The
Alarm Went Off At About 10:.
Oh, I Was Home Way Before Then,
Around 8:00.
I Came Home Early To Help You
Wrangle The Kids For Bath Time.
Yeah. No, He Was Here.
All Right, Well, If You Do
Happen To Hear Anything,
Could You Give Us A
Call, Please? Absolutely.
Thank You.
Hey.
Mm. Oh, Oh, Hey, Honey.
Could You Hold Back A Sec?
Nope. Uh, Lunch Rush
I'm Already Late As It Is,
Okay? See Ya.
Excuse Me, Miss.
Oh, Hey There.
I Guess You Didn't See
That Big Blue Sign.
This Is Handicapped Parking.
I Know. Primo Spot, Isn't It?
What? I Have A Thingy.
Yeah, I Noticed That.
You Don't Look Handicapped
To Me.
I'm Not. My Husband Is.
He's Blind.
Well,
Then That Placard's For Him.
Only He Can Park Here.
And How Is He Gonna Park A Car
If He Can't See?
Feeling
Pretty Stupid Now, Aren't Ya?
Lady,
You Got A Lot Of Nerve.
I Had To Park Next
To The Dumpster Way In The Back.
Oh, Don't Play Victim
With Me.
I Have To Walk In Heels
All Day Long.
You Get To Sit In A Chair
And Roll.
You Did Not Just Say That!
You Know, The Quicker
I Can Run My Errands,
The Faster I Can Get Home
To My Husband,
Who Needs Me, Because That's
The Kind Of Person I Am.
W
- What Are You Doing? Calling The Cops. You're Getting A Ticket.
Like Hell I Am! Give Me That. Get Off!
No! You Started It.
Hang It Up! Ow! Get Off!
Hang It Up!
Aah!
Hey, Hey! Oh!
Is There A Problem Here?
Jeez. What, Is There A Telethon
Going On Around Here?
Dude,
She Took One Of Our Spots.
Bitch! I Had To Find
Street Parking.
Hey, There's A Secity Guard Over There.
Go Get Him. No, No, No, No, No. Wait!
Okay, You Know What?
This Is Getting Ridiculous.
Oh, No, No.
You're Not Going Anywhere.
Hey!
Let Me Go!
Hey! Hey! Stop!
What Are You Doing? Don't-
Ow!
Well, It's Official.
I'm Going To Hell.
Hi, Daddy.
Hey.
Hey, Guys, Would You Go Play
In The Back For A While?
I Need To Talk To Your Dad.
Thanks.
Well...
Hey. Don't They
Have Soccer Today?
Let Me Answer That Question
With Another Question.
Why Did You Lie To Police?
-Lynette
- And You Made Me Lie To Them,Too,
Which Brings Up
Another Question.
-Did You Know That Perjury Is,Like,This Whole Big Thing?
-I Think You're Overreacting.
No,Overreacting Would Be If
I Threw A Brick Through You.
What Were You Thinking?
Help Me Understand.
I Just Wento Go Check Out How
The Construction Was Going,
But I Came Around The Corner.
I Saw This Giant Picture
Window That Says "Rick's. "
And Then I Realize I'm Gonna
Have To See That Guy's Name
Every Damn Day Of My Life.
Then I Noticed
This Pile Of Bricks.
Okay.
I Know This Whole
Thing With Rick-
It Really Caused
Us Some Damage.
I Know It Hurt Us,But We
Survived It,And It's Over Now.
Now That's The Thing,Lynette.
It's Not Over.
It Was Never Over.
I Don't Care About
Rick's Stupid Restaurant!
I Don't Even Care That He
Wants To Steal You From Me!
Of Course,He Would Want
To Steal You From Me.
That Makes Sense To Me.
I Care That He Made You
Act Like It Could Be Done.
Oh,Tom.
He Changed The
Way I Look At You.
But...
Nothing Ever
Happened Between Us.
You Have To
Believe Me. Come On!
I Am Notrying To
Get You To Apologize.
I'm Just Explaining The Brick.
Oh,My God.
You Thought I Was
Crazy,But It Wasn't A Dream.
You're Naked!
I Didn't Mean To Do It.
Oh,Really?
You Just Happened To Stumble
Naked Into My Front Yard?
I Didn't Mean It,Mike.
"Mike"? Wait.
Are You Sleepwalking?
Orson.
Hello?
Susan.
Did You Just Hit Me?
Oh,Dear God!
Orson,You're
Staying At My House!
There You Go.
I Have No Explanation.
This Doesn't Happen To Me.
I Don't Sleepwalk.
You Know,It's None
Of My Business,
But Seeing As I Have Seen You
Naked Twice In Theast Week,
I Think I Can Ask,Is
Something Bothering You?
I Don't Think So.
I Mean,Being Out Of Our
House Has Been A Little Weird,
But I'm Very Comfortable Here.
Clearly.
You Know,When You
Were Out On The Lawn,
You Said Something About Mike.
Mike?
What,Uh,What Did I Say?
Well,It Was Just
Sort Of Muttering.
Were You Having
A Dream About Him?
No. I-I Don't Believe So.
Well,Maybe It's Because
You Just Saw Him.
-He Must Be On Your Mind.
-Yeah,Yeah. You Know What,Susan?
I
- I Think It's Time For Us To Move Out.
You Can't. Your House
Isn't Finished Yet.
No,The Downstairs Will
Be Ready Next Week.
-We'll Be Fine.
-Well,If You Insist...
I Think It Will
Be For The Best.
Okay,But In The Meantime,Um,I
Do Have A Teenage Daughter,
So If You Could...
Boxers?
Yes. Thanks.
Hey!
Come On. You've Been
Cooped Up In This House
Since You Got Home
From The Hospital.
-Let's Go Out And Have Some Fun!
-No,I Think I'm Gonna Stay Here.
-I Don't-I Don't Wanna Be A Burden. -Carlos,I
See Handicapped People Out And About All The Time.
In Fact,I Met Two
Feisty Men In Wheelchairs
Yesterday At The Mall. They
Were Living Their Lives...
So It's Time For
You To Live Yours.
Come On. Come On.
I'm Just Dropping
Off A Few Letters.
You Might As Well
Just Wait Here.
Just Picking Up Some Vitamins.
I'll Be Quicker
If I Do It Myself.
I Just Have To Drop Off
A Gift To My Manicurist.
Why Don't You
Listen To The Radio?
Thank You.
Sorry,Babe. That Took
A Little Longer Than I...
Carlos?
Carlos?!
Carlos!
Oh,There You Are.
Thanks,Henry.
-Where The Hell Have You Been?
-I Was Starving,
So I Got That Kid To Take
Me To Go Get A Burger.
I Don't Believe This. I
Was Worried Sick About You!
I'm Sick Of Waiting Here!
You Promised Me A Fun Day,
And All I Got Is A Sunburn
On The Right Side Of My Face.
I'm Sorry. I Told You,I
Had Errands To Run First.
-What's That Smell?
-What Smell?
It Smells Like...
Nail Polish. Did You
Get Your Nails Done?
Is That What
You've Been Doing?
Excuse Me. Miss!
Is That Your Aston Martin
In The Handicapped Space?
What? Gaby,Are You Parked
In A Handicapped Spot?
Move It Along,Pops. We're
Gonna Be Here A While.
Wait,Wait,Wait. Did You
Get A Handicapped Tag?
To Answer Your Earlier
Question,Yes,I Got A Manicure.
I'm Sorry. Are We Good?
Oh,My God!
You're Exploiting My Blindness
So That You Can
Score Better Parking?!
That's A Really
Mean Way To Put It.
You Had Me Out Here,
Sitting Like A Dog With
The Window Cracked Open.
-You Used Me!
-Well,Why Shouldn't I Get Something Out Of This?
-You Know,The Blindness Didn't Just Happen To You.
-You Can't Be Serious.
Oh,You Bet I Am!
Every Morning,The
Toothpaste Has To Be
To The Left Of The
Sink,Because If It's Not,
You Can't Find It,And
I Have To Put It There.
And-And Sometimes- I
Don't Know-I'm Driving,
Or I'm In Line At The Bank
And I Think,"Is The
Toothpaste There?"
So Then I Have To
Run Home And Check
Because I Don't Want
You Reaching For The Tube
And Not Being Able To Find
It. I Just Didn't Think
This Was How It Was
All Gonna Tu Out,Carlos.
I Didn't Think That Every
Day For The Rest Of My Life,
A Part Of Me Is Always Gonna
Think,"Where's The Toothpaste?"
Can't You Just Leave
It In The Drawer?
That's Not The
Point,You Blind Idiot!
I'm Saying
If All I Get In Exchange
For This Crappy Situation
Is A Nice Parking Spot
For My $8 Manicure,
Then I'm Taking It!
Who Put Pear Slices
In The Waldorf Salad?
Guess That Would Be Me.
Katherine,A Waldorf
Salad Is Made With Apples.
It's Tradition.
Yes,A Musty,19th
Century Tradition
In Need Of Some Jazzing Up.
Look,I Just Thought You Have
So Much On Your Mind Already,
What With The Music
And The Decorations.
-The Least I Could Do Was Take Over The Food.
-"Take Over"?
What In God's Name Have You
Done With My French Onion Soup?
Oh,It'll Be Fine.
I Told The Chef
Nothing Is To Leave That
Kitchen Unless I've Tasted It.
-Katherine
-Trust Me.
After All,
I've Gotten Tons Of
Compliments On The Lisianthus.
Here,Honey. Let Me.
Thanks.
You're Welcome.
Just So You Know...
I'm Sorry For What I'm
Putting You Through.
If It Were Anyone But
You,It Wouldn't Be Worth It.
You Ready To Go To The Party?
You Tell Me.
How Do I Look?
You Look Very Handsome.
Thank You.
And You Look More
Beautiful Than Ever.
How Do You Know That?
Just A Hunch.
Bup,Bup,Bup! Don't Eat That.
We Had A
Refrigeration Problem,
And I Don't Want
You Getting Sick.
Oh,Dear. Well,I Should
Throw This Dip Out.
Thanks. It'll Be
About Ten Minutes
Before I Can Make
Up A New Batch.
Do You Mind Tellinyour Boss?
She's Not My Boss!
Bree! The Room
Is Simply Lovely.
You've Outdone Yourself.
Thank You,Mrs. Downing.
Listen,When I Present The
Founder's Award Tonight,
-I Was Wondering
-Oh,Dear. Has No One Spoken To You?
-About What?
-Uh,Well...
The Committee Has Decided
That It Would Be Best
If Katherine Mayfair
Present The Award This Year.
No! That's... That's
My Job. I Always Do It.
Oh,Well,You're
Already Doing So Much,
And,Well,Katherine
Was Quite Insistent.
What's That?
-Oh,It's Dip. The Caterer Just Said That
-I Thought We Agreed.
Nothing Leaves The Kitchen
Without Me Tasting It First.
Dig In.
Is Everyone Having Fun?
You And Kathere
Did An Amazing Job.
Boy,We Didn't Think You
Guys Could Work Together.
Yeah,We Were Sure One Of You
Would End Up Killing The Other.
You Really Should Have
More Faith In People.
Excuse Me.
Katherine,Darling,Are
You Okay?
Not Really.
Oh. I Hope There'sothing
Wrong With The Food.
Is Anybody Else Getting Sick?
Oh,No.
No,Dear. Just You.
Maybe You Should Go Home.
I Can't. I Have To Present
The Founder's Award.
Oh,No One Would Expect You
To Do That In Your Condition.
You Know What?
Um,I Could Do It.
No. I Can Get It Together.
Katherine,No One Expects
You To Be A Martyr.
-Why Don't You Go Home?
-I Can't.
Why Not? I'm Perfectly
Capable Of Presenting.
I've Done It For
The Last Eight Years.
And Let's Face It.
I Mean,No One Wants To
Accept An Award From A Woman
Who Looks Like She Should Be
In Line At The Needle Exchange.
This Is Important
To Me. I'll Be Fine.
And Now For The Presentation
For The Founder's Award-
Ms. Katherine Mayfair.
Thank You,Mrs. Downing.
I Was Honored
When You And The Other
Members Of The Committee
Asked Me To
Present This Award.
-"I Was Honored When You... " Myeah,Myeah,Myeah,Myeah.
-Bree,What's Up?
I Thought Giving Out
This Award Was Your Thing.
Used To Be. Not
Anymore. Things Change.
This Year's Founder's Award...
Ever Since I Started Working
With That Obnoxious Backstabber,
She's Done Nothing But Try To
Take The Spotlight Off Of Me
And Put It Onto Her.
Goes To My Dear
Friend... Bree Hodge.
The Obnoxious Backstabber
Just Called Your Name.
Bree Has Been A Pillar
Of The Fairview Community
For Many Years.
There Is No Better
Friend Than Bree Hodge.
Congratulations.
I Know You Tried To Poison Me.
Well,Uh,
This Has Been An
Evening Full Of,Um...
Surprises. Uh...
I Never Would've
Imagined That,Um,
I Would Be Recognized By
This Wonderful Organization...
Hi,Andrew. Guess What?
-Ur Mom Just Won The Founder's Award.
-Lynette,Listen To Me.
Oh,My God.
-You're Not Gonna Believe What's Going On Down Here.
-What? What? Is Everyone Okay?
Uh,Yeah,Yeah,Yeah.
We're-We're Fine.
It's Rick's Place
- Totally Went Up In Flames.
There,Uh,There Are,Like,Three
Fire Trucks Here.
Oh,My God! That's
Horrible! How Did It Start?
I- They-They
Don't Know.
Okay,I-I'm Gonna-I'll Call
You Back In About Five. Bye.
I Want To Thank You So Much
For Presenting Me
With This Award. I...
I Certainly,Uh,Wasn't
Expecting It.
Um,We Have A Small City
With A Great,Big Heart,
And I Am Honored
To,Uh,Accept This Award
From My Dear Friend...
The Photographer's Asking
If He Can Get Shots
Of The Two Of Us.
Wait.
I Need To Talk To You First.
I Misunderstood The
Situation,That's All.
Can We Just Leave It At That?
No,We Can't.
And Do You Know Why?
Because I Thought
Things Were Going Well.
I Was Having Fun With You.
Obviously...
I Misunderstood.
So Tell Me,
Was There A Straw That
Broke The Camel's Back?
Or Were You Planning
On Killing Me All Along?
Here's The Thing
You Need To Understand
About Me And My Friends.
We Each Have Our Niche.
Gabrielle's The Glamorous One.
Susan's The Adorable
One. Lynette's Smart.
Edie's... Edie.
And I'm The Domestic
One,The Organizer-
The One Who Knows That There Are
Three Tines On A Dessert Fork.
I'm The One Who Gets Teased
For That. That's Who I Am.
And That's Also Who You Are.
So?
So...
I Don't Really Know How
To Be Friends With You.
That's A Shame...
Because I Understand You Better
Than All Those Other Women Do.
I Know How Following The Rules
And Observing
The Little Graces
Makes You Feel Like
You're In Control.
We've Both Had Days
Where It Was Either
Set A Beautiful Table
Or Curl Up In A Ball And Die.
We're The Same,Bree.
And If You Think That
Means We Can't Be Friends,
Then I'm Sorry.
But It Might Also Mean
We Could Be Best Friends.
Who Knew You Were
So Insightful?
Isn't Learning Fun?
Terrific,Everyone. Thank You.
Pictures.
So... Did I Lie? Was It Cool?
You Were Right. It Really Was.
-"Thank You,Julie. "
-Oh.
It's Good To Get Out
Of My Own Head,You Know?
For Months Now,I've Been
Hung Up On Looking For My Dad
And Blaming My Mom...
And It's Gotten Me Nowhere.
I Just Wanna Start
Having Fun Again.
Thank You,Julie.
There You Are.
We Wanted To Get Some
Pictures With You. Mm.
Orson.
Hi. Um... Listen,I
- I Have A 12:00 Curfew,
So If My Mom
Asks,Can You Just-
Mike?
No,It's Julie.
Oh,You're Sleepwalking.
Yeah,I Heard About That.
I'm Sorry,Mike.
Again,Not Mike.
Why Don't I-I Get
You Back To Bed,
And-And
You Can-
I'm Sorry I Ran You Over,Mike.
Blindness-
It's An Affliction
That Prevents People
From Seeing What Is
Right In Front Of Them...
Like The Wives Who
Can't Detect The Jealousy
That Consumes
Their Husbands...
The Women Unable To See
That A Rival Might Also
Be A Friend...
The Men Who Stay Oblivious
To The Guilt That
Lies Deep Within Them.
Yes...
The World Is Filled With
Those Who Cannot See.
The Most Dangerous Are
The Ones Who Stay Blind
To The Evil Within
Their Own Hearts.
How Do We Protect
Ourselves From These People?
First,We Have To Open Our
Own Eyes And Find Them...
Before They Find Us.