Previously on Desperate Housewives...
the accountant's dropping off the
papers for my cayman island account.
This is everything you
need to access the money.
Edie got an opportunity...
But lost it.
mike...
you will go to rehab,or so
help me,I will leave you.
Made a promise.
I'll go.
I keep thinking about
what we covered up.
Katherine's aunt was determined
to reveal the truth...
and victor...
Was a victim of the tornado...
That brought devastation...
oh,my god!
to wisteria lane.
once the tornado had passed,it began.
A man gave his coat to
a stranger in need...
a woman shared her food
with those just passing by...
a teenager reunited a dog
with its worried owner.
These are the things that happen
in the wake of any great disaster.
People start to perform
small acts of kindness.
they do what they can to
help,all the while knowing...
it won't be enough.
why is it taking so long?
They should be going faster.
The fire captain said
they have to go slowly.
They don't want debris suddenly
collapsing into the basement.
Has anyone heard from gaby?
Uh,she went to the hospital with carlos.
He was pretty banged up,but
they say he's gonnbe okay.
Thank god.
Why can't we hear them?
If my kids are alive,they would
be yelling. tom would be yelling.
Okay,lynette,listen to me.
They are all going to be fine.
- I know it.
- Okay.
You really,really,really think so?
Yes,yes,I do. I do.
So I want you to go
over to those paramedics,
and I want you to let
them look at these cuts.
Because you don't want to be all bloody
when they pull your kids out of there,do you?
No. No,I guess not.
- what are you doing?
- What?
You don't know if her
kids are gonna be okay.
I'm just trying to comfort her.
By giving her false hope?
What do you suggest we do?
Well,you should be
saying,"lynette,this could end badly.
So you should start preparing
yourself for that now."
Edie,if you say that to lynette,so
help me god,I will wring your neck.
And I will help her.
Tom and ida and the kids
are buried under that rubble.
I mean,what is it with you people?
Why aren't you willing
to face the facts?
Because we're hoping for a miracle.
A miracle?
Maybe,just maybe,if we
stop flapping our gums,
and we start asking god to take care
of our folks,he might just help us out.
So you think a prayer circle
is going to help lynette?
Once you get to my age,you'll find it a lot easier
to believe that god really does answer prayers.
- So if you can just hang on two more years...
- don'T.
You know,maybe a moment of silence
wouldn't be such a bad idea.
Hey,guys! We got someone!
Mom!
- mom!
- Mom!
oh,my god!
Come on,tom.
straight ahead,sir. Go
ahead.Right over there.
Oh,my god.
Where's ida?
Tom! Where's ida?
Yes,in the wake of a great tragedy,
people do what they can to help...
all the while knowing...
it won't be enough.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:ÈâÈâ ¸â¸â ÏûÏû
Desperate Housewives
Season04 Episode10
The morning after the tornado,
the residents of wisteria lane
began to sort through the devastation
and slowly started picking
up the pieces of their lives.
Bob hunter found part of his
fountain in the middle of the street.
Bree hodge found her lawn
mower next to her coffee table.
And kayla scavo discovered
her music box in a tree...
among... other things.
She had your address in her
pocket,but there wano other I.D.
Did you know her?
Sort of.
Her name is sylvia greene.
Is she local?
I knew her from chicago.
She was... visiting.
Okay,I guess that's all we need.
Would you like me to follow up with
you after we contact the family?
No.
so...
I guess this means it's over.
The fact that she is dead does not
change the fact that you slept with her.
I know it doesn'T.
I made a terrible mistake,and
I am so sorry,katherine.
I'm sure you are.
I want you out of my house tonight.
- You don't mean that.
- Yes,I do.It's over.
Asar as I'm concerned,you could be
lying on that slabright next to her.
3 Days Later
come on,ida. You can
watch us pack from up here.
The things you accumulate
in a lifetime,huh?
Yeah,especially if you
never throw anything out.
so her niece and nephew are taking
all this stuff back to nebraska?
Well,the stuff that'll sell on ebay.
I'm guessing t rest will
end up in a dumpster.
What's all this baseball stuff?
There's a mitt and a jersey.
Was this her husband's?
No,that was ida's from
her pro baseball days.
Yeah,right.
Oh,you're serious?
Ida played in the all-american
girls league during world war ii.
- You didn't know that?
- No.
Oh,she was a superstar.
Arm like a cannon.
People said she could throw
a porkchop past a hungry wolf.
Ida?
I have trouble seeing her as the leadoff
hitter for anything other than osteoporosis.
She made the only unassisted
triple play in league history...
right here in granville field,1944.
That's why she wants her
ashes scattered there.
how did I not know this?
daddy said you were
over here. Can I help?
you realize we're cleaning,right?
We're not eating candy.
That's sweet,parker,but we've got everything
under control here if you want to go play.
No,I want to do something
nice for mrs.Greenberg.
She sort of saved my life.
What do you mean?
When the house started shaking,and
daddy was passed out by his asthma...
mrs.Greenberg made us
all go under the stairs.
- But that's not where they found her.
- Yeah.
There wasn't enough room for her.
She said she'd be okay in the corner.
Uh,parker,you want to help?
Ida has some ice cream in the freezer that
needs eating before it goes bad. Go on.
I know what you're thinking,but don'T.
If you'd been there,it wouldn't
have made a bit of difference.
Susan,we can't thank you enough.
Opening your home to
us-- it's so generous.
It's a horrible feeling to literally
not have a roof over your head,
and that smoky fleabag hotel
just wasn't safe for a newborn.
Please,this is what best friends do...
right before their friendship ends.
Why did you agree to let her stay?
How do you say no to someone in need?
That wasn't rhetorical.
Seriously,you got anything?
I know you feel guilty because
she let us stay with her once,
but don't you remember
how miserable were?
Oh,yeah. Every cup needs a coaster.
Every coaster needs a doily.
Every doily needs daily laundering.
This woman is gonna drive
me out of my frickin'--
hey,roomies.You need help?
no,we've got it under control.
Oh,and,uh,listen. Bob and lee introduced
us to this wonderful contractor,
so we won't be imposing for long.
Imposing. Who's imposing?
You can stay as long as you want.
I'm sorry. The words came out of my
mouth before I knew what I was saying.
Then stop talking,and don't be so nice.
Otherwise,she'll just
take the place over.
hey,susan,orson likes to
sleep with the window open.
Do you mind if we
rearrange the furniture?
Sounds good to me!
hello,gabrielle.
Milton. Hi.
It's a nice turnout.
victor was loved by a lot of people.
It's gonna be a very emotional day.
You seem remarkably composed.
Oh,no,no.I'm
a mess--
- you know,on the inside,where the mascara can't run.
- Ah,I see.
The reading of the will is today.
Is it? I'd forgotten.
- I thought you'd be curious as to how much you'll inherit.
- No.
I'm not thinking aboumoney today.
- I'm burying my husband.
- Of course.
It's just,I,uh...
spoke to the executor of the will,and I have
a ballpark figure of what you'll be getting.
Well,I guess there's nothing
disrespectful about a ballpark figure.
You're not getting a dime.
Victor showed me the photographs
of you and your ex-husband.
You broke his heart. You humiliated him.
So you'll inherit exactly
what you deserve--nothing.
Okay,I made a mista.
I'm sorry,but victor
wasn't entirely blameless.
He ignored me. He used me politically.
Oh,yeah,and he tried to kill carlos.
So I think I'm entitled
to whatever he had.
Ah,there's the thing.
You married a man from a very rich
family-- the operative word being "family."
Everything's in my name... always was.
the service is starting.
I think it's time for you to go.
Go?
You can't kick me out
of my husband's funeral.
I think it's appropriate,given
the circumstances.
Go to hell.
I'll be delivering the eulogy.
If you're stilin this pew
when I reach the pulpit,
I'm going to be telling all of these
people that you are a cheating,lying whore.
See? I told you it was
gonna be an emotional day.
hello,boys.
Bob,lee,I baked you some muffins to thank
you for introducing me to walter here.
And,walter,I decided
you're absolutely right.
Dark shingles are the way to go.
Why are you all staring at me?
- I'm sorry,but I'm not gonna be able to fix your house.
- What?
I've just had some bad
news in my personal life.
Oh,good heavens. I hope no one's died,
which is the only
possible excuse I'd accept.
No,it's not--it's
not that. It's just...
I don't want to get into it.
Walter,I can't find a contractor now.
- Everybody is booked for the next year.
- I'm sorry.
Walter. Walter.
Walter,I'm begging you. Please.
I'm living like a vagabond
in a teenage girl's bedroom.
I'm sleeping under a
poster of orlando bloom.
You can't leave me.
Yeah,well,sometimes people do that.
They just leave.
This is a nightmare.
What is going on?
Walter went rough a bad breakup,
and today he found out that his
ex moved in with someone else.
Oh,for god sakes. Tell him to put on
his big boy pants and find another girl.
Who says it's a girl?
Walter's gay?
Yes.
He can build home and decorate them.
Sometimes god gives with both hands.
Well,then you just have
to fix him up with someone,
give him back his will to work.
yeah,about that-- uh,most
of our friends are 9s,
and walter--we love
him-- but kind of a 3.
And in the gay world,3
does not go into 9.
Well,we'll just have to find him
someone who's not good at gay math.
Well,I drove all the way out there,
and I waited for hours and then
they wouldn't let me see him.
Uh,no. They just said that
I should--I should call you.
listen,I know it's a 30-day rehab.
I'm not trying to break him out.
I'm just trying to see him.
You know what? Could you
just call me when you know?
Thank you.
welcome to heaven.
Don't talk. I'm smelling.
What is that?
Duck a l'orange.
Bree says it's making a comeback.
And our oven is making its debut.
Oh,it gets better.
She did our laundry,too.
Smell my sock.
Oh,my god! I want to eat that.
she dusts. She irons.
Oh,and she does this magic trick.
No matter where you throw your
sweater,within seconds,it's on a hanger.
This has just replaced your
birth as the best day of my life.
Oh,hi,susan. I hope you
don't mind that I made dinner.
I hope you don't mind
that I'm going to kiss you.
You're funny.
Now I need you to be
honest about this recipe.
It's a dry run for a small dinner
party I'm having tomorrow night.
Again,if you don't mind.
Not at all.
In--in fact,if you wanna do a dry run
for sunday brunch,I'm there for you.
Dinner will beeady shortly.
Oh,and,julie,I fixed the hem
on that blue skirt of yours.
It's on your bed.
My hem is fixed?
She's like the mother I never had.
Oh,oh,no offense.
Oh,none taken.
hey.
How you feeling?
Uh,not so great.
Well,they should give you
something for the pain.
They gave me this button that I can
press,but I'm trying not to use it,
'cause the drugs make me
feel a little to mellow.
was the funeral sad?
Tragic.
I found out everything victor
had is in milton's name,
and he told his father about
us,so I'm not getting a penny.
it's a good thing you hooked
up with another rich guy.
yeah...
gaby,you sound weird.
Why do you sound so weird?
Gaby.
Um,remember that day,uh...
when al was going to drop
off the account information?
Oh,my god. He didn't?
No,no,no. He did.
It's just...
remember how windy it was that day?
No,no,no. That was the only copy.
I know,but edie was trying
to steal the papers from me,
and we got into this fight,and then
the tornado just took them away.
They're gone?
Kinda.
what is that sound?
I'm texting someone.
Gaby,that account was our future.
What are we gonna do now?
Carlos,just calm down,okay?
I'm sure al has an access code or a copy or some
super nerd way to get back into the account,okay?
I know we can fix this.
Yeah.
yeah,he could fix it.
Okay.
All right,you look very
tired,so I'm just gonna go.
But I'm warning you,gaby,if
we don't find those papers,
so help me,I'M...
Hi. Um,I'm a friend of al's,and I
was wondering if I could see him.
Of course. Please come in.
Right this way.
dear al, rest in peace
oh,al.
thanks again for your help.
Well,we'd do anything for your aunt.
I hope you know what an
amazing woman she was.
Hey,did you guys happen
to find a pearl necklace?
It's the only valuable
thing aunt ida owned.
Well,actually,I have it.
Yeah,she promised it to me if
she kicked the bucket first.
Oh,really?
In--in writing?
I'll be right back.
all right,let's hit the road.
At about the rest of these boxes?
Oh,that's junk. You
can just give 'em away.
Hey,listen. Is there a good place
we can grab a bite on the way out?
Um,well,there's a great diner
right near granville field.
Isn't that-- isn't that
outt that out of the way?
Yeah,you stopping there anyway
to spread your aunt's ashes?
We're kinda pressed for time.
Yeah,we thought we'd just put her
in the family plot back in omaha.
You can't do that.
Ida wanted her ashes
scattered at the field.
Yeah,I know,but that's
kinda crazy,don't you think?
It doesn't matter.
She was an amazing woman.
You should respect her wishes.
We should get going.
Hey,I-if you don't have
time to do it,I will.
Uh,you know,you're not family,so I
think that would be inappropriate.
Look,you're taking her pearls.
The least you can do
is honor her wishes.
Okay,at the risk of being bitchy,
this is none of your business,
so could you please just drop it?
Fine.
And for what it's worth,you
passed bitchy ten minutes ago.
Carter,get the urn. I
wanna get outta here.
Wait!
You'll never find it
I'll get it for you.
By the way,I'm staying at
ida's house for a while since,
you know,my house is a pile of rubble.
Oh,that's so sad.
You've got a week.
Here you go.
Thanks.
just put it in the cup holR.
Excuse me.
Are you al's wife?
I'm gabrielle lang.
You're the mayor's wife.
Of course I recognize you.
So I was shocked to hear about al.
I can't remember the last
time I was so devastated.
Didn't you just bury
your husband yesterday?
That sucked,too.
So what happened to al?
he was driving home,trying
to beat the storm,
and he ran into a downed power line...
and his car burst into flames.
Oh,sweetie,don'T.
I want you to remember al
like I do-- at his desk,
with a big smile on his
face,surrounded by all his files.
by the way,where are those files?
I cleared out his office.
Oh,I bet that was hard.
so where'd you put 'em?
In the garage.
Which is...
in the back.
well,look at me,monopolizing the widow.
You go mingle.
I'm gonna get you a cracker.
oh,crap.
Why do people have to die?!
Why,god?! Why?
Why? Why? Why? Why?
Oh,ank you so much for letting
us take over your dining room.
Please. Thank you for making us dinner.
Oh,you will be sending up dessert later?
Oh,sure. Just,uh,leave your trays
in the hall when you're ready.
- Puff pastry?
- Thank you.
Oh,here is a nice 12-year-old
scotch to wash that down with.
Uh,look,it's nice of you
to invite me for dinner,
but if you're hoping to change
my mind about doing your roof,
I'm just-- I'm
really not up to it.
No. No,no,walter,
we--we just heard
about your situation
and thought you could use a
little company. That's all.
Yes,and a nice home-cooked meal.
Trust me,there are absolutely
no tricks up our sleeve.
Uh,I noticed there are
four place settings.
Is somebody joining us?
All right,I'm here.
What was so important?
What's going on?
I'm moving out.
It's been a little weird staying
in the guest room of my own house.
But I thought you and mom
were trying to work stuff out.
We are. It's just...
your mom thought it might be easier
if we gave ourselves a little distance.
Well,then why doesn't she move out?
- Dylan.
- I'm serious.
You can't leave me here
alone with her. I'll go crazy.
Hey,come onwe're gonna see
each other all the time.
Why does she always have to win?
Yeah,I'm thinking of
starting my trip in paris.
Todd and I talked about going there,
but now I'm thinking of doing it myself.
Walter recently split up
with his life partner todd.
They were gay.
Small world,huh?
How is it small,exactly?
Andrew is also an
out-and-proud homosexual.
He's here,he's queer,and
we're used to it.
Since when?
You know what else
you two have in common?
A love of boots.
Andrew has some beautiful boots.
Oh,I can only imagine the fun you
two would have in the boot shop.
Um,mom,I'm gonna take
these bowls to the kitchen.
Oh,thanks,dear.
With you.
What are you doing?
I'm just trying to stay out of the way
of all those sparks that are flying.
Sparks?
The man's twice my age.
Yes,but he's also-- he's
got a great sense of...
okay,do you know how hard it
is to get a good contractor?
Oh,my god!
And poor walter just
had his heart broken,
so if it takes you being nice to
him to get our house fixed,then...
you're--you're pimping
me out for a new roof?
And windows.
And I am not pimping you out.
I'm simply asking you to show some kindness to a
lonely man who happens to be an excellent roofer.
- Look,if by kindness you mean sex
- watch your mouth.
I would never suggest that.
You can raise a man's hopes
without satisfying them.
I've done it all my life.
andrew,I haveot to get back into
my house,and you're my only hope.
fine.
For you,I will flirt,I will
flatter,and I will charm.
bless you.
And in exchange,I expect
a 60-inch flat screen tv.
Fine,and if you can get him to
come in on time and under budget,
I'll throw in surround sound.
No.
That walter guy needs to stay miserable,
because if he's not,he'll fix
her roof,and then she'll leave us.
Mom,we always knew is
couldn't last forever,
and she'll still be
here another week or two.
That is not enough time.
She just started stenciling the kitchen,
and i didn't want to tell you this,but
there is talk of an herb garden.
I've gotta stop her.
How?
I don't know,
but I've had a taste of ironed
pillowcases,and I am not going back.
oh,walter,you got a little right there.
Thank you.
Hey,everybody.
I'm sorry to interrupt,but the smell of
that apple pie just made my mouth water.
Well,say no more.One
slice coming right up.
Oh,susan delfino,this
is walter bierlich.
this is susan's house.
She's kind enough to take us in.
Hi.How are you?
All righty.Here you go.
Thanks.
oh.You're going to eat that...here?
Oh,I'm just gonna visit for a whE.
So,andrew,we miss you around here,
but I bet you love
having your own place.
Uh,yeah.It's--it's
cool.
Of--of course,it
does get lonely.
It'd be nice to have someone
stop by once in a while.
Oh,well,you'll reel somebody in.
You always do.
you should have seen his
last boyfriend--justin.
He was so hot.
You really had a thing for
the young,ripped musclboys,huh?
Um...
he did at one time,but
andrew's outgrown that.
He realized the folly
of being so shallow.
Exactly,and now,um,his tastes
have gone to the more mature,
cultured types,like,uh,walter here.
Oh!
This is a fix-up?
Well,I just--it never would
have occurred to me,you know,
because of the vast age difference.
But,hell.Why not?
Life is short.
Certainly shorter for walter.
Susan.
Oh,no,don't get me wrong.
I mean,I think it's great.
You should grab love
wherever you can find it.
Who cares if your friends
think that you're paying for it?
Oh,so why don't you take this
piece of pie upstairs to julie?
No,she's right.That's exactly
what my friends would think.
Well,then you need new friends.
Hey,listen.You know what?
You seem like a nice guy,
and it would be great to
parade you in front of my ex,
but,uh,then I'd be using you.
Well,he doesn't mind.
No,parade me.
he's got a mesh tank top that
would bring your ex to tears.
Yeah,well,you know,as
tempting as that sounds,
you know,I'm just not
ready to date,so...
thank you so much for the dinner.
walter,wait!
well,I guess I'll just
bring this pie up to julie.
You.
Sit.
so is someone meeting us here or what?
Well,here's the thing.I called
the general manager to ask
if we could scatter the ashes
here,and he said absolutely not.
So how are we getting in?
Oh,lynette.
Hey,you've abetted.
Might as well aid.
Leave us.
Okay,I know that it sounds selfish,but I
did what I did because I want you to stay.
why?
I-I thought you'd want your house back.
Well,yeah,sure,someday,
but right now I just love
having you take care of me.
All the cooking and the
cleaning and the alphabetizing...
it's helping me feel like I'm
not just about to fall apart.
Oh,sweetie,you're okay.
No.
I'm pregnant,
and my husband's in rehab,
and the only reason I seem
sane is because you're here,
making my house feel like a home.
This is a conversation that could benefit
from some homemade chocolate chip cookies.
Can I have milk,too?
I'll be right back.
do you maybe want to
say something first?
Oh,uh,yeah,I guess so.
Oh.
um...
"do not stand at my grave and weep."
Um,"I'm--I'm
not there.
I do not sleep.
"I am a thousand winds that blow.I am...
the diamond glints of snow."
"I am the sunlight on ripened grain.
I am the gentle autumn's rain."
"Do not stand at my grave and cry.
I am not there.
I did not die."
That was lovely.
Let's dump her.
And try not to stand downwind.
She played third be,right?
- Right.
- Right,right,right.
Oh,my goodness.
Wait.Uh,sorry.
Shortstop.
Oh,yeah.
Okay.
No,it was third.
Damn it,karen.
I'm running out of ida.
okay,don't move!
Stay right where you are
and show me your hands.
okay,split up,and I'll
meet you back at the car.
Go!
Hey,hey!
Right there!
Oh!
Lady,get back here!
Come on.Come on.
Uhh!Come on!
- Run,jane doe,run!
- Just grab her!
- Hey,stop,hey!
- I got her.
Come on.
so when I finally came clean,
his wife told me she shredded anything
that had to do with offshore accounts.
She was protecting al.
so we're broke.
I'm so sorry,honey.
I-I know this is bad,but
we have each other.
We'll get married again,and
everything will be fine.
For richer,for poorer,right?
In sickness and in health.
The whole nine yards.
I'm gonna go down to the cafeteria anget us
a couple of ginger ales to toast our future.
Hey,doctor.
He's looking better
and better every day.
Keep up the good work.
You haven't told her yet,have you?
I'm working on it.
Carlos,I know you're
scared,but give her some credit.
She's not gonna leave you
because you lost your sight.
You don't know gaby.
thank god those cops let
us off with a warning.
I was this close to my third strike.
I'm just glad we gave
ida what she wanted.
It's a beautiful thing you did.
then why don't i feel better?
I don't know.
Why don't you?
Because it wasn't enough,not
compared to what she did for me.
She saved my kids.
She's this amazing woman,and I
never bothered to get to know her,
so,yeah,I sprinkled her ashes,
but it would have been nice to
do something before she was ashes.
That's a lesson we all
gotta learn over and over--
appreciate people
while we still got 'em.
Yep.
Third strike?
What were the first two?
it's a long story.
That requires a pitcher
of beer and a dark bar.
I got time for that.
What are you still doing here?
I thought you found a motel room.
I did,but I wanted to set
something straight before I go.
I'm not leaving because you want me to.
I'm leaving because
I'm walking out on you.
Oh,is that how we're gonna play this?
Fine.Whatever.
You're leaving me.
Oh,yeah,and here's why.
You blamed what happened
on your ex-husband,
and I believed you.
You told me it was all his fault,
and now I find out it was yours.
We're about even in the
betrayal department now.
In fact...
I think you win.
it had been seven days since a
tornado devastated wisteria lane,
and the residents continued to
pick up the pieces of their lives.
Some salvaged precious friendships.
Some uncovered colorful histories.
Others found challenges
they hadn't expected.
And then...
there was one girl...
who stumbled upon the truth
she'd long been searching for...
only...
to wish she hadn'T.
Desperate
Housewives Season 4 Episode 10
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Sync: YTET - ÈâÈâ ¸â¸â ÏûÏû