Previously on Desperate Housewives...
Orson's wife Alma
disappeared...
Gaby found
a new calling...
Yes, I'm unbelievable.
Close your mouths.
Someone new
moved in...
He's a bachelor who
lives with his invalid sister.
But Lynette found
a dark secret...
Our neighbor
is a pedophile.
You can't sit
on this, Lynette.
Orson's mother
revealed his past...
He cheated on Alma,
broke her heart.
-For his precious Monique.
-Monique Polier?
And the police couldn't
find the evidence...
-We couldn't find a toolbox.
-The man's a plumber.
Until Mike
tried to hide it.
I'll take those.
The annual block party was a
winter tradition on Wisteria Lane.
It was a way for the residents
to spread holiday cheer.
Everyone was invited...
Including Art Shepard,
The newest resident
of Wisteria Lane.
But as the big
night drew near,
more than holiday cheer
was being spread around.
Hey, did you hear about the
new guy that just moved in?
Well, get a load of this...
Apparently, the perv's got all
this weird stuff In his basement.
No, seriously.
It's like this big kiddie
trap full of toys.
By Sunday evening,
most of the gossiping
had subsided,
and the neighborhood
was once again
consumed by the
spirit of the season.
Friends laughed
over eggnog,
lovers kissed
under mistletoe,
and the mood
was jolly.
That is, until
a certain guest
made his appearance.
Look who's here!
Merry Christmas,
everybody!
Merry Christmas!
Now, kids, who's been
good this year?
Joey, get back here.
What's going on?
I'm not sure.
Let's go, girls.
Art, maybe we should go.
Yes, for the residents
of Wisteria Lane,
it was the most wonderful
time of the year.
But for Arthur Shepard
and his sister,
it had turned t to be
a very silent night.
By Tyno, Wisteria Team
Forom.com & DHsubs.free.fr
Transcript by FRM
For the residents
of Wisteria Lane,
the holiday season
could only begin,
once the decorations
came out.
For some, that meant
pulling out the colored lights.
For others, it meant
locating that holiday wreath.
And then there were those eager
to display their nativity scene.
But for a romantic few,
it was all about
the mistletoe.
You have to kiss me.
It's the law.
While you're in a good mood,
I thought I'd spring something on you.
-My parents are coming to town.
-Your parents? Really?
And I wondered if you might be free
to join us for dinner Saturday.
Absolutely.
So I assume this means
they know about me?
But of course.
And they know
about me as in...
"Mum, Dad, bloody good news.
I've got melf a smashing new girlfriend."
That's adorable.
Please don't do it
in front of them.
Right.
So, um...
Do you want me to make reservations
at that little french place?
We could do that,
but it's a 4-hour layover and
they're going to be exhausted,
and I thought we might have
a more enjoyable time
if they came here and
you made dinner for them.
Okay, I guess it's time
we have the conversation.
Ian...
Haven't you ever wondered
why I've never cooked for you?
I just assumed
that you were lazy.
I wish.
My cooking...
is not good.
Well, my parents won't be
expecting a gourmet meal.
Will they be expecting
stomach cramps,
acid reflux,
night sweats?
Come on,
you can't be that bad.
It is really important that I make
them a home-cooked meal?
Well, it's just that they're very
old-fashioned hearth-and-home types,
and they might wonder why
you didn't make the effort.
But it's okay.
You'll win them over...
Eventually.
Okay, I'll give it a shot.
Thank you.
Now nothing elaborate.
Just a simple roast and, uh,
and something
appropriate to go with it.
Right...
Like an ambulance.
No, Amy, small
steps. Small!
Little Miss Snowflake glides.
She doesn't stomp.
Is  that better?
Getting there, sweetie.
If  she was a horse,
we'd have to shoot her.
Poor thing,
she tries so hard.
Yeah, she's a trooper.
Let's dump her.
What?! Why?
Pageant consultants are judged
on the strength of their roster.
You know, we can't afford to bounce
every nose-picking no-talent,
but we can definitely lose the one who's
dragging us down, and that's Amy.
We can't do that!
Her mother died last year.
Yes, I know, I know, and it's tragic,
but we are running a business.
Amy is sucking up all of our time,
and we should be focusing on Sherri.
She actually has
a shot at winning.
How will I tell her family?
We'll do it together.
We'll be very diplomatic.
Are you sure about this?
The poor kid's been
through the wringer and...
Amy!
For God sakes,
Little Miss Snowflake
does not scratch down there!
Well, then again,
her mother died a year ago.
How long is she
gonna milk it?
Mother Hodge,
I have your breakfast.
Just put it over there.
I'll pick through it later.
Merry Christmas!
Oh, wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What are you watching?
Home movies.
It's fun looking back
at the past, isn't it?
Well, it's one way to kill time
while you're waiting for death.
We also have cable.
Have you decided what
you're gonna do about Orson?
-Decided?
-Yes.
Have you called
a lawyer yet?
I don't think that's
any of your concern.
I don't mean
to pry, but,
I think you're a good
Christian woman,
and you deserve
better than my son.
Well, I will take that
under advisement.
If you give him a chance,
he'll draw you back in.
It's what he does.
Just walk away.
It's not that easy.
I love him.
You'll get over it.
I did.
Merry Christmas!
Oh, wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Okay.
Well, believe me,
Rita, he scares me, too.
You know what?
We should have a meeting,
get all the Moms together
and figure out what
to do about this guy.
Yeah, Saturday, your
house. Sounds good.
Hey, Rita, I gotta go.
Sorry, I can't talk now.
I have somewhere to go.
Well, my brother doesn't.
The youth center just fired him.
Are you happy?
I'm not sad. He shouldn't be
around kids. I saw those pictures.
Those boys were
on his swim team.
He was proud of them.
Turning that into something dirty
says more about you than him.
You can defend
him all you want.
I know what I know.
Did you know my
brother got spit on
at the hardware
store yesterday?
That they refused to
serve us at the diner,
that our tire got slashed
at the church parking lot?
I am not a well woman.
I don't need this stress.
Well...
I am sorry
that happened.
Have you considered even for a
Moment that you could be wrong,
that you misinterpreted
what you saw,
That you are ruining my
brother's life and mine
over nothing?
I have kids, okay?
Better safe than sorry.
So as long you're safe what
do you care who's sorry?
So I'm cooking dinner for
Ian's parents tomorrow night,
and it's the first time I'm meeting them,
so I sort of wanna impress them.
And yet you're cooking?!
Well, that's the thing.
Uh, so I was hoping, you know,
if you're not too busy...
Oh, no, no, these things
practically build themselves.
Thank you.
You are a lifesaver.
Actually...
I could probably use
the distraction.
I asked Orson to
move out last night.
Oh, come on! Why would you
bury your toolbox in the woods?
I knew the cops were
looking for it, and I panicked.
I was just trying to
buy myself me time.
Well, you may have
bought yourself 20 to life!
-Let the guy enjoy his breakfast.
-Stay out of this, Carlos.
Mike,  I want you
to look at me.
Yeah, you look me in the
eye and you swear to me
that you didn't
kill anybody.
How many times do I have
to tell you? I can't remember.
You can't remember,
or you don't wanna remember?
Um, guys.
Bree,  you have got to go
to the police with all of this.
I can't. Not yet. I need
some time to think.
His wife goes missing,
then his mistress turns up dead.
What is there
to think about?
I know it sounds suspicious,
but in my heart of hearts,
I just can't believe that
Orson could do such a thing.
Sweetie,
we all wanna believe
the best of the people
we care about,
But you cannot let your feelings for
a man blind you to cold hard facts.
What in the world?
Oh, my God!
What's going on?
They just arrested
Mike for murder.
What?!
They're saying he killed
that woman othe news,
That Monique person.
Oh, thank God!
I can't believe we're gonna
break that little girl's heart.
Do not wimp out
on me here.
We gotta do what's
best for the business.
-What if the father yells at me?
-Then I will jump in and defend you.
Okay, but if you do,
try and be diplomatic.
I'm always diplomatic.
Now just get in there,
you spineless 'mo.
Excuse me, Mr. Pearce?
I'm so glad you
could come today.
This is my partner Gabrielle.
Pleasure to meet you.
Shall we?
So, uh, what did you
wanna talk to me about?
Is there a problem
with Amy?
Not a problem, per se.
We're just a little concerned
that she might not have the, um...
temperament for
pageant competitions.
And what does that mean?
Well, when it comes
to performing,
she's not exactly...
Well, she tends to be...
Feel free to jump in.
I have no idea where
you're going with this.
Well, as Gaby
and I discussed,
Amy has certain limitations and
her odds of winning are slim.
Vern!
He is so competitive.
I constantly have to remind
him they're just kids.
-When did you lose the joy?
-Oh, I think you know.
Wait, I'm confused.
Are you dumping Amy?
Of course not, Bill.
Can I call you Bill?
It's just we feel that Amy would
benefit from some private coaching.
Maybe I could come to your
house? Say, Friday, 5:00?
Sure. Yeah, I guess.
Great! It's a date.
Maybe I should come, too.
After the harsh things
you said about Amy?
I don't think so.
I'm gonna need
a good lawyer.
And that may take
a little research.
And whoever takes my
case will need a retainer,
so if you don't mind,
I promise I'll pay you back.
Oh, okay.
And make sure he knows
about my wrench.
Apparently, they tested it and
found traces of this Monique's blood.
What's wrong?
I don't know if you picked
up on this, Mike, but...
I haven't been happy.
No, I didn't
pick up on it.
Well, I wanted to tell
you this weeks ago,
and I wish that I had,
because now
I know you're gonna think
that I'm breaking up with you
over  this whole blood
on the ax thing.
Wrench.
Whatever. But believe
me, that's not it.
It's just...
We are moving too fast.
What are you
trying to say?
Well, maybe we should
just... take a break.
You know...
date other people.
You're telling me this on the
day I'm put in a men's prison?
Well, I said the
timing was bad.
I am sorry. I...
I really am.
I just can't do this.
They told me somebody was coming,
but I did not expect it to be you.
Is Edie getting you
a good lawyer?
I doubt it.
She dumped me today.
What? Why?
Well, I was
arrested for murder.
Still...
It's tacky.
Well, okay then, uh...
I'll help get you out.
What's your bail?
A million dollars.
You don't have
to help me, Susan.
I want to.
Aren't you gonna ask?
What?
If I killed that woman?
I don't have to.
I know you didn't.
I wish I was that sure.
I have these flashes,
where I see her face,
so I must've known her.
And if I did, maybe
something happened.
maybe I got
angry, maybe...
There's an explanation for this,
and we're gonna figure it out.
Don't worry about a thing.
Miss Gabrielle!
When are you gonna
come outside and watch me?
Oh, um, the grass, honey,
and my allergies...
Go ahead and practice.
I'll watch you from here.
Are you sure I can't
help with anything?
I've been a single
Dad for a while now.
I got the dinner
thing down.
I've got the restaurant
I can't bring myself
to cook for one.
Not that I ever
cooked for two.
Well, no restaurant tonight.
You are having dinner with us.
That's sweet.
It's the least I can do to
thank you for helping Amy.
Oh. It's nothing.
Yeah, she's
a special girl.
So...
How is it for you,
being single again?
Oh, honestly?
I  hate it. It's like I've
forgotten how to date.
Me, too. You know,
I even let a friend of mine talk me
into one of those speed dating things.
How was it?
I didn't even go in.
I just sat in this
hotel lobby.
I watched all these lonely,
desperate single people filing in,
and then it hit me,
I'm one of them.
I know what
you mean.
Did you see that?
It spun three times
and then I caught it.
You didn't see.
Yeah, I'm sorry, sweetie.
I was distracting Gabrielle.
Oh, no, no,
it's totally my fault.
I'm sorry, sweetie.
Go outside and do it again.
I promise this time
we're gonna watch.
Come in.
Hey.
Wow, oh,
those are gorgeous.
Well, I figured you'd be too busy
cooking to manage a centerpiece.
Well, you, uh, you may not be a good
cook but you're certainly a tidy one.
Don't worry. Dinner's all
taken care of. We're having...
Blanquette de veau and
a grand marnier soufflé.
Well, that's very
ambitious of you,
and, uh, when will Bree
be done making it?
5:30.
But I am rewarming
it all by myself.
Oh, what's, uh,
what's all this?
Mike was arrested
for murder.
My God.
I mean, of course
he's totally innocent.
I'm just trying to help
him find a lawyer.
Shouldn't, um, shouldn't
his girlfriend be doing that?
Yeah. Edie dumped him.
Okay, I know how
this looks but
I just feel bad.
He's just a friend now.
Yes. Yes, a friend
you sat by for six months,
hoping he'd wake up
and ravish you again.
You are the only one allowed
to ravish me these days,
So stop worrying.
Orson, it's me again.
Please call.
We need to talk.
I'll do the chips.
You deal.
You got it.
Guys, why has it been so long
since we've played poker?
-I really need this.
-Oh, me, too.
There's nothing more relaxing than an
afternoon of finger food and girl talk.
-Hi, ladies!
-Hey! How you doing?
So did you tell the police that
you think Orson killed Monique?
What?!
No, I did not,
and I don't plan to.
But Mike is in jail,
and you said yourself
you thought Orson did it.
I said I had concerns,
Concerns that have disappeared
now that Mike has been arrested.
What are you saying?
You think Mike is guilty?
Hey, why don't we
start that girl talk?
I'll get the ball rolling.
Anybody have a yeast infection?
They found Monique's blood on the wrench
that Mike was trying to dispose of.
I mean, that hardly
screams innocence.
Her teeth were pulled.
You don't think that's worth telling the cops
she was messing around with a dentist?
Orson was slipping it
to the dead chick?
Mike is innocent.
I know that in my heart.
We all have
convictions, Susan.
I believe Mike's last one
was for manslaughter.
Okay, okay, we've all made
some excellent points
and blown off
a little steam.
Whoo! Let's play
some cards.
If you're so sure that
Orson is innocent,
why don't we go through his
things? Where's his desk?
At his office.
And what did you think
you'd find there anyway?
I don't know.
A blackmail letter,
a necklace made of teeth?
We're not gonna
play cards, are we?
Nope.
Well, I am certainly not
playing with a woman
that is willing to let Mike take
the fall for her psycho husband.
Well, needless to say, I won't be
cooking dinner for Ian's parents.
Fine. I'll cook myself.
Good.
Let me know if there
are any survivors.
And if you take Orson back,
you do the same.
Well, that was
incredibly awkward.
I'm sorry you both
had to sit through it.
Was it me?
Was I out of line?
Oh, I'm not
taking sides.
This will blow over.
You're right...
Hey, come on in.
You're just in time.
Thanks so much, Rita.
I think it's such a good idea that
we all get together and talk and...
Wow.
Wow. What is all this?
We decided to stage a
protest in front of Art's house.
A protest?
Mm-Hmm.
Rita, I want the word
"pedophile" to really stand out.
Do we have any glitter?
Say "molester."
It sounds scarier.
I'm sorry. I thought we were all gonna talk
about how to keep an eye on this guy.
We're past talking.
The guy's a menace.
Well, that's what we think,
but we don't exactly have proof.
The youth center just fired him.
How much proof to you need?
But, see, the only reason they fired him
is because people were gossiping,
and the only reason they're gossipg is
because of what I told Mrs. McCluskey.
Yeah, and you told me
to spread the word.
So that people could watch
their kids and be vigilant.
So you wanna wait until he
actually molests one of our kids?
-Whose side are you on, Lynette?
-Knock it off, gert.
Remember,
if it weren't for Lynette,
We never would've found
out about this creep.
She's our hero.
...The 22-Yard line,
the give is to Harrison,
who is hit immediately
and dropped for a loss
in his own backfield...
Bye-bye, Daddy.
See you, sweetie.
Have fun.
So I was, uh,
I was thinking you...
You wanna grab a cup of coffee
or something after class?
I'd love to grab
a cup of coffee...
or something.
Amy, you are so lucky
to have such a nice Dad.
Yeah, I know.
Leave him alone.
Excuse me?
You heard me.
I don't want
you dating him.
Oh, sweetheart.
I have a feeling
I know what this is about.
No you don't.
I think I do.
You miss your Mommy,
and it feels funny seeing your
Daddy be nice to somebody else.
But believe me, I'm not trying
to replace your Mom.
Well, I am,
And I have someone
all picked out.
What?
I want my Dad to
marry Sherri's Mom.
Sherri from class?
We're best friends, and
we have it all planned out.
Our parents are
gonna get married,
and then we'll
be real sisters.
What about your Dad?
Don't you care what he wants?
My Mom died.
All my Dad wants
is for me to be happy.
Now get in there and teach
me how to work the runway.
That's what we're
paying you for, right?
...Runs it left,
swings it around.
He fights his way to the
25 for another first down,
and that should
just about do it.
I tell you, with 1:12 left on the clock
and no time-outs remaining...
Orson?
Bree?
Orson.
Why haven't you
returned any of my calls?
I was afraid you were calling
to ask me for a divorce.
No, I wasn't.
They arrested Mike for the
murder of Monique Polier.
They did?
The other night, you wanted
a chance to explain everything.
Well, here it is,
and I want it all.
If I find out you've left anything out,
then I will ask for that divorce.
Okay.
You're working so hard, Sherri.
You must really wanna win this pageant.
More than anything.
Well, I think dedication
should be rewarded,
so I have a little
surprise for you.
What is it?
Well, you know how the pageant
starts with a big opening number?
This year, all the contestants
are gonna dance in pairs,
and I've arranged for you to
dance with your best friend Amy!
What's wrong, sweetie?
Well...
Amy sucks.
Well, I thought you two
were practically sisters?
We are...
but she still sucks.
And first impressions
are everything.
You said so yourself.
-Well, that's true...
-And this is the opening number.
If the judges see me tripping all over
that klutz, there's no way I'm gonna win.
That's a good point.
Now I wish I hadn't told Amy.
You already told her?!
She was so excited.
Well, she's
your best friend.
Why don't you just tell her
the truth? She'll understand.
What if she doesn't?
Well, friends come and go...
but a crown is forever.
I never loved Alma.
My mother pushed
us together, and,
I was stupid enough
to get her pregnant.
You had a child?
Alma miscarried a month
after the wedding.
I was trapped.
Well, you could've left her.
Mother wouldn't hear of it.
Divorce is a sin.
So I stayed in
the marriage,
hoping I would come to feel
what I was supposed to,
but I never did.
So I resigned myself
to a life without love.
And then I met Monique.
It was wrong.
I didn't care.
I loved her more than
I'd loved anyone...
Till you.
So why couldn't
you tell me this?
Because you told
me about Rex.
How he cheated on you,
how hurt you were.
Bree, I needed you
to feel safe with me.
Well, you haven't
done a very good job.
Handling the truth would have
been a hundred times easier
than dealing with all
the doubt and suspicion.
So you stayed in a loveless
marriage because of your mother?
I know how it sounds.
But after my
father died,
she was all I had.
His death caused
me so much pain...
I would've done
anything for her.
She saw that weakness,
and she ran with it.
You've got no idea how
manipulative she can be.
She ruins lives.
Now I've told you
everything.
What happens now?
Well...
First you pack up your
things and come home,
and then...
we toss your mother
out on her evil ass.
God, I love you.
Hi! I'm so
sorry I'm late.
-Where are your folks?
-They're not coming.
Their plane was
snowed in at O'Hare.
Well, that's too bad.
Well, no harm done then, huh?
You're 40 minutes late.
But they're not here.
You didn't know that.
And where's dinner?
Bree and I sort
of had a fight.
Look, I'm awfully sorry that
I'm late. I had an emergency.
Did this emergency have
anything to do with Mike?
I'm pretty sure that Bree's husband murdered
the woman the cops think Mike killed.
I went to his office...
Oh, for God sakes, Susan.
No, I found
evidence. Look.
Orson was committed to a
mental institution for over a year.
I mean, doesn't that suggest
- he's some sort of...
- I don't care!
Tonight meant a great deal
to me, and you blew it off.
I said I was sorry, Ian.
I have to help Mike.
I'm all he's got.
Actually, you're wrong.
He's got me.
What?
Tomorrow, I'll hire the best
lawyer in town to defend him,
and I'll pay every
cent of his bill.
You would do that for Mike?
Yes, on one condition...
You can't see
him anymore.
Why?
If you start visiting him,
being a friend to him,
he'll fall in love
with you again.
Then you'll have to decide whose
heart to break, his or mine.
As jealous ultimatums go,
that's very flattering, but,
I don't think
that's necessary.
Mike and I are done.
Then you should have no problem
accepting my generous offer.
You would really get him
the best lawyer in town?
An absolute piranha.
Do we have a deal?
Well, okay then.
You know, Mike barely
remembers me.
What makes you so sure he would
fall in love with me again?
What a perfectly
asinine question.
How could he not?
God, I was only
in the house 15 minutes.
Are there more
of them now?
Yep.
Go ahead, say it.
I know you want to.
This is all your fault.
You should've listened to me.
I know.
But be fair. There is no way
I could've anticipated this.
You tell people
Frankenstein's on the loose,
then you're surprised to see
the torch-wielding villagers?
I'm putting the kids to bed early.
I don't want 'em to see this.
Is that an ambulance?
I can't believe
you're doing this!
Amy, don't you want
me to have a chance?
God, I hate you!
I hate you!
Don't ever talk
to me again!
Hi. Bill?
I was wondering, do you
have plans Saturday night?
What... Excuse me, can you
tell me what happened?
Ma'am, I need
you to step back.
Okay.
We're brinng in
a female, late 30s.
And get crash cart ready.
She's in cardiac arrest.
-There he is.
Stop it! Stop it! You can't do this to
people! Have you lost your minds?!
Well, excuse us for wanting
to feel safe in our own homes.
Well, that's my home, and
I don't feel very safe right now.
Please, please, all of you,
just leave this street.
Please, I beg of you. Go!
Just get off my
street, please!
Wait, wait!
Art, wait, I'm sorry...
I'm sorry.
You're an idiot
to take him back.
I am no longer interested
in your opinion.
I thought
I made that clear.
Where are you
sending me?
Oh, we've rented you a condo
in a lovely retirement community.
It's our Christmas
gift to you.
So you're exiling me?
Cutting me off from
my new grandcldren?
That's our gift
to them.
You think you can be
rid of me that easily?
It's over, mother.
I told her everything.
Oh, I doubt
that very much.
You still have
secrets, my boy.
So do you, mother,
And if you want them
kept, you'll keep mine.
It's me. I have some bad news.
She's taking him back.
Meet me on the
corner in an hour.
We need to
deal with this.
I heard about
Rebecca on the news.
If there's anything
I can do to help, I...
With the funeral
arrangements, or, uh...
help you call relatives...
Wow.
You must be feeling
really guilty.
Of course!
I feel just terrible.
I mean, if you knew, if you
could just know how sorry I am.
Hey.
You know,
in a weird way...
I should thank you.
My sister was...
a really wonderful person.
She always saw
the best in me.
But there were things
she couldn't see...
Or chose not to,
God love her.
-What do you mean?
-I think you know.
See, I always knew that I
had to take care of Rebecca,
so I could never
let myself...
slip and do something
that would hurt her.
But now...
I'm free...
And all because of you.
You can't stay here.
Oh, don't worry.
I'm already packed.
Where are you going?
Why, you gonna write?
Well...
Good-bye, Lynette.
You take care of that
beautiful family of yours.
There's a reason people
can't wait for Christmas,
and it has little to do
with family reunions...
Or curling up with
a cup of eggnog...
Or that unexpected kiss
beneath the mistletoe...
Or receiving a present
from that special someone.
No, people look
forward to Christmas,
because they
know it's a time...
for miracles.
Hello, Alma.
Don't just stand there.
Tell me everything.