Previously on Desperate Housewives...
Mike's plan to
propose to Susan...
These things don't
belong to Jane.
"Mike Delfino."
Was a surprise to Ian.
Monique was murdered...
There's been an accident.
-And Orson...
-Don't forget your wrench.
Passed the blame.
A connection was made...
A heart was broken...
And Bree buried
her husband Rex.
My name is
Rex Van De Kamp.
I always hated cemeteries
when I was alive.
Now that I'm dead,
I like 'em even less.
Here's where
I used to live.
A whole lot nicer,
don't you think?
The place hasn't changed
much since I left,
as tasteful
and tidy as ever.
Everything perfect...
at least on
the surface.
My family was
the same way.
Look at us.
You'd never guess how ticked off
we all were the day this was taken,
but that was the thing
about us Van De Kamps.
To really fit in,
you had to have a smile
that gave away nothing.
Like my son Andrew.
To look at him, you'd never know
he spent six months on the streets
supporting himself with
panhandling and light prostitution.
Or my daughter Danielle.
Does she look like
the kind of girl
who'd seduce her
middle-aged History teacher?
I mean, they're my kids,
and I love 'em,
but I'm pretty darn
relieved to be dead.
Here's the clown
Bree replaced me with,
Orson.
I don't mind saying,
he's creeped me out
right from the get-go.
To me, he always has
the shifty look of a guy
who knows where
the bodies are buried...
But Bree thinks
he's sir Galahad.
The kids like him.
And all my friends...
now his friends.
So it pleases me to know that
at least one of my old neighbors
sees right
through the guy.
Mike, you just
missed Bree.
She's off to
see her folks,
and then we're finally
taking our honeymoon.
Yeah, not a bad time for
you to leave town, is it?
Well, I don't follow you.
I just keep thinking about
that night at Monique's place.
How you made sure
I left with my wrench.
The one with
her blood on it.
Well, it was
your wrench.
Why are you
rehashing this?
My ex-wife confessed
in her suicide note.
The case is closed.
Maybe it shouldn't be.
What do you think
the police would say
if they knew you were
there that night?
What do you
think they'd say
if they knew you
threw me off a roof?
Oh, Mike.
We could make so much
trouble for each other,
or we can forget what
we think we know
and be good neighbors.
Your call.
No, Orson Hodge
isn't exactly the guy
I'd have picked
to head my family,
but I'll give
him one thing...
He's got the smile
down cold.
By Tyno, Wisteria Team
Transcript by FRM
Forom.com & DHsubs.free.fr
Take a drive down
any street in suburbia.
You know what
you're gonna see?
Desperate women.
That's right.
One unhappy housewife
after another,
each completely
miserable...
in her own
unique way.
But I don't want
to talk about them.
No, I want to talk
about their men
and what
happens to a guy
when that special lady
in his life starts to lose it.
Like my friend Carlos.
He used to
have it all.
Hot wife, tons of dough,
then bam!
She gets a divorce, and
he gets stuck with the bill.
But does he sit
around and complain
like your average
hausfrau?
No, sir.
He finds creative ways
to get what you
can out of life.
Hey, bro!
Where you off to?
Oh, the hospital called.
They found the stuff I had on
me the night of the accident.
Coma, murder rap.
You've had a tough year, buddy.
You know what you need?
Some pampering.
Tomorrow you're checking
in to a nice hotel.
Room service,
jacuzzi, my treat.
You trying to get me
out of the house?
Mike, why would I...
Okay, there's this girl.
I knew it.
Dude, she's a dancer,
and if her online profile's
any indication,
she's a complete freak. We're
talking serious Daddy issues.
Look, I'll stay in my room.
You'll never hear me.
Yeah, but
you'll hear me.
I'm kind of exuberant by nature,
and when I haven't had it in a while,
I kind of do this shrieking
thing that, I mean, is kinda...
Okay. All right, I'll go.
Just stop talking.
Thanks, pal. I wouldn't want it
to put a weird spin on our friendship.
Too late.
This is my friend Tom.
Have you heard what
he's been up to lately?
This silly bastard opened up
his own pizza place.
He thought that
if he was his own boss,
he could sleep in
as late as he wanted,
but the problem with that
logic is that married guys...
Hey. It's after 9:00.
Come on, Thomasina,
it's time to get up.
Are never
their own boss.
Are you as
tired as I am?
More, but I'm tougher,
and I complain less.
Not when you give birth,
and you do that a lot.
Yeah?
Before I forget, you got
a call from Chez Nous
confirming your reservation
for our anniversary.
You heard that?
I wanted that to be a surprise.
Well, we've been going there
for the last seven years.
It's not exactly a surprise.
Anyway, I hope
you don't mind,
but I canceled.
You canceled? Why?
Honestly, I just don't feel up
to going out this year.
But it's our anniversary.
It's our ninth anniversary.
Come on.
The "big nine."
That's a year longer than my
Mom said we would be married.
Come on.
We gotta party down.
I'm exhausted.
Honestly, all I wanna do is pawn
the kids off on somebody else,
take a long bath
and be in bed by 8:00.
Okay.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you.
Hold it.
What about my sex?
I always get sex
on our anniversary.
We can still have sex.
Just try not to wake me.
This is Ian.
Don't really
know the guy,
but Susan Mayer
seems to like him.
The other night, he surprised
her with a proposal.
She said yes, but he's
still a little skittish
about the competition.
But Ian knows
that if love is war...
Hey. Where were you off
to so early this morning?
Sometimes you gotta bring
out the big artillery.
I should have had it
when I proposed.
It's not very good
form, I know.
Ian, oh,
you can't be serious.
Oh, that's just...
too much.
It's huge.
Well, we could go smaller.
Oh, no. No one's saying smaller.
No, that's crazy talk.
Rock me.
Oh, my!
Oh, it's so beautiful!
Oh, okay.
Okay, nobody move.
I got it.
I knew I should have
measured your finger.
No, it's okay.
I can get it resized.
You should go to the
jeweler's right now,
and when you get back, we can go and
look at some places for the reception.
Reception?
Yes, I was hoping we could pull
this together for next month.
What's the rush?
Am I pregnant?
Of course not.
I just, well, I just can't
wait to be married to you.
Are you sure?
'Cause you seem
a little anxious.
What would I have
to be anxious about?
Again,
sorry for the mix-up.
If you could just
sign right here...
I don't remember this.
You sure that's mine?
It was on you the night
you were admitted.
I got hit by a car.
I don't remember anything
about that night.
Well, it looks like you were
gonna propose to someone.
"Susan, be mine
forever. Mike."
Does that ring a bell?
Sure does.
Hey, Carlos.
Hi.
I have a little visitor
that I thought you might
get a kick out of seeing.
Remember my little boy?
Hey, Travers. How you
doing? Put her there.
I'm Carlos Solis.
I think you came by my house
one time trick-or-treating.
I remember.
You gave me a protein bar.
Right.
Sorry. My wife
forgot to buy candy.
Hey, is that football I hear?
Go on.
Check it out.
I didn't know your son
was coming for a visit.
Neither did I.
His father just dumped him
here for four weeks
so he could jet off with his
doctors without borders buddies
and fix cleft
palates in Kenya.
Selfish son of a bitch.
Come on. I mean,
you barely even see him.
It'll be fun.
A chance to bond.
Yeah, that's true,
but, um...
I have this major
party tonight,
and I was wondering if maybe you could
just keep an eye on him for a few hours.
Sorry. I can't tonight.
Come on! You love kids.
I mean, didn't you rent
that chinese chick
so that you could have
one of your own?
I have a date, too,
with a chick so hot I had to turn off
the smoke alarms in my house.
Fine.
Travers, come on.
Let's go.
This isn't
a child-friendly house.
Bye, Travers.
Wow, she's a looker.
I'll say.
Hey, what time's
that fund-raiser?
You got an hour.
Well, then...
Let's have
a little fun.
Look what you did!
Don't yell at me.
I'm just a passenger.
Well, your driver's an idiot!
Hey, it's not
Clyde's fault.
I mean, what man wouldn't be
distracted by such beauty?
Now you're
hitting on me?
I was talking
about the car.
Well, good.
I'm glad you like it,
'cause you're gonna
pay to fix this.
Of course.
$5,000 cover it?
Five?
Well, sure, I guess.
I'd rather not file
an insurance claim.
My opponent could find out
and try to make me look bad.
Opponent?
Oh, well, I guess you
don't read the papers.
I'm running for mayor.
My name's Victor Lang,
and I hope I can
count on your vote.
I think I'd rather vote
for the other guy.
You know, the one
who didn't wreck my car?
you're off
your game.
You didn't even get
a phone number.
Oh, don't worry.
I'll be seeing her again.
How can you
be so sure?
I didn't sign
the check.
What the hell
are you doing?
We neeto talk.
No, we don't. Get out.
Please. You won't
return my calls.
Well, I've been busy.
Plus, my Mom caught you
naked on top of my friend.
Just read this, and if you
still don't want to talk to me,
then I'll never
bother you again.
Fine, I'll read it,
but only if you get out
of the car right now.
Now? But the hot
wax is starting.
I know.
Ticktock.
You're still in there?
How long does it take
to pluck that unibrow?
Leave me alone!
Danielle, I have to be
at work in ten minutes.
Now can I please just come
in and brush my teeth?
I'm having a really
bad day, all right?
Just go away!
I'm gonna have
a really bad day, too.
I tend not to get tipped
when my breath stinks.
I'm pregnant.
Mike, what are
you doing here?
Oh, hey, I'm just
selling some old jewelry.
I spoke to my manager.
There's gonna be a charge
to remove the inscription,
but we can refund you
for the engagement ring.
That'll be fine.
Was that the ring
that you bought for...
Yeah.
Can I help you?
Yeah, I have
to get this sized.
It's a little loose.
Do you know
your size?
No.
Congratulations,
by the way.
Ian... seems great.
Thanks.
I can't find my sizer.
Here.
-Try this one.
-Oh, no...
How's that fit?
It's perfect.
Great.
Can I have it back now?
Sorry.
Hey, you've got a cousin in
the limo business, don't you?
Actually, I've got a cousin In the "limo
as a front for prostitution" business.
He's in jail.
Why do you ask?
Oh, I'm just planning a big
thing for my anniversary.
Aren't you just gonna go to Chez
Boring, like you do every year?
No.
Lynette's so over that, she was
ready to bag the whole night,
so got me thinking.
Nine years.
Time to shake things up.
Now I'm planning the greatest
anniversary of all time.
Check this out.
Lynette's gonna open the
door to find a limo driver
with a dozen
roses and a card.
The card is gonna tell
her to go with the guy,
not ask any questions.
He'll drive her
out to the country.
He'll drop her off,
Then drive away.
Just as she is starting
to freak out,
I show up in a
horse-drawn carriage,
which takes us up
to Whitman's bluff,
where we eat
a catered dinner,
listen to
a professional violinist.
Afterwards,
when we come home,
I'm sure Lynette will think
of a way to thank me.
You're one romantic
son of a bitch.
I have my moments.
Of course I'm not questioning
mayor Johnson's family values.
I'm sure they're what prompted him
to put his sisters, brother-in-law
and six of his cousins
on the city payroll.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have to cut this interview short.
I have some very important
business to attend to.
Ms. Solis,
What a nice surprise.
Are you here to make
a contribution to my campaign?
Not exactly.
Oh, no.
Did I forget to s...
I'm so sorry.
Let me make
it up to you.
I'll take you to dinner.
My treat.
It would be your treat.
I'm a hot date.
What's in it for me?
Well, I have, uh,
"an ingratiating wit,
trustworthy smile,"
According to the
"Plainview Herald."
Yeah. Check, please.
My family also owns
Lang Enterprises.
Dad's worth a...
few hundred mil.
Well, a girl's gotta eat.
Great. I'll take
you to Cucina.
There's no place
harder to get into.
That's what you think.
Mike, this is completely
unnecessary.
My paying for your
lawyer was a favor.
It wasn't a loan.
I appreciate it, but I just
don't like to owe anybody.
Well, I just don't want you
to have any trouble
getting back
on your feet.
No, it's fine. I had a windfall.
The hospital
gave me back
an engagement ring
I didn't even know I had.
Oh, really?
So you sold it?
You should have kept it
till the right girl comes along.
Well, I...
couldn't give this ring
to just anyone.
Oh, right, the, um,
the inscription.
How'd you know
it was inscribed?
Well, isn't that the custom?
I just assumed it was.
Well, listen, I've got
to get some fresh rags.
Thanks for the check.
I'll see you around.
Oh, you can
count on it.
-Are you sure?
-Yes.
I peed on five
different sticks.
Would you put that burrito away?
It's making me nauseous.
Join the club.
Look, I know your parents are
religious, but I know this clinic.
Absotely not!
So what other choice
do we have?
Well, gee, you could,
like, uh, marry me?
Marry you?!
I can't stand you.
Nice way to talk to the
mother of your child!
Oh, God.
Bathroom.
Hey.
Julie.
Hi. Uh, hey.
Your door was open.
Can I come in?
What are you
doing here?
I read your letter.
I had no idea
it would be so sweet.
I could really tell
it came from your heart.
I'm embarrassed
to admit, I...
cried.
My aunt Edie sort of
tied one on last night.
Anyway, I guess
what I'm saying is...
Okay.
"Okay"?
We can try again.
Julie, that's great!
And I want to
talk about this,
but I just kinda need
to take care of my aunt.
Can I call you
tomorrow?
Sure.
We're gonna have
to take things slow,
'cause it'll be a while
before I can trust you again.
I understand.
Thank you, Bruno.
The veal was excellent.
-Feel like dessert?
-No, thank you. I'm stuffed.
Then let me
propose a toast.
To a delightful evening,
and to the happy accident
that brought us together.
Victor, you are
so full of crap.
What?
There was no accident.
I know you told your
chauffeur to ram my car.
Why would I do that?
For the same reason you
"forgot" to sign the check.
You've been working me
since the second we met,
and I've been on to you
every step of the way.
What? What's so funny?
I just called you
a manipulative jerk.
I think
I underestimated you.
I also think this relationship
just got a lot more interesting.
There is no relationship.
This is our last date.
You didn't have any fun?
It was okay.
You know, you told a few good
jokes. you're sorta charming.
You're not bad-looking.
I just think I can do better.
Have you not noticed?
I'm a catch.
I have noticed,
and I'm throwing you back.
Gaby, let me tell
you something.
For my whole life,
whenever I've truly
wanted something,
I've always gotten it.
And tonight, right around the time
you were calling me a manipulative jerk,
I decided
I truly want you.
So brace yourself.
The chase is on.
You can chase me
all you want,
But trust me,
I'm way too
fast for you.
Bruno...
I'm gonna
marry that girl.
Can I just say
something?
You are way hotter
than your online profile.
So many guys say that.
What's wrong?
Oh, my friend's
kid is out there.
Hey, I got an idea.
Let's go upstairs.
I should warn you...
My therapist says
I'm sexually compulsive.
This could take hours.
Whatever your issues are,
we will work them out together.
It's almost 11:00. What is
he doing out therby himself?
I'm sure his folks
know he's out there.
Now relax.
I'm so sorry. I will be
right back. I promise.
Hey, Travers, what are
you doing out here?
Where's your Mom?
She had to go
visit a sick friend.
Come on.
No way. I didn't come over here
to babysit some little brat.
-He can hear you.
-I don't care.
Look, his mother's bound
to be home soon, all right?
Then we can pick up
where we left off.
Forget it.
I'm officially
no longer in the mood.
Sorry I ruined
your date.
That's okay.
She was
a very bad lady
who wanted to do very,
very bad things to me.
Night, Raoul.
-Where the hell have you been?
-Oh, I, uh...
ducked out...
just for an hour.
That's funny,
'cause I found Travers wandering
the streets three hours ago.
Look, he was
fine when I left.
I just didn't know
he'd go outside.
Yeah, you never know what
an 8 year old's gonna do.
That's why
you supervise him.
Hey, you don't get to judge me.
You don't have a kid.
Well, if I did,
I'd treat him a hell of
a lot better than you do.
Thank God he lives with
his father. I mean, come on.
What kind of
mother are you?
If you are done
lecturing me,
I would like
my son now.
He's asleep.
Come and get him
in the morning...
When you're sober.
Hey, buddy!
Your Mom's here for ya.
I know you think
I'm a terrible person.
I never said that.
Terrible mother, terrible person.
It's the same thing.
Because no matter
what else she does,
if a woman isn't a good mother,
she's a failure, right?
Look, um...
When I had Travers,
I knew I was in over my head,
and when Charles
and I split, I...
I gave him custody.
Because I wanted my son
to have the best life possible.
And that doesn't make me
a good mother, but...
I like to think it makes
me a realistic one.
Hey, Mom.
Hey, champ.
I missed you.
I missed you, too.
Guess what?
I've got so many fun things
for you to do today.
Cool.
Thanks for
the ice cream.
My pleasure.
I'll see you, little man.
Hey.
Travers said he's
staying at least a month.
Yeah.
So if you ever need
a babysitter, just yell.
I appreciate that.
Hey! Wait for me!
No, I don't want
a viola player.
I asked for a violinist. I don't
even know what a viola is.
Oh, it's just
a big violin?
Okay. Yeah, sure.
Okay, I'll see you at 8:00.
What was that?
It's just a little
surprise, okay?
-Let it go.
-"Let it go", that's cute.
Start talkin'.
I planned a little something
for our anniversary.
That is all
I'm gonna say.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
If we're doing this,
I need to buy you something.
What do you want? You don't
have to buy me anything.
Well, you didn't have
to plan anything,
but you did, even though
we had an agreement.
You like ties?
You're getting a tie.
What are you getting?
I have been dragging my ass
all day, and the only thought
that's kept me going
is the hot bath,
and now I have do my hair
and shave my legs.
So what do you
want to do, Lynette?
Just tell me what you want.
I told you what I want.
Hot bath, bed early,
but you choose not to listen.
Well, okay, I guess I can
just cancel the whole thing.
You can have your
dream evening alone,
and I'll get up a poker
game or something.
Thank you.
Hey. You know what? I've been
dragging my ass all day, too,
and you know what
got me through it?
The idea of doing
something special with you.
Happy anniversary.
All right. I'm off
to join your mother.
The hotel number's on the fridge
in case there's a problem.
Bree said her cell phone
isn't getting good reception.
Actually, we kinda
already have a problem.
Well, I'm already
late for my flight.
Can this wait a few
weeks till we're back?
Yeah, this could
wait a few weeks.
Oh, good.
I mean, heck, this particular
problem could wait...
nine months.
Good Lord.
How was your bath?
Oh, I couldn't relax.
I just kept replaying the fight
I had with Tom in my head.
Well, at least your husband
tries to be romantic.
Every anniversary, Gilbert
bought me an appliance.
The last one, he gave
me a vacuum cleaner.
He died two weeks later.
I didn't cry.
Who could that be?
Here.
All right. Here's
what we're thinking.
Clearly, the idea of the two of
you getting married is ridiculous.
So what do you
want me to do?
Glad you asked.
Bree and I have decided
that Danielle will join
us on our heymoon.
When we return, we'll tell our friends
she's decided to study abroad.
Once the baby is born and
adopted by a suitable family,
she'll come home.
What about me?
You leave.
Leave?
Get out of Fairview
and don't tell a soul why,
-Not even your aunt.
-I can't do that.
Why not?
Because I've got
responsibilities here.
People are counting on me.
Yeah, well, you should
have thought of that
before you impregnated
my stepdaughter.
I said I'm not leaving!
Easy there, turbo.
We'll be right back.
So who exactly
is counting on you?
Julie Mayer, maybe?
She gave me
another chance.
I can't leave if I've still
got a shot with her.
And what's gonna happen when Julie
finds out you knocked up my sister?
Didn't your stepdad just say no
one's gonna find out about that?
Okay.
Try this.
Julie's a nice girl,
and you, well...
you're a dog.
No knock.
I'm a dog lover myself,
but Julie deserves better.
You know you'll just
end up cheating on her.
No, I won't
hurt her again.
Sure you will.
Not right away.
Maybe you'll hold
out for six months,
but then it'll hurt
her even more.
Am I wrong?
You just have
to ask yourself
if you can be the kind of
guy she needs you to be.
If you can't...
walk away.
Beer is on the
house, guys.
Drink fast, get stupid,
lose money.
Mike!
Hey. How's it going, buddy?
Hey, you know,
uh, Orson, right?
Oh, yeah.
Hey, neighbor.
Hey, so let's get started, huh?
5-card stud? Two dollars ante?
Good evening, gentlemen.
Ian!
Hey... Ian.
Nice to see you, Mike.
What is fish and
chips doing here?
Susan asked me
to include him.
Said he always wanted
to learn how to play poker.
So we're going to give him
some very expensive lessons.
Be careful. He already
knows how to bluff.
Hey.
Hey. How's it going?
Good. Good, uh...
Just wanted to tell you, I have
to leave town for a while.
Really?
Is something wrong?
No, no, no.
It's just family stuff.
I don't know exactly
when I'll be back.
It could be a while,
though.
Okay.
I just want you
to know that...
It means a lot that you were willing
to give me a second chance.
You're, like, the only person
that's ever done that.
Austin...
What's going on?
Nothing, uh,
it's just...
I have to go.
Good-bye, Julie.
Austin!
I'll raise you.
Out.
Ah, another courageous
move for "foldilocks."
All right. I'll call you.
Flush, king high.
Full house,
7s and knaves.
Jacks.
We call them jacks.
Boy, this is your
lucky room.
Yes, I heard about your
engagement the other night.
Congratulations.
Yeah, about that, Ian,
Was that proposal spontaneous,
or did you have it all planned?
It was entirely planned.
I thought it would be
the ideal occasion.
Well, if it was planned,
why didn't you have a ring?
Well, I thought Susan might
like to choose the ring herself.
Ante up, boys.
So why'd she pick a ring
that was too big for her?
How did you
know that?
Guys, guys, guys, guys,
we came here to play cards.
Why are we talking
about jewelry?
Sorry, Tom, but I just found out
I bought a ring for Susan myself.
It was in my pocket that night
some son of a bitch ran me over.
Hey, Tom's right.
We should focus on the game.
After our talk,
I called the hospital.
They said my ring got in
with your wife's stuff.
So you saw it
before I did...
The same day you
proposed to Susan.
And your point is?
That that's why you were
in such a big hurry.
You wanted to seal the deal before
I found out about the ring and told her.
Do you think
I'm afraid of you?
Maybe you should be.
What do you think
Susan would say
if she found out why your
proposal was so spontaneous?
Guys, can we just play?
I'm trying.
Fine.
Deal.
Hello?
Mr. Scavo,
It's Lamar from
the limo service.
I got a flat, so I might be late
picking up you and your wife.
What are you talking about?
I canceled you.
No, you didn't.
Yes, I did. I left
you a message.
I must have
missed it.
Anyway, I dropped your wife off,
right where you told me.
Oh, God. When?
About two hours ago.
Guys, lock up
when you're done.
I'll open.
I'm out.
And I'll raise you.
You want a beer?
Hell, Tom's gone.
Let's go open up the good stuff.
Well...
Looks like
it's just you and me,
if you're still in.
With this hand?
You bet I am.
I'll re-raise.
And raise again.
Your stack's
looking kinda small.
Will you take a check?
You know I can't
match that.
How about this, then?
You win, you keep the money, and
you tell Susan whatever you want.
I win, you keep your
mouth shut about the ring,
and you leave me
and Susan alone.
Deal.
How was the game?
I won.
Lynette, I am so sorry.
I am so sorry!
You see, there was supposed to
be a horse-drawn carriage and...
Good. You got the flowers.
Coffee?
Yes, please.
Yeah, she likes
coffee, too. Thanks.
I'm really, really,
really sorry...
Please stop apologizing.
I appreciate what you
were trying to do.
It was a lovely though that
just went hideously, hideously,
hideously wrong.
Wait till the kids find out
that you saw a real coyote.
Hideously.
Well, I learned
my lesson.
Never again.
No more surprises.
From now on, I'll do
exactly what you say.
Don't... you... dare.
What?
I had a lot of time
to think tonight,
and I realized
you were right.
We have to keep
the romance going,
no matter how
tired we are.
The only thing worse thaor just
going through the motions Is not...
bothering to go
through the motions.
So you want me to
surprise you next year?
Knock yourself out.
Just wait, 'cause I will think
of something even better.
Well, after this year,
I would be happy
with any date
that included
food and shelter.
Nine years.
Nine years...
And I have loved
every minute of it.
Me, too.
Take a drive down any
street in suburbia.
You know what
you're gonna see?
A bunch of guys wearing
the same expression.
It's a look that says,
"Oh, crap.
My dreams are never
gonna come true."
"I'll never have a life
free from scandal."
"I'll never have
a son of my own."
"I'll never hold her
in my arms again."
"I'll never get to
tell her how I feel."
Yeah, the suburbs are filled with
a lot of men who have given up hope.
Of course, every once in a
while you do come across
some lucky S.O.B. whose
dreams have all come true.
You know how
you spot them?
They're the ones who
can't stop smiling.
Don't you just
hate those guys?