Previously on Desperate Housewives...
Gabrielle got even...
So did I hurt you, or
should I keep trying?
Tom got an idea...
I'm gonna open up
a pizza parlor!
Bree got a warning...
He's a cold-blooded killer.
The police got a clue...
Those blue marks,
I think it's a phone number.
You've reached Mike Delfino.
This should never
have happened!
And the battle for Mike's
affection got ugly.
How do you sleep at night?
Soon, with Mike on top of me.
It is often said that confession
is good for the soul.
No one knew this better
than a certain blonde,
who had been confessing
her sins to Father O'Malley,
once a week since
she was a child.
As the years had passed,
much to Father O'Malley's dismay,
a theme began to emerge.
I seduced the cable guy again.
I'm having a affair
with a folksinging duo.
Last week, I let Rabbi
Lippman get to third base.
And once she had been forgiven,
Father O'Malley would
tell Edie Britt
to go out into the
world and sin no more.
Unfortunately for Edie,
temptation seemed to be...
Hello there.
Everywhere.
Edie, what were we like together...
before the accident?
What do you mean?
You know, were we close?
Honestly?
We lived about 50 feet
from each other,
and you barely
knew that I existed.
Seriously?
It's true.
I mean, you weren't
rude or anything.
We'd wave or exchange "hellos"
as we went to get our mail,
but you never really looked at me.
But if we weren't friends, why are
you here every day helping me?
Because from the first
moment I laid eyes on you...
I sort of fell in love with you.
Yeah, and I'm not telling you this because
I expect anything, so you can just relax, okay?
Okay.
But when you do
come back home,
and we do run into each other
when we're getting our mail,
I'd really appreciate it if you'd...
just look at me.
That's all.
I'm looking at you now.
Yes, it's often said confession
is good for the soul.
Mike Delfino and I made
out today, and it was great!
But some confessions are
just bragging in disguise.
By Tyno, Wisteria Team
Transcript by YDY
Forom.com & DHsubs.free.fr
There was nothing Bree Hodge
hated more than an unexpected...
knock at the door.
She was always certain it would
lead to a dagreeable surprise...
Whether it be in the form of
a cosmetics saleswoman,
religious Zealots
or extended family.
But on this day,
the surprise awaiting Bree
was far more disagreeable than
she ever could have imagined.
Hello, Bree.
Carolyn.
This isn't a very good time.
I'm baking.
Bree?
Uh, hi.
We haven't met.
I'm Harvey Bigsby,
and I brought my wife
here to apologize.
It's a soufflé.
And timing is everything.
Oh, please, please, um...
She's been under a great deal of
stress since Alma's disappearance,
and she really hasn't been herself.
Much of that was due to
the mexican painkillers
that she was purchasing online,
but I put a stop to that.
Well, Orson tells me that the
two of you were very close,
and out of respect for that
friendship, I'm all ears.
After thinking it over, I realized
that maybe I was out of line.
I was definitely out of lin with
the terrible accusations that I made.
I'm deeply sorry for
the pain that I caused.
I hope that you can find it
in your heart to forgive me.
Well, I can appreciate how difficult
that must have been for you.
Apology accepted.
I'm so relieved.
As am I.
Well, you don't know how rusty
my golf game's gotten without
this one keeping me on my toes.
Well, perhaps we can all get together
for dinner at the club sometime.
That sounds lovely.
Great.
Darling, you are amazing,
you know that?
To rise above all that
unpleasantness with such dignity.
Well, thank you, darling.
But if you think for one second
that I'm gonna break bread with
that malicious, pill-popping shrew,
you're out of your mind.
Hey, Susan! Whatcha doing?
I just dropped my trowel. Thanks.
All  righty then,
you have a nice day.
Bye-bye.
S usan?
Ian!
What a surprise.
Were you, um, were
you hiding from me?
Uh, a little.
I...
Just, the last time
we saw each other,
it was so awkward
and complicated.
Water under the bridge.
And besides, this
is strictly business.
I'm throwing a party for an
editor friend in from London,
and I thought you
two should meet.
You could bring a date if you want.
Speaking of which, uh,
how are things with Mike?
Oh, uh, they're moving along.
It's a process.
And the, uh, blonde woman who's
been visiting him every day,
is she part of the process?
Uh, Edie? Oh, she's...
just a neighbor.
She visits Mike after
her hepatitis C treatments.
Well, I do hope you
can come to the party...
so you can meet my editor friend.
I just, I just don't think
that's a good idea.
Right.
Well, at least I, uh,
I got to see you.
You have...
This is ludicrous,
the Biedermeier armoire.
It's my understanding that your
client doesn't even like antiques.
Totally immaterial.
It's a valuable asset.
Fine.
Let's discuss the Kosta Boda vase.
Nope, it's a premarital acquisition.
We can verify that with receipts.
It was a gift to Mr. Solis.
Maybe you were sick that
day at law school, Myron,
but it's called community property.
Don't patronize me, Kenny.
We're prepared to go
to the mat on this one.
Oh, enough. Just give
her what she wants.
Look, I'm sick of fighting.
It's just stuff.
I'd like a moment
alone with my client.
This has been going
on for months. I'm done.
Draw up the papers.
I'll sign whatever.
You're giving me everything
I want? Just like that?
Just like that.
We expect to see the paperwork
by the end of business.
How sweet is that?
We nailed their asses.
Mrs. Solis, they complely folded.
That's the thing,
Carlos doesn't fold.
That son of a bitch
is up to something.
Before you come in,
cover your eyes.
-Tom, I...
-Do it!
Okay, now...
When I say "open,"
don't look with your eyes.
look with your imagination.
Okay.
Okay. Open.
Oh, dear God.
Damn it, you looked with your eyes!
It's a dump!
What are you thinking?
Oh, I'll grant you,
it's a fixer-upper.
It's a burner-downer.
Come on, honey, go with me.
We can put in booths with
checkered tablecloths,
a jukebox, a big-screen
to watch sports on.
How can you not see
the potential in this place?
Well, I just don't.
Tom, you know how I feel
about this pizza thing.
Well, hopefully,
it'll grow on you.
Don't...
Tell me you didn't sign a lease.
There's gonna be a dartboard!
Tom!
No...
There were multiple offers.
I had to move fast.
You leased a building
without telling me?
Well, maybe I didn't tell
you because I knew
you'd try and talk me out of the
best opportunity in my life.
Okay.
Okay, here's what
we're going to do.
You said there were multiple
offers, so we can sublease.
Now let's get the hell out of here.
You said you'd support my dream.
My mistake. I assumed you'd have
a dream worth supporting.
I'm gonna stay here tonight.
Fine.
Two lemonades for the victors.
You  keep playing like this, Bree,
and we are a cinch for the finals.
Hello, Tish.
Hello, Rebecca.
Did you see that? She just
deliberately snubbed me.
Maybe she didn't notice you.
Rebecca, I just spoke to her.
And  call me paranoid,
but Amy Griswold did
the same thing to me on
the golf course last week.
What is going on?
You really don't know?
No! I have no idea. What?
Tish is very good friends
with Carolyn Bigsby.
Carolyn knows Tish?
She knows everyone.
Anyway, Tish won't talk to you
because you married Orson
even after Carolyn told
you that he killed his wife.
That is ridiculous.
Orson did not kill Alma.
And besides, Carolyn just apologized
to me for that yesterday.
Well, maybe that hasn't
gotten back to Tish.
Oh, you don't believe any
of that nonsense, do you?
Do you?
Bree, you're the best doubles
partner I've ever had.
Can we talk about this
after the tournament?
Hello.
I'd like to make a reservation
for this evening,
under the names Hodge
and Bigsby, and, um,
we'll be needing a table
in the center of the room.
How long will Daddy be gone?
Well, that sort of depends on Daddy.
Are you two mad at each other?
Yeah.
A little.
But that's okay.
That's okay. We still love
each other very much.
But just like kids, sometimes grown-ups
throw tantrums and need a time-out.
Why can't he take a
time-out in his room?
'Cause he decided to take
it in his pizza place.
No fair.
That sounds fun.
Not this pizza place. It's a rat hole.
But once your Dad
comes to his senses,
and stops being petulant,
he'll come home.
What's "petulant"?
It means childish, stubborn, careless
with my money and your futures.
Huh?
It's a grown-up word, and
when Daddy comes home,
you'll learn a new one...
Grovel.
They got in a really big fight.
Daddy's sleeping at the restaurant.
No, no, it's good that
you told me, sweet pea.
You keep those little
ears open, okay?
Okay. Bye, Mom.
Bye.
Oh, hey, that's for me. I'll take that.
Okay.
Well, I'm beat.
I'm gonna take a nap.
Uh, hold it.
You're a sweaty mess.
So? I was working out.
So you're not laying on anything in
this house until you take a shower.
Fair enough.
It's all yours now, right?
I don't know, Myron.
It's a bunch of legal mumbo jumbo.
Just read it and call me back.
Crap!
What?
Why did you put those shorts back on?
Why do you care?
Uh, it's just that they're filthy,
anI was gonna wash 'em for you.
You wanna wash my shorts?
I don't want to, but if you wear them one
more time they're gonna ask me themselves.
Wait a minute.
I forgot something in the pocket.
No bleach.
Got  it.
So it's a job contract?
Yeah, Welch and Simon are offering him
$2 million over 3 years, plus stock options.
Well, that's fantastic!
I get half, right?
Well, no.
If you're legally divorced
when he signs the contract,
then you don't see a dime.
That conniving, underhanded snake!
Thank God I broke into his desk.
At least now we know why he was
so quick to fold on your settlement.
All right, well, let's just say something
happened to postpone the divorce.
I would still get my share
of that $2 million, right?
Well, in theory, but...
How would you manage that?
I know how Carlos thinks. More
importantly, what he thinks with.
-Was that Susan Mayer?
-Yeah. Why?
Mr. Delfino asked not to be disturbed.
Mike? It's me.
Are you decent?
Hey, Susan.
Hey, you.
Whatcha doing?
I suckered McCluskey into
taking the kids for a while,
so I could kick back and
catch up with my old friend...
Margarita.
You care to join us?
Believe me, I would
love to, but, um...
I gotta get dinner started for Julie.
Okay.
Oh, you know, what the hell?
She's 16.
If she hasn't figured out how to
feed herself by now, I've failed.
That's nice.
So where were we?
You were trying to figure out how
to kill Edie without doing time.
Oh, right.
Oh, I wish Paul Young was still
around. He'd know what to do.
Fine, Gaby! Don't say hi!
Hey!
Cocktails? Nobody called me?
It was spur-of-the-moment.
We're numbing the pain
of our miserab lives.
Well, I was trying to do that with
exercise but why risk a heart attack?
Make mine a double!
I don't recognize her.
Who is she?
That's what we're
trying to figure out.
Your phone number was
written on her hand.
I'm sorry. I can't help you.
He's had a bit of memory loss.
After 2004, things are...
fuzzy.
No memory, huh?
That's convenient.
Well, thank you for
your time, Mr. Delfino.
You  killed a cop once, didn't you?
That was self-defense.
Hope it wasn't just beginner's luck.
You wanna charge me
with something, go ahead.
Otherwise, get the
hell out of my room.
Were you always this
angry, Mr. Delfino,
or can't you remember?
So do you sell by the slice,
or do I gotta buy a whole pie?
What are you doing here?
I knew how hard
you were working,
So I figured I'd bring you
a little something to eat...
and drink.
You know, I can't pronounce this wine,
which means it's either really
expensive or I have had too much.
I can't believe that Lynette
doesn't just love this place.
And if you ask me,
she's just a negative nellie.
She's just being realistic. I mean,
the restaurant business is...
- brutal, it's...
- Tom.
Listen to me, okay, 'cause
I'm a very intuitive person,
and you have a real aura
of success about you.
Come on.
I'm serious.
I believe in you,
Tom Scavo.
Thank you...
Wait, wait, what,
what just happened?
-We kissed.
-No, you kissed me.
-No, no, no, you wanted me to.
-No, no, no, no, no, I didn't.
Really?
Cause this is you.
My wife doesn't get me.
Hey, let's have some more wine
alone, in a deserted building.
I was just looking to vent.
I wasn't looking for anything more.
Okay, but when opportunity knocks...
Nora, please!
I love my wife!
Really?
You mean, the one who
thinks that you're a loser?
No, the one that loves me enough
to keep me from screwing up.
And I think it's about time
I got back home to her.
You led me on.
You shouldn't have done that.
I'm just gonna say it.
Tequila makes me happy.
Yeah, we're drinking on the porch.
You got a problem with that?
Oh, I know them. They live on Cypress.
They just celebrated their
53rd wedding anniversary.
Show-offs.
Don't worry. It won't last.
You're just fooling yourselves!
Hey, I know them.
Oh, 53 years.
What do you think their secret is?
I'll take a wild guess.
The man never opened a pizza place.
Oh, I just thought of something.
I'm never gonna celebrate
a 53rd wedding anniversary.
I'd have to live into my 90s.
Oh, my God. I'm gonna die.
Bite on this.
Can I tell you guys something...
something I can only tell you guys?
Oh, God, here she goes again.
What grade is he in?
Not what I was gonna say.
What I was gonna say,
is with all his conniving and trickery,
I still love Carlos.
Yeah, he's hot.
Anyway, what if I never find
that passion with anybody else?
Well, maybe you should try
to patch things up with him.
Nah, I already paid a lawyer.
I'm taking him down.
I brought this on myself. I tell Tom,
"I want you to be your own man".
But the truth is, I don't.
I want him to have what
he wants if it's what I want.
I'm a bitch with a capital "C".
No! No, you're not!
You're a great wife
and a great mother.
Although... don't you have children?
I had passion with Mike...
And drama.
Lots of drama.
Love isn't supposed to be that hard.
Oh, sweetie!
But, you know, with Ian,
everything was always easy.
You know, that's the kind of guy I could
see myself living into my 90s with.
So go to Ian!
Tell him you made the wrong choice,
and he's the one you wanna be with.
What have you got to lose?
Excuse me, ladies?
Look, Susan, God called you a cab.
I'm looking for, uh, 4347.
Ida Greenberg?
I'm Ida Greenberg!
Yeah, you are!
See you later!
Go, Ida!
Susan.
You came.
Of course I came.
Oh, I just love your house.
It always smells like you.
Oh, my Gosh!
Is the thing... is that tonight?
Well, yes. Isn't that why you're here?
No! No, no!
Actually, I just... I just
had something to tell you.
Well, of course. Ah, Doug, see
if you can find Judith for me.
Thank you.
Well, as long as you're here, I want you to
meet that editor I was telling you about.
Oh, I don't think that's a good idea,
cause I didn't really bring my "a" game.
Is it hot?
Are you sloshed?
Susan!
Oh, is this the Susan you've
been telling us all about?
Yes, this is she.
Could you, um, give us a moment?
Oh, of course.
What's going on?
Nothing. I just had a few drinks
with my girlfriends, and thank God,
because it gave me the courage to come over
here and tell you what's really in my heart.
Go on.
But first, I think I should
use the powder room.
Uh, oh... of course.
It's, um, it's over there.
She seems nice, Ian.
Oh, yes, she's, um,
she's absolutely delightful.
Oh, I'm so sorry that
you had to see that.
I see you've met Judith.
So with a hundred bucks riding
on it, the pressure's on me now.
I reach into my bag, I grab my 4-iron
and bada bing... hole in one.
And there's been no living
with him ever since.
Did I not tell you how hilarious
these two are together?
Oh, they are a regular
barrel of... Tish!
Why, hello, Bree.
Carolyn.
Do you two know each other?
Well, that saves me an introduction.
Uh, Tish, you know, I was wondering if
you need any help with the Christmas gala.
Last year, I was on the
decorations committee...
Oh, my God, I forgot to
call you. What an idiot!
We'll talk first thing tomorrow.
That would be lovely. Thanks.
Nice to see you.
Nice to be seen.
Well, I need to powder
my nose. Care to join me?
Oh, I'd love to.
I'm so happy we did this.
Yes, me, too. It's been
a delightful evening.
So, so fun.
Could you get us some
extra tissues? Thank you.
You know, I realized
something just the other day.
You've never seen a picture
of Alma, have you?
No. Why?
Granted, it's not her best look.
What is all this?
That's the police report that
Alma filed after Orson hit her.
It's all in there. The bruises,
contusions, broken wrist.
This is not possible.
Photos don't lie, Bree.
Is this why you apologized?
Yes.
I wanted you to spend time with
me so you can see I'm not some
crazy nut out to get you.
I'm sorry, but if something like that happened
again,  I could never forgive myself.
Thank you.
I had a feeling you might need these.
Bring me another one.
Hey, buddy...
You wanna slow down
a little bit, huh?
Harvey?
Look, I'm going through something,
And I don't have anyone
else to talk to about it.
I had an affair.
Uh, does Carolyn know?
No, she has no idea.
I met this girl on a flight from
Paris, and we just... connected.
No, I know it sounds
crazy, but it was...
love at first sight.
Well, are you still seeing her?
No, that's the thing.
A few months ago, she stopped
returning my calls, and,
then I went by her place and I've looked
for her everywhere, and she's just...
disappeared.
No, I'll tell ya, now I know what you
went, through with Alma. It's brutal.
It gets better. Trust me.
I just can't get past it. I'm...
I can't get Monique
out of my mind.
Monique?
That's her name.
Monique...
Polier.
Isn't she beautiful?
She's... very pretty.
They're back.
You two girls were gone a long
time, everything okay?
Mm-hmm, absolutely.
So... who wants dessert?
What have you been up to?
Just a quiet night with the girls.
Listen, something happened tonight,
and it got me thinking, and...
You mean more to me than
any restaurant ever could.
Oh, stop right there.I am the one who
should apologize. I have been a bad wife.
No, no, no, no, no!
You were just trying to keep me
from doing something reckless.
Yeah, well, any wife can support
a husband who never takes risks,
and I don't want that kind of husband, and
I'll be damned if I'm gonna be that kind of wife.
So you open your pizza place, and
we will find a way to make it work.
You don't know how much
it means to me to hear that.
God, I love you.
So what happened tonight?
Okay, but don't react until
I've told you the whole story.
And remember, it's actually a good thing,
because it brought us back together.
Ding-dong.
I don't know what Tom told
you, but he came on to me.
I'm sorry. I didn't quite catch that.
Why don't you just come on over
here and say that to me again?
Stay away from me.
I have been trying to
stay away from you...
Mom?
Everything's all right, so you can
just go back into your room and play.
Kayla! Don't move.
Okay. Never mind.
I'm leaving.
First, I'm just gonna
give your Mom a hug.
Your association
with my family is over.
When Kayla comes to visit, you will
drop her at the end of the block.
You will never again see
my husband, and if you try to,
I will do to your spine what
I just did to your front door.
Nod if you understand.
And you, I'm gonna see
you on Saturday, right?
Don't forget your swimsuit.
Good morning! You're
looking bright-eyed and...
bushy.
Did you stay here all night?
Well, I slept on the sofa.
When I brought you home, you
were still, as you americans say...
tossing your tacos.
Please, keep the food
references to a minimum.
Bless you.
So what else happened?
You don't remember?
Well, I'll tell you what...
I'll repeat what you said last night,
and you say whether it was you or
the booze talking. Are you ready?
You said you missed me.
Susan or booze?
Susan.
You said it was a mistake breaking up
with me and that you wanted to start again.
Susan or booze?
Susan.
Then you said that you wanted
to dress me up like a schoolboy
and spank my naughty bottom.
Susan or booze?
Oh, I didn't say that.
Yeah, all right then,
but if you had, um...
Susan or booze?
A little of both, so... boozan.
Detective Ridley.
Your Jane Doe in the morgue
is named Monique Polier.
Who's this?
Just before she died, she was having an
affair with a man named Harvey Bigsby.
You got that?
Yeah. Uh, can I get your name?
I'll need to bring you
in for a statement.
Carlos, could you come help me?
I'm watching the game.
It'll just take a second. Please?
What, Gaby?
You look... nice.
Oh, thanks.
I'm gonna go meet some
new friends for dinner.
But my zipper's stuck.
Can you help me?
Man, this is really stuck.
It's like somebody put superglue
on it or something.
Weird.
Well, you know what? I don't wanna
be late, so I should probably change.
Oh, Carlos, this old thing?
You've seen it all before.
I'm just gonna wear
the little blue number.
Will you hand me those stockings?
I've got a raggedy nail.
You're gonna have to
help me put those on.
Are you sure about that?
Well, I'd do it myself, but
I don't wanna get a snag.
It's been a long time.
Really? It seems like
yesterday to me.
You want me to help
you hook that?
Sure.
Why not?
For old time's sake.
What about your new friends?
I've decided I'd rather
catch up with an old one.
Mr. Bigsby, Detective Ridley, homicide.
I understand you know her.
Uh, all right, yes, we
were sleeping together.
Can we do this somewhere else?
Sure.
Carlos, do you think
we're making a mistake?
What do you mean?
The whole divorce thing.
Maybe we shouldn't
go through with it.
It's not like we're gonna find this
kind of passion with anyone else.
Are you saying you wanna stay together?
Yeah,
I guess I am.
Why don't we just put all of this behind
us and stay together? What do you say?
Oh, baby...
If you knew how long I waited
to hear you say that...
Well, what? What's so funny?
Oh, man.
I thought I'd be able to get through this
without cracking up, but you are just too funny.
There's a little something
that I need to own up to.
I know that the only reason you slept
with me was because I got a new job.
You got a new job?
Honey, that's wonderful!
Gaby, please.
You were a model,
not a model actress.
There is no job.
The contracts in my desk were
fake. I mailed them to myself.
What?
Why would you do that?
Well, let's see...
You did this just
to get me in bed?
No, I did it because I knew you'd smell
money and come crawling back.
Then I could turn you down
and walk out on my own terms.
Your terms?
You don't get to screw around
on me, take my money and then
walk away without a scratch.
I want you hurting, baby,
and judging by the
look on your face,
when you saw 2 million
imaginary dollars disappear,
I succeeded.
You are a bastard!
Better a bastard
than a whore.
Oh, God!
Hello? Uh, there's been an
accident. My husband, he...
I'm gonna have to call you back.
Carlos?
Honey?
Oh, yeah.
It's on.
There is a place in St. Timothy's church
where sinners go to confess their sins.
And once they're done,
they expect absolution.
But the truth is, not all confessions
are worthy of such forgiveness.
Most who unveil hidden agendas
deserve the condemnation they receive.
Most who disclose vengeful motives
merit the punishment that follows.
Only the truly repentant have any right
at all to expect a second chance...
Come on. What's my surprise?
I thought you'd never get here.
Which is why it's best to think
twice before you confess...
Mike?
What's wrong?
That...
That girl who died...
Especially if you don't know
what it is you're confessing to.
I think I knew her.