previously on desperate housewives.
maybe you haven't noticed,
but I'm in love with you.
Victor caught gaby by surprise...
why would a four-star chef wanna slum at a pia joint?
Lynette took a gamble...
- he has a history...using cocaine.
- No,no way.
Well,but he's been clean for almost a year.
Mike bet on love...
I win,you leave me and susan alone.
And lost...
don't panic.
But still came to susan's rescue.
You okay?
Yeah.
And mrs. Mccluskey revealed her secret
for a lasting relationship.
It was late on a tuesday night
when the power went out all over fairview.
for most of the residents,
it was a minor inconvenience.
But for those with secrets,
the darkness proved quite useful indeed.
Millie russell was able to
indulge in another night of midnight binging.
Timmy cooper was ableo sneak another peek
at his father's adult magazines.
Marilyn quinn was able to
steal a few more puffs of her forbidden tobacco.
but these secrets paled compared to the one
a certain old woman was hiding in her basement.
You sit tight,ida.
I got batteries here.
No,I keep them in the freezer for just such an emergency.
I'll run 'em over to you.
By the way,yowouldn't happen to
have any extra ice laying around,would ya?
No,I've just got some stuff in my freezer
I don't want thawing out anytime soon.
Yes,as a rule,darkness helps us
keep our secrets safely hidden.
Oh,crap!
But every rule...
karen,what's happened?
Are you okay? ...
Has its exceptions.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:Mina Ö¥Ê¿µ°¸â
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Desperate Housewives
Season 03 Episode 19
When the lights went out on wisteria lane,
karen mccluskey wasn't the only reside left in the dark.
Everyone else felt the pain of going without power as well.
Ow! Damn! Thumbtack!
Oh,wait.
Here we go.
But it's hardly a long-term solution.
Well,at least it'll keep me
from stabbing myself while I look.
But this is silly.
Why don't we just borrow a flashlight from mike?
Mike?
He's a plumber. He's bound to have a spare.
Sure,but we can't keep leaning on him for everything.
"Mike,we're drowning. Save us."
"Mike,it's dark. Give us a flashlight."
Let's go ask gaby.
Actually,I wanted to talk to him anyway.
I thought we might ask him over for dinner.
Dinner?
You know,as a-- as a thank you gesture.
Well,ian,you've tasted my cooking.
It's not a thank you.
It's revenge.
well,then I'll cook.
You know,you told me
I should put my jealousy behind me.
I think breaking bread together
would be a great start.
Well,let's not bother him tonight.
You know,
I don't really even need a flashlight.
My eyes have totally adjusted to the dark.
what was that?
Don't walk in the kitchen.
Anyway,where is your sense of romance?
It's a blackout.
You have a defenseless lady.
getting any ideas?
Well,I-I-I'm starting to,yes.
It's funny.
All that time I wasted worrying mike
would come between us--
it seems so laughable now,doesn't it?
Kiss me.
Hey,carlos,we had a blackout.
You need a flashlight?
carlos,you okay?
Oh,uh,sorry,man.
I thought I heard a thud.
I just,um,bumped into a chair.
I didn't think
that you were coming home till tomorrow.
Nah,fish weren't bitin'.
So,uh...
you got a girl in here?
No.
Why?
Oh,'cause when I came home,
I thought I heard sex nois.
No,that was just me.
Okay.
Night.
oh,god,that was close.
All this sneaking around is ridiculous!
mike and I dated foR...five minutes.
He's not gonna care.
What if travers finds out?
look,I don't want him to be confused,
and until we figure out where this is going,
I just...
think we should keep things on the down low.
Hey,I didn't say we had to stop.
- I just said we had to  quiet.
- What?
I suppose we should tiptoe around like schoolchildren
so our parents don't catch us doing it?
I feel like I'm 12 again.
I'm just saying,I don't think
that the whole world needs to know our...
12?
Okay,look...
I will find us another place to rendezvous.
But I'm not gonna skulk around forever.
And no one's asking you to.
I respect you too much for that.
if you don't mind...
oh,for god sake...
I'm gonna be right there.
Here you go.
So can you still cook with the power out?
Of course!
Absolutely!
Please,please,tell me we can still make pizza.
No dice.
Some genius installed pizza ovens with electric starters.
Oh,this is awful.
On a good night,we barely break even.
Tonight is gonna kill the whole week.
Not necessarily.
The stovetop's gas.
I bought pasta for the staff dinner.
You give me ten minutes,
I'll whip up a spaghetti carbonara
that'll knock their socks off.
Oh,my god!
You are a lifesaver!
And,uh,since it's not on the menu,
you can charge whatever you want--
say,20 bucks?
For pasta? Are you crazy?
Won't hurt to ask.
Oh,I don't wanna scare them away.
Okay.
So...
good news!
Our chef is preparing his special spaghetti carbonara.
Ooh,yummy!
And we're offering that for $12.
Great!
For the appetizer portion.
The entrée is $20.
Fine.
2. 22.
Okay.
shouldn't there be an emergency light?
sometimes in these elevators there's A...
ta-da!
Well,aren't you clever?
I'll just call hotel security
and let 'em know we're--
no,wait!
This is the first time
I've had you to myself all night.
I'm sorry.
It's those fund-raisers.
Everybody wants a piece of the candidate.
What are you doing?
Taking my piece.
Are you insane? We're in an elevator.
Exactly.
Going down...
no! come on.
Cut it out.
The power could come on at any moment.
I know.
That's what makes it so exciting--the risk.
But,uh,
I-I'm kind of running for mayor here,remember?
It's an elevator,silly.
It has an emergency stop button.
I don'T.
oh,my god,that's amazing!
What are you doing?
That's my phone.
It's on vibrate.
oh,god!
Oh,man,I was just starting to get into it.
Less talking,more dressing.
you two okay?
Yeah,fine,thanks.
Must've gotten pretty hot in there.
You have no idea.
karen,don't worry about a thing.
I'll collect your mail till you get back.
Well,how long's this blackout supposed to last?
Well,they say it may last for days.
Days?!
Uh...hey,blondie,come here.
Come here.
Hey,listen,
I don't really need to go to the hospital.
I'm fine.
You fractured a rib,
and you might ve a concussion.
You need looking after.
No,some of the stuff in my freezer might melt.
How about I just run out and get some ice
and then meet you at the hospital?
Ma'am,you can replace groceries.
You don't understand.
Some of my groceries-- they--
they have sentimental value.
Sorry.
Yeah,well,I don't need to ask your permission.
Ma'am,no!
Get your hands off me,you big ape!
Get the restraints.
I'm gonna sue your ass!
hey!
Well,what are we waiting for?
Get me to the hospital.
I'm not a well woman.
What was that all about?
Your friend's afraid the stuff
in her freezer is gonna spoil.
Oh,well,thank god the power's back on.
Now she won't have to worry.
I made you waffles!
eat 'em while they're hot.
What?
Will you marry me?
They're just toaster waffles.
Ah,that was just the pre-proposal,actually.
The real one will be much more romantic
with a big diamond the size of a doorknob.
But just so you're prepared,
I do wanna marry you.
Well,just so you're prepared,
consider this my pre-refusal.
Come on. What's wrong?
You're wearing my shirts.
You burn my breakfast.
You're here every night.
It's like wee married already.
We're having a good time.
Why risk ruining it?
See,what happened to the thrill seeker
that seduced me in the elevator?
She wouldn't be afraid of taking a little risk.
Oh,you don't wanna marry her.
She's a tramp.
Hold out for a good girl.
No,no,no.
I've found what I'm looking for.
Come on. What gives?
Look,victor...
getting divorced really kicked my ass.
I'm sorry. Just...
next time I get married,I've gotta be sure.
Okay,I get it.
I just wish there was a way
I could prove how much I love and ore you.
Well,if you canhoke down
that lousy waffle I made you,
that'd be a starT.
oh,there's mike.
Should we see if he's free friday night?
Yeah. Yeah,why not?
Sure.
You know what?
Do you wanna run this ice cream side before it melts?
look,ian is going to come invite you to dinner friday,
and you are not--I repeat--
not going to accept.
Why is ian inviting me to dinner?
He wants to thank you for saving us,
and he wants to show that he's not jealous of you.
How's that for irony?
I didn't plan to kiss you,
but you didn't exactly resist.
I was in shock.
Why were you so upset when you mentioned ian?
Because we had just had a fight...
about you.
Really?
You talk about me a lot?
Mike,I am marrying ian.
We have hired a caterer.
We are going with the salmon,
so just back off!
Hey,ian.
Hi,ian.
I just asked mike.
He can't make it.
Yeah,I'm sorry.
I've got plans tonight.
Oh,but didn't we say friday?
Friday?
Oh,friday I'm wide open.
Splendid!
Shall we say 7:30?
It's a date.
edie!
Mrs. Epstein!
Listen,I'm late for my hadassah meeting.
Here's the key.
Take your time.
Oh,and don't be shy.
Check out those closets.
They're very spacious.
Edie,what are we doing here?
Checking out a house.
I told you,I'm not looking to buy right now.
Well,who's talking about buying anything?
I...
am giving it away.
Edie,we cannot have sex in here.
It's someone else's bed!
That's just wrong!
Look,we can't use my place.
We can't use yours.
But I'll be damned
if I am gonna pay for a hotel room
when there are all of these empty houses
all over town that I have the keys to.
Though reluctant at first,
carlos soon saw the wisdom in edie's plan.
Secret affairs e a lot like real estate.
The three keys to success are...
location...
location.
- careful. I can't sit down that fast.
- Sorry. I'm sorry.
But it's gonna be worth it.
Okay,so tell tom the secret of your risotto.
Well,I saut?spinach and onions in white wine--
no,no,the profit margin.
Uh,basically,it costs a dollar to make--
and we charge $20!
4 people who would've shared a $15
izza are now spending 80 bucks.
Okay,kids,dig in!
- There's just one little problem with that,lynette.
- Yeah?
Those families you're talking about have kids,
and there's no kid that's gonna eat anything
with spinach in it.
Um,tom...
it's delicious,huh?
Mm-hmm! Oh,yeah!
Yeah?
Rick learned how to make this in italy.
Go ahead.
Try it.
I wanna see what you think.
It's good.
It's awesome!
But?
But it's just not us.
Us?
What is us?
Look,we're a neighborhood pizza place.
We serve pizza.
I like this better.
I'm getting bored of pizza.
Porter,the adults are talking.
Look,we serve good food at good prices.
We're not looking to be the next,you know,
trendy flash in the pan.
That's--that's not what I'm looking for either.
Um,see,my food-- it's not trendy.
It's classic.
Rick...
obviously you're a great cook,
and when you have your own place,
I will definitely eat there,
but I see no reason to change my menu.
More,please!
hi!Can I help you?
Uh, yeah, I'm here to see mr. Lang.
He's not here.Is that for him?
Yeah.But it's very persal.
- Okay.
- I don't think I should leave it with the maid.
Do I look like the maid?Give me that!
Victor lang if you want the negatives.I demand 50,000!
do not call the police!I will contact you!
you!Blackmailer!
Oh, man, you weren't supposed tlook!
Get off of me!
Ow!No!
$50,000?Are you insane?!
No, that's not for you to decide!
I want all the negatives of those photos, or I start breaking fingers!
No, you can't break my fingers!
Come on!Aah!
give me the pictures!
hey, hey, hey, hey!Hey, break it up!Break it up!Come on!Come on!
She's crazy!She's crazy!
That's for calling me a maid!
he works the hotel security monitors.
That's how he got the photos.
That miserable cockroach.
Well, if you wanna smack him around a little, I can go inside and turn up the radio.
Again, no, thank you, but I will need those photos.
Oh, no, no, I'm gonna hang on to these.
They're a little revealing.
Ma'am, we can't charge him without evidence, and if he walks,
he can do what he wants with the originals.
Okay...yeah.
But guard them with your life.
Yeah, especially that one.
we've been open for three months now, and we've barely turned a profit!
we are building a customer base!That takes time!
Go on, ask her.
No, you ask her!
why are you being so stubborn?
And you would rather see the restaurant fail than succeed with rick's idea!
And I can't believe that you two are ready to toss out my concept.
You know, why don't you just rename the restaurant "lynette and rick's"?
- Can we have fudgsicles?
- no!
Sorry, lynette, but the menu is not changing.End of discussion.
I don't think so.
I'm giving it a try.
That's not your decision to make.
yeah?Well, then why don't you come down to the restaurant and stop me?
Oh, that's right.You can'T.
I told you she'd say no.
ms.Mccluskey always has some fudgsicles.
Yeah, but she's in the hospital.
where's the ice cream?
She didn't have any.
oh, man!
- There wasn't anything good in there?
- No.
Lang sexcapade caught on tape!
what the hell were you thinking?
How was I supposed to know the cops were gonna release the photos to the press?
Everybody in town knows the police chief is the mayor's brother-in-law--everyone!
Enough, jerome!
I want you to organize a press conference, and then I want you to help me prep for it.
Well, this is gonna be a bloodbath.I don't know how you're gonna prep.
Just get me a bucket of piranhas, and I'll stick my head in it.
you know, you're a single guy.Maybe people won't care.
I'm running a family values campaign, and I had sex in an elevator.
I think they will care.
look, I know this is my fault, so if you wanna bite my head off, go ahead.
You know, gaby, there are only two things that matter to me these days-- my campaign and you.
And if I had to lose one of them, I'd rather it was the campaign.
Is there anything I can do?
Uh, yeah, you can stick around on election night.
I have a feeling I'm gonna need some serus consoling.
Mmm!God, that is so good!
I know.It's hard to decide, huh?
No.No, I'm gonna go with the crab cakes and the little quesadillas.
Well, all we need is a wedding cake, and we're done.
You are the most decisive bride I've ever met.
I just guess I'm in a rush.
Oh?Oh, gotcha.
Well, don't worry.You are not showing at all.
Oh, no, no, no.No, I'm not pregnant.
No, I just know know what I want, which is ian.
So I'm just eager to...you know, no- not get it over with, per se, but just to...
get to the good part, which is the marriage...to ian.
Seems like a great guy.
I don't suppose he has a brother.
Oh, so you're not seeing anyone?
No, I'm between disappointments.
Well, are you free for dinner tomorrow?
Is this some lame setup?
Please say yes.
Well, there's this guy coming to dinner, and he is single and handsome and charming and...
you had me at "guy.¡±
So how do you knowim?
Oh, uh...he's just a neighbor.
- Hey, buddy, whatcha doing?
- Nothing.
You seem a little mopey lately.Is everything okay?
Yeah.
Can we go see mrs. Mccluskey?
You guys didn't have to come down here.
No matter what that C.A.T.Scan says, I'm breaking out tomorrow.
Well, parker really wanted to come vit you.
I'm gonna put a little water in these.
Don't tell your brothers.you were always my favorite.
I saw the man in your freezer.
- lynette!
- Yeah?
Could you run down to the snack bar and get me some green jell-o?
Oh, sure!
Okay, time for a little grown-up talk.
So can you understand now why I had to do what I did?
And how you can never tell anyone, not even your mom?
Hey, they didn't have jell-o, so I hope pudding is okay.
Uh...yeah, let's-- let's give it to parker.
A good boy like him deserves a treat.
what are you thinking about?
Just...this room doesn't really work.
It's just too sterile.
Can we go back to that spanish colonial on 3rd?
Sure.Fine.
You know what i was thinking?
I'm really happy, and I haven't felt this happy in a long time.
How about you?
Are you happy?
Oh, my god!
Oops, sorry.Bed's not made.
- Russell!
- Why don't you check out the subzero in the kitchen?
It's to die.
Well, I see you can't close a sale without opening something else.
Oh, please, I heard about your open house on holly drive.
They're still disinfecting the jacuzzi.
- Slut.
- Bitch.
you thk he's gonna tell anyone?
He's a gay realtor.He's speed-dialing as we speak.
Then go stop him.
What's the big deal?
Who cares if people find out?
- I do.
- Why?
Are you embarrassed to be dating me?
No!it'S...you know, if gaby finds out, she's gonna hit the ceiling.
Oh, why would she care?She's dating that victor guy.
Please, that's not gonna last.
Oh, my god.
You're still in love with her.
No, I just...look, I mean, we've been getting along, and don't wanna...
I don't know who the bigger moron is-- you or me.
Hey, don't be like this.
Look, we're having fun, right?
Apparently that's all we're having.
Edie, come on!
No, fun's over.
Ah, mike.Thanks for coming.
Thanks for asking me.
Susan.
- hi.
- Um, mike,
I want you to meet maggie gilroy.
I don't believe this.
You're setting me up?
You need to move on, okay?
I don't wanna move on.
I came here to see you.
Well, I'm not available, so if you feel like kissing someone tonight,
point those lips at maggie.
Here we go--your beer.
Did I mention that maggie is an amazing chef?
We're embarrassed to be cooking for her.
Stop.
So, um, mike, do you have a favorite type of cuisine?
Nah.After three months of prison food, everything tastes good to me.
So you were in prison?
He was totally innocent.
Yeah, a woman was bludgeoned to death, and her blood wound up on my wrench.
Oh, my god.
But he was cleared.All charges dropped.
Here.Eat this.
It's just so awful.
I mean, to go to jail for a crime you didn't commit.
Oh, it was just a few months.
Now my first stretch for manslaughter...
that was brutal.
My worst cellmate was this guy called "stilts.¡±
When they arrested him, they found a bowl full of ears.
ow!I-I think that was meant for you.
Sorry.
So why don't I just go and brew some coffee?
And, uh, I brought a little surprise for dessert-- wedding cakes for you to sample.
Great.
Thanks a lot.Now maggie thinks you're charles manson.
I don't care.I love you.
Don't say that.
It's true.I remember everything now.
When i got run over, I was on my way to propose to you.
- I don't wanna talk about it.
- I do.
What would you have said?
You know what I would have said.It doesn't matter now.
The hell it doesn'T.Susan,
if you can look me in the eye and tell me that when we kissed,
you felt nothing, then I'll just go,
but only if you can say that and really mean it.
Can you?
Who wants wedding cake?
Maggie, these cakes are fantastic.
Great.Well, all you have to do is choose one, and we're done.
Did you notice the themes?
Themes?Yes.
This one is very british-- fondant icing and toffee ganache.
And this is your classic american-- white cake with buttercream frosting.
So which one do you like the best?
Wow.It's kinda hard to decide.
Well, that depends on what you're looking for-- rich and elegant...
or down-to-earth and sweet?
I don't know.
You want to taste 'em again?
No, I know what they taste like.
I'm just torn, okay?
There's no need to get upset.It's--it's just a cake.
It's not just a cake.It's a major decision!
Well, hey, if you like 'em both so much, why don't--why don't you have two cakes?
How would that look?
"Oh, hey, everybody!
Here's my wedding cake.
Oh, and what's that over there?
It's my other wedding cake.¡±
I have to pick, and I will!
So just stop pressuring me, okay?
I'm sorry.
I think I was just having a little sugar rush.
Thanks again, and sorry.
seriously, just put it on hold for just a month or two.
Excuse me.Am I interrupting something?
No.It's nothing.
I think it's time to level with him.
I just told susan I want her back.
Excuse me?
Look, I know it puts a crimp in your plans, and I'm sorry, but I love her.
Well, that's too damn bad, isn't it?Because she doesn't love you.
Really?
She didn't seem to mind when I kissed her.
What?Did he just kiss you?
No.It--it was days ago.
- And you let him?!
- No!He--he pounced.
It was hardly a pounce.
You bastard.We...we had an agreement.
Susan doesn't have to rry you because you won her in a game of cards.
What, he didn't tell you how we played poker for you?
You bet me in a game of poker?
It's not--not how it sounds.
I merely suggested that-- that if I won the hand, then he--he would stop badgering you.
And if he won?
Well, I-I forget the exact terms, but the point is, he lost, as I knew he would.
I never would have wagered you if I didn't have a very good hand.
- Get out!
- Susan, please.
- You heard her.
- You, too.
I've had it with both of you.
You're tugging at me like I'm some kind of wishbone.
- You're just upset.
- No, I am beyond upset.
You two want a decision?Well, here's what I decide.
There will be no kissing, and there will be no wedding, and there will be no damn cake!
what's this?
Uh, pumpkin sage ravioli.
It's a little thank you for taking a chance on me.
are you kidding?I should be thanking you.
We took in 3 grand tight.
Oh, woW.Candles, too?
Yeah, I think we should use 'em all the time.
It softens up the ambience.
So come on.Eat.
Oh.Oh, my god.
If we serve this for tomorrow's special, will will clear 4 grand.
Great.Uh...just be sure to run it by tom.
Why?You know he'll just shoot it down.
I mean, I get it.He's in pain.
He doesn't like being sidelined, but that is no reason to...
you know what?Let's talk about something else.
Yeah, sure.
I mean, unless you'd like to go.You're here so late all the time.
No.No, I like being here.
It beats going home to an empty apartment.
Don't you have any friends to hang out with?
My friends come in two varieties-- the ones I drove away bere I got clean and the ones
I should avoid if I wanna stay clean.
Oh, yeah.I gotcha.
you ever wear your hair down?
What?Yeah, sometimes.why?
It looks really good.
You should do it more often.
Oh, well...thanks.
- This is delicious.
- Thanks.
- Do you want some more wine?
- Sure.
daddy!
The paper has a story about your restaurant.
You're kidding!
Well, come--come here.What does it say?
"When scavo's pizzeria opened its doors, you could almost hear the city groan,
"'just what we need-- another pizza joint.
' But with an updated menu from new chef rick coletti...¡±
is he the man who cooked us that really, really
Yeah, that's the one.
What--what else does it say, honey?
"There's more than just crayons on the table.
"The veal piccata is divine, "and the mushroom risotto is an...
- e-x-q-u--"
- exquisite.
"An exquisite treat.
"Scavo's has been transformed from a mundane family eatery into the area's hottest--"
that's enough, kayla.Daddy's tired.
Okay.
More fallout from lang bang.
Okay, I know you guys like a good scandal, but I think the citizens of fairview
are more interested in the real issues.
mr. Lang, given your 15-point drop in the polls, what do you have to say to your constituents?
Well, I would ask them to, uh, not base their view of me on a single lapse of...
it's not going very well, is it?
You picked up on that, did you?
Who is she, mr. Lang?Give us a name.
No, I will not identify the woman.
What are you hiding?Is she a prostitute?
no!She's not a prostitute.
I'll answer questions one at a time, people.
that does it.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.What are you doing?
Gaby, stop, please.Please, stop.
Excuse me.Excuse me.
Excuse me.I am the woman in the photos!
what are you doing?
Standing by my man.
what's your name?
My name is gabrielle marquez, and I want you to know,
right before those photos were taken, victor asked me to marry him.
what did you say?
I said, "yes.
I would be thrilled to be mrs. Victor lang.¡±
are you gonna get married?
have you set a date?
are you really getting married?
In fact, I was so overcome, that when we were trapped in the elevator,
I seized the moment to...
express my joy.
So this is a love story?
The only reason victor kept it from you was to protect me...
because he's the kind of man who puts a woman's honor before his own,
and that's the kind of man you marry.
That's the kind of man you vote for.
where are you honeymooning?
What's that smell?
ma'am.
Are you karen mccluskey?
That little bastard gave me up, didn't he?
today, at the mayoral candidate's press conference,
a woman identified as gabrielle marquez, a former model,
surprised reporters by announcing her engagement to mr. Lang.
the only reason he didn't tell you was because he was protecting me.
carlos?
I don't know if you've heard...
yeah.I heard.
In a few months, I will be mrs. Victor lang.
I just heard on the radio the power company is still having problems,
and there might be another rolling blackout today.
Do you want me to leave ida's number in case something happens?
I'm sure I'll be fine.
Did you read our review in the paper?
Yep.
Okay.I'm off.
power-- it's the type of thing most people don't think about...
until it's taken away.
Whether it's the political power of the many...
or a lover's influence over just one...
we all want some sort of power in our lives...
if only to give ourselves choices.
Yes, to be without choices, to feel utterly powerless, well...
it's a lot...
like being alone...in the dark.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents