Previously on Desperate Housewives...
Ian's wife Jane
passed away.
Gaby made a new friend.
A "friend" friend,
not a girlfriend.
The finger of guilt...
I think it's a
phone number.
Pointed toward Mike...
They tested my wrench and found
traces of this Monique's blood.
But he still couldn't
remember.
Bree found a bag
of evidence.
We have to
do something.
Not until we put these
back in her house.
Orson had a night...
-What do you want?
-A grandchild.
That he'd soon
rather forget.
You raped my husband.
I could be expecting
right now.
It had been two months
since Mike Delfino
had awakened
from his coma,
and the memories
he had lost
were finally
starting to return.
He could now recall the first
time he saw Wisteria Lane...
And the first time he met
his new neighbors...
And the first time he heard
Susan Mayer laugh.
But the memory he most wanted
to reclaim still eluded him.
That's why he had gone
to see a hypnotherapist,
so that he could finally
remember everything.
I thought you'd
never get here.
I'm sorry.
The traffic was terrible.
Sorry about that.
I called my landlord when
the pipe started leaking,
and he recommended you.
I was so flustered, I couldn't
find a piece of paper.
I wrote your number
on my hand.
After you finish the sink, maybe
you could help me wash it off.
Look...
I'm flattered,
but I'm seeing somebody.
Me, too.
But he's married,
and I'm drunk.
Well, your s-trap
is cracked.
I don't have
one with me.
Yeah, well, that water's
just gonna keep seeping,
cause a lot
more damage.
I'll, uh, be back
in an hour.
I'll be waiting.
Ms. Polier?
I've, uh... got that
part for the sink.
Hello?
What happened, Mike?
I almost had it.
I was so close.
Close to what?
When I went back
to Monique's place,
somebody else
was there.
Who?
I don't know.
I couldn't see it.
Yes, there were
still many things
Mike Delfino
couldn't remember...
Then why are
you smiling?
But he'd finally remembered
the most important thing of all.
'Cause now I know
I didn't kill her.
By Tyno, Wisteria Team
Transcript by FRM
Forom.com & DHsubs.free.fr
It was 6:00 in
the morning,
and Bree Hodge was
faced with a dilemma
familiar to countless
housewives.
Should she wake her husband
to discuss recent events
that were weighing
heavily on her mind?
Or should she left him continue
to get the rest he needed?
Bree  made the
obvious choice.
I'm sorry, but you've been
out cold for ten hours,
and we need to talk.
I remember
drinking the scotch
and then Alma
suddenly sitting up.
But after that, nothing.
Oh, dear.
I'm not sure how
to tell you this, but...
After Alma knocked you out,
she assaulted you.
Where?
Sexually.
She had sex with you.
But that's impossible.
Your drink was laced
with pills for...
erectile dysfunction.
But I was dead
to the world.
No, dear, you were
dead to the waist.
I had sex with Alma,
and I wasn't even conscious?
How reminiscent
of our marriage.
Okay, this is no joke.
She raped you,
and your mother helped.
Look, after we get dressed,
we're going to the police.
I can't do that.
Orson,
I know you're
embarrassed,
but what they did to
you was a crime.
No, I can't go
to the police.
Not now, not ever.
Orson, your ex-wife
is a homicidal rapist,
and your mother is
straight out of "I, Claudius."
Why do you refuse
to deal with them?
I think it's time I told you about
the night Monique Polier died.
What do you think
of this one?
Pretty sexy.
Is sexy what you're going for at
the funeral of your boyfriend's wife?
You're right.
I'll keep looking.
Why are you even going?
Won't it be weird?
No, it'll be fine.
Ian wants me there.
Yeah, but it'll be all
of Jane's friends and family,
and you'll be the other woman
who swooped in like some...
Okay, yes,
it'll be weird.
But it's not about me.
This is about
Jane and Ian.
What if I wore
this one?
Then it'll be about Jane,
Ian and your boobs.
I have got to get more
depressing clothes.
Okay, I just need to keep a low
profile through the memorial,
'cause once I get
through this,
Ian can officially introduce
me as his girlfriend,
and we'll finally be a normal,
non-adulterous couple.
What does this one
say to you?
Modest, reserved and definitely not
dating the dead lady's husband.
Sold.
I'm not gonna get you
towels for your birthday.
Let's go to the
jewelry department.
No, Zach, I only accept jewelry
from men I plan on sleeping with.
Well, okay, so where
does that leave me?
You can buy me
that toilet seat cover.
Fine. All right,
we're just friends.
Can I at least take you out
for a birthday dinner?
There will be
no celebration.
I'm turning 31.
I'm a single woman
in her 30s.
I now have to subscribe
to "Cat Fancy."
It's the law.
Age is just a number.
It doesn't mean anything.
It means something to me.
Being  alone at
this age, it's hard,
and  it's only
gonna get harder.
I'm so depressed.
Let me buy
you a car.
No, thanks.
But I do need a, uh,
liquid soap dispenser.
Go.
Hello.
Oh, sorry.
Didn't mean to disturb you.
I was just trying to
see whether or not
this was a regular king
or a California king.
Well, I think
it's a regular.
California kings
are much longer.
Is your... wife
particularly tall?
Oh, I'm, uh,
I'm not married.
Oh. Well, why
don't you try it out?
That's okay. I can
wait till you get off.
Oh, that'll happen a lot faster
if you just hop on board.
I'm sorry?
It was a...
shameless sex joke.
I was flirting with you.
Right!
Sorry, I can be
a little dense.
Can we start over?
No. Moment's gone.
You killed it.
Uh, look, you know,
I'm in a bit of a hurry,
but maybe we can try
this again sometime.
It could happen.
Hey, sorry
I took so long.
Mr. Young?
Oh. You know
my friend Zach?
No, I don't think so.
I'm Luke... Purdue?
I'm on your legal team. I'm taking
point on the Halverson deal.
Yeah, right. Hey.
Again, it was
nice meeting you.
Sir.
That was really weird.
I don't even know the guy,
and he works for me.
Works for me, too.
Bree...
Please don't touch me.
All this time, you've said
you wanted the truth.
That's before
I knew what it was.
You see, that's why I've tried
to protect you from this.
Yeah, but you weren't just
trying to protect me, were you?
What do you
want me to do?
Exonerate Mike.
How could you
stand by and let an
innocent man be
dragged off to prison?
You think I haven't
felt terrible?
And this, after he'd
been in a coma
because some lunatic
ran him over.
He has had
a rough year.
I wanna help Mike.
How do I do that without
implicating myself?
I could go to jail.
I don't care
if you go to jail.
You have done a horrible thing,
and you have to make it right.
I mean it, Orson.
If you don't fix this,
I will.
Well, I guess I'm in
no position to argue.
No, you're not.
Morning, Andrew.
Hey, Orson.
I was just gonna ask if you
guys wanted some coffee.
Yeah. Thanks.
I could use some.
It's gonna be
a long day.
-Thank you.
-Thanks.
Thank you.
Mom!
Dinner is in an hour.
You know the rules.
And so do you.
I know, I know,
but he gave me the face.
You fell for the face.
What are you, a rookie?
Okay, you're right.
Sorry, buddy.
Mom's the boss.
I feel nothing.
Hi, Lynette.
Hey, Tom.
How's the restaurant going?
You ready for
the big opening?
Oh, we're getting there.
Let me give you a coupon.
Free extra topping
on any medium or large.
How nice.
But you know what
would be even nicer?
Hire my nephew
to work for you.
You know, the coupon's
good all week.
Look, I don't know what lies
you've heard about Austin,
but you can't be listening
to vicious gossip.
I heard he got arrested
for beating some guy up.
Okay, that one's
pretty accurate.
Edie, I'm all staffed up.
Come on!
Help me out.
Seriously, ever since
Julie dumped him,
he's been depressed and mopey.
He's driving me crazy.
Please, any crappy
job you got.
Well, I guess I could use
an extra guy in back.
Have him there tomorrow,
8:00 in the morning.
Thank you.
Thank you so, so much.
Uh, Edie, you forgot
your coupon.
Tom, please.
You've checked out my butt enough
times to know that I don't eat pizza.
Zach!
I know. You said you wanted to be
alone for your birthday, but, uh,
that's just dumb, so
I'm gonna take you out.
Oh, that's so sweet,
-but I, uh...
-Don't worry.
It's just gonna be one friend
keeping another friend company.
It's not gonna be a date.
Oh, well, um,
Luke's gonna be here in 20 minutes,
and that kind of will be a date.
Luke?
That's, uh...
my lawyer guy?
Yeah.
That isn't a
problem, is it?
'Cause this is what friends do.
They talk about each other's dates.
No, I'm cool.
Have a great time.
Uh, I'm gonna
get out of your hair.
So you think this
guy's really into you?
Well, he seemed to like me
in the mattress department,
so  here's hoping I like him
the mattress department.
What?
Friends say these things.
Orson.
Oh, well, I'm in luck.
The whole coven's here.
I just stopped by
to say thank you.
Mm... you're welcome.
I bought a pregnancy test,
but it's too soon to take it.
I wasn't talking
about the sex.
Though hats off, mother,
for colluding in my rape.
I think it's great that we can
still surprise each other.
No, I was talking more about
what you did for me and Bree.
What did I do?
Your  little stunt
made her so angry,
she demanded
we go the police.
She forced my hand,
So I told her
everything.
Everything?
That is rather unwise.
I faced my worst fear,
the moment I felt sure would end
my marriage, and guess what?
It didn't.
She forgave you?
Not entirely.
Not yet.
But she'll come around.
The good news is,
the months of dread,
the fear of discovery...
that's all over.
So thank you...
and good-bye.
Wait!
I could be carrying
your child!
I don't care if you've got
the Hodge septuplets in there.
I'm sticking with Bree.
Why must he make
everything so difficult?
Oh, uh, floor's done.
I told you I wanted this floor
to sparkle like your Mom's.
Now does this floor look
"Bree Hodge" clean to you?
Uh... no. It looks "Andrew
Van De Kamp" clean.
But your disappointment
in me is very Bree Hodge.
Okay, just for that, you get
to help me take out the trash.
I know you think
I'm being a hard-ass,
But I'm just looking for a basic
level of professionalism that...
Austin?
What the hell's
going on here?
Just, uh, just talking
to the delivery guy.
Hey, where'd he go?
Are you high?
Only...
Totally.
Austin!
Dude, not smart.
But I have good reason,
and when you hear it,
you're not gonna make
that face anymore.
Julie Mayer dumped me,
and I'm very...
very upset.
Your face is
not changing.
Get your stuff.
Get the hell out of my restaurant.
You're fired. Go on.
Floor's looking pretty
clean right now, isn't it?
You said he'd come
back to me.
You said deep down,
he still loves me.
Well, you heard him
today. He hates me!
You ravished him
against his will.
He's bound to be touchy
in the short run.
I'll handle Orson.
You just worry about the baby.
He  said he
doesn't care.
He says that now,
But he will not abandon
his own flesh and blood.
You're his flesh
and blood.
He put you in a home.
You know, I usually don't
say this to expectant mothers,
but for God sake,
have a scotch.
I should just
call the police.
What?
I know what he did.
If he's never gonna love me,
why should I protect him?
I'd rather see him in jail
than playing house
with tammy tightass.
Knock it off, Alma.
I will make Orson
come around.
I don't believe
you anymore.
She's got her claws in him,
and she's not letting go.
Don't be so sure.
I was looking over
at their house last night,
and I saw
something very...
curious.
What?
You can't see
it down here.
We need to
be up higher.
How can you see anything from here?
There's not even a window.
Gloria?
Gloria?!
Just calm down,
sweetheart.
Gloria, let me out!
Stress isn't good
for the baby.
What are you doing?!
Gloria?!
So how are you
holding up?
Better, now that
you're here.
Oh! No, I wanna, um,
keep a low profile.
But I've kissed
a hundred lips today.
I assure you, it would look
more conspicuous if I didn't.
Okay, that's enough.
Ian, oh,
you must be shattered.
I know I am.
Thanks for coming, Lynn.
You know, Jane used
to kid me about you.
Huh. Did she?
She'd say, "Lynn, if anything
ever happens to me,
I want you to marry Ian."
"You're pushy.
Maybe you can get him
to pick up his socks. "
Listen, um, if you
ever need to talk,
I'm here.
Why don't you stop over some
night for a home-cooked meal?
Oh, that... that's
very kind of you,
but I wouldn't dream
of putting you out.
Well, I won't take
"no" for an answer.
Have you got
my number?
I sure as hell do.
Well, I'm sure I'll find it
in Jane's phone book.
Let me give it to you,
just in case.
Call anytime.
Oops. Watch yourself.
So I was there
on a plumbing job.
It makes complete sense.
I had no reason
to want her dead.
I always thought hypnotherapy
was a bunch of bull, but damn.
This is huge, man.
You didn't kill anyone.
The murderer has to be
this yellow gloves guy.
Yeah, but no matter
how much I concentrate,
I still can't see a face.
Ah, you will.
Look at the progress
that you've made so far.
You're gonna
find this guy,
and then you're gonna
hand his ass over to the cops.
Yeah...
something like that.
Hey, guys.
Well, Ian seems
to be holding up.
It's just a mask.
The man is devastated.
Tomorrow night, I'm gonna swing by
his place to offer him a casserole
and a shoulder to cry on.
Will that shoulder be
wearing a spaghetti strap,
and Chanel no. 5?
You know me so well.
Oh, look at him.
Even in mourning,
the man is scrumptious.
I'm sorry for eavesdropping,
but don't you think your conversation
is a little inappropriate?
I mean, we're here
to grieve, not cruise.
I'm sorry,
and you are...
Susan Mayer.
I'm... a friend
of the family.
Then you know how
lonely Ian's been.
And if I want to do
something about that,
it's no business of yours.
Look, just to save you
the embarrassment,
Ian's seeing someone.
Who?
I'm not at liberty to say.
Under the circumstances,
they'd prefer to keep it quiet.
I don't believe it. If there was
some bimbo in the picture,
I'd have heard about it.
As far as I'm concerned,
he's free meat.
Okay, it's me.
What?
I'm the bimbo.
He's my meat.
All righty.
I just wanted
to clear that up.
And now I'm going to go
find myself a seat with a...
better view.
Here are your W-4s.
Please sign them and get them
back to me as soon as possible.
Also, I'm gonna need a copy,
hi, of your driver's license.
-Austin?
-Yeah?
What are you doing
here? I fired you.
Well, Mr. Scavo gave
me my job back.
Hey!
You hired him back?
Did he tell you he
was stoned on the job?
Yeah, and he knows if he
does again, he's outta here.
-So I wanted...
-Look, I don't know what kind
of hustle you pulled on him,
but it's not gonna work on me.
Lynette.
No, I fired him, and you
are gonna stay fired.
Honey, can I see you
in the back for a sec?
What the hell
are you doing,
Talking to me like that
in front of my staff?
Well, I'm sorry, but you totally
blindsided me out there.
No, I was the one
who was blindsided.
You just went off on me without
hearing what my reasons were.
Well, I'm sorry.
Let's hear them.
What are your reasons for
bringing back Joe Bong hit?
I'll tell ya,
if you drop that tone and
stop making that face.
What is...
This was
a business decision.
In case you
hadn't noticed,
and I hadn't, until the waitresses
pointed it out to me, Austin is hot.
He's gonna bring in every
girl from Fairview high
And half the boys
in the chorus.
What's more,
Edie is gonna include our menu in the
welcome packet she gives to new homeowners.
I'm not sure she'd feel so
generous If we fired her nephew.
Those reasons
working for ya?
Yeah.
I just wish you'd told me
before you rehired him.
I mean, I am the manager.
Right...
But I'm the boss.
Well, kinda.
No, no.
Not "kind of."
Really.
I'm the boss.
You pulling rank on me?
Look, at home,
you get to be in charge,
and you decide how
we discipline the boys,
what car we buy,
everything.
I consult you.
Oh, sure, and if you
disagree, you ignore me.
Look, when I go home,
basically, I check
my balls at the door,
and that's fine.
It works.
But for this to work, when
you walk through that door,
you gotta check yours.
Okay.
Really?
Really.
This place
is your dream, so...
Consider them checked.
Thanks. Now I need you
to do just one more thing.
Whatever you say...
boss.
I don't care if you think
you know what's best!
You don't! I do,
because I'm the boss,
and what I say goes.
Yeah, that's it.
Give it to me.
So when I make a decision,
it stays made!
-You got that, Lynette?
-Yes, sir.
-Okay, that's enough.
-No, just one more.
And if I want your opinion,
I'll ask for it!
But I probably won't,
because I'm the boss!
Are we clear?
Seriously, stop
or I will hurt you.
Okay, I've made my point.
Anybody needs me,
I'll be in the back...
drinking a beer.
This is delicious.
Don't get too full.
You have to leave
room for dessert.
What are we having?
Well, let's just say it's
going to be served upstairs
and involves
whipped cream.
Is it pudding?
No.
Oh! You're flirting.
Okay. Do it again.
I swear I'll get it.
It's okay. Do you
want some coffee?
You bet I want coffee...
nice and hot and...
Just finish your soup,
and we'll get naked.
Sorry to bother you,
Mrs. Solis.
I work with Luke.
Is he available?
Charles?
What are you
doing here?
You forgot to initial some pages
on the Halverson contract.
Can't this wait?
The market's already
open in Tokyo.
Uh, go ahead. I'm gonna
open some more wine.
Mr. Young wants to make sure
you understand that last part.
Do you?
Yeah.
I get it.
So when we
think of Jane,
Let us remember her kind
heart and her loving spirit.
And now if there's someone who'd like to
share a special memory of our dear friend?
I would.
Hi. I'm Lynn Dean.
Jane and I were
sorority sisters.
If she were here, she'd make
me sing our pledge song,
but I think there's already been
enough grief for one day.
Now I know how badly
we've all felt for Ian
during his long,
lonely vigil,
So I'm sure you'll be as
happy as I was to learn
His vigil wasn't quite
so lonely after all.
Oh, dear God.
No, he found a warm,
caring woman
to share his burden...
and so much else.
Some people might find
the fact that she's here today...
inappropriate.
But I think she's a hero.
She dared to brave the scorn of
those who might find her actions
questionable or
even unsavory.
I was gonna ask her to stand,
but I see she already has.
Susan Mayer,
say hello.
Hey.
Guess someone's in a hurry
to get on with the evening.
Yeah.
Well, I should go.
What?
I have a lot more work to do
on that Halverson deal.
Sorry.
But can't it wait
till after dessert?
And by "dessert,"
I mean sex.
You are clear
on that, right?
Painfully,
but my job's at stake here.
I really don't have much of a choice.
Oh, I think you've got
lots of choices.
Here's one of them.
Hello?
What do you think
you're doing?
What?
I gave you an order,
and I expect you to follow it.
Now get out of there.
I'm trying, sir.
It's just that I'm meeting
some resistance to the plan...
we've agreed on.
Okay, she's not letting
you leave? That's fine.
Here's what
I want you to say.
Okay, I'll give
that a shot, sir.
Is that your office?
Yeah, they, uh, they really
need me over there.
Okay. So come back when
you're done. I'll wait up.
I can't.
No, I really can't.
What is with you?!
An hour ago,
you were really into me,
and now you can't
get out fast enough.
Okay. Truth?
I thought I could
do this, but I can't.
I'm just not
attracted to you.
Of course you are!
No. See...
I really only date
women in their 20s.
What?
Sorry.
You're too
old for me.
I still got a lot of kick
for an old broad, don't I?!
Mom?
Mom, are you all right?
Don't move her. She might
have broken something.
Yes, we need an ambulance,
please, at 4354 Wisteria Lane.
My wife's had a bad fall.
Please hurry.
How is this?
Mrs. Hodge was very lucky.
She only suffered
a slight concussion.
If you have any more questions,
the doctor should be back soon.
Thank you.
Thank God.
I was so worried.
Yeah, I'll bet.
What's that
supposed to mean?
I heard you two
yesterday-
All that stuff about you
maybe going to jail.
Well, that's none
of your business.
But if you think I had anything
to do with Bree falling...
I'm not stupid.
I know the cops have been all
over you about that dead woman,
and Mom said for you
to fix it, or she would.
Is this "accident"
how you fixed it?
All right, you're
upset. I get it.
No, no, you don't get it.
There's a reason my Mom put
me out on the street last year.
You've never met that guy.
You've never met bad Andrew.
But hurt my Mom,
and you will.
I love your mother.
I'm gonna do everything
I can to protect her.
Yeah, so am I.
Hi. I'm Bree Hodge's son.
You see that guy
right there?
That's her husband.
Do not under any circumstances
let him be alone with her.
Why?
Because it's his fault
that she's in here.
He's a dangerous guy.
Now I've warned you.
If anything happens
to her, you're liable.
Night, Dad.
Oh, you're home.
I thought you'd still be
out on your date.
Date's over.
What do you want?
Oh, I thought since I can't
take you out for your birthday,
I'd at least leave
you a present.
Don't worry.
It's not expensive.
Ah, Zach!
So how'd your date go?
Is he crazy?
You're not old.
You did not see the look on his
face when I tried to kiss him.
It's like he was
sniffing expired milk.
That's ridiculous.
You're gorgeous,
And you're just gonna
get prettier every year.
Ah, that's so sweet...
But it's a lie.
Every tick of the clock
takes away something.
Zach, what am I gonna do
when I'm not pretty anymore?
That's never
gonna happen.
I'm gonna take
a little nap, okay?
Just for a minute.
Take as long
as you like.
Susan, I've looked
everywhere for you.
I didn't think
to start with the, um...
embalming room.
Yeah. I'll be having
night terrors from now on...
which I deserve.
Look, no one
is judging you.
If anything, they're judging
that dreadful Lynn.
I should be thanking you
for driving her away.
It usually takes a crucifix
and some garlic.
I'm so sorry
I ruined Jane's funeral.
No, you didn't.
Yes, I did.
It's just...
What?
I thought after we got
through this really...
painful day,
things would start
to get better.
I thought I could be
more a part of your world.
Now all your friends and family
are just gonna think of me
as the crazy lady
from Jane's funeral.
Oh, God. Oh, Ian.
Okay, this is not
supposed to be about me.
You should be upstairs...
saying good-bye.
I'm just gonna
hide out here
with the departed
until everybody leaves.
No.
No more hiding.
We have been doing
it far too long.
You have nothing
to be ashamed of.
You helped me through the
most difficult part of my life.
I love you, and I want to spend
the rest of my life with you.
I want to marry you.
Ian, are you
proposing to me?
Well...
I guess maybe I... I am.
Before you say
another word...
Take a look around.
Ah. Right.
I hadn't really thought a lot
about this moment,
but when I did...
the table we were at
didn't have a blood gutter.
Then may I reopen the subject at
a more opportune time and place?
Yes.
I accept your
proposal to propose.
Shall we?
Now I want you
to dig deep.
If you feel your
memory blocked,
just count to three,
and the block will melt away.
It is natural and easy
for you to recall anything.
Now remember
Monique Polier.
Remember the night
you met her.
Ms. Polier?
I've, uh... got that
part for the sink.
Hello?
Sorry.
Monique's upstairs
taking a nap.
She wasn't feeling well.
Mike? Did you
see something?
I'm her boyfriend.
I, uh, figured she'd want to
wake up to a clean kitchen.
Well, I'll just finish up with the
sink and be out of your hair.
Why don't you let me
take care of the sink?
I mean, I'm pretty handy,
and it's getting late.
I don't mind staying.
No, look, it's okay.
I got it under control.
Here.
Well, this should cover
what we owe you.
Tell Ms. Polier
I hope she feels better.
Will do.
Oh, hey...
Don't forget
your wrench.
Mike? Where
are you going?
Mike!
Hey, Mr. Delfino.
I need to talk
to your stepdad.
Orson's not here. He went
to the hospital with my Mom.
She's fine!
Thanks for asking!
Mr. Hodge?
You're wife's just sleeping.
I suggest you go home
and do the same.
I will.
You're okay?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm fine.
It's just, uh...
There was a time where
we were all so happy.
I just don't seem to
remember it anymore.
Recapturing the past
is a tricky business.
While most memories are just
memories of a happier time...
Hey, there.
Others can be
quite deadly.
Hey, Mike.
What brings you
to the hospital?
I've been seeing
an hypnotherapist.
She's helping me fill the
gaps of my memory.
How is it going?
It's working.