Previously on Desperate Housewives...
Nora looked for
trouble and found it...
You will never again
see my husband.
Julie got to know
Edie's nephew...
She couldn't take
her eyes off my abs.
I felt violated.
Susan and Ian made plans...
I'd love to go to
France someday.
Would you like to
go next month?
Gabrielle and Carlos reunited...
It's been a long time.
And dinner with the Bigsbys...
That's the police report that
Alma filed after Orson hit her.
Was full of surprises.
Look, I'm going
through something.
I had an affair.
FRIDAY
It was supposed to be an
ordinary day for Carolyn Bigsby.
She had planned to bake
her husband a strudel,
give her dog a bath
and water her african violets.
Yes, Carolyn had planned to do all
sorts of things she thought mattered.
But earlier that day,
a woman who wasn't her friend
told Carolyn something she
wasn't supposed to hear.
From that moment
on, Carolyn felt...
nothing really
mattered anymore.
Hello, Carolyn.
Yeah, hey, how are you?
Carolyn?
What are you doing here?
I've been thinking, Harvey, that if you
loved this Monique woman so much,
maybe you should be with her.
For God sakes,
Carolyn, she's dead.
Yeah, I know.
Yes, Carolyn Bigsby had planned
on it being an ordinary day...
Harvey!
You come out of there, damn it!
But as every housewife knows...
Down. Nobody goes anywhere.
Plans change.
THE NIGHT BEFORE
She dreamt of the last
time she saw me...
and of the last
time we spoke.
Hey!
Mary Alice, are you okay?
Yes, thank you.
I'm fine.
Okay. See you later.
It was still hard for
Lynette to accept
that this unremarkable
exchange had been our last.
Or that moments later,
I would enter my house,
and put a bullet
through my brain.
FRIDAY MORNING
I had the Mary Alice
dream again last night.
Oh, hon, again?
I haven't had it for months.
I don't know why it came back.
Well, somebody just bought her old
house. Maybe that triggered something.
It was awful, as always.
I saw she was in pain,
and I just walked away and...
There was nothing you could do.
And that's what I did, nothing.
Hey, is that the new neighbor?
-Oh, he's cute!
-Edie said he's a bachelor...
Keep talking.
Who lives with his invalid sister.
You can stop now.
Should we go introduce ourselves?
Yeah, let's give him the
scoop on the neighborhood.
Do you think he knows Mary Alice
shot herself in his living room?
Then again, he probably
wants some time to unpack.
Orson?
If you have a moment, there's
something I'd like your thoughts on.
Certainly.
What is it?
The menu for our
holiday open house?
No, it's the police report from the
night you beat your first wife.
I'm still working on the menu.
I assure you,
I did not beat my wife.
She suffered these
injuries in a fall.
Oh, how did she fall?
I pushed her.
It was self-defense.
She attacked me.
Why would she attack you?
She spilled some red
wine on a white tablecloth.
She was trying to clean
it up with dish soap.
When I pointed out her mistake, she
started screaming, "Shut up, shut up!"
And striking me repeatedly
with a sauté pan.
Well, look...
The police dropped the charges.
Where did you get this?
Carolyn.
Well, of course.
Who else?
If she paid this much attention
to her own marriage, maybe
Harvey wouldn't
have cheated on her.
Harvey cheated?
Yes, with some flight
attendant named Monique.
Darling, I could never
strike a woman.
Well, you do believe
me, don't you?
All right, I accept
your explanation.
I just wish there were fewer
things for you to explain.
By the way, to remove a red wine
stain, you sprinkle salt to absorb it.
That's  just what I was saying
to Alma when she clocked me.
Whoa, what fresh hell is this?
-Hey,  Tom...
-Whoa!
Whoa, whoa!
You have stepped onto my property,
and you've talked to Tom.
That's two rules you've broken, and
I'm not sure that top doesn't make three.
Would you tell your lunatic
wife I'm not talking to her?
You're the lunatic if you think
I'm letting you anywhere
-near my husband.
-Just drop Kayla off and go.
Kayla won't be visiting today.
We're moving.
And here's where you can
send the child support.
Mexico?
An old friend of mine got me a sweet
job dancing at a nightclub in Tijuana.
Great, and you're taking Kayla?
Thank your wife.
She's been itching to get rid
of us ever since we got here.
She finally got her way.
Wave bye-bye to your Daddy, honey.
Nora, can't... can't we
just talk about this?
Oh, we're not allowed to talk.
Remember?
She's Tom's daughter. You can't
just take her out of the country.
Watch me.
Does either party have anything to add before
I rulon the division of assets and alimony?
No, we're confident that your
ruling will reflect the pain and
suffering endured by my client.
Your honor, does the definition of
"suffering" encompass the seduction
of my client four days ago?
Excuse me?
She thought he was coming into some
money and hoped to stall the divorce
until she could claim her share.
How dare you!
That is a vicious lie.
Oh, Carlos, give it to me!
Carlos! Yes! Yes!
Carlos...
You recorded our lovemaking?
It's all right here, your honor.
When she climaxes, she actually
starts screaming out dollar amounts.
Mrs. Solis...
Would you like to respond?
As a matter of fact,
I do have a few thoughts.
Carlos, you're a dead man!
Do you hear me?
Oh, the ruling seems fair
to me. You get the house.
I just get everything in it.
I said dead!
No alimony.
That's a drag.
But, hey, you like
to work, right?
Come on, just give me one clean shot
at him. I'm willing to do the time!
Mom, I was packing your suitcase,
and you're totally out of toothpaste.
Do you want me to go to
the store and get some?
What is this?
Oh, um, it was Austin's, okay?
Edie's nephew? Since when
are you friends with him?
Uh, we are not friends. I was
tutoring him, he brought beer,
I told him to throw it out,
and he did. End of story.
Did you have any?
Oh, I cannot believe your timing.
I'm about to fly off to Paris, and you're
inviting boys over for oktoberfest.
Oh, that's it! Go to your room and finish
packing. This conversation's over.
The last time I checked,
I was the parent.
Yeah, well, the last time I checked,
I was the daughter who never gave
you any reason to doubt her.
-Okay, I know I...
-And don't play the parent card with me.
I just finished packing your suitcase, doing
your laundry and balancing your checkbook.
And now I'm going to the
store to buy your toothpaste.
Well, a simple "No, I didn't
drink any beer" would've sufficed.
Bree!
You haven't returned any of my calls.
I've been worried.
Have you told the wife-beater
you're leaving him yet?
Sorry, no.
Turns out he has an explanation
for the police report.
Oh, come on. There's never
a good reason for hitting a woman.
I used to think that, too.
Then I met you.
Good day.
I'm trying to help you.
You're living in a fool's paradise.
Well, I guess that
makes us neighbors.
What's that supposed to mean?
It means you should stop worrying about my
marriage and start worrying about your own.
don't play coy with me.
You've got something
to say, then just say it.
Okay. Does the name Monique
mean anything to you?
Hey, I found this site that offers
really cheap fares to Tijuana,
but should I even be thinking
of going to Tijuana?
It's fine with me...
Soon as you figure out a way
to leave your genitals here.
What are you saying, Lynette? I'm not
allowed to visit my daughter? What?
See? This is exactly
what she wants.
She takes Kayla,
and I get blamed.
Well, screw her.
Let's sue for custody.
Full custody?
You'd go for that?
You bet I woul'd.
Kayla will be much better off
without Crazy in her life.
So will we.
I am right there with you.
I just... I never thought
you'd want a fifth kid.
I don't, but I didn't want the first four,
and they're starting to grow on me.
Hey,  look whose plastic
handcuffs got taken off.
Okay, you' clearly still a little
miffed about the settlement.
But come on, be fair.
I did buy most of the stuff
in this house, honey.
What the hell are you doing?!
Oh, I'm helping you pack.
Think  of all the money you're
gonna save on bubble wrap.
Do you know how
much that was worth?!
much I was worth?!
When we met, I was
on the coverf magazines.
I had a career and a future,
but I gave it all up for you,
and what did I get in return?
If you break one more
thing, so help me...
What? What are you gonna do?
Carlos, have you lost your mind?!
Well, you're helping
me pack my stuff.
I'm helping you
remodel your house.
You know, I don't
know about you,
but I always thought there should
be a window that was right there.
We can stop this right now,
or we can keep on playing.
Your call.
Toothpaste, mouthwash...
Did somebody get an anonymous e-mail?
Said the boy with the
economy-sized acne cream.
There you go again,
checking out my basket.
Ugh, go away. Do you know how much
trouble your stupid beer can got me in?
Well, then let me make it up
to you. I'll carry your stuff.
Whatever.
Yeah?
Harvey, it's me.
Hey, hon, I'm in the middle
of something here, so, um...
I know about Monique.
Um, could you excuse me a second?
Look, I don't know who you've
been talking to, but, um...
Did you love her?
She was just a friend, and she
disappeared eight months ago.
The police just found her body.
Eight months ago. That's right when
you fell into that big depression.
And I kept thinking,
"Why is Harvey so blue?
How do I cheer him up?"
That was about her, wasn't it?
It's over.
She's dead.
But if she weren't,
who would you be
with, me or her?
She's dead.
That'll be $12.99.
I'll take your fields card.
Couldn't keep your
wallet in your pants?
Mr. Bigsby?
Look, um...
I gotta go.
Mommy, look at us!
I'll look as soon as I get
back from the store.
Bye, mom!
This is Edie.
Yeah, I'm his aunt.
He shoplifted what?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Be right there.
You're still packing?
We're going to be late.
Nope, we're fine. Besides, I can't leave
until Julie gets back with my toothpaste.
Oh, we don't need it. I packed
a large tube and some dental floss.
Really?
why are americans so amazed
when the english display the slightest
acquaintance with dental hygiene?
Okay, I'm gonna need some
help with this big baby.
Go! Zip, zip, zip!
Uh, Susan, do you really need all this?
I mean, we're not emigrating.
It's my first time in Paris.
I want it to be magical,
and that means
accessories, so back off.
It's the fashion capital of the world.
Uh, while I'm working, you can take
my credit card and buy some new things.
No, no, I am not gonna
spend your money.
I have an expense account.
And you just tell me this now?
I'll tell the driver
you'll be a minute.
Hello?
Yes, this is her mother.
What?
Well,  you're gonna
love the neighborhood.
Are you all moved in?
Uh, pretty much. Just waiting on
some medical equipment for my sister.
Oh, yeah, I heard she isn't well.
Can I ask what's wrong with her?
Oh, of course. Unfortunately,
she has this rare degenerative...
Oh, that's rough.
Excuse me.
You told me you weren't even friends with
him. Now you're shoplifting together?
-Mom, you know I wouldn't steal.
-Yeah, I wanna believe that,
but suddenly you're having
boys over, you're drinking beer...
And soon she'll be listening to that rock
'n' roll music everybody's talking about.
So how are we gonna handle this?
Listen, I have somebody in
the car who's late for a plane.
-Can you give me two minutes?
-Mom...
I am so disappointed in you.
Hello, Carolyn.
Yeah, hey, how are you?
Look, make him work it off.
You get a free stock boy for a month.
A month?
It was a $10 bottle of whiskey.
Exactly. You weren't even smart
enough to steal the good stuff.
Harvey, don't walk away.
Come on.
Let's sort this out.
Hey, Nora.
How's tricks?
I thought it was your
car I saw in the lot.
You're a conniving bitch.
Ah, I see you've
heard from our lawyer.
So it's not enough that
you run me out of town.
You gotta steal my damn kid.
Carolyn, what are
you doing here?
I've been thinking, Harvey, that if you
loved this Monique woman so much...
Even you have to admit
Kayla would be better off
with us than in a dingy apartment
over a Tijuana strip club.
Believe me, Lynette, you
do not wanna screw with me.
You went after my husband.
If anyone should be afraid, it's you.
Go!
Harvey!
Harvey, you come
out of there, damn it!
Down.
Everybody down.
Nobody goes anywhere.
Don't move.
Get down.
You can't be serious.
We have tickets.
The plane leaves in two hours.
I'm sorry. I know, Julie
picked a lousy time to rebel.
I just can't fly off
and ignore it.
You're overreacting.
It's an adolescent prank,
and you're turning it into
some great bloody crisis.
You have a lot of
meetings anyway.
Wel go some other time.
I can't leave Julie right now.
We'll take her with us.
Oh, that's responsible parenting.
Stealing whiskey?
"That's it, young lady.
I'm taking you to Paris."
Ah, ah, but that's just some ruse.
Once  we get her on the plane, we'll make
her fly coach-middle seat, no mercy.
I'm sorry.
It won't be Paris without you.
What the hell's going on?
It's Mrs. Bigsby.
She has a gun.
What?
I said nobody move!
She's at the back.
I think we can make it.
Hey!
Attention, shoppers, wee having
a special today on not getting shot,
but it's only available
at the back of the store!
Hey, how are ya?
Thanks for joining us.
Do I know you?
My son Jordan's in your
Sunday school class.
Oh, he's a great little boy,
so don't do anything that'll make him
wake up tomorrow without a Mommy.
Um, for the rest of
you, hi, I'm Carolyn.
I'm sorry for putting
a crimp in your day,
but I'm pretty sure that my cheating husband
is in re right now phoning the police,
so I'm counting on all you folks
to help me keep them oside till
Harvey and I have a chance to...
talk things over.
Harvey!
You're inconveniencing your customers.
Get out here!
Yeah, she's got hostages!
Oh, my God.
Austin's there, and Julie!
Get your ass out there
before someone gets hurt!
What am I, a moron?
She'll shoot me.
She has got ten innocent
people out there.
Sometimes you've got
to take one for the team.
Sweetie, it's Mommy.
I need to talk to Daddy.
Porter's hogging all the legos.
Tell him I said to share.
Now put Daddy on.
I did tell them,
but he says he needs
them all for his robot.
Put Daddy on, and
I'll buy you a real robot.
You will?
A big one with laser beam
eyes. Now go get Daddy!
I'm getting a real robot!
A real robot?
Come on, that's not fair.
I'm having a real bad day here.
Is a little cooperation
too much to ask?
Lynette?
It's terrible. Terrible.
Excuse me, what's going...
what's going on?
Crazy woman with
a gun in there!
No, no, no! Stay back!
Carolyn! Open up!
My daughter's inside!
Sorry, store's closed.
Yeah, but there's a crazy
woman in there!
Yeah, I know.
Quick, turn on the TV.
It's kinda on the fritz.
Well, turn on your radio.
If only you'd come
ten minutes earlier.
Some woman is shooting up
fields market. She's got hostages.
Oh, my God!
Yeah, we're all watching it
over at Bree's house, and...
Uh, is everything okay here?
Yeah, everything's fine.
Having a little squabble.
Give us a minute.
Carlos, where do you think
you're going with that?!
Information is very
thin at this time.
We do not see anybody in the front
of the building at this hour but...
Coffee's almost ready, and if
you'd prefer to watch the coverage
on channel 9, it's on in the den.
Orson, Greta needs a coaster.
Bree, have you heard?
Oh, it's just awful. Deviled egg?
Oh, thank you.
I told you she'd have food.
I'm sure some of you might be
thinking that this is all my fault,
and that I'm the bad guy
here, but I'm not. He is.
Will you people stop calling me?
I'm right in the middle of something.
He humiliated me.
First he cheated on me with
a stewardess named Monique.
How cliché is that?
And then he told people about it.
Now there are news
trucks out there.
Judy Pope's husband has
an affair, nobody finds out.
Mine cheats, and they
break into programming!
The whole town is laughing at me!
You hear that, Harvey?
I only told one person.
Well, it was clearly the wrong one.
I told you to stop calling me-
Tish, I'm sorry. I thought
it was somebody else.
Oh, my God, was that
today? I'm so sorry.
I know, Tish.
Yeah, I know.
I know I volunteered
for the winter fair...
How can you look so calm?
Aren't you scared?
No, because I'm not
gonna die today...
and neither are you.
Tish, I really don't
think that I can.
I'm telling you, um...
Oh, Tish, for God sakes,
turn on your damn TV!
Excuse me,
my name is Susan Mayer.
Ma'am, this is a restricted area.
I would like to trade places
with one of the people inside.
Don't... don't you do that?
Oh, you mean our hostage
exchange program?
Okay, you don't have to be nasty.
My daughter is inside there.
Ma'am, we're doing everything
we can to get her out safely.
Now please step back.
I want the perimeter locked down.
Nobody goes in, nobody goes out,
and see if you can get me an open
phone line with the manager's office.
Attention! Attention, Carolyn Bigsby!
Where's that coming from?
This is Susan Mayer... again.
First of all, I'm sorry for
the "crazy lady" remark.
Second, I have a proposition for you.
Find her now!
Let Julie go and take me instead.
Repeat, take me.
I will be a model hostage.
If we have a deal,
signal by sending Julie to the...
No, take your hands off me!
Carolyn, Carolyn!
Call my cell! It's 572...
Now we don't know where anyone
is inside the building right now,
but we are standing by,
waiting for information.
I'm hoping to talk to the chief of
police in just a couple of minutes,
get a few more details...
Andrew, honey, would
you please get the phone?
Police have just released the
name of the hostage taker.
It's Carolyn Bigsby, wife of
store owner Harvey Bigsby.
Harvey has informed police that
he is barricaded inside the store...
Oh, my God, Bree, don't you ow her?
Uh, yes, um...
I just... ran into
her this morning.
Uh, mom?
That was Edie Britt on the phone.
She's inside the market.
Is she all right?
Yeah, uh, she's locked
inside the manager's office,
but she said that Julie Mayer and
Mrs. Scavo are with the hostages.
Bree, would you mind watching the kids?
I've got a doctor's appointment,
and Lynette is taking her
sweet time at the market.
I'm sorry. Are you guys having a party?
we continue to report live on
the scene as the hostage standoff
at fields market enters its third hour.
According to a police spokesman,
there has been no further
contact from the hostage taker.
We continue to wait for
the latest information.
No new news at this point.
We will bring you the latest as
soon as it becomes available.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
I just, I'm running out of food, and it's
not as if I can go to the ocery store.
Bree...
Thank God I found this stale
baguette so I can make bruschetta,
and there's shrimp in the freezer,
so I'm gonna make my
rice and seafood dish.
Bree, this is not your fault.
I had toell her.
She hurt me,
so I hurt her back.
If anything should happen
to Julie or Lynette...
Is there anything I can do?
You can peel a clove of garlic.
Okay.
I wanted kids.
I wanted kids so badly but
Harvey had two
from his first wife.
He said it made her fat.
Harvey likes them lean.
I run four miles a day.
This is my first
cookie in six years.
You hear that, Harvey?
I'm breaking my diet!
She's starting to lose it
out there. What do I do?
Just keep her calm,
tell her you're sorry,
and see if you can get her to
release the kids and old people.
Okay, I'll try.
Carolyn...
Honey, uh, it's me, Harvey.
Look, I'really sorry.
What I did was wrong,
but I still love you a lot.
Cut the crap.
I had my hair done this
morning. Did you notice?
-Did you even notice?
-Well, I was distracted.
You were shooting at me.
Tell her let the kids go.
Who the hell was that?!
You got a woman in there?
She's a customer!
Don't lie to me, Harvey!
She's another one of
your whores, isn't she?
Oh, fantastic!
Carolyn, I swear...
shut up.
I hope you're having a good
time in there, whore,
'cause I got a bullet for you, too.
God, what a nightmare.
You know what the weird part is?
What?
I keep thinking about that
crazy lady in the market, and...
I understand her.
I could be her.
Come on.
No, I mean it.
The rage that I have felt
in these past six months...
If I had had a gun in
the courthouse today...
you could never shoot me.
I don't know what
I'm capable of anymore.
This divorce has
turned me into this...
bitter, hateful person,
and I don't like her.
Hey, baby.
And for what it's worth, I don't like
what it's turned you into either.
Then let's stop
being those people.
Okay.
Hey, just so you know...
I heard the woman in there
teaches Sunday school.
A Sunday school teacher
would never hurt a kid.
No way.
Thank you.
I'm sure Lynette's
gonna be fine, too.
Oh, I'm not worried
about Lynette.
Hell, with Lynette in there,
they don't even need that negotiator.
You put Lynette in a room with a woman
who wants to shoot her husband,
she'll have them renewing their vows.
Right.
Lynette is very persuasive.
I give it an hour, tops.
Then we'll all be back home
eating our hamburgers.
She was gonna go to
the store tomorrow,
but we were out of hamburger.
I wanted hamburgers.
I hope all this is giving you
a little perspective on our situation.
Shh! She told us not to talk.
You're thinking about
your kids, right?
How awful it'd be to
never see them again.
Well, that's what you're asking me
to feel, but for the rest of my life!
Nora, please!
Hey, what'd I say?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
We'll... we'll be quiet.
You and your friend are
really startinto bug me.
She's not my friend.
-She's trying to steal my kid.
-Nora, shut up!
Is that true?
No! I... we're...
We have... We're sharing
custody, and then,
she tried to
seduce my husband, so...
She put the moves
on your husband?
Why didn't you say so?
That was a shot! We just heard
a shot fired inside the building.
A shot has been fired.
I believe the phrase you're
looking for is "thank you".
We just had a shot. We heard a
shot fired inside the market.
You can see police are responding,
taking this very seriously.
We are going to just continue to stand
and watch and wait and see what happens.
It was on television at the airport.
I came as soon as I could.
The last thing I said to her
was that she disappointed me.
Police have just confirmed
that a hostage has been shot.
Repeat, a hostage has been shot.
There's no word on the name of the victim
at this time, but it is believed to be female.
Mrs. Hodge?
When's mommy gonna
be back from the store?
I'm sure she'll be back soon.
Why don't we, uh, go have some cookies?
Mommy said we can't have
cookies before dinner.
I'm sure she won't mind. Come on.
Let's go. Come on.
Okay, I gotta keep the pressure
up to stop the bleeding!
Good news is you won't
need that lawyer now.
You are gonna get
through this just fine.
There is a parking lot full
of ambulances out there.
You gotta let us take
her out of here!
No one's leaving.
Listen to me... Lynette...
About Kayla...
Oh, forget it! Forget it!
We'll work that out later.
No...
I don't have... have
later, you stupid bitch.
Okay? So listen.
Okay, I'm listening.
Kayla's the only good thing that
I've ever done in my whole life.
I need you to really take
really good care... of her.
Okay?
I don't have all day. Come on.
Yeah, yes, I will, I will, I will.
I will love her like she
is my own. I will, Nora.
Nora?
Nora!
Oh, don't look at me that way.
You know you wanted her dead.
How can you say that?
Well, you told me about her and
your husband after I made it pretty
clear where I stand on whores.
I did not want this.
Don't you dare say
that I wanted this.
Shut up!
No, I will not shut up!
What's the matter with you?!
Have you not been paying attention?
My husband cheated on me!
Who cares?!
Who cares? We all have pain!
Everyone in here has pain,
but we deal with it!
We swallow it and get
going with our lives!
What we don't do is go
around shooting strangers!
She deserved it!
Well, maybe you deserved
to be cheated on!
I'm.. I'm... I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have said that.
Yeah, you shouldn't have.
By Tyno, Wisteria Team
Transcript by YDY
Forom.com & DHsubs.free.fr
Lynette Scavo had
a dream that night.
It was one she'd had
many times before.
Hey!
Mary alice, are you okay?
Yes, thank you.
I'm fine.
Okay. I'll see you later.
But this night,
something changed.
No, you're not. I can tell.
Please...
Tell me what's wrong.
Let me save you.
You can't.
Why not?
Sweetie, we can't prevent
what we can't predict.
Isn't there anything I can do?
Yes.
You can enjoy this beautiful day.
We get so few of them.
This was the last time Lynette
would ever dream of me,
and for her sake,
I am grateful.