Previously on Desperate Housewives...
It means a lot to her to feel included.
Sometimes dark clouds
have silver linings...
He sort of asked me out.
It's okay with you if
I go out with him?
Sometimes they don't.
Once that baby comes, I'm gonna
be stuck raising a child alone.
When it comes to life
on Wisteria Lane...
Will you marry me?
Things that seem too
good to be true...
Does she know you
killed your wife?
Usually turn out...
Get away from him
now while you can.
To be deadly.
Brides are sensitive creatures,
and no one knows this better than the
bridesmaids who have to deal with them.
Well, I think a 10-foot train is great,
but a shorter one would be just as nice,
and you wouldn't have to worry
about people tripping on it.
Personally, I love smoked rabbit, but for a
sure crowd-pleaser, you can't beat chicken.
Uh, sure, who doesn't
love a string quartet?
But if you got a band, maybe people
could dance, as opposed to sway.
But the one area where a bridesmaid's
tact is most required involves the dress...
So what do you think?
she's required to wear.
Well, um...
I'm not sure that I've ever seen
this shade of green before.
Yeah, don't you think it'll be
gorgeous with my coloring?
Yes, it would look perfect.
For someone with your coloring.
I mean, I was lucky to find these. Not easy
putting a wedding together in two weeks.
Then why the rush?
Yeah, Bree, I'd have thought of you
as a person who wants time to plan.
Well, Orson and I talked about it, and
we just feel at our age, it's silly to wait.
And with your help, I'm sure
we can get it all done.
Well, we are happy to pitch in.
Oh, uh, that reminds me.
I have to get a copy of
the seating chart for you.
Gaby, you are in charge
of the centerpieces.
And don't worry, Susan.
I will thinkf a job for you.
Here's a job.
How about talking you out
of marrying a homicidal dentist?
His wife vanished, and
he didn't even tell Bree.
How much more proof do you need?
He says he's innocent.
She believes him.
If we say we don't, she'll
just end up hating us.
Well, I'm sorry.
I cannot sit here on my key lime ass and
watch Bree make the worst mistake of her life!
And what mistake would that be?
Well...
Honestly...
Yes, a bridesmaid can question
many of the bride's choices.
These dresses are hideous.
But the groom isn't one of them.
By Tyno, Wisteria Team
Transcript by YDY
Forom.com & DHsubs.free.fr
The perfect couple...
We've all met them, haven't we?
That man and woman so
clearly made for each other,
we feel certain they're on
the road to happiness.
But that road has many detours,
and even perfect couples
can find themselves...
at a dead end.
You want what?!
You heard me.
And I want the bedroom stereo.
I want the marble console and
that painting of St. Augustine.
You don't even know who he is.
I know he matches the drapes.
People, can we focus here?
And I want my pearl necklace back.
Don't think I didn't notice
that you swiped it.
That was my Mama's and hers before
her. I think it belongs in my family.
There was a time that you thought I belonged
in your family, and you got over that.
-Stop eating my fries!
-I'm hungry.
You know what the doctor said.
You should see his cholesterol.
This man bleeds baking grease.
Enough!
You two are gonna have to find
a way to deal with each other,
because you are about to
bring a child into this world.
And  divorced or not,
once that child arrives,
you will be bound together
for as long as you live.
Well, in that case...
Have some more fries.
I'll pick Kayla up on Sunday.
Whenever.
Just go. You and Turk
have a great time.
Oh, trust me, we will.
The man is a jackhammer.
Bye, Tom.
See you Sunday!
Where is she going?
She and Turk are going down
to the river for the weekend.
That's Turk? That's
the new boyfriend?
Uh-Uh, no.
Hey, hey, hey, Tom, please.
I don't want my daughter hanging
around with a guy like that.
You haven't even met him.
He could be the sweetest
man in the world.
More importantly, ever since he entered
the picture, squeaky fromme is never around.
It has been bliss.
I haven't made this face... in a week.
If you ruin this, so help
me, I will hurt you.
Just look at him.
Look at him, please.
I swear, that is a child's skull
hanging from his rearview mirror.
Doesn't that concern you?
No, I'm good.
Could be a monkey.
Uh, I think I will have the...
mesclun salad.
That's it? That's all you're having?
Well, all the food is very expensive.
You don't need to whisper.
The waiter knows
they're robbing us blind.
You can have whatever you want.
In that case, I'll have the lobster bisque
and the veal with the black truffles.
Is that okay?
Yeah, that's fine.
I'll just have jane moved
to the V. A. Hospital.
-Oh, my God.
-I'm kidding.
It's fine.
I'll have what she's having.
Of course.
God, I love seeing you laugh.
Oh,  well, it's been a long time
since I've been in the mood to.
Thank you.
Oh, dear God!
Did I squeeze too hard?
No, it's my wife's parents.
Oh, is this gonna be awkward?
No, no, no, not unless,
of course, they see us.
Ian?
Awkward.
Jeff, Renee, what a delightful surprise.
It's so good to see you, dear.
Hello. I'm Renee, and
this my husband Jeff.
Susan Mayer.
Uh, doctor...
Dr. Susan Mayer. She's new
to Jane's neurology team.
I just assumed you worked
in Ian's publishing house.
Well, yes, and how nice
that would've been, huh?
Um, but, no, no, I'm a...
A brain specialist.
Well, Dr. Mayer, maybe I can ask you,
our daughter's most recent
E.E.G. showed brain spikes,
but it didn't change the
score on the glasgow scale.
Why is that?
What an excellent question.
And this is the, uh... spinal cord.
And it, of course,
attaches to the brain.
You don't have to dumb
it down for us, doctor.
We've been dealing with
Jane's condition for years.
Oh, good.
Um, well, then let's,
let's get technical.
Uh, let's give Dr. Mayer the night off.
She was in surgery for ten hours
today performing a craniotomy.
That's exactly the procedure Jane had.
How'd it go?
Uh, well, it just... Wow!
I hear my, my phone vibrating.
Um, hello, uh, Dr. Mayer.
Yeah, what?
You say that his brain shut off?
Oh, well, I'll be right there.
Um, stat.
I'm sorry.
Duty calls.
Orson?
I moved the furniture back!
Good lord, Bree, not again.
Don't you want our first
dance to be perfect?
There'll be 200 people staring at us.
You know, Bree...
Since that incident at our engagement party,
there's been a lot of dark talk about me.
Well, I don't pay attention to gossip.
I'm just saying I would understand
if you had second thoughts about
marrying a man who's under a cloud.
Well, no one who knows you could seriously
believe that you could hurt a woman.
Strangers may talk,
but I know the truth.
Really?
Men have lied to me before.
Believe me, that'll never happen again.
So you trust me completely?
Clearly, I do.
The body is unusually well-preserved
because it was buried in clay.
Do we have a cause of death?
Blunt  force trauma to the head.
I want you to pull all the missing
persons reports, cross-check against
her height, age and weight.
I'm also running a D.N.A. panel since we
won't be able to use her dental records.
Why not?
Whoever killed her
pulled out all her teeth.
Nora?
What are you doing back?
Are you okay?
Shut the door!
I don't want kayla to find me like this.
What's wrong?
Tuck and I had a fight.
What?
No!
No, no, no!
What happened?
What happened is, Turk is an ass!
On the way to the river, we stoped off
at is bar. Then we were paying pool,
and I got a little bitchy with one of
the waitresses. So who cares, right?
I mean, who cares? It's a bar,
and we all do it, right?
R... Right.
So he tells me to watch my mouth.
And I'm like, whoa!
Get a load a Mr. Two Strikes trying
to tell me how to act in public.
And  then he called me a whore.
We're done.
Okay, whoa!
Take a deep breath.
You don't break up with a guy because in
a weak moment he calls you a whore.
And then on the way out,
he threatened to hit me.
Okay, but he didn't.
-And, you know, until...
-Oh, jeez, Lynette, whose side are you on?!
I'm on the side of love.
You  guys seem like
such a perfect couple.
I know.
I just, I...
You know, you don't wanna throw that all
away 'cause of a little fight with no hitting.
No.
It's over.
I just got off the phone with Turk's
parole officer, and I was like,
"Guess who ain't in Nevada no more"?
Click.
I think I'm gonna have
to stay here tonight.
Freeze!
Austin?
Anyway...
Mom just got backfrom her cruise to Jamaica
with new boobs and a 24-year-old cabin boy.
Needless to say, me and Mr.
"Can I get yousome more hot towels?",
we didn't exactly hit it off.
So after I broke his nose, I figured it was
great time to come visit my favorite Aunt.
Your mom always did
have lousy taste in men.
So, I figured I'd crash here for the night.
Then itch down to Mexico.
Hang out, party.
Yeah, I'm thinking,
like, no way in hell.
You're gonna stay here with me until
things blow over with your mom, okay?
Cool.
Thanks.
Oh, wait, you're 18, right?
Well that's what my I.D. says.
Yeah, mine, too.
You were supposed to be on bed rest.
I'm bored.
Well, why don't you try putting a pair of
pants? That should kill a couple of hours.
Hey, babe.
What is she doing out bed?
That can't be good for her.
Or the stairs.
What do you want?
The mediator was right.
A month from now we're not just
gonna be Carlos and Gaby.
We're gonna be mom and dad, and I don't
wanna be at war with the mother of my child.
So, here.
Your Mama's pearls?
Carlos...
Thank you.
And...?
And what?
Wouldn't you like to make
some reciprocal gesture?
Fine.
You can come to Bree's
wedding reception as my guest.
Thanks.
-Here.
-Here?
You're throwing a... reception?
Yeah, that's our wedding present to Bree.
So I give you a priceless family
heirloom, and in return,
you invite me to a party at
my house that I'm paying for?
Well, what kind of gesture
did you have in mind?
Things I'll do for jewelry.
Susan, I am so sorry.
Dr. Mayer?
Panic.
Pure panic.
Here.
These are for ruining our first date.
Not in front of Mike!
Oh, look, Mike, Ian brought you flowers.
I'll just go put them in some water.
Look, I was just trying
to protect Jane's parents.
Oh, please.
They still haven't accepted the fact
that Jane isn't going to wake up.
If they knew that we were on a date,
that I was trying to move on, well,
it would devastate them.
That a really lovely excuse, but
it isn't the whole story, isn't it?
Excuse me?
A part of you feels that
you're cheating on her.
No. Well, perhaps a small part,
but that doesn't mean...
It's all right, 'cause I feel guilty, too.
That's why we should just stop is right now,
because it's all way too complicated,
And I think we'd both be happier if
we just went back to being friends.
Well, I don't think I can do that.
The truth is, I haven't thought of you
as just a friend for some time now.
Maybe I shouldn't have let
myself feel that way, but I have.
I can't go back, I'm sorry.
Well, if we can't be friends...
Then I guess we'll be nothing.
Hey, leave that alone.
Sorry, I was just...
Turning it down.
What, you're not a music fan?
Sure, it's just, um...
Got anything where a pimp
isn't beating his ho?
I'm Austin, Edie Britt's nephew.
I'm Julie, Susan Mayer's daughter.
Anyway, um, I was trying
to do my homework, so...
On a Saturday?
Well, make sure and take regular
breaks and stop for a sensible dinner.
Just keep it down.
You had it really loud.
That's how I like it.
How do you like it?
You know what?
You're not that hot.
Hey, what are you doing?
Oh, I'm working on a seating chart.
For Bree's wedding.
Nora? Who invited her?
I did.
We need to find her another boyfriend,
and weddings are crawling with single men.
Hey, I hope you're not seating
her next to any of my friends.
Hey, sacrifices must be made, Tom.
No, Jerry Rawlings!
Not Jerry Rawlings!
If she gets her psycho hooks in Jerry
Rawings, he will never speak to me again.
Oh, there are other urologists in the world.
Go back to that other guy.
The one with the cold hands?
Oh, it's once a year. Suck it up.
Get a grip, Lynette.
"Get a grip"?!
I am hanging on for dear life here.
You are the one that brought
this little problem into our family,
And the only thing I should be hearing
from you is, "how can I help"?
I am also putting Stevie Handson at
her table, so you might want to start
shopping around for a new golf buddy.
Get a grip.
Hi.
My name is Susan Mayer.
Your neighbor told me
I could find you here.
Yeah?
Well, I was at my friend Bree's
engagement party the other night.
You know, when you came in and you did
that whole "Orson killed his wife" thing?
I was just wondering
if you could elaborate.
He killed her.
What else do you need to know?
Well, what makes you so sure?
Do you have any proof?
Look, I can't talk now.
-I get off at 6:00.
-My friend is marring that men in two hours.
Please?
Okay, I need $10 in unroled pennies
and I need to see you count it,
'cause last time you sttif me!
After Alma disappeared, the police
came and searched the house.
The police?
-What did they find?
-Nothing.
And that's bad, why?
Don't you get it?
When the police showed up, Orson had scrubbed
every inch of the place clean with blich.
No fingerprints,
no skin cells, no D.N.A.
It was like Alma had never existed.
Who cleans a house like that
unless he has something to hide?
So when I left the bank,
I called the detective
that worked the case,
And he said that the only reason
Orson was never charged was
because they never found the body.
So he was an actual suspect?
-He was the only suspect.
-Oh, my God! What are we gonna do?
Well, you know
what we have to do.
That was close.
The florist put three mums
in my bridal bouquet,
but not to worry.
Crisis averted.
Bree... we have to talk.
Ah, Reverend.
Any word from the bridal party?
They're still in the bride's
room. You know women.
They're probably in there
fussing about mascara and blush.
He did not hack her up and
dissolve the pieces in acid!
I  said it was a theory.
The point is, Alma disappeared under
very suspicious circumstances.
I don't have time for this.
I'm getting married now.
This is your day. You can push
the ceremony back an hour.
Now get that detective
on the phone,
talk things out with Orson.
I can't talk to Orson.
It's bad luck for the groom to see
the bride before the wedding.
You know what's really bad luck?
Marrying a wife-killer.
If the three of you don't
drop this right now,
I will never forgive you.
Bree, we are just doing this
because we love you.
But...
If you can honestly tell us that
you don't have the slightest doubt...
None whatsoever.
Dearly beloved, we are gathered
here together in the sight of God,
-to join this man and woman in holy...
-Excuse me?
Could you give us
just a second?
-Is something wrong?
-I just need a moment.
Before we do this, there's
something I need to ask you.
What?
Did you kill your wife?
Susan talked to that Carolyn woman.
Why didn't you tell me that the
police seached your house.
Because it's embarrassing,
and they didn't find anything.
Is that because you scrubbed
the house so thoroughly?
When I'm upset, I clean.
For God's sake, Bree,
I swear to you
I did not kill my wife.
Okay.
Proceed.
Dearly beloved,
We are gathered here
together in the sight of God,
to join this man and woman
in holy matrimony,
which is an honorable estate...
Hey! Look at you, miss popular!
So are you having
a good time over there?
As if,
And I don't know what idiot
stuck me at that table,
But every guy over there
is just a boring stiff.
All of them?
What about... Jerry?
Jerry's fun.
You mean Mr. Fatty hair plugs?
Oh, yeah, he's a blast.
Um, how about Steve?
You know what?
I hear his family has money.
Well, then maybe they could all chip
in and buy him some deodorant.
I'm through with those losers.
I'm gonna stay
right here with you.
Are you gonna eat that?
Hey, look at you!
God, I hate wearing a tux.
On my way in, Bree's Aunt Fern
asked me to park the car.
She's got glaucoma.
To her, you're nothing
but a hispanic blur.
Let me fix your tie.
Hey, you're wearing
Mama's pearls.
Yeah.
Hey, Julie!
Have you met
my nephew Austin?
Yeah, we've met.
I just didn't recognize
him with his shirt on.
She couldn't take
her eyes off my abs.
I felt violated.
Hi, Edie.
Nice party, huh?
It was.
Perfect.
Well, it's nice to see you
two getting along again.
We've sort of turned a corner. Really?
Does that mean you're gonna
be getting back together?
-Maybe.
-God, no!
Wow, is that shrimp?
What would make you think I would
even consider taking you back?
Well, you invited me
to be your date.
"Guest," Carlos. I said "guest."
Come on, you've been flirting
with me since I came in...
"Here, baby, let me fix your tie."
I mean, for a woman
who's not interested,
you sure are sending
some mixed signals.
You want a clear
signal? How's this?
-Ian!
-Susan!
What are you doing here?
Well, my cousin is Dr.
Hodges' dental hygienist,
and her husband...
He couldn't join us
since he'd come down with
a spot of impetigo, so she called me,
Knowing how much I love
a good garter toss, and so...
Ian.
Yes, I'm such
a terrible liar.
Impetigo, where did
that come from?
So what are you really
doing here?
Look...
I can't stop thinking about us,
about how great
we could be together,
and I think you're making a mistake.
-Ian...
-Susan, please don't go.
Can't we at least
talk about this?
I can't, 'cause I have...
bridesmaid stuff.
HI there.
I just wanted to say
you're doing a great job...
Tad.
That's, um, that's such
a masculine name.
My boyfriend
seems to like it.
Okay, here's the drill.
My ex is here, and I wanna piss him off,
so just act like you're all hot for me,
and there's a 100 buck
tip in it for you.
Right. Uh, so should
I... cup your boob?
No, I'll drive.
Tequila, straight.
Hey, are there any decent
single women athis wedding?
Not that I've seen.
Ah, damn it. Not a one.
Hey, Carlos.
You should come over to our table.
That's where all the hotties are.
Hey, everyone!
I'd say it is time that we get
Bree and Orson up here
for their first dance
as a married couple.
Ladies and gentlemen, I give you
Mr. and Mrs. Orson Hodge!
Orson,
you look so serious.
I'm trying to remember my steps.
You're upset, aren't you?
You're still thinking about
what I said at the church.
Which part, darling?
The "I do" part, or the "did
you kill your wife?" part?
I'm sorry, but I had to ask.
That's my point.
You had to ask.
You are gonna
rot in hell for this.
Hey, I just brought
two lost souls together.
Okay, how about this?
He cheated on my friend.
He deserves every bit of... crazy.
She's gonna rain down on him.
Hell... rot... you.
What are they doing?
Rounding second
and heading for third.
Carlos!
Oh, hey, Gaby.
Look, I made a new friend.
Yes, I've been watching you make
your new friend, and it's disgusting!
Do you mind?
We're trying to dance here.
Who the hell are you, anyway,
and why the hell are
you at this wedding?!
This is not gonna end well.
They're just two random people
who met at a wedding.
Can't pin it on.
It was her!
Lynette Scavo,
I wanna talk to you!
I'll see you at home.
What are you thinking?
I didn't invite you here to embarrass
me in front of my friends.
Oh, no, you just wanted me to watch while
you sucked the zits off some teenage waiter!
That's it. I take my invitation back.
You are no longer welcome
in my house.
Fine, I'll go!
Just give me back the pearls.
-No!
-Gaby...
-Carlos, no!
-They were my Mama's!
No!
Now look what you've done!
Mrs. Solis!
-No, Carlos!
-Hey, give me that!
-Give me those!
-Pardon me. Excuse me.
-Get away! Those are mine!
-No, the hell they are!
Mrs. Solis?
-Not now, Xiao-Mei!
-Mrs. Solis!
Oh, for God sakes, what?!
I think maybe it's time.
And I wish you both
a lifetime of happiness.
That was beautiful,
Aunt Fern. Thank you.
Hey, they mopped up
all the amniotic fluid,
so we should feel safe
start the conga line!
Actually, I'd like to
say a few words.
Bree, Orson,
Your love is an inspiration to us all.
-That's very sweet.
-Hmm.
How do you know him?
I thought he was on your side.
Well, I know, this is a second
wedding for both of you,
and I think you're jolly brave.
So often, people find excuses
not to fall in love again.
They're, they're afraid.
But it's rare to find somebody
that you connect with,
so when you do, you have
to follow your heart.
Bree, Orson,
I salute you.
All right, let's get the
music cranking and the...
Actually, Tom, could you
just hang on a second?
Uh, I also would like
to say a few words.
To Bree and Orson, uh, yes,
what could be better
than a second love?
And this time you enter into it
a little older, little wiser,
but also,
and this is key, uh...
with a bit of caution.
Because...
while love can be
spontaneous and wonderful,
it can also be selfish.
And sometimes,
the best thing you can do
is just to walk away.
Uh... Not you two.
I mean, you two
crazy kids are great.
Congrats, yeah.
Well, then, let's...
Hang on. I'd like
to respond to that toast.
Bree, Orson,
sometimes walking away
can seem the best choice.
It's certainly
the safest. But...
But what do you do when you find
someone who makes you feel joy,
when you thought you
never would again?
Do you, do you just let them go?
No.
No, I can't do that.
You, you wanna...
No.
I'm good.
All right then, let's dance!
Well, I thought you might
need a change of clothes.
You're still mad at me, huh?
What were you thinking,
setting Carlos up with skank?!
I'm sorry.
I was desperate.
I had a little too much to drink.
And you are divorcing Carlos...
No, Lynette, Carlos will
never be fair game.
You know the rules.
You're right.
You are right. You're right.
I'm so sorry.
It's just...
What?
I'm so unhappy.
Ever since that woman
pushed her way into our lives,
I can't even
wo up a smile.
And the more she pushes,
the more I resent Tom.
Tom, for something
he did 12 years ago.
And I'm afraid
if I can't fix...
this, that...
The anger is just gonna
fester until...
Lynette, listen to me.
You and Tom
will survive this.
No, seriously, Gaby, I am so
tired of pretending to smile.
You and Tom...
will survive this.
Yeah?
How can you be so sure?
Because some marriages
were built to last...
And some aren't.
Trust me,
I know the difference.
I'm looking for Bree Van De Kamp.
Could you excuse me
for just a minute?
Orson, congratulations.
Excuse me. Are you
Mrs. Van De Kamp?
It's Hodge now.
Yes, I'm terribly sorry
to barge in like this,
but we need your husband
to come down to the morgue.
We may have found
his wife's body.
Push, Xiao-Mei. Push.
Okay, okay.
Deep breaths now.
You're getting close.
It's time! I can't believe
this is happening!
I think I'm gonna cry.
Carlos, I am so sorry about the...
Yeah, i-Me, too. Me, too.
I was way out of line.
I forgive you.
It's worth it when you experience
a moment as beautiful as this.
Okay, I can see the head now.
Oh, get the camera!
Get the camera!
Oh, my God!
Oh, man, I gotta get the
color fixed on this thing.
How could this has happened?
What kind of half-Ass fertility
clinic are you running?
Prior to implantation,
your embryo was accidentally
switched with another client's.
So if we got theirs
and they got ours,
Then it's possible...
No, I'm afraid your
embryo didn't take.
Again, on behalf of the
clinic, I am so sorry.
It's rare, but these
things do happen.
Excuse me.
You screw up our lives,
and the best you can do is,
"That's the way
the cookie crumbles"?!
And who is this guy? Why is he
writing down everything I say?
This is Mr. Darby, our attorney.
We thought it wise
to have him present.
Do you know what else
would've been wise?
Sticking the right baby
in the right belly!
Mrs. Solis, please.
That's not Alma.
Are you sure?
Absolutely.
Thank God.
Carolyn. What is she doing here?
You didn't honestly think they'd
take your word for it, did you?
It's not her.
Well, that's it then.
Sorry for wasting your time.
This means nothing.
I'm telling you,
that man is as guilty sin!
We know what you think.
Now would you please
leave us alone?
He's a cold-Blooded killer.
He's kind and decent, and nothing you could
say will ever make me doubt him again.
Now please go.
You deserve him.
Darling, I am so sorry you had
to endure that. Are you all right?
I'm fine. Let's just go
back to our guests and
forget any of this
ever happened. All right.
Tu me manques, Monique.
Well...
I feel so...
Me, too.
Well, you know what
the good news is.
What's that?
Now that there's no baby,
it'll make the divorce a lot simpler.
Yeah, that's something.
So...
I'll see you
at the mediator's.
See you then.
Have you met
the perfect couple...
The two soul mates,
whose love never dies?
The two lovers,
whose relationship
is never threatened?
The husband and wife,
who trust each other completely?
If you haven't met
the perfect couple,
let me introduce you.
They stand atop a layer
of buttercream frosting.
The secret of their success?
Well, for starters,
They don't have to
look at each other.