Previously on Desperate Housewives...
The new neighbor...
-He's cute.
-He's a bachelor.
Became a hero.
In a crisis that brought
Julie and Austin together,
while Carlos and
Gaby broke apart.
I had a career and a future,
but I gave it all up for you,
and what did I get in return?
The police assembled
their pieces of evidence.
Your phone number was
written on her hand.
I can't help you.
No memory, huh?
That's convenient.
Karen McCluskey had always
believed in helping others,
whether they wanted
her help or not.
What's all this?
You know how you never got around
to painting your garage door?
Well, it's done.
Hope you like blue.
Baxter!
You found him!
Yeah, and I got him
neutered, too.
I figured you wouldn't want
any more strays around here.
-Karen!
-Hi, Alberta.
I took these down for you since, you
know, Christmas was six months ago.
Yes, Mrs. McCluskey's helping hand
was known throughout Wisteria Lane.
But on this day, it was
about to get slapped.
What the hell
are you doing?
Jeez, Edie, you scared me.
What are you doing here?
Getting Mike's house ready. He comes
back from the hospital tomorrow.
Since when do you have
a key to his garage?
He gave me one...
in case of an emergency.
Don't lie to me, prune.
Fine, I found it under his mat.
Look, I'm not doing
anything wrong.
I just come over once a week and start
his mower so the engine doesn't get rusty.
And do you mow your
lawn with it, too?
What's the big deal?
I'm doing him a favor.
Well, he doesn't need
any favors from you.
I'm gonna go through
Mike's house room by room,
and if I find as much as one paper
clip missing, I'm calling the cops.
Funny you should talk
about stuff that's missing.
Oh, don't act for me.
I know that Mike's been having
troubles with his memory.
My guess...
You don't want him to remember how
crazy he was about his old girlfriend.
I don't need to resort to
deception to land a man.
Oh, Edie,
I saved the pictures...
And I can show them
to Mike anytime I like.
Yes, Karen McCluskey
believed in helping others...
Where are you
going with this?
Which she felt gave
her the right...
To help herself.
By Tyno, Wisteria Team
Transcript by YDY
Forom.com & DHsubs.free.fr
So remember
to be polite...
Each year as part of
their fund-raising drive,
the Fairview adventure scouts
would award a shiny new bike
to whoever sold the most
magazine subscriptions.
And each scout would set out utterly
convinced the prize would be hers.
That's the beauty of youth.
Little girls believe
anything is possible...
That is, until they grow
up anget divorced.
Hi.
What if I told you there is a
way you could help children,
while also reading your favorite
magazines at a reduced price?
Would you like
to hear more?
Sure, knock yourself out.
Wise choice.
For the lady of the
house, we offer...
Redbook, Glamour,
"Vog-you"...
I think you mean
Vogue, sweetie.
You sure?
I should know.
I was on the cover.
No way.
Uh, way.
Oh, see that coat I'm wearing in
this shot? That's genuine ocelot fur.
Although the photographer was the real
animal, if you know what I'm saying...
Which I hope you don't.
And don't ever
do drugs, okay?
Being a model must
be so amazing.
Why did you stop?
Well, I fell in love,
got married and moved
to the suburbs for the
whole fairy-tale
happy ending thing.
That was a crock.
So you going back
to modeling?
No. No, no, no,
no, no, no.
Why not?
What else are
you gonna do?
You're going back to modeling?
This is so sudden.
Well, let's not get
ahead of ourselves.
I'm just gonna fly to New York, meet with
my old agent and take it from there.
Come on, you guys, this is
exciting. Be happy for me.
We are. We're just gonna
miss you, that's all.
Well, now that my divorce is final,
I need a reason to wake up in the morning.
I have this hole in my life that
can't be filled by shopping.
That's right, I said it.
Oh, my Gosh.
Lynette.
I'll get the kids.
They're dying to see you.
Hey.
Hey!
Oh, my Gosh!
You  didn't have
to do this!
Hi!
You  look great.
Well, apparently, taking a .38 slug
to the shoulder agrees with you.
Yeah, um, listen, about that...
The kids don't know what happened.
They don't?
I thought they were little young to
deal with their mother getting shot.
All I told them is Kayla is
staying with her grandmother,
and I made up a story
about how I got hurt.
-Hey, Mom!
-Oh, here they are!
-Hey!
-Mommy!
Hello. Oh, this side. Hi!
Hello!
I can't believe you got
in a fight with a hobo.
Yeah...
Well, let's see how well you
do on a morphine drip.
Mommy, come inside. We helped Mrs.
McCluskey make your favorite lunch.
Fantastic! Lead the
way, I'm coming in.
-Hurry up. I'm hungry.
-Let's go. Let's go.
There she is!
Hi, my little bunny!
Hey, why don't you go inside
and get the party started?
I've gotta... Okay?
-Gotcha.
-Hi, bunny. I'll be right there.
Hey.
-Hey, Lynette!
-Uh, yeah.
-You're home.
-Yeah.
How you doing?
I'm good.
I just...
How do I...
Thank the man
who saved my life?
You don't have
to say anything.
I'm gonna make
you a cake.
-A cake?
-Yeah.
I never make cakes.
This is huge.
In that case...
Thanks.
Yeah, I'm gonna
make you a cake.
Christmas carols?
It's not even Thanksgiving.
I'm starting my cards
early this year.
It puts me in the mood
to spread holiday cheer.
And with the pack of lies in this family
newsletter, she spreads holiday denial.
Andrew, it's etiquette. Nobody wants
to read the truth at Christmas.
Well said, darling.
Honey, would you put on another CD?
Something with sleigh bells.
Oh, by the way, Orson, I need your
mother's address at the nursing home.
Oh, well, I appreciate the thought,
darling, but you needn't send her a card.
Oh, don't be silly. I'm sending one
to the man who reads our gas meter.
I can certainly send
one to your mother.
She's completely senile. She'll
only try to dunk it in her coffee.
Well, all the more
reason to send her one.
Let the nurses know that she has
family at home who loves her...
and who could drop by at any minute
and slap them with a lawsuit.
Bree, I hear what
you're saying-
Orson, what's the big deal?
It's just an address.
Fine.
I'll get my book.
The home is somewhere
over in Lakeview.
Lakeview?
Oh, you gave me the impression
that she was back east.
Well, that's because, frankly,
I wanted to avoid this conversation.
But if she's only 30 minutes away,
why haven't you been visiting her?
Okay, the truth is...
It breaks my heart
to see her now.
I want to remember
her as she was.
-But, Orson...
-Bree,
I refuse to sit in a room that smells
of disinfectant and lime Jell-O,
making small talk with a woman
who doesn't remember me.
Now let it go, damn it.
But by all means,
do send a card.
The elves will tickle her.
Well, shall we?
Wait.
Julie's gonna know we came home early
from the restaurant to check up on her.
I don't want her to think
I'm overprotective and clingy.
The girl was held hostage. It's only
natural you're gonna be a little bit clingy.
Yeah, it's been a week.
I'm getting on her nerves.
How about this?
We came home early because
we hated the restaurant.
The service was dreadful,
and the lobster was inedible.
Okay.
Wait, if we hated the restaurant,
then why are we bringing home food?
Good point.
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Are you kidding?!
That's lobster!
Okay, I thought the
restaurant was fantastic,
and you were the fussy snob
who was impossible to please.
Why do I have to
be the fussy snob?
Because you're british.
Fine.
But I trust you'll make
it up to me later
by doing the things a gentleman
expects when he's sprung for lobster.
I'm not getting any
tonight, am I?
You're  supposed to
be having dinner!
It's my fault. I found the
restaurant to be absolutely...
Oh, let it go. We came home because I was
worried about you, and with good reason.
You, put on your
shirt and get out.
Well, I didn't bring a shirt.
-See, I was out running and...
-Who cares?! Go!
How  could you
treat him like that?
If Austin hadn't been in that
supermarket, I might not be here.
Yes, and I am grateful, but I found a way
to say "thank you" without taking my top off.
A couple of buttons came undone.
It's not like my boobs were out.
Okay, well, it's, uh, it's
getting late and I really...
No, Ian, am I overreacting here?
Well, I can understand on the heels of a crisis,
two people might bondand find themselves...
You're a very naughty girl!
Julie, that boy
drinks, he steals,
and now I find him mauling
you on my couch? That's it.
I forbid you to see him.
You can't do that.
I choose who I date.
Yeah? Well, I choose to
ground you. Two weeks, baby.
Fine, I'll just see
him at school.
Well, then you won't go to
school. I'll homeschool you.
Right, you're gonna teach me trig?
You can't even balance your own checkbook.
Yes, and you will be poorly educated,
and you won't get into college,
and you will work for minimum wage for
the rest of your life, all because of that boy!
I hope you're happy!
Mom, I like this guy, and I'm
sorry if it makes you unhappy,
but I'm going to
keep seeing him.
Doesn't the place look great?
I came in and straightened up.
I wanted everything
to look nice for you.
You okay?
Yeah. Yeah, it's just that...
I'm home, but it doesn't
really feel like home.
It will. Give it time.
The important thing is that
you're back from the hospital,
and every day
you're getting better.
Hey, the worst is behind you.
I need the Delfino
search warrant.
We're not gonna get it
without proble cause.
The guy's phone number was
written on a dead girl's hand.
The judge is gonna need more.
I thought you might say that.
Here's Monique Polier's lab work.
The infrared spectroscopy
matched paint fragments
in the head wound to the
proximo line of pipe wrenches.
They're high-end, only used
by professional plumbers.
And guess what our boy
Delfino does for a living?
I'll see what I can do.
What do you mean
you can't shoot her?
Francesco, if you can airbrush her acne,
you can airbrush the track marks.
Now don't call me
again unless she O.D.S.
Gabrielle, ma petite fille!
Oh, sit!
You look amazing,
younger than ever!
It's my new dermal filler.
It's banned here, so my assistant
smuggles it in from Brazil.
Isn't it fun? I have
my own drug mule.
That's great!
Well, I have some
fun news of my own.
-I'm ready to model again.
-Really?
The last time we spoke,
you couldn't wait to quit.
You were giving
it all up for love.
What happened
to prince charming?
Divorce.
Oh, single again?
Isn't that ironic, since
I'm the one you called...
How did you put it?
A "career-obsessed lesbo who would
die alone and be eaten by her cats."
Did I say that?
Water under the bridge.
I thought it was funny.
It's even funnier now.
Look, Marcella, I'm back.
And we made such a great team
before, and I think we can be again.
I don't know, darling.
Things are different now.
You're not gonna be able to jump
right back in where you left off.
Well,  I just wanna work.
Boy, I'm still not sure.
You know what might help?
If you groveled.
Are you serious?
Well, I can't tell because your
face doesn't move anymore.
No, I'm joking!
Welcome back, darling!
Hi.
Thank you.
Well, hello there!
How pretty you look today!
It's wonderful that
you're up and about!
You must be enjoying
these colorful balloons!
Why are you talking to
me like I'm a moron?
Oh, I'm...
I'm so sorry.
The nurse pointed me over here.
I'm looking for Gloria Hodge.
I'm Gloria Hodge.
Who might you be?
Well, I must say, I'm surprised
at how lucid you are.
Orson led me to believe...
That I was in the final
stages of dementia?
No, I'm afraid that's just
wishful thinking on his part.
Well, how can he feel that
way? You're his mother.
I wouldn't judge
him too harshly.
Ours is a...
complicated relationship.
There is love,
to be sure,
but we have a way of
disappointing each other.
Well, how does
he disappoint you?
He's cold, rigid...
And...
And utterly incapable
of letting go of the past.
And how do you
disappoint him?
I refuse to die.
Yes, I see. Well, surely
this rift isn't irreparable.
Do you know how people in nursing
homes spend their days, Bree?
They think about the past,
and all the things they'd do
differently if they had the chance.
Please tell Orson
that I'm sorry,
And in spite of everything,
I still love him.
Well, I have a better idea.
Why don't you tell him yourself?
That would be great.
I really appreciate it.
Okay. Thank you.
So what did Ted say? When do
you have to go back to work?
He said take as much
time as I want with pay.
You should get gunned
down more often.
-Hey, there they are!
-Hey, guys!
How was school?
Mommy, were you shot?
Shot? Where did
you hear that?
Jordan Blackwelder.
That's the same little creep
who tried to ruin Santa Claus!
And he said that the same crazy lady
that shot you killed auntie Nora dead.
It was on the news
and everything.
Okay, listen, kids.
I am sorry.
We  shouldn't have lied, but sometimes parents
wanna protect the kids fromcary things.
And look, the good news is,
Mommy's fine now.
And we'll all see auntie
Nora again in heaven.
Or wherever.
Did they let you
keep the bullet?
No, no, afraid not.
That blows. We wanted to
bring it for show-and-tell.
Hey, sweetheart, you okay?
What if the crazy
lady comes back?
She won't.
How do you know?
Well, because she's...
Up in heaven
with auntie Nora.
Or wherever.
Julie Mayer, you get back here!
You're grounded, remember?!
Edie Britt, I wanna talk to you.
I just survived a hostage situation.
Haven't I suffered
enough for one week?
You keep your nephew away
from my daughter or else.
Look, I don't like it either,
but the harder we try
to keep them apart,
the more they're gonna
fight to be together.
Just let it run its course.
Are you crazy?!
If we don't do something,
those two could end up having sex!
"Could"?
Oh, my God.
-You don't...
-Let me put it this way-
I got a box of condoms
in my dresser.
Eleven are gone.
Can only account
for eight of 'em.
How can you be so
calm about this?
Edie?
Yeah?
Can you help me
with this tie? I...
Hey.
Mike...
You're out of the hospital.
Yeah. He's home.
In fact, we're gonna go
out and celebrate tonight.
I'll be with you in one
sec, okay, babe?
Yeah.
Since you asked,
I'm calm because I know if two
people are meant to be together,
there's nothing anyone
can do about it.
Okay, I should be back at around 6:00.
They can have one snack.
Try and push apples,
but if they threaten violence,
I have an emergency
candy bar under the sink.
Not anymore you don't.
Oh, jeez.
Mommy?
Where are you going?
To the market.
No!
Hey, sweetie,
it's a different market.
You're gonna get shot again.
No, I won't.
Lots of mommies go to the
store every day, and they're fine.
It's really not a scary place.
You went to the store, and you
got shot, and auntie Nora died.
I'm only gonna be in there
ten minutes, I promise.
Can't she go?
Fine. I'll go.
Thanks.
Don't give a hoot if
I get shot, do ya, kid?
You must be Tanya.
I'm Gabrielle. We're gonna
be co-models today.
Now I don't know if you've ever done one of
these big shoots before, but don't be nervous.
Durkin and I are old friends.
He's a sweetheart.
Now just remember, he's the king, do
exactly what he says, and you'll be fine.
I've been modeling
for two years,
I've done six magazine covers,
and I'm sleeping with Durkin.
Well, I guess you're
all set then.
I've got some wardrobe choices.
I want to be buried
in this dress!
This is for Tanya.
The "Mom" stuff is at the end.
"Mom"?
Okay, luv, let's get
the blood pumping!
The concept is "lock
up your daughters".
Okay? Get to work, everybody.
Tanya, I want you to hover down here
on the lawn, looking absolutely delicio.
Thank you very much.
And up here on the porch, Mom
and Dad looking all scandalized.
Excuse me, Durkin?
Yes, luv?
It's Gaby.
Gabrielle Marquez.
You shot me in Milan, remember?
Yes! Yes!
Lovely to see you again.
Did you have a question then?
I do.
Aren't you a little worried
that I'm gonna pull focus?
I mean, it's a little confusing.
People are gonna see Tanya,
and then they're gonna...
See that guy, and they're
gonna wonder who I am.
You're the Mum.
People aren't gonna buy that,
so here's what I was thinking.
I slap on one of those gowns,
I play Tanya's "big sister",
home from college
to raise a little help.
And we're gonna cram all
that on a subtitle, are we?
I'm sorry. Is just,
this outfit is hideous!
Just make it work.
Fine.
I just need a moment
to get into character.
Gabrielle, what's the holdup?
We've got to get moving here.
Ready, ready!
What's that?
Oh, I made it work.
I'm "hot Mom".
Get me her agent.
Before we begin, would either of you like
some cookies, milk, lemonade, perhaps?
Mom, why are we here?
Ah, cutting to the chase.
I like it.
I have a confession to make.
This whole dating drama has
been keeping me up at night,
and I hate being the
bitchy, naggy Mom.
When it comes to parenting, I am much
more comfortable playing the good cop.
Do you see where I'm
going with this, kids?
No.
Well, in that case.
Meet the bad cop.
Daddy!
Hey, baby girl.
That the guy?
Yep!
Get him.
This is so unfair.
Look, you defied my wishes,
you broke my rules.
Did you really think I was just
gonna throw in the towel?
Face it. I outsmarted you.
Who's Ian?
What?
You're dating some
british guy named Ian.
How did that come up?
I'm sorry. I didn't realize
it was a big secret.
You know, when you said it was
true love with you and the plumber,
I was a good guy.
I stepped aside, and now
you're on to someone else.
Big picture, Karl. His hand
up our daughter's shirt.
-Don't change the subject!
-That is the subject!
How serious is it
with this Ian guy?
I don't know!
It's complicated.
Yeah, he's kind of married.
He's what?
It's not what you think.
Well, in her defense,
his wife is in a coma.
All right, that's it!
All right, I forbid
you to see this guy!
What?
No! I don't take
orders from you!
Mom has a point, Dad.
You can't tell a woman who
she can and can't date.
-It's her choice.
-Exactly. Thank you.
Wait, no, that does
not apply to you.
You know, if you don't
care about my feelings,
I don't know what
I'm doing here.
Your feelings?
My God, you are the
worst bad cop ever!
Go to your room.
Not you!
Get back here!
You're under arrest!
No, I'm not!
Hey, buddy, you've been
reading comic books for a while.
Don't you wanna
go and play?
No, I wanna stay with you.
Yeah?
Okay.
Hey, Art.
Oh, hey! How are ya?
Good, uh...
Listen, as if saving my life wasn't
enough, I have a little favor to ask.
Sure. What's up?
My kids are having
a hard time.
They're pretty freaked out by
that whole supermarket thing.
You're my hostage!
Keep moving, or I'll
blow your face off!
Okay, it's my turn.
Give me the gun.
Not so much them.
Right.
But my other son, Parker.
So. Back to the favor.
Hey, Parker.
I want you to meet
our new neighbor, Art.
He lives in the house
across the street.
His sister has the cool
wheelchair witthe joystick.
Hey there, Parker.
Hi.
In the daytime,
Art coaches swimming
at the rec center, but...
Please, I can tell
Parker? Please?
And compromise my secret identity?
No way, Mrs. Scavo. No way.
Secret identity?
Oh, great, now the
cat's out of the bag.
Oh, might as well tell him.
It's okay. You can
trust him, really.
Art is the one who saved
me at the supermarket.
He's sort of a superhero.
Give me a break.
It's true.
All right, if you're a superhero,
what's your name?
I'm...
Protector Man.
Because I protect
people from bad guys.
You don't believe
me, do you?
Okay.
I really shouldn't
do this, but...
Did you really
save my Mom?
I really did.
He really did.
That's why you don't
have to worry.
That's Protector Man's job.
Your job is to run and
play and have fun.
Okay?
Okay.
Oh, my cousin
went to Purdue.
What the hell?
Delfino.
Nice to see you
up and about.
Here's our search warrant.
Search warrant?
Let me see that.
How we doing?
We couldn't find a toolbox.
The man's a plumber.
Keep looking.
Sir, I can't find a thing.
You tired?
You, come with me.
Marcella, look,
I don't know what
they told you,
but all I'm asking for is
a simple costume change.
You don't get to
pull diva crap.
Tanya gets away with
it because she's a star.
You are nothing.
Where do you get off
talking to me like that?
I shot 36 covers by
the time I was 20!
Well, you're 30 now.
When you make that
face, you look 35.
Do you know how many photographers
would die to work with me again?
Yeah. Zero.
I had to call in major favors
just to get you this job.
I don't believe that.
Well, you know
what I don't believe?
You gave up a brilliant career
to play house in the suburbs,
and the minute it falls apart, you come
back here expecting a homecoming parade.
Well, guess what, sweetie?
We've moved on.
Now get your polyester
ass over there,
and act like the pro
you used to be.
Beautiful, Tanya.
That's it. Chin up.
Fantastic!
Mother, hold the plate higher.
Beautiful, Tanya.
Oh, you are gorgeous!
Yes, girl! Lovely, lovely!
Hiya, Mike. Welcome home.
You remember me?
Yeah, I think so.
The corner house with
all the gnomes out front?
You're thinking
of Martha Huber.
Terrible story.
Someone beat her to death, and
then buried her in the forest.
Ironic, huh?
Isn't that where
gnomes live?
I don't really know that
much about gnomes.
Anyway, I know the
cops were here earlier.
So?
Well, you won't remember this,
but one night two years ago,
you drove me to the hospital
after I had an attack of angina.
Probably saved my life.
Anyway, I figure
I owe ya. Here.
You might wanna
wash that wrench off.
It's got something on it.
Sorry I'm late.
Mrs. Prescott broke
a crown and...
Orson, how well you look.
Hello, mother.
A word, darling?
I can't believe
you did this!
And I can't believe you told me
that she was senile! You lied to me.
Yes, to spare us the misery of her
company. You don't know her, Bree.
She's a loathsome woman, and
I refuse to break bread with her.
Now you listen to me.
That woman gave you life,
and the Fifth Commandment tells us
to honor our parents no matter how
hideous or repellent they may be.
-That's not exactly what...
-Orson, it's implied!
Now get out there and
show her some respect!
Fine, but if you expect anything
more from me than forced civility,
you will be deeply disappointed.
Bree, this salmon is superb.
Well, thank you!
It did win me the blue ribbon
at the gourmet county cookoff.
I just love the sauce.
What gives it that kick?
You'd never ask a magician
how a trick is done.
You've barely touched
your salmon, dear.
Is everything okay?
Yes.
I was just wondering
why you're here.
I want us to be friends.
Okay, let's suppose I just had a
massive head injury and believe you.
We're pals. Now
what do you want?
Orson, why does she have
to have an ulterior motive?
I want out of that home.
Ah, there it is.
It's a hellhole! Besides,
I'm perfectly healthy now.
My hip is better,
I can handle the stairs,
and you said when I got strong
enough I'd get to go back to my house.
Oh, here's the thing. I sold it.
What?
You heard me.
What about my things?
All gone.
Oh, I also sold the car.
See, that's the thing
about hellholes.
They don't pay
for themselves.
How dare you?
You had no right!
Okay! Maybe I will share
my secret ingredient.
I should have smothered you in
your crib when I had the chance.
Paprika! There, it's out!
That's the mother I remember!
I was wondering
when she'd show up.
Yes, Orson,
I am your mother,
so you more than anyone should
know how I deal with betrayal.
So...
Can we call her grandma?
I've got one more load, and
then I'm gonna do my homework.
Do you have anything you
want me to throw in?
No, I'm good. Thanks.
Mom, listen.
I know I've put you through
the wringer lately, and...
I'm sorry.
16 years of being perfect.
You were due.
That's what I don't get.
You've always
trusted my judgment.
Why can't you trust
me about Austin?
Relationships have nothing
to do with good judgment.
It doesn't matter
how smart you are.
You can still get hurt.
You do your homework.
I'm gonna finish the laundry.
Okay.
There you go, Mrs. H.
All right.
-Can I use your bathroom, just...
-Come on in.
Please, stay for dessert.
I'll work on Orson, and
we'll discuss this together.
You saw what he
sentenced me to...
A room no better
than a furnished coffin.
I have nothing
to say to him.
Well, then talk to me.
I know you're upset, but
don't shut me out. Please.
Please, Gloria, let me in.
Well, I didn't mean
it literally, but okay.
We'll, um, we'll sit together.
And we'll talk.
What are you doing?
I'm not going
back to that place.
Gloria, stop!
Let's get my mother back
to the home, shall we?
Not that it's any of my business, but,
is everything okay with you folks?
Oh, yeah, there was a little tension
earlier, but I think it's all been resolved.
Oh, what the hell?
No, I absolutely forbid it!
Just for a few weeks till we find
a place where she'll be happier.
You should've heard
her in the car.
She's absolutely miserable
in that nursing home.
I don't care.
My mother's not moving in here
till she fits in a jar on the mantle.
How can you be so cold?
You don't know who she is.
I've worked my entire life to
get away from that woman.
Why?
What could she possibly have done
to make you hate her so much?
Look, there is nothing to be
gained by dredging up the past.
Orson, if there's something
I should know.
Could I speak to
my son a moment?
Of course.
So you know,
I've decided to accept
your wife's kind invitation.
I won't allow it.
Oh, I think you will.
We're going to end
our quarrel right now,
or I'll tell your
wife what it's about.
You wouldn't.
Just try me.
I gave you life.
You know I won't
hesitate to take it away.
Now give mother a kiss.
Why in the hell would
I wanna do that?
To make it look real.
Hey, you're back!
I'd give you a hug,
but I'm really sweaty.
So how was New York?
Oh, it was fine.
Bree said you got
a job on the first day.
You're such a star!
I want details.
You know, just hours and hours
of sitting around, looking pretty.
But I think I'm done
with modeling.
So you're not gonna
move to New York?
Well, if something great
comes up, I might fly out,
but I'm pretty settled here.
Oh, thank God!
We were all so worried
we were losing you.
Okay, now I'm hugging you.
Oh, it's amazing.
Your life is such an adventure.
Can't wait to see
what you do next.
Yeah, me, too.
Okay.
Mr. Protector Man?
Shh! That's a secret.
Hello?
Ah, sweet!
Mom, look!
Hey, don't touch anything.
I'm just gonna write a
note, and then we'll go.
Okay.
Parker? Hey!
Come back here!
Honey?
Come on, we're leaving.
Parker.
Parker, come on,
we're leaving.
Why didn't you come
when I called?
Superhero houses are great!
Parker, come on, we're
gonna get out of here.
-Why?
-Oh, I just say so. Come on.
There are so many things we
wish we could tell the young.
We'd like to persuade them
not to grow up so fast,
but they won't listen.
We want to tell them
that beauty fades,
but they refuse to believe it.
We warn them that their
actions will have consequences,
but still they defy us.
Sadly, the young can't begin to understand
the world is a dangerous place.
So it's up to us to do anything
we can to protect them...
What if I told you there is a
way you could help children...
Absolutely anything.