Previously on Desperate Housewives...
A reporter just did a story on homeless
teens, my son is one of them.
Oh, my God.
Orson found Andrew.
Have I done stuff for money that
I'm not proud of? Yeah, sure.
And the prodigal son returned.
Mike fell into a coma...
-What could be more romantic?
-I could think of... of something.
And Susan fell into the
arms of another man...
a bit too soon.
The day Mike Delfino
woke from his coma,
Edie Britt was
the first to know.
Once she was sure
he was responsive...
Mike?
Edie decided to share
the good news with others.
Code red! Code red!
My friend just woke
up from his coma.
And that is how word
began to spread.
Mike's physician, Dr. Craig,
was busy with a patient
when he first heard the news.
Not long after,
he called his aunt Ida,
who was busy
knitting a sweater.
She told Lynette Scavo,
who was busy watering her lawn.
And she told her husband Tom,
who was busy playing
at computer game.
He then e-mailed
his friend Carlos,
Who was busy plotting strategy
with his divorce lawyer.
And Carlos called his
soon-to-be ex-wife Gabrielle,
who was busy doing
the same with hers.
Yes, word of Mike's
miraculous recovery
spread quickly
throughout Wisteria Lane,
And stopped cold
everyone's busy, busy life...
Everyone, that is...
Except for Susan Mayer,
who was busy doing something
she would soon wish...
she hadn't.
By Tyno, Wisteria Team
Transcript by FRM
Forom.com & DHsubs.free.fr
Edward Sibley was the beloved
founder of the town of Fairview.
Prior to that,
and a horse thief.
Of course, no one remembers
those parts of Edward's past.
Luckily for him, history is
designed to be rewritten...
And no one knew this
better than Bree Hodge.
So you're just gonna
lie to people?
Oh, I'm not talking about
a lie. Just a polite fiction
to explain to everybody
where you've been.
I mean, we can't
possibly tell them that
you've been living on skid row,
sleeping in a cardboard box.
So why do I have to go
to this history fair anyway?
I mean, it's just some
dumb school contest.
We all know Danielle's
not gonna win.
She never wins anything.
Is it weird eating off plates?
'Cause if you were more
comfortable, you could just
aat straight out of the garbage.
This is a family event,
and we're all gonna
enjoy it together.
Now, Danielle, stop sniping and start
thinking of an alibi for your brother.
I know. We could say he joined a cult,
and we had to kidnap and deprogram him.
Well, that would certainly spare
the family some embarrassment.
Why not throw in
a killing spree, too?
Well, here's a thought.
We say he was at drama camp.
It reflects Andrew's interest
in the performing arts,
while giving us
a private joke to savor
about the drama
of his estrangement.
Uh, yeah,
he is always like that.
Uh, guys, why can't
we just tell the truth?
Uh, I got out of line,
you kicked me out,
I lived on the street,
and I came back home.
We'll need a name
for this drama camp.
We got ties here, people!
Designer ties,
two for a dollar!
Oh, do you like
those barbells?
Make me an offer.
I'm feeling generous.
Here's the customer
I've been waiting for.
I'll give you $5 for this.
Carlos, I see you got my flier.
You're having a garage sale
featuring menswear
and sporting equipment.
I need cash, and you don't expect
me to sell my stuff, do you?
Those are my good cuff links!
Those are my cds!
Oh, my God,
this is my baby blanket.
My Mamá knitted this!
And it pains me to sell it.
It's just that my lawyer told me
what you're offering
for spousal support,
and I can't get by on that.
Hey, I am doing
the best that I can.
I've got a few deals
in the pipeline,
but I'm not making near as much as
I used to. So I should be punished?
Attention, shoppers,
for the next 20 minutes,
free golf club with
every purchase!
Gaby, I'm trying to be civil,
but if you don't
knock it off right now,
I swear, the gloves are coming off.
Oh, honey, the gloves
aren't just off...
They're 70% off!
Get your cashmere gloves!
Hey, Parker,
where's your uniform?
You got your game in an hour.
No, I don't. I quit.
W hat?
I hate baseball.
Daddy  said I don't have
to play it anymore.
Well, daddy should have
checked with mommy,
so she could have a chance
to tell him why he's wrong.
Hey, you're playing.
But, mom, I suck!
Everybody says so.
That's why they made up
a fake position for me.
It is not fake.
There is not a team I know that could get
along without their backup far right fielder.
Okay, come on,
let's go practice.
All right, let's try it again.
Nice and easy.
Watch the ball hit the bat.
You ready? You can do it.
Here we go.
Okay, Parker,
I keep telling you, you gotta
keep your eyes open.
How are you gonna hit the
ball when you're doing this?
You threw it too fast.
Throw slower.
If I threw any slower,
we would be bowling.
Hey.
Hey, whatcha guys doing?
I'll tell you what
we're not doing, quitting.
Oh, hey, buddy,
did you change your mind?
No.
Lynette, I told him that
he didn't have to play anymore.
He's got five more
games in the season.
He made a commitment.
He's gonna see it through.
But, Lynette, he doesn't like it,
and if you haven't noticed,
he kind of sucks.
Yeah, well, that's not the point.
What kind of message are we sending if we
let him quit whenever the going gets rough?
Honey, it is kids' baseball. It's a way to
kill three hours before they eat pizza.
Why you being such a hard-ass?
Well, it's called parenting, Tom.
Watch and learn.
Okay, P-Dog,
this is a curveball.
Again, opening the eyes.
Can't stress it enough.
Are you sure it's okay
if we stay another day?
Well, let's see. What excuse did we use
when we had this conversation yesterday?
That we work hard,
and we deserve to relax.
No, I believe that was
last Thursday's rationale.
-Uh, fresh air is good for us?
-Ah, Tuesday.
Okay, here's one...
Julie needs to spend more
time bonding with her father.
Brilliant!
If we keep this up,
we could stay here
till christmas.
You know, sometimes
when you smile like that,
That, that really makes
me think that, that...
What? What were
you gonna say?
Well, it makes me think
that could love you.
I... don't mean "love" in the
swooning schoolboy sense.
You know,
fireworks exploding,
Bells ringing.
To me, it's about this...
A mundane task
that's suddenly a joy,
because of who
you're doing it with.
That's love to me.
Someone to fluff
while you fold,
someone to whisper
to at a boring party,
Someone to...
Shh. Do you mind?
You're kind of drowning
out the bells.
So I am.
I think I can feed myself now.
Mm, you said that yesterday,
And I wound up with
a cleavage full of pudding.
You heard the therapist.
It's gonna be weeks
before you're up and running.
I just wanna get home, unpack.
You just let home
come to you, okay?
The whole street's
dying to see you.
Bree is even bakin'
ya a peach pie.
She's the redhead, right?
Right.
Husband's a doctor...
Rex.
Rex is dead.
Really?
When did that happen?
About a year and a half ago.
What?
Yeah. You were at his funeral.
What are you talking about?
That's not possible.
I just met him right
before my accident.
Mike...
What year is it?
2004. Why?
It's called retrograde memory loss.
It's caused by the swelling
and frontal lobe damage.
You say he's lost two whole years?
Yeah. Is that unusual?
Ah,  patients more typically
lose several weeks.
The damage may be more
severe than we thought.
Well, do you think
he'll get his memory back?
He might,
at least partially.
You could be of some
assistance with that.
How?
Bring  him some personal belongings.
Photos, letters.
He's gonna need some help
to remember what he can't.
Oh, I'm sure I could
fill in a few blanks.
Hey, did I tell you that, uh,
Burnham Fox is looking
for a new creative director?
P.R.? What makes you think
I wanna work for a P.R. firm?
Easy hours, big paycheck,
access to great parties...
Yeah, what was I thinking?
Honey, we agreed that
I would chase my dreams,
and that ain't it.
Look, I was just
making conversation.
Batter up!
Is he up?
Oh, come on!
Come on, Parker!
Keep your eye on the ball!
Strike one!
Hey, people,
he's just a kid, okay?
Come on.
Strike two!
Hey, hey,
that is not helpful.
It only takes one, Parker!
Only takes one! Come on, Parker!
It's not your son's fault.
He's just up against
the best pitcher in the league.
Yeah, guy's a machine.
Who is that kid?
Nicky Abbott.
He's a neighbor of mine.
The kid's got an arm
like a 13-year-old.
Strike three! You're out!
I'm gonna go buy
him an ice cream.
It's okay, P-Dog.
You're gonna get 'em
the next inning!
So tell me,
what else do you know
about this Nicky kid?
You're short 50 cents.
Please, that's all I got.
Hey, give the kid
what he wants.
Thanks.
Hey, aren't you, uh,
Parker Scavo's mom?
That's right.
Come. Walk with me.
So...
Money's a little tight, huh?
A little.
Yeah, I heard your old
man's out of work.
That's gotta be tough.
Yeah, they, uh,
cut my allowance.
No! A kid's gotta
have an allowance.
How else you gonna buy
the things you want, right?
Like that cotton candy.
That's a little piece
of heaven, huh?
Hey, I got an idea. Maybe we
could help each other out.
My son's having a little
trouble hitting the ball.
Yeah, I saw that.
Yeah.
Ever seen one of these?
Carlos, what are you doing here?
I mean, besides loring
my property value.
I had a little news,
and I wanted to see your
face when I delivered it.
I'm tired of fighting,
So I called my lawyer and told him to give
in to your demands for spousal support.
Really?
Wow. Well, thank you.
Okay, you've seen my face.
Now you can beat it.
Wait. There's more.
Since I'm gonna be giving
you all that money,
I have to cut back
on some stuff,
like the rent
on my apartment.
But the good news is,
according to my lawyer,
I'm completely within
my rights to do this...
Honey,  I'm home.
Wait! You can't stay here!
Now there's the face
that I was looking for.
Batter up!
Strike one!
Wow, that was
kind of slow.
His arm must be getting tired.
Yeah, well,
after all those fastballs...
Come on, Parker!
You can do it!
Strike two!
Oh, my God! Yes!
-Mr. Faladi.
-Yes?
Yes? I cannot thank you enough for
getting Danielle interested in history.
She has never worked so
hard on a project before.
Well, don't tell anyone,
but she is my favorite student.
Oh, and it's so good to
see that Andrew's back.
Where's he been
all this time?
Drama camp.
A very prestigious drama camp.
Do I know you?
Yeah, uh, you gave me a ride
in your black Sedan once.
You know, the one
with the reclining seats?
-Excuse me.
-Yeah.
Wasn't that Dr. Keck?
You know him?
Yeah. Yeah, we, uh...
met at drama camp.
Oh, good Lord.
You mean, you...
Yeah, I "performed" for him once.
Are you all right?
I'll be all right. I'm fine.
Howard Keck?
You sure?
I mean, he's a very respected
member of the community.
Yeah, well, they all were.
What were you and Andrew
talking about today at the fair?
Uh, nothing.
I was gonna make some cocoa.
Would you like some?
Orson, I saw the two of you whispering
right after Dr. Keck ran off.
What happened?
Look, Andrew asked me
not to say anything,
but I don't want there to be
any secrets between us,
so please don't
let him know I told you.
Well, of course not.
What is it?
How to put this? Uh...
When Andrew
was on the street,
he, uh, he didn't just
beg for money.
At times, he...
Well, he did things to earn it.
Oh, good. I mean, I'd hate to
think he had no work ethic at all.
Uh, what I mean is...
Men hired him, uh, to...
Do things, things
he wasn't very proud of.
Yard work?
Afraid  not.
Orson, you're scaring me.
Did he do something awful?
No! Nonot awful.
I mean, people do it all
the time. I do it with you.
I just don't pay you for it.
I think someone
could use a cocoa.
Look, we mustn't judge Andrew.
-He was desperate.
-I'll never forgive myself.
It's all my fault for pushing him
away.
Bree, don't do that to yourself.
The important thing now is
that he's home and he's safe.
How does this Dr. Keck
fit into all of this?
I mean, is he treating Andrew
for some awful disease?
Actually, I think
he was one of Andrew's...
clients.
Howard Keck?!
Oh, that's ridiculous.
He's got a wife and a daughter.
He plays on Tom Scavo's bowling team.
Well, that's clearly not
the only team he plays for.
This is a nightmare,
an absolute nightmare.
Please don't cut into that pie.
I made it for Mike.
Mike? Delfino?
Yes. I left you two messages.
Didn't you check your voice mail?
He woke up from his coma.
Who is it? It is Sharla Banning?
I'm not telling who it is.
I'm just asking the question.
If you know a husband
has been unfaithful,
do you tell the wife?
Absolutely. If he's cheating,
he could bring home a disease.
Okay, that's what I was thinking. I mean,
that's how Bunny Connors got chlamydia.
She told me she got it from wearing
someone else's bathing suit.
No, that's how she got crabs.
Poor Bunny.
It's always something.
If it's not the clap,
it's a botched face-lift.
Be that as it may,
do we all agree that
I should tell this man's wife?
I wouldn't.
Women always say they wanna know
if their husband's cheating,
and they always resent
the person who tells them.
So if Tom was cheating,
you wouldn't tell me?
No! But I would hire someone
to beat the crap out of him.
Aw, you're sweet.
Bree, I'm sorry. I think you gotta
follow your heart on this one,
even if it isn't the easiest thing to do.
Gaby...
Are you and Carlos
getting back together?
Why?
Uh... would you excuse me?
What are you doing? I told you
I was having friends over!
I'm thirsty!
And this is my kitchen, too.
Hey, ladies!
Oh, for God sakes,
put some pants on!
Well, I wanted to, but somebody threw my
laundry out of the dryer while it was still wet.
Don't act like you
didn't deserve that.
What are you talking about?
You peed in my shampoo. Admit it!
-What?!
-Yeah, the cap was loose,
and I know how your
sick mind works.
Oh, really?
Well, in that case, you should know that
if I was gonna do something like that,
I wouldn't do it
to your shampoo.
I would do it to your mouthwash,
soup and decaffeinated coffee.
Ladies.
To answer your question... No,
we are not getting back together.
I love this music.
What's it about?
Making love, regret,
cigarettes.
Cigarettes?
That's what I assume.
It's french. They write
what they know.
I'd love to go to France someday.
Would you like
to go next month?
Are you serious?
Yeah, I'm going on business.
Come with me.
Oh, Ian, I just took a week off.
I couldn't possibly justify
taking another.
Oh, you'll manage.
We've already proven ourselves
masters of the flimsy rationalization.
Well... okay.
You gotta promise me we'll
actually leave the hotel room.
It's Paris, dear. You can pretty
much make love anywhere.
I thought you said you didn't
get reception up here.
We, the occasional
signal gets through.
Please don't answer.
Oh, it's Julie. I have to.
Hello? What's up?
Hey...
Uh, I can't...
No, can you say that again?
The signal's really bad.
What?
Oh, my God.
-Is something wrong?
-Mike woke up.
Um, Julie, when did he...
Julie? Julie!
Oh, damn it!
Oh, my God.
Oh! Oh, my God!
Uh, I... I have to go.
Um, I gotta
get out of here.
Yes, of course.
Uh, I think that
you're sitting on my bra.
What'd the coach say?
What do you think he said?
Parker's off the team.
That's not fair!
It's not his fault!
It doesn't matter,
because his mother bribed
an 8-year-old pitcher,
who also, by the way,
was kicked off of his team.
Not Nicky, too!
What were you thinking?
I was trying to repair my
son's shattered self-esteem.
With a $50?
Honey, everything would've been
fine if you had just let Parker quit.
Well, excuse me for not
wanting my son to be a quitter.
Yeah, 'cause I guess having two
in the family would be a bit much.
Whoa. Where'd that come from?
You say that you support my decision
to leave advertising
and follow my dream,
but it is obvious to
me that you resent it.
That is not true!
Why do you keep dropping all these hints
about the job at Burnham Fox then, huh?
I just figured, since you're taking your time
figuring out what your dream even is,
you might wanna make
a few bucks in the meantime.
I have a dream, too.
It includes keeping this house.
Oh, like I don't...
-Are you fighting?
-No!
No.
It was excitement, because
we have just decided
you don't have to
play baseball anymore.
-Ah! Isn't that great?
-But I can't stop now.
Huh?
Not when I'm finally getting good.
You were right, mom. I just
needed a little more practice.
So come on, come on!
Let's go practice!
See you outside.
So what's on the next page
of your parenting handbook?
-Ian, can you please hurry?
-I am hurrying!
We should've been on
the road ten minutes ago.
It's not like checking out of a hotel.
There's doors to secure.
-I have to turn the gas valve off.
-Can't you do that stuff later?
When? After the place
is overrun by raccoons?
Of course, the joke would be
on them when it blows up.
Mike is awake! He's lying there
and he's wondering where I am.
Yes, I get it.
You're in a hurry.
Just please give me a minute.
I bet you'd move faster
if Jane were awake.
Ah, here's the picture that you took
of me in my bikini at that pool party.
You could've warned me
I was showing a little nip.
Oh, Susan Mayer.
Remember her?
Yeah.
She's pretty.
Yeah, she is, sorta,
in this picture.
Is there a date
on this thing?
The nurses said that
she visited me a lot.
We were close, huh?
You have just
come out of a coma.
Can we not talk about Susan
till you start to regain your strength?
Why?
Oh, God.
I hate to be the one
telling you this...
Well, if you don't want to...
That tramp
treated you like dirt.
She strung you along.
She slept with other guys.
You broke up with her twice.
Well, why did she keep visiting
me when I was out of it?
Well, she's a bit of a stalker.
I was worried that she was gonna come in here
and disconnect one of the tubes or something.
But don't worry.
She's glommed on
to some new guy,
and she's up in the mountains
at his place with him right now.
Wow.
She told the nurses
that she really loved me.
That's the one thing about
Susan that you must never forget,
she is a liar.
You waiting to see
Mike Delfino?
Uh, yes. I'm a...
I'm a neighbor.
But, uh, he already has a
vitor, so I'll come back later.
Well, don't be surprised
if he doesn't recognize you.
He's suffered
significant memory loss.
Really?
Oh, that's too bad.
You sure you don't want to go in?
Ms. Britt's here all the time.
She won't mind.
No. I've waited this long.
I can wait a bit longer.
Gaby!
Hey, Carlos. What's up?
My key won't work.
That's probably because
I had the locks changed.
-Gaby!
-Can't be too safe.
You never know when someone might
move in on you when you're not looking.
Hello, 911?
There's an intruder
breaking into my home.
Can you tell them
to come armed?
I think he's mexican.
I'm telling you,
I'm her husband.
I bought her this house.
My name is on the deed.
Ma'am, if you're married,
it's a matter of public record.
I can find out very quickly.
All right, but we're going
through a very messy divorce,
and he moved back in on me.
And everyone knows
the wife keeps the house,
and the husband gets
the crappy apartment.
It's the american way.
Call my lawyer. This is all
totally legal, and she knows it.
She's just trying
to get back at me.
I hear that.
You wouldn't believe the stuff
my wife pulled when we split.
Whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
you can't take sides!
Police officers aren't
allowed to take sides.
I pay your salary.
Ted, did you see that?
This lady just assaulted me.
Oh. It was a swat.
Ted, does this hurt?
Get your hands off me!
Police brutality!
This is all my fault.
Why punish Parker?
Sorry, Mrs. Scavo.
Rules are rules.
I can't put him back on the team.
Just one more game.
He'll suck,
the other kids will taunt him,
and he'll wanna quit again.
See, everybody wins.
I wish I could help, but...
Please? You can't
bend the rules just once?
Did you know the team could
use some new batting helmets?
Are you asking for a bribe?
You pretending
you're above that?
I'll get my checkbook.
Hello, Vera.
I made you some of those, uh, shortbread
biscuits that you like so much.
How sweet!
Can you stay for some tea?
It's been so long.
We have some
catching up to do.
Yes. Yes, we do.
I know how painful
this must be for you.
It isn't easy for me either,
considering Andrew's role in it.
And why have you told me this?
Because I thought
you'd want to know.
Why?
So you could do something.
Do you think I'm an idiot?
That I know nothing about the
man I've lived with for 27 years?
I've always assumed
Howard had some... outlet,
a friend tucked
away somewhere.
I didn't know.
I didn't care to know.
But thank you
for painting so vivid,
so indelible a picture
of my husband's activities.
I'm sorry.
I just felt that
if it were me, I...
-You'd want to know.
-Yes, absolutely.
Then I owe you an apology,
because I've been sitting on a
little secret about your family.
Oh?
Actually, it's not much of a secret.
My daughter tells me it's common
knowledge among the cheerleaders.
What is?
The fact that Danielle is
sleeping with her history teacher.
But where are my manners?
I should have brought
some biscuits with that.
Well, aren't we just
the parents of the year?
Sitting in the stands,
waiting for our son to fail,
so we can weasel out
of a bribery scandal.
Two bribery scandals.
Gotta count the batting helmets.
Strike one!
You know, for what it's worth,
I don't think you're a quitter.
Good.
And you don't resent me?
No.
Ball one!
Okay, well, maybe a little.
Why?
You get to chase your dream while I get
to spend the rest of my life in advertising.
Strike two!
Maybe I'd like to write a book or,
you know, start my own magazine.
And then I think, "No, I can't.
I have a family to support,"
and I am okay with that...
Ball two!
Most of the time.
You know what?
I'm gonna look into that
job at Burnham Fox.
Don't you dare!
You are gonna
chase your dream,
and I am gonna support
you 99% of the time.
It's all I could
really ask for.
How the hell
did he do that?!
Yeah! Come on, come on!
Crap, they're cheering for him.
Oh, he's never gonna quit now!
What are we gonna say to him?
I don't know, buddy.
Looks like a pretty bad sprain.
Probably gonna be out
the rest of the season.
Damn.
Hey, but you know what?
That was one heck of a hit.
Sure was.
I posted your bail.
We can go.
-Gaby...
-Don't talk to me.
Oh, lighten up.
You were in there
for maybe an hour.
The whole thing is funny,
and you know it.
Come on, Gaby!
We've been going at each
other for months now.
Can we just stop?
You know as well as I do we're
gonna end up back together.
Wow, you are crazy.
No, what's crazy is throwing
away the past three years.
Why can't we just say what
we really feel for a change?
Fine, I'll get the ball rolling.
I still love you.
That's too bad,
because I don't love you.
Yeah, right.
I don't...
And I haven't
for a very long time.
That's a lie. You're just
saying that to hurt me.
No, if I wanted hurt you, I would
tell you about last weekend...
When I slept with
John Rowland.
Carlos, what are you doing?
Carlos!
What are you doing?! Carlos!
You can't leave me out here
in the middle of nowhere!
Carlos!
Danielle! Danielle, he is your history
teacher, and he is 35-years-old!
-Robert says age is just a number.
-Don't you dare leave this house!
You can't break us up!
I love him, d he loves me!
Come on, mom.
I am so tired of feeling like
the worst mother who ever lived.
You're not.
There's grandma.
I've tried so hard to
set a good example.
I've done the best I could to
teach you kids right from wrong.
Why isn't it taking?
It took.
I mean, we know the difference between
right and wrong. We just chose wrong.
Why?
Sometimes when you push a kid
really hard to go one way,
the other way starts to
look more entertaining.
You're awful.
Yeah, I know.
I blame shoddy parenting.
You know, we never...
discussed what it s like for
you while you were... away.
I just want you to know,
if you ever wanna...
talk about it, there's
nothing you can't tell me.
Thanks.
Not right now.
Okay?
I'll pick up my bags later.
It's not my fault
you weren't there.
-What?
-It's not.
I know what you're feeling, but...
How could you possibly
know what I was feeling?
For six months,
I have prayed every day
for that man to wake up,
and you made me give up on him.
I did not make you.
Okay, not on purpose, but you did.
You were sweet and
charming and english.
And that's why when my
prayers were answered,
I was a hundred miles away,
naked in someone else's arms.
This should never
have happened.
You can say
what you want about this,
say that you feel guilty,
say that it was bad timing,
vut don't you say that this
should never have happened!
Because you're the...
You're the best thing that's
happened to me in years.
Ian, I'm sorry.
I know how you feel.
It's Mike.
It's my Mike.
Well, then you should go.
Thank you.
Oh, my God.
You are awake.
Hi, Susan.
Oh, God!
It's so wonderful to
hear your voice again.
They say you've been here lot.
Yes! Yes, I have.
Almost every day.
I can't tell you how much I'm kicking myself
for not being here when you woke up.
Where were you?
I was in the country.
But I'm back now.
Okay.
Is something wrong? You...
You don't seem
happy to see me.
To be honest,
I don't remember you.
What?
I remember moving to Fairview
and meeting people,
but after that, nothing.
The doctors say
it's the head trauma.
But you're gonna all right.
And I'm gonna
help you remember.
And if you don't mind,
I'm kind of tired now.
Okay.
Right, you, um,
you sleep.
I'll come back tomorrow.
I'd rather you didn't.
Well, I've got therapy.
Maybe next week.
Okay.
We all have our reasons
for rewriting history.
Sometimes we need to
provide ourselves alibis...
Drama camp was awesome.
Uh, we're talking
zero supervision.
Sometimes we wanna hurt
someone who has hurt us...
So you can tell Carlos that
he can have the photo albums.
She says that they hold
no sentimental value for her.
And then there are times we just wanna
spare ourselves embarrassment...
I don't know how
these rumors get started.
No, Parker only quit the team
'cause he hurt his ankle.
Of course,
there are some who feel that to rewrite
history Is just another way to lie...
And poor Howard has to
work late again tonight.
Of course,
he does it all f the family.
But what is history anyway...
You say I dated Susan
for a long time.
Do you think I was in love with her?
But a set of lies
agreed upon?
I don't.
I really...
really don't.