Previously on Desperate Housewives...
The Scavos prepared
for a grand opening...
This could be the best thing
that's ever happened to our family.
While Gabrielle had
a few too many drinks...
I'm gonna take
a little nap, okay?
And a cry for help made
Orson lose his cool.
Suicide is the worst thing
that could happen to a family!
Mike got arrested...
Oh, thank God.
And a friendship
hit the rocks.
-For the sake of our friendship...
-Make no mistake,
our friendship is over.
Orson's Mom
was determined...
In the eyes of God,
you're the other woman.
To bring Alma and
Orson back together.
She raped you, and
your mother helped.
I think it's time I told you about
the night about Monique died.
Alma became a prisoner...
Gloria?!
Bree...
was set up
to take a fall.
And Mike was finally able
to remember the past.
Orson Hodge had
always assumed
that the moment
before he died,
his entire life would
flash before his eyes.
But as he fell from the roof of
the Fairview Memorial Hospital,
it wasn't his
life he saw.
It was one night
in particular.
Monique?
I've got wonderful news.
Bonnes nouvelles!
Monique?
There's been
an accident.
Oh, my God.
What have you done?
It was self-defense.
I came to tell her to stay away
from you. She attacked me.
Mother...
she's dead.
I know.
And I'm sorry,
but what's done is done.
No! I'll go to jail.
You killed someone!
I'm your mother!
You've got to help me!
But I loved her.
I once lost someone
I loved, thanks to you.
You owe me.
Hello?
Ms. Polier?
I've got that part
for the sink.
Hello?
Ms. Polier?
Ah, I'm sorry.
I'm Monique's boyfriend.
She's upstairs lying down.
She wasn't feeling well.
Well, I'll just finish up with the
sink and get out of your hair.
Look, why don't you
let me take care of that?
I mean, I'm pretty handy,
and it's getting late.
I don't mind staying.
I've got it under control.
Here, let me, uh,
let me pay you.
That should cover it.
Thanks.
Oh, hey...
Don't forget
your wrench.
You handled that
very well, son.
Now help me
find a tarp.
What  are you doing?
You don't want her identified
through dental records, do you?
I must say,
I never realized your
job was so difficult.
It's not enough to kill her.
You have to desecrate
her body, too?
Get away from her!
Now look what
you've done!
I think my damn
hip's broken.
Help me.
Yes...
Orson Hodge had
always assumed
that his life would
flash before his eyes
the moment
before he died.
Luckily, for Orson...
That moment...
I got a pulse!
Let's get him inside!
Was not scheduled for today.
By Tyno, Wisteria Team
Transcript by FRM
Forom.com & DHsubs.free.fr
The first light
of sunrise.
The sound of
the cat purring.
The smell of
fresh coffee.
Yes, there are many things
a housewife
likes to wake up to.
But an unexpected
guest in her bed...
is not one of them.
Zach?
You're... in your
underwear.
Well, I needed to put on something
to get the morning paper.
You've been
here all night?
Sure.
I'm not one of those guys who
gets up and leaves right after.
Right after what?
Do you wanna
hear me say it?
Fine.
You were...
amazing.
Okay, listen to me
very carefully,
and this is no time
to be vague.
What exactly
was I amazing at?
Please tell me that
once contained a mint.
After a few drinks,
you told me how
lonely you were,
and that I was the kindest man
you'd met in a few years, and, uh...
then you kissed me.
-And then you took off your...
-Okay, okay, stop talking.
I'm getting nauseous.
This is so great.
I have so many
awesome plans for us.
"Us."
Oh, man. It feels so
good to say that.
Oh, God.
Here it comes.
Would you like me
to hold your hair, honey?
No!
Hey, what are
you doing?
I'm lying in bed, thinking
about the opening tonight,
when it hits me...
We could run
out of breadsticks.
Oh, honey, you
have had, what,
four hours sleep in
the past three days?
You need rest. Who cares
if we run out of breadsticks?
I do!
Tonight's the most
important night of my life.
Everything's
gotta be perfect.
Here. Try that.
It's good.
No.  Too salty.
If  they're salty,
we'll sell more beer.
See? You're a genius.
Don't patronize me!
Oh, my God.
This is gonna be a disaster.
Hey, chill out.
You're acting like I did when
I was six months pregnant.
Uh, excuse me.
You were hitting people.
Only two.
And the mailman had the good
taste never to bring that up again.
Come on. Let's go
get some sleep.
The dough maker and the
chairs get delivered at noon.
I know. I'm the one
that put in the order.
I will handle anything
that needs to be done.
And you, take these
and get some sleep.
Come on. We need you
at your best tonight.
You're right.
I'm sorry. Crazy.
Honey glaze.
Honey glaze will cut the
salt in the breadsticks.
Tom, I do not need to be
pregnant to kick your ass.
Now go.
Go on.
Andrew, you're here.
What happened to me?
You kinda had
an accident.
You fell off
our ladder.
Oh, that's right.
Is Orson here?
Yeah, he's at
the hospital but,
he's not
exactly visiting.
Suicide?
No. Orson would never
try to kill himself.
The police are wrong.
It must have been an accident.
But they found his footprints
on the trunk of his car.
The only reason he'd
be up there is to jump.
But why?
Maybe he was
feeling guilty.
For what?
Mom, I looked
at that ladder.
Someone sawed
through the rung.
And you think...
I heard you two in your
room the other day.
You told him to turn
himself in or else...
The next day,
you fall and nearly die.
You think that's
a coincidence?
And you say he's
just down the hall?
Yeah, but don't worry.
I told them not to
let him near you,
and we're gonna get you
home as soon as we can.
Can I help you?
I'm here to pick up
my wife's belongings.
Jane Hainsworth?
Oh, yes.
I'm so sorry
for your loss.
I'll be right back.
You doing okay?
Not really, but having
you here helps.
Oh, hey, Mrs. Mayer.
Andrew, what are you
doing at the hospital?
You haven't heard?
Hey.
Susan.
I just heard from
Andrew what happened.
I had to come see you.
If you want me
to go, uh...
No, no. Come in.
I know we've
been fighting.
Something like this happens, it just
puts everything into perspective.
I am so sorry.
It was all my fault.
If I hadn't got so caught
up in protecting Mike...
Susan, stop.
Mike is innocent.
He had nothing to do with
Monique Polier's murder.
Do you know
something?
Yes, and I intend
to go to the police.
Oh, my God.
Does this have something
to do with Orson's accident?
I can't tell you
right now.
You're just gonna have to
trust me. Can you do that?
Of course.
I should let you rest.
So we're back
to being friends?
We never
really stopped.
Um, excuse me. These
things don't belong to Jane.
Are you sure?
Oh, every couple
has their secrets,
But I'm pretty sure she
wasn't a closet whittler.
"Mike Delfino."
Oh, these are
Mike's things?
Yep. Someone made
a big mistake.
Helen, you screwed
up the labels again!
He had an engagement
ring with him.
Ooh, that's pretty.
You know, Mike and
I are good friends.
I could return these
things to him, if you like.
Sorry. He'll have
to pick 'em up himself.
It's hospital policy.
It's also hospital policy to put the
right labels on the right boxes!
Ian!
Ian, you're not
gonna believe this.
Bree just told me she can
prove Mike's innocent.
What?
It's true.
He's gonna be a free man.
Isn't that great?
Yes, it's bloody
fantastic.
Here.
I'm gonna go get Bree some
flowers. I'll be right back.
No, no, that's great news.
Thank you, doctor.
So Orson's gonna
pull through?
You'd rather
he didn't?
No.
I just don't know what he's gonna
tell the police when he wakes up.
It wasn't your fault.
Orson, falling off that roof
was an accident, right?
Well, sort of.
Sort of?
Depending on what
Orson tells them,
I could get charged
with attempted murder.
Well, I'm so glad she has
you to take care of her,
and  of course your Mom
comes first, Andrew.
And I wouldn't even ask
except, you know,
-we're opening tonight-
-Chairs are here.
Oh, God. Seriously?
Fantastic. Thank you.
It's just two quick hours,
and then we'll get you right
back home with your Mom.
Thank you, Andrew.
Okay. Bye-bye.
Did you finish folding
the takeout menus?
You never asked
me to do that.
I shouldn't have to tell you every little
thing, you know. Show some initiative.
Wait.
Where are my chairs?
I didn't order these.
-You're Lynette Scavo?
-Yes.
Well,  then you
ordered these.
No. Why would I order 50 high
chairs for the opening of a pizzeria?
I don't know.
I thought it was one of
those kiddie pizza places
with the games and
the animatronic rats.
Give me that.
Easy there, sally.
"Animatronic rats."
Where do they find you people?
Okay, okay,
here it is. See?
I ordered 50 of
item number 7-3...
Did we find
the mistake?
I switched
the 7 and the 1.
So... we're
both wrong.
Now this place opens
in five hours.
How long will it
take to fix this?
Hi. I need to rent 50
chairs by tonight at 5:00.
What?
Why not?
What do you mean,
it's bar mitzvah season?
There's no such thing.
You still have five.
I will take those. Scavo.
Okay, that brings us to 22.
Javi, Rico, we got
chairs to find. Move it.
Looks like someone crawled into
a bottle of Merlot last night.
I sort of threw myself
a little birthday party.
So if you don't mind, I'd like
to get back to my dry heaving.
Quick question.
Was that Zach Young I saw leaving
your house 8:00 this morning?
Uh, oh, yeah. Um...
He just came by to, uh...
drop off a birthday card.
Really cute little
cat with balloons.
All right, bye.
Follow-up.
Why was Zach in your driveway
at 7:00 this morning...
In his underwear?
We had sex
last night!
What?!
I mean, I think we did.
That's what he told me.
Weren't you there?
No, I don't remember
anything!
I just woke up, and he
was in bed next to me.
Thanks again, Gaby.
Hey, Carlos.
If you don't remember,
then how can you be sure
that you and Zach had sex?
Well, we were
both half-naked,
and there was
a condom wrapper.
And he said I was amazing,
which totally sounds like me.
He thinks we're a couple now.
You have to help me.
I am not getting involved.
God, I can't believe you bagged
another neighborhood kid.
Where are you going?
To warn the Scavo boys.
I wanna speak
to my wife.
She's  resting.
If we can get back
to these questions...
I fell off a roof.
I need a physician,
not a psychiatrist.
Well, I'm afraid
it's hospital policy
when there's a suspected
suicide attempt.
I didn't try
to kill myself.
But you do
have a certain...
history?
You spent most of 1976
in a psychiatric hospital.
I don't care
to discuss that.
You won't be leaving
here until we do.
My parents were
very religious.
When I was 16,
my father had an affair,
caused quite a scandal
at our church.
He became depressed.
He started drinking heavily.
My mother grew
concerned.
She didn't like
leaving him alone.
One night, she had
to visit a sick friend,
and she asked me
to keep an eye on him.
But I had made plans
with friends.
I thought I could
duck out for a while.
When I got home,
I found him in the bathroom.
You blamed yourself?
I didn't need to.
Mother blamed me
enough for both of us.
That must have caused quite
a strain in your relationship.
Yes.
But now and then,
she suggests little ways
I might make it up to her.
Yes, I'm calling to check
on the status of a patient.
Last name Hodge.
What do you mean,
"which Hodge"?
Gloria!
Thank God. I thought
you'd forgotten about me.
When are you
letting me out of here?
It won't be long now.
In fact, something interesting
happened last night.
Orson tried
to kill himself.
Oh, my goodness.
Is he okay?
He'll be fine.
My point is,
Suicide is hardly the act
of a happily married man.
Gloria, for God
sake, give it up.
He doesn't love me.
He will, dear.
Bree will be
gone soon,
and he'll need a good woman
like you to console him.
What are you gonna
do to Bree?
Gloria?
-Oh, hey, hon.
-Hey.
Did you get
some sleep?
Yes. I'm still kind of groggy
from those pills, but...
And now I'm awake.
Okay, little mix-up
with the new chairs.
Which you were
in charge of.
Okay, okay,
we could point fingers,
but what's important is forgetting
about what we expected,
and focusing on what we
have, which isn't so bad.
I mean, all the different
kinds of chairs
give the place a kind
of bohemian vibe.
Plus, if we get a lot of babies,
look, we're just totally set.
Tom, I'm sorry.
I am. I'm sorry.
I just, I realize
it's not... perfect.
But...
Please say something.
What can I say,
Lynette?
It is what it is.
Why do I have
to babysit Mom?
All my friends are
gonna be at the opening.
Austin was gonna
sneak us beer!
Damn it, Danielle,
I have to work!
Our mother's lying
helpless upstairs
'cause her husband
tried to kill her.
Now for just one night,
could you try to be responsible?
I liked you better when
you were a psychopath!
Here you go.
Oh, you're... here.
I wouldn't have
missed it.
You know how I feel
about Lynette and Tom.
Look, Zach,
I'm glad you're here.
I've been wanting
to talk about us.
Me, too. You, uh,
being in my life now,
having the connection
that we do,
this is really the first time that I've been
happy since my mother killed herself.
Would you excuse
me a second?
Of course, baby.
Hurry back.
I am in hell.
I just tried to break up with
Zach, and the little twerp
played the dead
Mommy card.
Well, you can't let him
make you feel guilty.
But I am guilty.
I don't remember how
we ended up in bed together.
Maybe I led him on.
I gotta be sensitive here.
Could you threaten
him for me?
What?
You know,
intimidate him.
Do the whole jealous,
latin ex-husband thing you do.
Tell him if you can't
have me, nobody can.
Forget it. I'm not gonna
to do that to poor Zach.
Hey, I am looking
out for Zach, too.
If I dump him,
it'll destroy him emotionally.
Better to scare him off.
Please?
Fine.
Thank you!
Okay, look,
there he goes.
Go!
Go get all cholo
on his ass.
Hey, Mr. Solis.
Hey.
Look, I need to talk to you
about something.
It's a little
awkward, but...
Mr. Solis?
What?
You were just saying that
something was awkward?
Never mind.
Forget that
I said anything.
Hey. So how'd it go?
You did not have sex
with Zach young.
Really?
Did he tell you that?
He didn't have to.
What?
I was standing next
to him at the urinal.
I don't care how
drunk you were.
If you had sex with him,
you'd remember.
Little Zach Young?
Well, just how much
would I have remembered?
Hey. What are
you doing here?
I thought Bree
might like some soup.
It's my own
special recipe.
I'm surprised
to find you home.
I thought the whole street
was going to Scavo's tonight.
Well, I was
supposed to go,
but Andrew said I had to
stay home and babysit Mom.
Well, that's just silly.
A vibrant young lady like
you should be at the party,
turning boys' heads.
You go.
I'll look after
your mother.
You mean it?
Just take her
dinner up first.
I don't think I can manage
the tray with my cane.
Thanks, Grandma.
You're the best!
This soup
smells so good.
You wanna score some points?
Don't say I brought it.
Tell her you
made it yourself.
Hey!
Hello?
Over here!
Honey, there is
a line out the door.
We are gonna
make a killing tonight.
I'm happy for you.
For us.
Now it's "us"?
Because I thought I was the one
who was trying to ruin everything.
Hey, look,
I know I overreacted...
Yes, you did.
But I have customers.
The place came
out great, huh?
Sure did.
Looks like, uh,
the whole street's here.
Yeah.
Except for Orson,
who fell off a roof.
You know anything
about that?
Why would you
think that?
I heard you talking to Carlos.
Now answer the question.
I can't talk
about it here.
It's complicated.
It always is with you.
Hey. I just had a slice
of pizza. It's pretty good.
Is it really good,
or are you just pretending
you had a slice?
You and I did not
have sex. Admit it!
Of course we did.
Zach!
How can you claim to care
about me and lie to my face?
I'm sorry.
I'm tired of just
being your friend.
I thought if you saw me as a lover,
you can think of me as a man, not...
not a boy.
Zach, a real
man is honest.
All you've ever
tried to do Is bribe
and trick me into falling
in love with you.
A little advice next time?
Don't play games.
Just stand up and
be the kind of man
a woman would be proud
to share her life with.
Hello!
I think it's high time
to make a toast.
Tom, where are you?
Where... Ah.
Tom, you did it.
There are a lot of people in this room
that didn't think you could pull it off.
Okay, well,
maybe just me.
Anyway, congratulations.
The pizza is excellent,
and the service is sublime.
Cheers.
Speech!
Thank you.
Thank you for coming.
It means everything
in the world to me.
I gotta tell you, when I arrived here this
afternoon, I saw all these weird chairs,
I thought the evening was
gonna be a total disaster.
But now when I look out,
I can't even see the chairs.
I just see people eating,
laughing and
having a great time.
It's absolutely perfect.
And none of this
would've happened
without my amazing
partner Lynette.
Who, uh...
To...
I'm sorry.
I'm a little...
I think what my husband
is trying to say is,
if you really want to test a marriage,
open a restaurant together.
Anyway, thank
you for coming.
Eat a lot and
come back,
'cause our kids
need braces.
Actually, as long as everyone
has their glasses raised,
I have something that
I would like to say.
Well, I thought of waiting
for the perfect romantic spot
in which to ask
this question,
but being here tonight,
enveloped by so much love
and warmth, I realize that, um,
this is the perfect
romantic spot.
Susan Mayer...
Drop the pizza.
Will you make me the happiest man
in the world and be my wife?
Absolutely, yes!
Ladies and gentlemen,
please, I have something
that I'd like to say also.
Gabrielle Solis...
Will you marry me?
Should I clap?
No, there will be
no clapping!
You, moron,
come with me!
Time for your pills,
Mr. Hodge.
It's after 6:00?
I need to speak with my wife.
What room is she in?
Your wife checked out.
Already?
She was very eager
to get home.
Don't worry.
She'll be fine.
I have to talk to her.
Oh, that reminds me.
Your mother called.
She said she didn't
want to wake you up,
and she wanted to make sure
we'd be keeping you overnight.
Moms are like that,
so protective.
Bree, it's me.
Are you there?
Please, pick up.
Bree?
Please, somebody,
pick up the phone.
I know that
you're mad.
I'm not mad,
Zach. I'm done!
But you said
to be honest.
I did not say to
humiliate me!
I'm sorry. All right?
I was just trying...
What do you
want from me?
I want you to
leave me alone!
This friends thing isn't gonna work
'cause you're always gonna want more,
and I'm never gonna
love you... ever.
20 years from now when you're
all middle-aged and alone,
you'll regret this.
Okay, I'll take
my chances.
Thought you
might need this.
Bless you.
So how did it go
with Seabiscuit?
He's devastated.
Of course.
It's my fault.
I should've known he couldn't handle
the whole "let's be friends" thing.
I don't blame him.
I'm having kind of a hard time
myself being just your friend,
Watching you
with other guys,
being your confidant.
Really?
I think it's been nice.
For you, maybe.
Look, seriously, I don't know how much
longer I'm gonna be able to keep this up.
Well, hang in there
as long as you can,
'cause I still need you.
I'll do my best.
What are you
doing here?
I have better things to
do than babysit Mom.
She's fine.
Gloria's watching her.
What?
I told you Mom's ready to
go to the cops about Orson.
How could you leave her at
home with his crazy mother?
She brought soup!
Gloria?
What are you
doing here?
I came to take
care of you.
I'm so sleepy.
Good. Then the
pills are working.
Andrew?
Danielle?
They're gone.
It's just us.
Now...
You rest, hon.
I'm gonna draw you
a nice, warm bath.
Oh, Bree...
I wish I could make you understand
how deeply I regret having to do this.
Monique...
that was easy.
She was a slut.
You're a good woman.
You didn't know Orson
already had a wife.
But he did.
And he made a vow
to her before God.
What sort of mother would
I be if I let him break it?
I'm sorry.
But I will not let him
be his father's son.
Wake up, Mr. Hodge.
I've got dinner.
That water's not
too hot, is it?
No.
It's just right.
Mom? Are you all right?
Andrew?
You've done this
before, haven't you?
No!
Is she all right?
She will be.
Get her some blankets
and some dry clothes.
Orson?
Orson!
Something's wrong.
I think I'm...
having a stroke.
You need an
ambulance, mother.
It's too bad there's no one here
who'd dream of calling you one.
What are you doing?
I don't want her
dying in our house.
Hey there.
Are you all right?
Your mother...
She tried to kill me.
Don't worry about her.
She's never gonna
hurt you again,
and neither will Alma.
Alma?
She's dead.
What?
I don't know what happened,
but she's gone.
And she's taking
our troubles with her.
Tomorrow morning,
one of our neighbors
will stumble on
a gruesome surprise.
Two bodies side by side.
The police will conclude
that Alma fell from the roof,
and when my mother found her,
she suffered a stroke.
When they search
the house,
they'll find the note Alma wrote
when she faked her suicide,
and next to it, a bag
containing Monique's teeth.
In the face of
such evidence,
they'll have no choice but to drop
the charges against Mike Delfino.
Now, you and I are gonna take that
honeymoon we never got around to.
I'd love that.
What about
your mother?
After all the things she's done,
she's just gonna get off scot-free?
Thank you, doctor.
I know you did all you could.
Good news, mother.
The doctor said your stroke has
left you completely paralyzed.
You can't even speak.
Which means all our secrets
will be safe forever.
Oh, here's the best part.
Your brain is
functioning normally.
So I don't have to worry
about putting you in jail.
You're already there.
Now,
I'm gonna turn
your head,
so you can watch
me walk away.
You don't wanna miss it,
'cause it's the last time
you will ever see me.
A surprising thing
happened to Orson Hodge
as he'd left Fairview
Memorial Hospital.
His life began to flash
before his eyes.
But it wasn't his
past he saw.
It was his future.
Ordinary suburban days,
filled with ordinary
suburban moments,
each made beautiful because
of the housewife by his side.
Yes, Orson could finally envision
a life free from secrets and pain.
And he couldn't wait
for it to begin.
Honey,
I'm home.