www.tvsubtitles.net
Previously on Desperate Housewives...
- I want a child.
- We made a deal. No kids.
- Tampering with prescriptions...
- File on Noah's daughter.
...uncovering evidence...
What are we looking for?
- What was that?
...breaking and entering...
- Bree is a lady.
- A very beautiful, classy lady.
Remember, they tend to end up
with doctors, not pharmacists.
...and a whole lot of revenge.
[Mary Alice]
Since she was a little girl,
Susan Mayer wanted to be a mother
in the worst way.
OK, I'm gonna get your bottle.
You're so cute, yeah!
And from the first day she brought Julie
home from the hospital...
[baby grunts]
Oh! How did you...
She was.
Oh, my gosh!
Despite her desire
to do well by her daughter...
[baby cries]
...Susan suffered
through countless failures.
So sorry!
Of course, it took Susan
a few years to realize
that even the best of parents
make mistakes now and then.
[Tapping]
But now that Julie was a tenage girl,
Susan had started to realize...
- [sighs]
...there was no room for error.
Julie, what is Zach doing out there?
I told you not to speak to him.
That's why he's throwing gravel
at my window.
Right, that's it.
I'm gonna handle this once and for all.
Zach, what do you think you're... Ow!
[Susan] Ow! Ow!
Mrs. Mayer, I am so sorry.
One pebble wasn't working
so I tried a whole handful.
- Ow... ow...
- I'll make it up to you.
- How, will you give me your corneas?
- Mom, lay back.
I wanted to talk to Julie. She hasn't
been returning my phone calls.
Well, I'm here now.
What do you want?
Come on, Julie.
I just wanna see you again.
You know. Talk, hang out.
Maybe it would be better
if we just cooled it for a while, OK?
Why?
You threw rocks in her mother's face.
How's that for a start?
Thank you so much.
I've been trying to break up with him
for weeks. Finally, an excuse.
Yes, Susan had failed
many times as a mother.
You did good, Mom.
So she took her victories
where she found them.
You're welcome.
Spring comes every year
to Wisteria Lane.
It's the time when flowers
start to bloom.
When butterflies
emerge from their cocoons.
When bes begin to search for nectar.
[Buzzing]
Spring is also the time
when a young man's fancy turns to...
...obsession.
We must buy that.
Hello, there.
Oh, my heavenly days!
Rex, look, it's George.
Nice to see you, Bree.
Dr. Van De Kamp.
George.
So, how's your health?
Not good. My cardiologist is an idiot.
The doctor upped his dosage twice
and it's still not helping.
I'm sure it'll all work itself out.
It's funny running into you both.
I have tickets to a bonsai exposition
in Mount Pleasant Friday night.
- Would you like to go?
- I would love to! Rex?
A whole evening of bonsai trees?
Wouldn't it be easier to shoot me?
Probably.
Well, why don't we
just go by ourselves, then?
Actually, Bree,
we have that thing, Friday night.
What? We don't have a thing.
I think your husband's trying to say
he doesn't want you going out with me.
Rex, are you still jealous?
No.
We dated during the separation
but we're just friends now, aren't we?
Strictly platonic.
- But if you feel threatened...
- I don't feel threatened.
Good. Then it's a date.
Are you going to make a purchase today?
I have finally convinced Rex
to buy his first orchid.
Study up. I hate people
who own precious flowers
and don't know
how to take care of them.
You know what I hate? Weeds.
They pop up and you have
to work so hard to get rid of them.
I find, with the right chemicals,
you can get rid of almost anything.
- See you Friday.
- Bye.
Mrs. Solis, what a surprise. We haven't
seen you in here in quite some time.
My husband and I went through a down-
sizing phase but we snapped out of it.
Life is good.
Oh, and this would make it
so much better!
Excellent.
Slip inside, see how that feels.
Oh! I'd love to have this
in my driveway by Saturday.
I'm having a big barbecue.
I want everyone to see it.
- How exciting. What's the occasion?
- My husband's going-away party.
Really? Where's he going?
It's a sort of
government-sponsored sabbatical.
How long is he going to be gone?
Eight months.
Six with good behavior.
- Isn't the leather interior wonderful?
- It is.
It is.
It's just the smell's a little intense.
It was imported from Italy.
It's 100ยบ% Italian calf.
[Vomiting]
I'm so sorry!
It just hit me out of nowhere.
It's so weird. Smells have been
making me nauseous lately.
- Boobs tender? Achy back?
- Yeah.
- Has it been going around?
- Only for centuries.
I went through it carrying my eldest.
The truth is,
you're never gonna fit a child
safety seat in the back of that Spyder.
The four-doors are much roomier.
Wha... Wait, uh... I'm sorry, you...
You think I'm pregnant?
No, I'm not pregnant.
Oh, you have all the symptoms,
I just assumed.
- Well, you assumed wrong.
- I'm sorry.
- I'm on the pill, for God's sakes!
- OK.
And I don't want a four-door.
I want a sexy little convertible.
- I wanna buy one, now.
- I'll start the paperwork.
Well, not this one.
I vomited in this one.
Right. We'll find you a fresh one.
[Phone rings]
[Woman] Peterson Advertising.
Lynette!
- You forgot your Halpern file.
- Oh, my God. Lynette.
If there was one person
Lynette never expected to se again,
it was Annabel Foster.
Eight years earlier,
Annabel had begged Tom to marry her.
But he told her
he wasn't the marrying kind.
Then one day,
Tom happened to met
a rising young executive
by the name of Lynette Lindquist.
And after a few torrid weks,
Tom decided perhaps he was
the marrying kind after all,
causing an embittered Annabel
to move back to Chicago.
Permanently.
Or so Lynette had hoped.
You look fantastic!
Thank you! And you!
You're here, in the office.
Tom's office.
Going on three months now.
- Oh.
- Didn't Tom tell you?
It, uh... must have slipped his mind.
[Forced laugh]
Ah! Afraid to tell the wife you're
working with the old girlfriend, huh?
I guess that makes me
your dirty little secret!
[Annabel laughs]
Well, I'll let you get back to work.
- See you later.
- Can't wait.
Oh, I almost forgot.
Your file. Here.
Hey, Paul. What's up?
Something's been nagging me,
I want to talk to you.
- OK.
- That night I found you in my house.
- Why were you really there?
- You know why.
- I came to drop off your key.
- Some things were moved around.
- What were you looking for?
- What are you talking about?
Do I have to call the police?
Do whatever you want.
Suit yourself.
OK. OK! Susan made me do it.
She has this fixation
on why Mary Alice killed herself.
Keeps blathering on about
blackmail notes and dead babies.
She got really hot and bothered
when she found the name "Angela".
Written on one of your video tapes?
Did she find what she was looking for?
No. You came home before
she had a chance to watch the video.
I see.
She sort of thinks you're evil.
Thank you, Edie.
What was that all about?
Susan Mayer's obsession with Mary Alice
almost got me arrested.
Now Paul's after her.
If I liked her better, I'd warn but...
You know.
Thanks.
[Chatter]
Susan.
Well... Talk to you girls later.
Still avoiding me, huh?
No. No.
What do you want?
I heard that you and Edie
broke into Paul Young's house.
- Who told you that?
- Edie.
Well... Yeah, we did. Um...
We were just looking...
It doesn't matter, it was dumb.
I want you to stay away from that guy.
I was planning on doing that anyway.
Good.
Mike.
I know why I was planning to stay
away from him. Why do you want me to?
I just know he's a bad guy.
So please, don't mess with him.
I won't.
I promise.
So, I've been thinking
about the pharmacist.
George. What about him?
I don't think you should
go out with him.
Please, he's the only friend I have
who's interested in cultural things.
Bree, I'm worried because
he is obviously still in love with you.
No, he just wants to be friends.
He told me so.
Well, what else
would a man in love say?
- He's desperate to spend time with you.
- He does not seem desperate to me.
I saw the way his hands trembled
when you touched his shoulder.
They did?
When we first started dating,
the same thing happened to me.
I don't remember that.
Listen, continuing to see him
would just give him false hope.
Well, I certainly
don't want to hurt him.
- Again.
- No, you don't.
I even think it would be a good idea
to switch pharmacies.
Really?
Well, OK.
You know what I'm gonna
miss most about him?
George always has a way
of making me feel good about myself.
Yeah, he's a terrific guy.
Honey, do your hands still tremble
when they touch me?
No. But, come on,
we've been married 18 years.
Yes, we have.
And you still don't know
when I need you to lie.
Excuse me, this home pregnancy test,
is it a good one?
I guess.
OK, um...
- Do you have a rest room?
- It's for employees only.
Oh, it's right over there, Mrs. Solis.
Help yourself.
Thank you.
What did I tell you
about being rude to customers?
Stick a smile on your face
or I'll keep you in back
where no one has to look at you.
Bree, what a pleasant surprise!
What brings you here?
Didn't we fill Dr. Van De Kamp's
prescription last week?
George, as it turns out, I won't be able
to go with you to the bonsai expo.
Why not?
It would be a mistake for us
to spend too much time together.
Dr. Van De Kamp said something
about me. What was it?
- It doesn't matter.
- Please, tell me.
He said you're still in love with me.
[Sighs] That's... That's stupid.
I'm not in love with you. I'm not.
The truth is, I'm in love with Ginger.
Ginger? The stock girl?
Yes. It's very serious.
Oh! Why didn't you tell me?!
Well, we're taking it slow,
but she is definitely the one.
Oh, my goodness,
this changes everything.
Listen, a friend of mine
is having a barbecue on Saturday.
- You should come.
- Really?
Yes, and bring Ginger.
Ginger? I don't know if she can make it.
You have to bring Ginger because
if Rex sees the two of you together,
he'll relax.
Oh. Uh...
- OK.
- [Gabrielle] Son of a bitch!
You are out of toilet paper.
Bree, I'll call you later.
Lynette!
Hey, honey!
- Are you home?
- Three months?
God, you... scared the hell out of me.
Were you ever gonna tell me?
I wanted to, but I kept putting it off.
I knew how you'd react.
Congratulations,
you read me like a book.
Why would you hire that woman?
Well, technically, Peterson found her.
I just vouched for her.
- Tom...
- Honey, I'm just helping her out.
It's the least I can do. She was
devastated when I left her for you.
I felt bad.
Do you still have feelings for her?
All right, I'm not talking to you.
You can tell me. You still care
about her, don't you? Just a teeny bit?
I was just trying to be a good guy.
That's all.
- You can't work with her.
- What do you want me to do? Quit?
Talk to Peterson,
he can get her transferred.
Weren't you guys
starting something up in Belize?
- Honey, you're crazy.
- No, I'm serious.
If she stays, I will haunt your office.
I'll bring your lunch every day.
I'll bring the kids to visit,
I will change diapers on your desk.
Every birthday cake in the break room,
every retirement party,
I will be there, watching her.
Well, I'd better
get you a parking space,
'cause she's staying.
Don't you think it spices up the room?
[Doorbell rings]
I was just leaving you a gift
to apologize for,
you know,
throwing gravel in your face.
- Well, you didn't have to do that.
- I kinda did.
- See, I want us to be friends.
- Yeah, well...
- That's not gonna happen.
- Why not?
Aside from you blinding me?
Several weeks ago,
you freaked out in my house.
You screamed,
you threw furniture around...
[sighs] OK, I realize that
I was out of line that night.
But I was upset.
And we have to get over that,
for Julie's sake.
For Julie's sake?
How does it make her feel that her
mother and boyfriend can't get along?
Julie does not think of you
as her boyfriend.
In fact, I don't think
she wants anything to do with you.
- She said that?
- Yeah.
- I don't believe you.
- Believe whatever you want.
It's because you tell her stuff about me
that's not true!
[Paul] Zach! Come here!
Right now!
Please. Don't ruin this for me.
[Mrs. Huber] How do you know Mary Alice?
- Who?
- Mary Alice Young.
She lives next door to me in Fairview.
She's here in this picture with you.
That's Angela Forrest, we worked
at the rehab center 15 years ago.
Don't be dense.
Don't you think I know my own neighbor?
Does this Mary Alice have children?
A teenager. A boy.
What?
Angela and I worked with
a very disturbed young woman
who gave birth to a baby boy.
About a year later,
Angela and her husband disappeared.
Not long after that,
I heard that the child was missing too.
People said it was just a coincidence.
But in my heart, I always hoped
she had given him a proper home.
Are you saying she stole the baby?
Don't look shocked, Martha.
It makes your face look fat.
The biological mother was a drug addict.
If Angela really is your neighbor,
which I doubt,
then that child was very lucky.
Lynette, hey! If you're looking for Tom,
he's out with a client.
No. I actually wanted to see you.
You know, that's really funny,
I was thinking the same thing.
I've been here all this time. We should
go out, for lunch, the two of us.
Yeah. I'll check my book.
So, Annabel... [clears throat]
...do you have feelings for Tom?
- What?
- You heard me.
OK, you wanna talk about this?
Let's talk.
Yes, Tom and I were in love.
But he married you.
I'm not looking
to break up a happy couple.
Anyway, that's rather
more your speed, isn't it?
Morning, ladies.
Just coming in for a little more fuel.
Yup. One man's sludge
is another man's liquid gold.
[Slurps]
Well, back to the trenches.
Watch your step. Tom and I are a team.
Our marriage is rock solid.
Nothing you do could ever break that up.
Then why are you down here right now,
warning me?
[Snort of derision]
[Bells ring]
Gabrielle! What brings you down here?
Oh, sweet Mother of God,
what have you done this time?
- You're pregnant?
- Yes.
And it's impossible, I'm on the pill.
Which you probably think is a sin,
but it works.
It's a 99.9ยบ% effective sin.
Maybe it's in that one tenth
of a percent that God resides.
Couldn't wait to throw that in,
could you?
God is screwing with me.
He doesn't like the way
I live my life so he's punishing me.
Have you done something
that would warrant being punished?
The gardener?
- I thought that was over.
- No, it was, and then...
You just had to be there.
My point is, I'd be an awful mother.
I'm selfish and self-centered...
The only person
more self-centered is Carlos.
He's so self-centered, he doesn't
know how self-centered I am.
We'd be terrible parents.
Gabrielle, I'd like to help,
but I'm not sure what it is you want.
It's just, I wanna know
who to be angry at.
Here's a thought: Don't be angry.
Be thankful.
Children are a gift, are they not?
I don't have time for this crap.
I have a party to plan.
Thanks.
- Edie, hey.
- Hi.
- Wow. Things are really coming along.
- Yeah. Slowly and expensively.
It'll be worth it.
You're doing an amazing job.
So look, you're basically... a predator
and I need some advice.
I know Tom loves me,
but I don't trust this woman.
I think there's an agenda there.
I don't know.
Maybe I'm being paranoid.
No, no. You did the right thing
coming to me.
There are two ways to approach this.
First, what kind of shape
is this woman in?
Fantastic shape, she's gorgeous.
OK. Now there's really only
one way to approach this.
- You're gonna have to act fast.
- I'm listening.
It's pretty simple.
When I feel threatened by a woman,
I pull her in.
I make her my best friend.
You said you didn't have
any female friends.
I don't. And I've never felt threatened
by another woman either.
But the point is...
- Keep your friends close...
- Keep your enemies closer.
Tom. We're having a dinner party.
I'm thinking of inviting Annabel.
- We're not moving.
- Susan knows something. Edie said...
I don't care what Edie said!
I'm not leaving Julie!
You wanna risk our lives, our future,
over some... schoolyard crush?
It's more than that. Julie loves me.
Then why does she refuse to see you?
Mrs. Mayer lies to her. If it wasn't
for that, she would be with me.
Are you sure?
- Julie's a very special girl.
- I know.
She could have
just about any boy she wanted.
I think you're a wonderful kid.
I do, but...
You're not that special, Zach.
Not really.
- She kissed me.
- Lately?
Let's pack our bags and get out of here.
Leave this whole mess behind
and start over.
And there will be other girls,
I promise.
No!
If Susan goes to the police, it's over.
They'll take me away. Take you away.
Don't you get that?
If Julie doesn't love me anymore,
it doesn't matter.
None of it matters.
Oh, McGruder had absolutely
no idea what was going on.
During the entire shoot, he was
practically holding Benson's hand!
After the way Burnham screwed him over,
I'd be nervous too!
My God, it was awful!
Excuse me, I need to get in here
so I can clear the plates.
- You want some help?
- I'm good.
Oh... Looks like we got company.
Hey, guys. Isn't it time for bed?
Oh, they never get to see you.
Let 'em stay up for a while.
OK, come here.
I want you to meet someone.
- This is Miss Foster.
- Hi.
She's an old, old friend
of your Daddy's.
- What you got there?
- A picture we painted.
Let me have a look at that.
[Porter] It's all of us with Mommy
and Daddy. We're really happy.
Oh, that is so adorable.
- When did you do this?
- Today. Mom told us to.
I told them to paint something nice.
The sentiment's theirs.
- But you told us to.
- Hold on, grown-ups are talking.
Well, this is really neat.
Hey, how would you boys
like to paint my portrait one day?
Sure, you're pretty.
OK, great. So like your dad said,
it's time for bed.
I'll take 'em back upstairs.
Come on, guys.
Thank you.
- [Boys giggle]
- [Tom] Here we go.
I must say,
your home is warm and inviting,
your children
are absolutely precious.
This whole evening was practically
a commercial for the perfect family.
You think?
You couldn't have planned it any better.
And I mean that.
Good.
[Gasps]
Hello, Susan.
Paul...
Hi.
I understand you and Edie
went snooping through my house.
- Huh?
- It's OK, I'm not mad.
So, what do you want to know
about Angela?
It was Mary Alice's birth name.
She was named after her aunt Angela.
When she was a teenager, they fell out
so she changed her name to Mary Alice.
This was before we were married, so
forgive me if I'm hazy on the details.
That's it? That's the explanation?
Ridiculously simple, isn't it?
She changed her name because
she got in a fight with her aunt?
That doesn't seem like
something Mary Alice would do.
Neither did suicide,
but we both know she did it.
So, can we finally put this behind us?
Or do you need to break into my home
for anything else?
Uh...
No. Um...
I'm good, thanks.
Though, if you wouldn't mind,
I'd like to see that videotape I found.
The one marked Angela.
It would be nice
to see Mary Alice when she was young.
I'm afraid that box of tapes
was thrown out with the trash.
OK, then.
Susan, I'm serious when I say I hope
you'll leave my family alone now.
This endless suspicion of yours
has become very tiring.
Yeah, I couldn't agree more.
[Cell phone rings]
Oh, that's my cell. Sorry.
OK.
My God, it's Peterson. Excuse me.
- Peterson?
- Hello?
Yeah.
So, that was quite a show
you put on tonight.
Show?
The boys paintings, all these references
to how happy we are?
Why not subtly remind Annabel
you're happily married?
It wasn't subtle.
And it's an insult to me.
I did not mean it that way.
Are you so insecure
that you have to pull that crap?
[Whispers] Keep your voice down!
It doesn't matter if she has feelings
for me as long as I'm not interested.
Have I ever, ever given you
any reason to doubt me?
Anyone is capable of anything.
The first time we met,
you were cheating.
With you! Cheating with you!
It's a pattern of behavior.
Give me a break!
Well, what am I supposed to do?
You hire your old girlfriend and don't
tell me about it for three months?
If I'd told you on day one,
you'd still jump down my throat.
- Annabel is ancient history.
- She's in the next room.
How long do we have to be married,
how long until you trust me?
I trust you.
How many times have you said, "Touch
another woman and I'll take the boys
and you'll never see us again"?
That's just... something
wives say to their husbands.
Not all wives.
God, Lynette, you're just so convinced
that I'm gonna be unfaithful!
It makes me sick,
the distrust, the paranoia...
You know, it seems
you won't be happy
until you drive me out
to prove yourself right!
OK, wait. Forget I said that.
It's too late.
You said it.
Then just consider it something
that husbands say to their wives.
[Door opens]
Well, Peterson's on cloud nine.
He discovered some inside scoop
on the Metro account.
The bad news is, we have
to re-do the entire presentation.
- Tonight?
- They need it first thing.
Peterson says
we might be pulling an all-nighter.
I can't drive, I've been drinking.
I'll drive. Come on.
- Thanks.
- Don't worry, Lynette.
I'll deliver him back to you
as soon as I can.
Please do!
[Music and chatter]
Honey, take over a minute.
I'm giving a speech.
Make sure they stay
pink like that, OK?
Are you OK?
Oh! Yeah, I just didn't realize
how disgusting meat could be.
Everyone, I just wanted to say it means
a lot to me that all of you came.
And as you know, in a few days,
I'm taking a little
government-sponsored vacation.
Lucky for me, breakfast is included.
[Laughter]
- Oh, God
- [Carlos] The bottom line is,
I'm going to jail,
and when a man goes away to jail,
which I hope none of you
here ever have to do,
he sees who his real friends are.
So thanks.
[All] Hear, hear!
Excuse you.
Stay put until I need you.
Don't talk to anybody
and for God's sake, don't get drunk.
I'm supposed to be
at my cousin's wedding.
It's not a wedding, it's a commitment
ceremony. Now sit down and...
...try to... fit in.
I got you a hotdog.
No, thanks, I'm full.
They have a croquet set.
Wanna go hit some balls?
- No.
- That's fine. I can just sit here.
Zach.
I don't wanna be your girlfriend
or hang out.
I want you to leave me alone, OK?
OK.
[Sighs]
In that moment,
while looking at the pills that
had ben so obviously tampered with,
Gabrielle's nausea was suddenly replaced
by an even stronger sensation.
Rage.
[Inaudible]
What are you doing?
I'm so sorry. That was an accident.
Answer my question.
What are you doing here?
- I was invited.
- By who?
You know what?
I don't believe I have to answer to you.
- I think you do.
- What's going on here?
He crashed the party. This guy
clearly is not taking no for an answer.
It's OK. George has a girlfriend.
You brought her, didn't you?
- He doesn't have a girlfriend.
- I do so.
She's right over there.
- That's his girlfriend?
- See? We were worried for nothing.
So, any time you want to apologize...
Oh, come on, Rex.
You owe George some sort of gesture.
Oh, what the hell.
[They shriek]
[Laughs]
Rex, have you lost your mind?!
To be fair, I only pushed him.
Carlos! You son of a bitch!
I am pregnant and it's all your fault.
Wow. This is turning into
one hell of a party. [laughs]
Are you OK?
I think I can honestly say, no, I'm not.
I'm so sorry.
Thanks.
But you know what they say about kids?
That you can't imagine
having them until you do,
and then you can't imagine
life without them?
It's true.
All I'm saying is,
maybe this is a blessing in disguise.
I don't know who the father is.
What?
Yeah.
- So you and John have still been...?
- Yeah.
Gabby!
I know, Susan,
I don't know what I'm gonna do!
- [Both scream]
- Oh! Oh, my God!
- Oh, my God! That's my house!
- I'll call 911!
Yes, that's-that's my house!
Oh! Oh!
Oh, my...! Look, my kitchen!
Oh, it's a big fire!
Turns out, someone left the gas on
with candles burning.
That's not possible.
We don't burn candles during the day.
Uh, well, I did have a French
vanilla candle burning earlier, but...
I'm almost positive I blew it out.
You're almost positive?
Yes! I did!
I did, I... I think.
[Fireman] The fire was contained.
The damage could have been
far more extensive.
You've gotta be
more careful from now on.
Don't worry. We will be.
- Bree, hi.
- Hi.
You left the party so quickly,
I didn't have a chance to apologize
to you for what Rex did.
George, I'm so sorry he humiliated you
in front of all those people.
- I don't know what got into him.
- Isn't it obvious? He hates me.
No, he doesn't hate you,
he doesn't even know you.
- You don't really even know him.
- I know this much.
He's not gonna let us be friends.
Well, that's not his choice to make.
What if he asks you
not to see me any more?
What if he orders you not to?
Well, I decide who I need in my life,
and I've decided that I need you.
And that's all there is to it.
He could make it awfully difficult
for you to spend time with me.
Well, who says he has to know
how I spend my free time?
[Laughs]
[Susan] I'm having trouble
with the family across the stret.
I think one of them
may have set a fire in my house.
And I don't know why,
but I fel like it's got something
to do with my friend who killed herself.
I called the police,
but they didn't take me seriously.
This family's got a secret,
a bad secret.
I'm in over my head.
I need you to find out
everything there is to know
about Paul Young and his family.
Do you think you can help me?
As a matter of fact,
I know I can.
[Mary Alice] Spring comes every year
to Wisteria Lane.
But not everyone remembers
to stop and smell the flowers.
Some are too busy
worrying about the future.
Or mistakes they've made in the past.
Others are preoccupied
with not getting caught.
It's a window!
Or thinking of ways
to catch someone else.
Still, there will always be a few
who remember to take a moment and
appreciate what spring has given them.
Just as there will always be those
who prefer to sit in the dark,
brooding over everything they've lost.