Previously on...
Lynette found that dating Tom's boss...
If I asked you to have Tom
work a few nights this week,
you'd do it?
You just say the word.
Had its advantages.
I'm sending Tom to Mumbai for a year.
Julie made a big decision about her baby...
I'm gonna keep her.
And the baby's father made a commitment.
I'll get a job.
I'll take... I'll take classes.
I'll do whatever it takes.
- Carlos and Gaby argued...
- Carlos.
I am not gonna let Bree
take the fall for a crime I committed.
After Bree was arrested for murder.
This is one of those times where
the best things you can do
is do nothing.
But Bree's attorney was confident...
Did you, uh, have some
new thoughts on the case?
Why don't we discuss them over dinner?
As well as convincing.
Since Bree Van de Kamp was arrested,
she had experienced
a wide range of emotions.
One moment, she felt afraid.
The next, she was angry.
And through it all, she felt ashamed.
But now that her trial was approaching,
she was beginning to feel...
a little rattled.
Bree, are you okay?
Yeah. Just all this witness preparation
is making me nervous.
Gaby's been in there for ages.
Trip's very thorough.
He just wants to make
sure we're all ready.
- There you are. That took a while.
- No kidding.
I haven't been grilled like that
since Carlos got my last credit card bill.
Well, as alibi witnesses,
you're gonna be asked about
every detail of the night
So... how many dinner guests
were there that night?
14.
- What color dress was Bree wearing?
- Red.
What sauce did she serve with the chicken?
Oh. I got this.
Barbecue?
Gaby, of all the things
I've been accused of,
the idea that I would serve barbecue sauce
at a dinner party!
Oh, you're right. I'm sorry.
That sounds way worse than
saying you killed Alejandro.
Wait. Uh... Who's Alejandro?
Uh, my gardener.
I'm always getting...
my mexicans confused...
which I'm allowed to do,
because I'm mexican.
I gotta run. You, uh,
you gonna be all right?
Of course. With you in my corner,
how can I not be?
Okay. What was that
little prom photo moment
with the hands?
We warned you about this.
You're still going after him, aren't you?
Of course not. I am totally
focused on the case,
and so is he.
Okay, fine. What am I supposed to do?
He is the most intelligent,
caring, charming man
I have met in ages.
And by the way, it isn't
exactly a one-way street.
He's been showing quite a bit
of interesting in me, too.
- Um, Bree...
- And besides, if I reject him,
he might be too humiliated
- to do a good job on my case.
- Yeah?
Something tells me he's gonna bounce back.
Yes, after Bree Van de Kamp was arrested,
she felt a range of emotions.
But the one thing she
didn't expect to feel...
was jealousy.
At the Fairview childbirth center,
there are certain conversations
you expect to hear...
discussions about the magic
of a changing body...
Look at me. I'm a cow.
The beauty of natural childbirth.
Just so you know, I'm getting the drugs.
Or the importance of healthy nutrition.
Take a chip, lose a hand.
But Julie Meyer found herself
having a conversation...
I can't believe Bree's
on trial for murder.
I mean, come on.
Killers don't wear aprons.
That was rather unexpected.
I know. It sucks.
You know what else sucks?
Somebody trying to relax you
by talking about a murder.
You're right. I'm sorry.
So what would be a good
thing for you to visualize
that might help relax you?
Me punching Porter in
the face for being late.
Okay. Forget visualization.
How about we try
some of that breathing stuff again?
Ugh. No. I hate that "Hee-hee-hee."
Feels stupid.
I know. But it works.
Relaxes you when you start
to get stressed out.
Okay, nice job, everyone.
We're gonna show the birthing DVD now.
Julie, sorry, sorry, sorry.
I had to clean out
the fryer before I could leave.
No worries. Plus you
smell like french fries.
I love french fries.
It's because you're about to go through...
You missed, like, the whole class.
She did great. Let me tell you,
this girl can visualize.
I planned on getting out early,
but a shift opened up,
and I had to take it.
What do you want me to say?
I want you to say that you'll be on time
for one thing we do as
we get ready to have this baby.
"Hee-hee-hee-hee."
It's not funny, Mrs. Delfino.
Look. I said I'm sorry.
The point is, I'm here now,
and I'm 100% focused and ready to help.
Just stay calm.
The crowning begins,
and the head of the baby becomes visible.
Hello. This is Bree Van de Kamp.
May I please speak with Trip?
Oh. Was he having lunch alone?
Oh, right. The blonde woman
with the convertible.
I see. Right.
Thank you.
Okay, I know there's been a lot of talk
about what you should wear to the trial,
so I've selected a few outfits
that just scream "Acquittal."
What do you think?
Black and white stripes?
Oh, good point. Don't need to
put an idea in the jury's mind.
How about ruffles? I read somewhere
that no one has ever been
convicted while wearing ruffles.
- Well...
- Okay. You're right.
There's always a first time.
To hell with ruffles.
How about this one?
It's lovely, but I am
being accused of sleeping
with a total stranger and killing him.
And red is the color of
blood and whores. Got it.
Don't worry. We'll find something else.
Bree, something wrong?
Apart from me standing trial
for murder in three days, no.
Life is good.
Relax. It's gonna be okay.
And remember, you're actually innocent.
Juries can sense things like that.
- I hope you're right.
- Of course I am.
And Trip's a brilliant lawyer.
He's gonna get you off in no time.
I'm just worried that he's been
a little distracted lately.
He seems fine to me.
I have some other dresses in the back.
Let me bring 'em out for you.
It's gonna turn out fine, Bree.
Honestly, I'm not worried at all.
India?
Not India. He said he's going to Mumbai.
That's in India, you idiot.
- How long are you gonna be gone?
- A year.
What? Dad, you're gonna miss
my eighth grade graduation.
It won't be so bad.
We can send him pictures.
We can skype.
So he's supposed to teach me
to drive over the computer?
And he's gonna miss the birth of my baby.
I am sorry, guys.
Look, I talked to my boss.
He's not changing his mind.
There's nothing I can do.
Besides, it's... it's just for a year.
It'll go by like that.
Daddy, no!
I don't want you to go.
I know. I love you so much, baby.
Guys, could I have
a minute alone with your dad?
Yeah, sure.
Guys, it's gonna be okay.
We're gonna get through this!
I don't know how we're
gonna get through this.
So how did Jane take the news?
Um, timing could've been better.
We're not exactly in
a good place right now.
Well, maybe some time
apart will do you good.
Hmm. Maybe.
It's gonna be...
really weird being so far away.
I know. It's gonna be so hard on the kids.
Actually, I was talking about you.
I don't think we've ever been apart
for more than a month.
Who's gonna tell me what to do?
What to think?
Whether your shoes are on the right feet.
Exactly.
I'm really gonna miss you.
I'm...
so sorry.
Why?
There's nothing you can do about it.
Hello.
Are you looking for Trip?
Yes. Well, he's meeting
with the judge on my case.
I'll wait for him.
So how exactly do you know Trip?
He... hires me from time to time.
And what is the nature of your work?
I really can't say.
Discretion's an important part of my job.
Oh. I see. Well, part of your discretion
is falling out of your blouse.
Excuse me? Look, this is
Mr. Weston's place of business.
Maybe you should meet him
in your place of business...
perhaps a seedy motel
room or a street corner.
Are you calling me a hooker?
Well, if the push-up bra fits,
or in your case, doesn't...
That's it. Screw you, lady.
Tell Trip I'm off his case.
Lindsay. Lindsay.
- Trip?
- What the hell?
Uh, she wanted me to tell
you that she's off the case.
What was she doing on the case?
She's a private investigator
who was working on
a really big lead for us.
Wh-why did she quit?
No idea.
I'd better go talk to her.
No! I mean, you know how careful
you have to be with some women.
They can misinterpret the littlest things.
I'll talk to her.
So what do you think, maid of honor?
Nice.
You do realize you're gonna
have to wear this... in public?
You got a problem with it?
No. It's just... the purple
is such a... bold choice.
Aren't you afraid it's gonna
pull focus from the bride?
And the sky and the earth?
Lee, look at my wedding dress.
All of this wearing all of that...
Santa Claus in a thong riding a unicorn
would not be able to pull focus from me.
Lynette, you okay? You seem a little...
distracted.
I think she's still in shock.
No, it's just...
this whole thing with Tom.
Oh, Lynette, it's gonna be fine.
My dad traveled all the time.
My siblings and I adjusted.
Yeah, but he said he was gonna miss me.
Really? Suddenly I'm interested.
That's great.
And it was the way he said it,
too, like...
he'd been kind of missing me already.
Well, what are you gonna do?
I don't know.
There's no way I can let him
get on that plane to Mumbai.
Or eat these
if you're going to fit in that dress.
Lindsay! Hi.
I think we got off on
the wrong foot earlier.
- Keep walking.
- I suppose I deserve that,
but if I could just have a...
I'm on surveillance! Stay down.
Ooh, how exciting.
What are we surveilling?
well, nothing now.
I've been waiting six weeks
for that cheating bastard
to leave his curtains open.
I'm sorry.
Trip told me where to find you,
because I wanted to apologize
for my unkind words.
You were merely doing your job,
and I was very rude.
Well, you were more than rude.
Yes, I was also off-color.
I never should have...
implied you're a hooker
or insulted your bosoms.
They're lovely.
No.
Not that. You like him.
You thought I was sleeping with him,
and you got jealous.
I'm not jealous of you and Trip.
Is there a "You and Trip"?
Oh, god, no. He's, like, 100.
Look, I'll come back to your case,
and I'll give you a free
pass on the crazy jealousy.
It's not all your fault.
- What do you mean?
- Trip's a good lawyer.
He listens carefully.
He tells you he'll protect you.
Female clients are always
getting the wrong idea.
Well, that might be
the way it normally goes,
but I happen to believe
there really is something
between Trip and me.
Sorry, but I know him.
He's all about the job.
He's into your case, not you.
Porter is going to be fine. Trust me.
Oh, sure. He'll just wear a helmet
so he doesn't crack his head open
when his head hits
the delivery room floor.
Baby, I'm telling you,
when the man gets in there with you,
it just clicks.
They see the blood and stuff,
and it starts to seem
like a video game to them.
I'm getting a bad feeling about this.
Okay, you know what?
Mike almost passed out
when he saw that video.
And he was a little shaky
in the delivery room, too.
But once M.J. was born,
he was my rock.
M.J. took his first step right there.
We were so excited.
Then he took his second step right there.
Fell right on his face.
He was... bleeding and...
I was a mess.
And Mike knew exactly what to do.
He always did.
Oh, mom.
I'm okay.
Just so many memories of him here.
Anyway...
the point is...
you shouldn't worry about Porter.
I just...
I think that he's not into this anymore.
That he's losing interest in being a dad.
He was late for class because of work.
You gotta cut him some slack.
It's not just that.
He's missed some doctor's appointments,
and he missed the tour of
the birthing room at the hospital.
We had a deal.
He was supposed to help raise
the baby so that I could finish school.
But now I'm afraid that
it's all falling apart.
That was delicious.
I'm glad you liked it.
More wine?
Lynette, it's our third date.
I'm pretty much a sure thing.
Something wrong?
You're acting a little weird.
Yeah, there's...
I have a little favor to ask you.
Please, don't send Tom to Mumbai.
You have a very odd sense of foreplay.
I know. It's just...
the kids are upset, and Tom is a wreck,
and I don't think I can
go through with it.
Okay.
Really?
Yeah. I didn't want him to go.
I was just doing it for you.
I'll send McGuinness instead.
That son of a bitch had the nerve
to beat me in tennis last week.
Oh. Thank you.
I am so grateful.
Well...
I can think of one way
that you can show your gratitude.
- Mm.
- Whoa.
Um, maybe you're the one who
needs another glass of wine.
Gregg. No.
Okay, what's going on?
I just... I'm not ready for that step,
and I don't know that I ever will be.
Ever?
I'm sorry. There's... someone else.
You just realized that?
No. No, I just realized how
much I want it to work.
So let me get this straight.
You use me to get back at your ex,
and now you're dumping
me for some other guy?
That's unbelievable!
Unbelievable.
And in local news,
the trial of Bree Van de Kamp
is set to begin tomorrow.
Van de kamp is accused
of killing Ramon Sanchez,
whose body was discovered
beneath a condominium
development in Chapman woods.
Hey. Couldn't sleep?
Hey. No.
Huh.
Thought I'd take a walk.
Remember the last time
we were up this late together?
The night we buried Alejandro.
God, if we could only go back.
Hey.
You having trouble sleeping, too?
No, I woke up to get some water,
and I saw you from the window.
What are you guys doing up?
We can't sleep because our friend
is going on trial tomorrow
morning for murder.
Oh, relax. Bree's innocent.
The jury's gonna see that.
Juries make mistakes.
Well, you know, it doesn't help Bree
for us to be negative right now.
Do you know what I was thinking
we should do to help her?
Go to the judge and tell her the truth.
I was thinking the exact same thing.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Wait a minute.
What's going on here?
What, it never even crossed your mind?
Well, we have a plan in place,
and if we just hold on a little longer,
everything will be back to normal.
And what if Bree is convicted, huh?
What are we gonna do then?
I don't know.
Clearly. Do you even care?
Lynette!
Okay. It's late.
Well, let's just talk about it tomorrow.
Well, I don't get this.
Why are you guys mad at me?
Because you're not having
any trouble sleeping.
Don't freak out. It's just me.
Trip, what are you doing here?
It's the middle of the night.
I had a feeling you might be up.
Do we need to discuss my case?
Nope. Just the opposite.
Doughnuts... "Casablanca."
That's one of my favorite movies.
- Yours, too?
- Never seen it.
I'm, uh, more a "Caddyshack" kind of guy.
But I had a feeling about you.
- May I?
- Sure.
My trial starts in six hours.
Is this really what we should be doing?
Do you know anything about sports?
No more than I have to.
This is just like going
to the championships.
You practice your ass off to get there,
but the night before the big game,
you just forget about it.
I can't believe I'm going through this.
But if I have to...
I guess what I'm saying is,
of all the gin joints in all
the towns in all the world,
I'm glad you walked into mine.
Am I supposed to know what that means?
Start the movie.
Thank you.
In the matter of people vs.
Bree Van de Kamp,
we are here for opening statements.
Ms. Stone, you may proceed.
How well do we really know
our friends and neighbors?
They borrow our lawn mowers,
sit with us in P.T.A. meetings,
Bring us tuna casseroles.
But as this case will demonstrate,
they also have secrets...
Secrets they keep from their neighbors,
secrets that can poison
a place like Wisteria Lane.
Ms. Stone wonders how well
we know our neighbors.
Well, in this case, as it turns out,
pretty darn well.
Breen Van de Kamp's friends will tell you
that she is a woman of honesty,
integrity, and compassion.
Bree Van de Kamp is an alcoholic,
a woman of loose morals.
She would pick up strange men in bars,
have sex with them,
frequently waking up with
no recollection of what happened.
If picking up people in bars is a crime,
there might be a criminal or
two in this very courtroom.
The defendant lured Ramon
Sanchez into her house,
seduced him, and bludgeoned him.
There is no connection whatsoever
between my client and Mr. Sanchez.
And while it isn't against
the law to sleep with any man
who'd buy you a martini,
it is illegal to kill them.
Has Bree made some
questionable choices? Yes.
Does that make her a killer?
No.
It makes her human... like the rest of us.
This is a case about a woman
who led a secret life,
but here's the thing about secrets.
Like bodies, they don't
always stay buried.
Welcome to big top burger.
Hi. I'm looking for Porter Scavo.
Is he done yet?
No, Porter's working the drive-thru.
Oh. I thought he was
only working till 1:00.
Well, I heard him say
he'd cover the afternoon shift,
so that's till 6:00.
Now can I get you something to eat?
No, I think I'll get something to go.
Welcome to big top burger. Can I help you?
I've got a better idea.
How about you help
the mother of your child?
Mrs. Delfino?
Dear god. Is there another person
who could say what I just said to you?
No, of course not.
Porter, why are you making julie
do all of this stuff without you?
I'm busting my butt trying to
make money for her and the baby.
I'm working three jobs.
Well, then tell her that.
She's worried that
you're losing interest in being a dad.
I'm talking to the clown! Shut up!
Can you please pull up to the window?
Look, Mrs. Delfino,
I barely graduated high school,
I ditched college,
and this is about as much
as my baby's daddy is gonna achieve.
You can always go back to college.
When?
Everybody says how expensive
it is to have a kid.
With the crap money I make,
I'll be working all the time.
Look, I get it.
It's just not right for Julie
to do this without you.
I totally agree. Julie's given up so much
so I can be in this kid's life.
But I'm starting to realize...
that was a bad trade for her.
Look at her, a regular black widow.
It says here she slept with
15 guys in a 2-month period.
And she was drunk the whole time.
Sounds like college.
Excuse me. But you don't know
what you're talking about.
Do you even know this woman?
Actually, a friend of mine
used her to cater a party once.
Said she had shifty eyes.
They do look pretty shifty.
W-well, I do know her, and she's innocent.
Yeah, I don't think the police go around
arresting innocent people.
She must have done something.
Oh, so you guys read one article,
and just like that, she's guilty?
It's not just us.
Everyone says she killed the guy.
She's the last person in this
world who would kill somebody.
She's a friend and a mother
and probably the most
decent person I know.
And she would die if she knew
how people are talking about her.
Well, she better get used to it.
If I'm a juror, she's going
away for a long, long time.
And with every exhale,
the tension is being blown out,
and every inhale brings
in positive energy.
Now you're imagining
a peaceful scene...
that beautiful lawn by
the science building
at your college.
And you're walking
towards the chemistry lab
to finish the research
for your dissertation.
And now on that same lawn,
a graduation ceremony
in which you are finally
receiving your PhD.
Mom, what are you doing?
The other day, you were
talking about a murder trial,
and now you're talking about
stuff that will never happen.
I think it will.
How?
Because I am going to move
back up there with you
and help raise the baby.
What?
I'm gonna sell this house, and M.J. and I
are going with you so you
can finish your degree.
But... what about Porter?
Well, there will always be a place for him
in his child's life,
but Porter needs to find
his own life right now.
No. I can't let you do this.
You love the lane.
Oh, I do, but nowhere near
as much as I love you.
And besides...
I think it'll be good for me, too.
What do you mean?
Well, I told you, honey.
There are memories here
that are just too hard
to live with every day.
Mom...
this would be awesome.
But... are you sure you wanna do this?
I'm sure.
Okay. Lay back down.
As Mike used to say,
we gotta practice birthing a baby.
You are gonna love it there, McGuinness.
And hey, if you don't, it's only a year.
I'll give you my "India
on 50 rupees a day" book.
All right, people, let's get started.
Thanks again. I am so
glad to be staying here.
Yeah, well, thank your ex-wife.
She's the one who convinced me.
Really? Lynette did that?
Yeah. Real piece of work, that one.
I don't know how you put up with it.
I'm sorry. Um... aren't you guys dating?
No. She dumped me.
Apparently, she's hung
up on some other guy.
I'm surprised you didn't
wanna go to Mumbai
just to get away from her crap.
I know. She can be, uh,
a bit of a handful.
Oh, yeah, that's why you dumped her,
'cause she's a "Handful."
I'm telling you, guys,
23 years living with that psycho...
He's either a saint or a masochist.
Okay. Okay. Let's...
let's start the meeting.
Oh, seriously. I barely survived one week
with that ball-buster.
Gregg, I'm asking you, drop it.
I'm just saying Lynette
is a first class bitch.
Uhh! Oh.
Well, I hope that was worth it,
'cause you're fired.
Okay, Mr. Weston,
is the defense ready to
call its first witness?
We are, your honor.
The defense calls Susan Delfino.
How long have you known my client?
Nearly 20 years.
So it's fair to say you
know each other well?
We're like sisters.
She's the most honest
person I've ever met.
Can you tell us what happened
on the night in question?
It was a progressive dinner party.
I'm sorry. I don't get out much.
What is a progressive dinner party?
The whole street throws it.
Every house is responsible
for a specific course.
- Oh, sounds like fun.
- Unless you don't know how to cook.
They skipped my house that night.
Now as you traveled from house to house,
were you with Bree the whole time?
No.
Really?
Where did she go?
She left my house to
go check on her entree.
Wouldn't that have given her
time to kill Mr. Sanchez?
Or have sex with her boyfriend
while the chicken burned,
which is what she was doing
when the whole neighborhood
walked in on her.
I imagine that must have been awkward.
Clearly, you haven't spent
much time on my street.
And then what happened?
The party finished at my house,
and then Susan, Lynette,
and Bree stayed late
to help me clean up.
- How late?
- Around 2:00 in the morning.
And the coroner's report
said that the time of death
was between 10:00 P.M.
and midnight. Interesting.
So there's no possible way
that Bree could have killed
Ramon Sanchez that night?
No way. Bree couldn't hurt a fly.
The only thing she killed
that night was the chicken.
No. As god as my witness,
Bree did not kill him.
That's it from the car.
My assistant's gonna
pack up the rest of it.
Security's been told not to
let me back in the building.
I swear, Tom, I am
trying to be supportive,
but I'm having a hard time following this.
Why would you hit your boss?
I just... never liked him.
So? There's lots of people you don't like.
Mr. Indich in 3F,
who never picks up after his dog...
I can't even get you
to write an angry note.
You know what? I lost my temper.
Because he was going to transfer you?
No.
Because he was dating Lynette.
Oh, my god.
Are you still in love with her?
Jane, look, you have to understand.
Lynette has...
Been a part of your life
for 23 years. I know.
She's the mother of your children.
I get it. You've given me
this speech a hundred times.
Now answer the question.
Do you still love her?
Yes.
Wow.
And I was, what?
Some... wall you built to try
and hide that from yourself?
No.
You were the woman who was there for me
when I was broken and confused,
and I-I still care about you very much.
No.
Tom, you don't get to
break somebody's heart
and still say you care about them.
If it matters...
I loved you.
So you recognize this man as well?
Yes. I slept with him, too.
I can imagine how painful this is,
having to publicly acknowledge
liaisons with all these men.
No. You can't.
You didn't have to testify.
Why did you subject yourself to this?
Because I admit my transgressions.
Was killing Ramon Sanchez one of them?
No. Absolutely not.
That seemed very heartfelt.
So your conscience is clear?
Yes. It is.
Your honor, I'd like
to enter into evidence
prosecution exhibit 24.
Objection. We haven't seen this.
They can't blindside us...
This just came into
our possession last night.
It rebuts Ms. Van de kamp's testimony
regarding her clear conscience.
I'll allow it.
Does this letter look familiar?
Yes. I wrote it.
It's a suicide note, isn't it?
Yes.
This letter was discovered on
may 7th at the Frost Hotel,
where Ms. Van de kamp had taken a room.
The manager heard shouting,
including a reference to "A gun."
Police were summoned, but
Ms. Van de kamp was gone.
This was found in the wastebasket.
Proceed, Ms. Stone.
Do you recall anything
else of significance
occurring on may 7th?
No.
That's the day your boyfriend,
Chuck Vance,
a decorated Fairview police detective,
was killed in a hit and
run accident, wasn't it?
Objection. My client isn't on trial
- for killing detective Vance.
- Not yet.
- Your honor...
- Withdrawn.
Please. Read the letter.
"I never thought I could feel such...
remorse, such guilt."
Your honor, if we could
take a short recess...
Denied.
"No one knows who I really am."
"I'm entirely alone."
"Living with this secret is too painful."
"I can't go on."
Doesn't sound like a clear
conscience, does it,
Ms. Van de Kamp?
No further questions.
- Bree.
- Please, I just need to be alone.
Not until you tell me what that was about.
I already told you.
I was in a very dark place,
with the drinking
and my friends abandoning me.
But I did not kill anyone.
You have to believe me.
I do believe you.
I just... hope the jury does.
Come on. You don't know
that it's your fault.
Please, Tom loses his job
the day after I dump his boss?
There's gotta be some connection,
and the worst part is this is exactly
what broke us up in the first place...
me trying to control his life.
You really suck at this gay friend thing.
I'm sorry.
I can't take you seriously in that dress.
You look like a giant taffeta bruise.
I know. It is horrible.
Maybe if I accessorize.
Unless the accessories are
two hands over your eyes,
forget it. Why don't you just
tell Renee you hate the dress?
Because she'll pick another one,
and I'll hate that one, too.
It's what I do.
I did it to Tom all the time.
I didn't want him to go to school,
and then I didn't want him to quit.
I wanted him to get a new job,
and then I hated it. I don't know.
Maybe I wasn't unhappy with Tom.
Maybe I was just...
unhappy.
Well...
at least we know you were
right about that dress.
Now turn around, let me get you out of it.
Seriously? We're this close?
When I tell the whole
neighborhood about it,
I will be kind.
You're a good friend, Lee.
Celia, give me the remote!
No! Stop! Give it!
Girls, don't make me come in there!
- It's my turn!
- It's not!
Who did this?
Celia.
Is that true, Celia?
This belonged to my grandmother.
You are in big trouble, young lady.
Sweep up the rest, and go to your room.
It's not my fault. She pushed me into it.
- You pushed her?
- She wouldn't give me the remote,
and it was my turn to pick what we watch.
So you broke this.
It was my turn.
Juanita Solis, you were gonna
let your sister take the blame
for something you caused?
That is horrible!
This is your fault. Own up to it.
Don't you see how bad...
Mom? I'm sorry.
Mommy?
It's okay.
Go wash up for dinner.
I'll take care of this.
And the fracture found
on the victim's head
is consistent with a blunt force injury.
A blunt force that someone
of Ms. Van de kamp's size would
be capable of inflicting?
In my opinion.
Your honor, the defense
asks the court for a recess.
How did you find that?
When Gaby mentioned her
"Gardener," Alejandro,
my alarm bells went off.
I had Lindsay do a little investigating.
Oh.
"Oh"?
We're halfway through your murder trial,
and I find out the victim
is Gaby's stepfather,
and all you can say is "Oh"?
I'm sorry.
I wanted to tell you, but we made a pact.
Who did?
You and Gaby?
Me and Gaby and... other people...
people that I care about.
You care about them
enough to lie for them?
To commit perjury?
How about enough to go to jail?
You don't actually think
- that's gonna happen, do you?
- I don't know.
After the D.A.'s suicide note stunt,
it's possible.
To the jury, you look like
you're hiding something,
and the fact is, you are.
Look, I just... I just...
I wanna win this case
for you, okay?
And if this is something
that can exonerate you...
It can, but not without
betraying my friends.
Bree...
You're facing 20 years to life.
This could be your only way out.
I think it's time to tell
the truth about Gaby.
Yes, recent events in
the lives of my friends
had stirred up intense emotions...
excitement about starting a new chapter...
guilt over causing another's pain...
disappointment in a failure to change.
Then there are those who are asked
to put all emotion aside
in order to make a coldhearted decision.
Gaby, what are you doing here?
I finally found the perfect scarf.
It's... elegant.
It's dignified. It's beautiful.
It's you.
You are so sweet.
You didn't need to do this.
Yes, I did.
I haven't truly thanked
you for what you're doing,
the way you're sacrificing
yourself for me and my family.
You're just a much better person
than I could ever hope to be.
Oh, Gaby.
Sync by YYeTs
Corrected by MystEre
www.addic7ed.com