Previously on
"Desperate Housewives"...
Susan made a decision.
I'm gonna sell this house and
move back up there with you
and help raise the baby.
- What about Porter?
- Well...
There will always be a place for him
in this child's life.
Karen's health took a turn
for the worse.
Looks like the cancer's spreading
faster than anyone thought.
Ben was summoned
before the court.
You're on a witness list
for Bree's trial?
Bree's friends cautioned her.
You have a crush on your lawyer.
You're on trial for murder, Bree.
You gotta keep a clear head.
And so does he.
Lynette ended her relationship
with Tom's boss.
She dumped me. Apparently she's
hung up on some other guy.
And this led...
You really suck
at this gay friend thing.
I can't take you seriously
in that dress.
To an unfortunate
misunderstanding.
(Mary Alice) Karen McCluskey
had never been sure
what her neighbors thought
of her.
Did they see her
as merely a babysitter...
An entertaining source
for gossip...
Or just the mean old lady
who lived down the street?
But for the first time
in her life,
she found herself thinking
about such things...
Because she knew that her life
was coming to an end.
Roy, it's time to go!
What's going on, Karen?
(Voice breaks) I'm, uh,
starting hospice care.
I thought you told the doctors
that you wanted to...
Croak at home? Yeah, I did.
But the oncologist is convinced
this is for the best.
What does he know?
Young quack thinks
I can't take care of wife.
He's worried about you, Roy.
You've got
high blood pressure, angina.
I'm racing you to the grave
as it is.
I don't want to push you in.
- I know.
- Hang on.
Karen...
Would you prefer
to die at home?
- Well, sure, but...
- Then...
- We'll take care of you.
- Yeah. We can do it.
We'll take shifts.
It won't be hard.
Whoa, Nelly.
No, this is sweet,
but you gals have troubles of your own.
Bree's got her trial.
Lynette's marriage
is falling apart.
Gaby, those kids of yours are turning
into serial killers before our very eyes.
Okay, I'm not gonna argue
with you because you're sick...
And totally correct.
But I'm with the girls on this.
Let us take care of you.
I'm gonna require a lot of care,
you know.
We know, and we're gonna
be there for you.
Hey, boy nurses!
Bring the stuff back
in the house! She's staying.
- Come on. Let's go help.
- (Gaby chuckles) Okay.
I'm... actually speechless.
I don't know why
you're all doing this.
Don't you?
Yes, Mrs. McCluskey
had wondered
what her neighbors thought
of her.
She was pleased to discover
after all these years,
they thought of her
as a friend.
Desperate Housewives
Season 8, Episode 22
Sync & corrections:
UKsubtitles.ru
The town of Fairview
had been rocked by scandal.
A housewife had been accused
of murder,
and her trial was growing
more sensational each day.
It truly was
all anyone was talking about...
- (Camera shutter clicks)
Which is exactly
what another housewife
was worried about.
(Carlos) Gaby!
(Door opens)
- (Closes door)
- Ah, there you are.
Yep, just sitting here on the porch,
reading the ol'...
Sports section.
You hate sports...
And reading.
But I love you,
and you love sports,
so I've... started
to really get into it.
Really?
What's your... favorite
basketball team?
The... "Turtles".
- What the hell is this?
- It's nothing.
- You said the trial was going well.
- It was. It is! This is just a setback.
Damn it! How... Gaby, how many
setbacks is it gonna take
before Bree goes to prison
for something I did?!
Hey, Lee! Sports talk.
Gettin' a little heated
over here! (Chuckles)
I can't do this anymore, Gaby.
I have got to step up.
Are you crazy? No!
How do you not feel
guilty about this?
I do, every second
of every day.
We just have to hold on
a little longer.
Bree says Trip knows what he's doing,
so we've just gotta give him a chance.
Yeah, I-I don't know.
I mean...
Turning yourself in now
would just be foolish.
You'd be throwing your whole life away,
abandoning our family. And for what?
To prove a point about
what an honorable guy you are?
Please, let's just see
how this plays out.
Okay.
(Sighs)
But if things get any worse,
I'll have no choice.
(Smacks newspaper)
(Sighs deeply)
- Lee! No!
- What?
- (Lowered voice) Stop!
- Don't tell me you've changed your mind.
Oh! No. I still wanna sell.
Thank God, 'cause I've already
spent my commission.
- On what?
- Isn't it obvious?
I had some
personal renovations done.
(Whispers) Ahh.
My ass!
I had my ass lifted.
Oh!
Um... of course.
How did I not notice?
That is one...
Perky Fanny.
(Chuckles)
I'm sorry. I've never been good
with ass compliments.
- So why don't you want the sign up?
- Well... (Sighs)
I haven't told the girls
I'm moving yet.
- Why not?
- I don't know. (Sighs)
Maybe because I can't even
believe I'm doing it myself.
- It's always hard to move.
- Yeah.
Putting my house on the market
in the middle of Bree's trial?
I mean, I just feel like
a bad person.
Okay, the fact that you're
worried about your friend
shows that you're not
a bad person.
(Sighs)
By the way, if Bree gets convicted, do you
think she'll put her place on the market?
- Lee!
- And if Lynette gets divorced,
that house is gonna be
way too big for her.
(Smack) Wow! I...
It kinda smacked me back.
(Cell phone rings)
(Ring) (Grunts)
(Beep)
Hello?
(Lowered voice) She's gone.
Hey, Penny! What's going on?
Where are ya?
Dad's. Did you hear me?
Jane's gone.
Whoa. Whoa. She's "gone" meaning...
She's not there right now?
Or... or she's gone gone?
Her stuff is moved out.
Even her toothbrush, mom!
- They broke up!
- Oh, my...
Hang on.
(Gasps) Your dad's on the other line!
Call me back!
Okay! Stay calm!
- I am.
- I was talking to me!
- Hey, Tom. What's up?
- Hey, are you gonna be around tonight?
Uh... I don't know.
Maybe. Probably.
Yeah. Why?
Um, I need to talk to you about something,
and I'd... I'd like to do it face-to-face.
- Oh, okay. What time?
- (Sighs) How about 8:00?
8:00?
8:00 is my favorite time.
- What? Why?
- I don't know. It just... always has been.
You know, eight is great.
- You okay?
- Uh, me? Oh, yeah. I'm just...
- (Bang)
- Cleaning the oven and...
(Clatters)
The fumes are getting to me,
and I'm drunk... a little.
(Laughs nervously)
So I'll see you tonight?
O-okay. Bye.
Okay. Bye! (Chuckles) (Beep)
(High-pitched voice) Yeah!
(Chuckles)
(Indistinct conversations)
Thank you.
Yeah, mm. Don't
thank me just yet.
Mm. Bree...
I don't know exactly.
what Ben is gonna testify about,
but if it's as damning
as the prosecution seems
to think it is...
You don't have to
worry about Ben.
If his testimony is damaging
in any way,
- I'm gonna have to put Gaby back on the stand.
- No.
(Lowered voice) The dead guy
was her stepfather.
She has some connection
to this.
Absolutely not.
(Whispering) I'm the client.
You're the lawyer.
- You have to do what I say.
- It's your call.
But I've gotta tell you,
you're forcing me
to try this thing with one hand
tied behind my back.
Well, luckily, you have
more talent in that one hand
than most lawyers have
in their whole body.
You can do this.
I know you can.
Mr. Faulkner,
I am ordering you to answer.
Ms. Stone, repeat your question.
During your phone conversation
with the defendant,
she thanked you
for protecting her.
What was she referring to?
I'm sorry. I really don't
remember the conversation.
Maybe this will refresh
your memory.
- Your honor?
- Go ahead.
Mm. (Click)
(Bree) I know, but even when
suspicion moved on to you,
you still protected me,
and that's very honorable.
- (Ben) Really, it was no big deal.
- Maybe not to you.
You're not the one
who put a body in the ground.
You have to understand,
a day doesn't go by
when that does not
weigh heavily on my conscience.
(Click)
So...
What were you protecting her from?
Again, sir, I'm ordering you to answer
the prosecutor's questions.
All right. I've had enough.
You're in contempt.
Bailiff, take Mr. Faulkner into custody.
Perhaps a night in jail
will help him to see things
differently.
- Can I at least make a call?
- One call. We're in recess.
(Bangs gavel)
(Lowered voice)
So they're arresting him?
- What happens now?
- They'll bring him back tomorrow.
The D.A. will ask
the same question again.
And what if
he still doesn't answer?
Frankly, Bree,
I'm more worried if he does.
(Shifts gears)
(Turns off engine)
(Gasps)
Oh!
Oh, my goodness, Renee.
You startled me.
- Is everything all right?
- No, it's not.
I just got a phone call
from Ben. He's in jail.
I know. I am deeply sorry
for this whole mess.
Do you wanna come inside?
I'm really not in the mood
for tea and biscuits.
Ben and I are
getting married next week,
and "correctional facility"
isn't exactly my dream venue.
I wish there was something
I could do.
There is. Ben is sitting
in that jail cell right now,
and I don't even know why,
and he won't tell me.
So you have to fix this.
Just release him from
whatever promise he made you.
Believe me, I wish I could
do that, but I can't.
Why not?
- (Sighs) I just can't...
- Bree...
Did you... kill that man?
Of course not. How could you
even think that? (Sighs)
I'll apologize when someone
starts telling me the truth.
(Sighs)
Okay, let's get those lips
a little more glossy.
All right, enough, enough.
I'm meeting with Tom,
not prepping for a shift
at a bordello.
Yeah, but you're finally getting
back together. You've gotta look perfect.
(Both chuckle)
Oh! And we still have time
for that Brazilian bikini wax.
If you mention that again,
I will strike you.
(Car door slams)
What the hell?
(Gasps, whispers) It's Tom!
- You said 8:00!
- He said 8:00!
I need to be alone with him.
You have to hide!
- Hide?!
- Yes!
What if you guys start
doing it right here?
I can't listen to that!
Well, maybe I could.
Hide! Hide! Put your fingers
in your ears! Go on!
Oh!
Hey. (Giggles)
You're early.
- Yeah. Sorry.
- You... you going somewhere?
No. No, I was just...
No.
It's fine, Lynette.
I understand. Y-you...
- You got a life.
- (Chuckles) (Laughs) No. No, I really don't.
Come on in. You want a drink
or something?
No, thanks.
I'll just be a minute.
Come in.
Tom?
I'm filing the divorce papers
tomorrow.
You're... what?
We just gotta get out
of this gray area
that we've been stuck in.
It's... time
for both of us
to move to the next phase.
I just wanted
to tell you in person.
That's all
I really have to say.
Aren't you going after him?
Why not?
Because now I know.
Jane wasn't the problem.
It's me.
(Whispers) He doesn't want
to be married to me.
(Door opens)
(Door closes)
I guess we can both agree...
Orange is not my color.
Look... (Sighs)
I'm sorry I missed
the cake tasting, sweetheart.
Uh... I mean, did you maybe
bring one of them with you?
Mm, preferably
with a file in it.
Really? You're making jokes?
Hang in there, darling.
The trial can't last forever.
They gotta let me
out of here some time.
Or you could answer
their questions and get out now.
Yeah.
That's not how I'm built.
Ben, you have no idea
how long this could go on.
Am I gonna need
to cancel our wedding?
No! They got no motive,
no weapon.
And Bree's alibi is solid.
She was with all of you
at that...
that progressive dinner party.
Wait. That was the night
of the murder?
Yeah. Why?
- Oh, my God.
- Renee, what is it?
(Sighs) Um...
I remember something
about that night.
I was looking out my
window, and it was late.
And I saw Bree
getting out of her car.
Enjoy your visit,
Ms. Perry?
- I'm sorry. Do I know you?
- Emily Stone.
I'm the prosecutor
in Bree Van De Kamp's case.
- I don't have anything to say to you.
- Oh, I think you do.
You have something to say
about the night of the murder.
Back there, when you were
talking to your fiancé,
- ...we heard every word.
- You can't do that.
There's no expectation
of privacy in jail.
So... let's talk.
I'm not gonna help you try
to convict my friend.
That's a shame,
because if you don't,
I call Immigration,
and Mr. Faulkner's on
a one-way flight back to Sydney.
Ready to talk now?
Mr. Faulkner, how are you today?
Oh, good.
Yeah, refreshed.
I asked you yesterday
if you were willing to discuss
your telephone conversation
with the defendant.
I remember.
Still won't answer.
Uh, can we just save everyone some
time and send me back to jail?
Bailiff, remove Mr. Faulkner.
We'll see you back here
tomorrow.
Your Honor, the prosecution
calls Renee Perry to the stand.
Renee?
Renee, what are you doing?
(Speaks indistinctly)
Renee!
I was lying in bed
when a noise from the street
woke me up.
It was about...
(Sighs) 3:00 A.M.
So I got up and I went
to the window.
And what did you see?
I saw Bree.
Her clothes were
kinda muddy, um...
Leaves in her hair.
(Sighs) She was...
Walking up her driveway.
Was she carrying anything?
(Sighs) Yes.
What was she carrying?
A shovel.
No further questions.
Renee, what did you just do?
I did what I had to do.
I told the truth.
What you said in there
could really hurt Bree.
Do you not understand
what's at stake here?
Friends aren't supposed
to turn on each other.
Oh, so I'm one of
the "friends" now?
What is that
supposed to mean?
All year long, you've been
keeping a secret from me.
Hey, just so we're clear,
I didn't want
to testify against Bree.
The D.A. was gonna
have Ben deported.
Oh, so, yeah, I picked
the man I love over you.
And judging by the way
you guys have treated me,
I made the right choice.
Trip. Trip!
That was bad?
Not out here.
(Door opens)
I need the room.
- Uh, but the judge asked me to...
- Get out.
Okay.
- Did you see their faces?
- Whose faces?
The jurors.
I've been watching them.
After Renee's little story,
no one on that jury is buying
what you're selling.
What about you?
I don't know, Bree.
You haven't told me the truth yet.
Twice I've been blindsided
because I don't know
what the hell is going on.
You need to tell me
what happened that night.
(Whispers) I made a promise
to my friends.
You're gonna lose.
Do you understand that?
You are going to go to prison.
- You're scaring me.
- Good. You should be scared.
You're throwing your life away,
and it... and it pisses me off,
- ...'cause this affects more than just you.
- I don't understand.
Look, I-I-I'm saying
that you were wrong before.
You're not just my client,
and I'm not just your lawyer.
I'm also somebody who...
Really...
- Oh, to hell with it.
- (Gasps)
Mmm.
It was Carlos.
(Gasps)
You have to promise me
not to use this against him...
(Whispers) Or anyone else.
Tell me everything.
(Sighs)
It was self-defense.
Alejandro
broke into her house,
and when Gaby came home,
he attacked her.
This gem
just came on the market,
and as you can see,
it's a warm, cozy, homey place.
(Lowered voice) And don't worry,
they're taking the furniture.
- I just love your kitchen.
- Oh, thank you.
I can't tell you how many
mornings I've sat here,
looking out on the Lane,
having a cup of... Gaby.
- Gaby? - Gaby... who I haven't told
I'm moving yet. (lnhales sharply)
Okay, Mr. and Mrs. Newman,
let me show you the upstairs.
- Uh, we're not done looking down here.
- Oh, but the upstairs is way better!
It's... that much closer
to heaven.
Come on, go, go!
- Hey.
- (Door closes) Hi! How's it going?
Great. It's my turn
to take care
of Mrs. McCluskey, so obviously,
I've been drinking.
- Can you take me to the courthouse?
- Sure.
- (Thud overhead)
- Someone upstairs?
- Nope.
- (Mrs. Newman) Look at this closet space!
Just some old friends
from high school.
(Mr. Newman)
Are these low-flow toilets?
Who are very eco-friendly.
So I should get back to them.
I'll pick you up at noon.
Hey, great place
you have here.
Um... Gaby, uh,
these are my good friends
Fred and Jean.
Hello. (Chuckles)
(Clenched teeth)
What year did you graduate?
(Chuckles)
Mr. Weston,
if the defense rests,
we can move on
to closing arguments.
Actually,
I have another witness.
A new witness at this point?
She's not new.
The defense recalls...
Gabrielle Solis.
(Gallery murmuring)
- (Whispers) You promised.
- I also promised to keep you out of jail.
- (Lowered voice) What is he doing?
- I-I don't know.
You understand that you are
still under oath?
Ms. Solis,
I'd like to show you
a picture of the victim.
Do you recognize this man
as Ramon Sanchez?
No.
Your honor, I want a recess.
Only your lawyer can ask
for a recess, Ms. Van De Kamp.
Please sit down.
Do you know this man
by another name?
His name is Alejandro Perez.
And how do you know
Mr. Perez?
He was...
He was my stepfather.
- (Gallery murmuring)
- Your Honor,
I insist on another recess,
please.
I'm... feeling a little...
(Thud)
(Gallery gasps)
Bree!
- (Gavel banging)
- (Judge Conti) Order! Order!
We're in recess until tomorrow,
at which time we will see
if Ms. Van De Kamp
is able to continue.
(Whispers) Bree?
(Whispers) Don't touch me.
(Whispering) Jeez! You scared
the crap out of me!
They know it's Alejandro,
and you don't tell me?
Shh!
She just fell asleep.
Okay, this has
gone far enough.
First thing tomorrow,
I am telling the D.A. the truth.
No, you're not!
You're not doing anything.
- You got a better idea?
- Yes!
I'm gonna
tell them it was me.
Are you out of your mind?!
No! Look, listen to me.
I am a victim of abuse.
The jury's gonna side with me.
Who they're not gonna side with
is you, a 2-time felon.
- Gaby, you're crazy.
- No, I'm not.
Since the first moment we met,
you've protected me.
And I've been happy
to let you do it
because I've been
this selfish, spoiled brat.
Well, I don't want to be
that person anymore.
I'm tired
of taking from you.
So, please, this time,
just let me protect you.
You really think
that a jury is gonna believe
that you dragged a dead body
through the woods yourself?
Adrenaline. Fear.
You'd be surprised
what people can do.
I don't think that story's
gonna be enough, Gaby.
Well, I'll tell them exactly
what happened that night.
He came over,
he started attacking me,
and instead of saying you
killed him with a candlestick,
I'll say it was me.
(Crickets chirping)
Honey, it's 2:00 in the morning.
Are you okay?
I was just thinking
how proud I am of you.
Really?
You were just saying... (Sighs)
How much you wanna change, but...
You already have.
Five years ago, you never would
have offered to sacrifice yourself for me.
Thank you.
(Sighs deeply)
But there is no way I'm letting
you take the fall for this.
What?
But you just said you were proud
of how much I've changed.
Exactly. You've become this amazing
role model for our daughters.
They need you now
more than ever.
Wait.
But they need you, too.
No, they need a father who accepts
responsibility for his actions.
It has taken me a year, but I'm
finally going to be that guy.
Now I am going down to the court
first thing in the morning
and confess everything.
Carlos! Wait a minute!
I love you very much, Gabrielle, but there
is nothing that you can do to stop me.
(Scoffs)
Why would I put you
on the stand?
I was at
that progressive dinner party.
I can testify that Renee was
so stinking drunk
she couldn't tell her ass
from her elbow.
Okay.
That could be helpful.
I think I can, uh...
Fit you in next Monday.
(Chuckles) Look at me.
I'm wearing a wig
and toting an oxygen tank.
Do I look like I'm gonna
make it to Monday?
Put me on the stand.
You'll be glad you did.
Gaby's running late.
What the hell?
Why don't you take a seat?
(Indistinct conversations)
Listen, if they take me
into custody right away,
I won't get a chance
to talk to the girls.
Let's not talk
about that right now.
I don't want them seeing this
on the news.
- (Sighs)
- You need to tell them that I love them
and that
you're in charge now.
Honey, I've always been
in charge.
I don't know why you made me
wear this thing. (Sighs)
No, it's, uh, it's freezing
in the courtroom.
You'll thank me later.
(Sighs)
So handsome.
I'm gonna miss this face.
(Whispers) I love you.
Ladies first.
G-Gaby? A little rude.
You snooze, you lose.
Gaby, wait!
(Alarm beeps) Hold on.
(Electronic whirring and
beeping) That's weird.
Remove your coat, please.
(Wand clatters)
Okay.
(Rip)
Sir...
- (Click)
- Sir, you wanna explain this?
I swear, I have no idea
how that...
Bye, Carlos.
Gaby, get back here!
We need backup!
- Gaby!
- Love you!
And, Mrs. McCluskey, you are a resident
of Wisteria Lane. Is that correct?
I've lived in that neighborhood
for 35 years.
Wow. That's a long time.
Now Renee Perry has testified...
Let me tell you something
about a neighborhood.
Okay.
It's not just a bunch of houses
in the same place.
It's a community.
It's lives
that are connected,
people who care
about each other.
That's beautiful.
Now back to Ms. Perry...
I know it sounds sappy,
but damn it, it's true.
And these wonderful people
I'd lived beside...
Well, they're my family.
Your honor, I'm... I'm not sure
what we're getting from this.
Well, you will in a minute,
honey.
When you're in a family,
like me and the girls,
you protect each other.
That's just the way
it has to be.
So when, uh,
Gaby's stepfather came back...
(Trip) Uh...
After everything
he'd done to her...
W-w-what do you mean?
(Scoffs)
It's no secret he abused her
when she was a kid.
- Objection.
- Overruled.
So that night,
when I saw him
creeping around the house,
I followed him in,
I picked up the candlestick,
and I killed
that son of a bitch.
(Gallery gasping and murmuring)
- (Gavel banging)
- (Judge Conti) Order!
- (Murmuring continues)
- Order!
Order in this courtroom!
Quiet down,
or I will clear
the courtroom!
Stop the trial!
I have something to say.
(Whispers)
McCluskey just confessed.
Mine can wait.
(Scoffs) Your honor,
this is preposterous.
There's no way that frail woman
could've committed this crime.
Adrenaline.
Fear.
You'd be surprised
what people can do.
Counselors...
- My chamber now.
- (Bangs gavel)
(Murmuring resumes)
What the hell was that?
Your honor, I had no idea.
- (Scoffs)
- She begged me to put her on the stand.
I thought she was gonna
discredit Renee Perry.
Obviously, she needed to
get this off her conscience.
Oh, you are such a liar!
This is a stunt, a last-ditch
effort to save his client...
- (Chuckles) And I want him sanctioned.
- Enough.
Mr. Weston, where do you plan
on going with this?
Well, now that the issue of
sexual abuse has been introduced,
I'll need to bring Ms. Solis
back on the stand.
Of course, she'll talk about what
a monster her stepfather was,
and as I recall,
most of our jurors are parents.
After I've taken them
through the sordid details
of what your victim did...
You can't possibly allow this.
Given the testimony
of the last witness, I have to.
Okay, Ms. Stone,
what do you want to do?
Ms. Stone?
(Sighs)
Your honor, at this time,
we move to dismiss all charges
against Bree Van De Kamp.
(Applause, gallery murmuring)
(Exhales deeply)
(Gavel bangs)
Ms. Stone,
is there anyone else
that you would like to file
charges against at this time?
Given her advanced age
and declining health,
the people have decided not to press
charges against Karen McCluskey.
(Judge Conti)
All right, in that case,
Ms. Van De Kamp, Mrs. McCluskey,
you are both free to go.
- Case dismissed.
- Aah! (Laughs)
(Applause)
Congratulations.
Thank you.
(Lynette) Hey! Oh!
- Oh, God! Oh, God.
- Oh, thank you.
(Crickets chirping)
Roy?
Why aren't you
at Bree's big victory party?
Uh, thought I'd
sit this one out. (Chuckles)
Filed divorce papers today,
so I'm not really, uh,
up to bumping into Lynette.
Anyway, I, uh...
I wanted to come over
and see how Karen's doing.
Incredible thing
she did today.
Yeah, I'm proud as hell.
But it took
a lot out of her.
I brought her home, put her
right in bed. (Chuckles)
Still, she is
one tough broad.
Ah.
What you got there?
Karen's pot roast recipe.
(Chuckles)
Best one I ever tasted.
She swore I'd never
get it out of her.
So how'd you convince her?
(Sighs) I...
Told her
we have this gift.
We know these are
our last days together.
So what's the point
of holding back?
I didn't want anything
to be left unsaid.
So... (Sighs)
We finally had that talk.
Yes, sir.
She told me... (Chuckles)
She was the one
that lost our passports
on the way to Mexico that time.
(Chuckles)
I told her the truth
about my time in the service,
how I wasn't some tough guy
but scared to death.
She thanked me for always
being able to make her laugh.
And I...
(Voice breaks) I told her...
(Sniffles) She was
the love of my life.
Tom...
It's so important
to say these things
when you can,
because when it's over,
it's over.
I hear ya.
Do you?
(Pops)
(Women scream and laugh)
Yay.
(Sighs)
- Somebody make a toast.
- Uh... oh, to Bree,
Um, who put her life on the line
to protect us,
and we will never forget
what you did.
- (Gaby) Aw.
- Hear, hear.
And... to Karen McCluskey,
the bravest woman
I have ever known.
- Aw.
- (Chuckles)
And to you ladies, who could've
abandoned me during my hour of need.
Okay, okay.
Less thanking, more drinking.
(Clinking)
- (Lynette) Cheers.
- Hey!
- Hi!
- Congratulations, Bree.
I cannot tell you how relieved
I am that you weren't convicted.
Oh, that is so sweet.
Seriously,
do you have any idea how
living across from a murderer
can affect housing prices?
(Chuckles)
Ah. (Sighs)
- Do you have a sec?
- What's up?
(Mouths words)
Have you told the girls
you're moving?
Um, not yet.
Well, I thought it'd be easier
after the trial,
but now
everybody's so happy.
- I just haven't found the right time.
- Well, you're gonna have to find one.
I got an offer
on your house.
Oh, hey,
you're out of ice.
- Oh, do you have any at your house?
- Ye... (Door opens)
- I think I've got a bag.
- I'll be right back.
- What are you doing here?
- (Door closes)
You left so quickly, I-I didn't
get a chance to m...
I'm sorry,
a private party
for my neighbors and friends.
You're mad. I-I get that.
But...
Please let me explain.
There's nothing to explain.
You swore to me you wouldn't
put Gaby on the stand,
and then you did.
You lied to me.
To win this case...
For you.
(Sighs)
And... and... and also for me.
Bree, there was no way I was
gonna let you go to jail.
Plus there's
this thing between us and...
Oh, please. You're just pretending
there's something between us
so you could get information
from me.
I-I wasn't trying to get...
(Bree sighs)
Bree... (Sighs)
I probably shouldn't even
be here.
I had to tell you...
(Whispers) I'm so sorry.
(Sighs) Renee,
you I can forgive.
And, Ben, you're my hero.
(Chuckles) Come on in.
And you are not welcome
in my home.
Can I talk to you?
(Sighs)
They're kinda waiting for me at Bree's.
(Bag rustles)
I'm in charge
of the ice, so...
Lynette!
Lynette, please.
Look...
At the end, before I left,
our problems looked
this big...
So I went away.
But now...
I realized they...
they only seem that way
because we were
so close up against them,
and... and... and they were
blocking me from seeing
how much I love you,
which is...
(Drops hands)
I see that now,
and I need
to tell you that...
Because you have to
say these things
while you still can.
Tom, my...
Ice is melting,
and I'm not exactly sure
what you're saying.
I'm saying...
(Voice breaks) That I know
you've moved on,
and I hope
that you'll be happy.
Because you, Lynette...
You will...
Always be
the love of my life.
That's all.
What do you mean
I've moved on?
Gregg told me
that you broke up with him
because you're in love
with someone else, so...
Yeah, I am.
You.
Me?
(Sighs)
Sync & corrections:
UKsubtitles.ru
(Mary Alice)
This is how it started.
The woman who had lived
on the street for years
came outside...
And introduced herself
to the woman who was
moving in next door.
Welcome to the neighborhood!
- I'm Martha Huber.
- Mary Alice Young.
So... you got a husband?
Mine's dead.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- Me, too... in theory.
Oh. (Chuckles)
I have a husband and a son.
They're in the other van.
They'll be here soon.
Ooh! I used to have a chair
just like that.
Kept breaking,
so I threw it away.
I hate cheap furniture.
Yes, well, uh,
I should go help the movers.
Nice to meet you.
Wait! I hardly know
anything about you.
You didn't even mention
where you folks are from.
Up North.
"Up North"? That doesn't tell me
anything. Where exactly?
Small town.
You wouldn't know it.
Try me.
Why do you need
to know that?
Why don't you wanna
tell me?
Well, it's no big deal.
It's just...
And just like that,
Martha Huber figured out
I was hiding something.
Ohh, you're busy.
We'll just have a long chat
once you've settled in. Okay?
And my new neighbor made it
her mission to find out
what my secret was.
And this was the beginning...
Of the end.
♪♪♪
(Gunshot)
It was just after breakfast
when Susan Delfino
told her friends
she'd soon be moving
from Wisteria Lane.
They were shocked
their old friend
was actually leaving...
so shocked
it took them a moment
to notice another old friend
had returned.
Oh, my God.
Hello, ladies.
Did you miss me?
So three months
after we got to Paris,
- Robin and I broke up.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
Yeah, a long distance move
can be tough on a relationship.
That, and I decided I just
wasn't into women anymore.
Although in Paris, it's hard
to tell the difference.
The women don't shave,
and the men carry purses.
(All laugh)
So... what team
are you playing for now?
Ah, I'm out of the game.
I decided to channel my sexual frustration
into starting my own business...
a line
of frozen French pastries.
Bree, you remember
how my croissants
were always the best
on the Lane.
I remember you thinking that.
(Chuckles)
So, basically, you sell microwavable
French food... to the French?
Yep. As they got lazier and
fatter, I got thinner and richer,
now my accountant
has me buying "chateaux"
just to do something
with all my money.
(Laughs)
So other than wanting to rub your success
in our faces, what brings you back?
I have a little business proposition...
For Lynette.
Tighter.
(Scoffs) If I go any tighter,
you won't be able to breathe.
Jean, you're talking to a woman
who gave herself salmonella
to lose 10 pounds
before prom.
Beauty is suffering.
Now tighter!
Hey.
(Gasps)
What are you doing here?
You can't see me before
the wedding. It's bad luck.
Uh, so I, uh, picked up
the programs from the printer.
(Gasps)
Oh, my God.
Do I have to do everything?
This is ivory.
I told you to get beige.
Are you color-blind?
You do know I'm black, right?
Honey, I-I can't help but notice,
uh, you seem a little...
- Bitchy?
- No, I was gonna say, uh...
Less angelic than usual.
I am busting my ass to plan
the happiest day of your life.
So let's ditch the sarcasm,
shall we?
You know what?
It is bad luck
for the groom to see the bride
before the wedding,
and I just realized why.
(Door closes)
Jean, I told you tighter.
I don't care if I can breathe.
(Under breath) At this point,
neither do I.
What was going on
out there?
Katherine came back
for a visit.
And before you get too excited,
no, she's not a lesbian anymore.
Really? Damn.
Hey, while you were out dishing with
your friends, our gardener quit.
He wouldn't name names, but apparently
one of us is a little too hard to please.
(Crunches) Yeah,
you should work on that.
- So you gonna get a new one?
- When? (Crunches)
I have a job, too, you know.
Carlos, you help the poor
and downtrodden...
a group with
a very flexible schedule.
(Cell phone rings)
I'm working crazy hours.
House stuff is up to you now.
(Ring)
Mm! It's my boss.
(Ring and beep)
Hello, Mr. Hoffman.
Really? Me?
Y-yes, I'm very interested.
Thank you.
I-I don't know
what to say.
Okay,
I'll see you then, sir.
(Beep) What was that about?
I just got
a huge promotion.
I'm the new head
of v.I.P. Sales.
Seriously?
- Babe, that's amazing.
- Mm.
- What's... wrong?
- I don't know.
It's so big.
It's a whole department.
They're really trusting me.
What if I can't do it?
Gaby, don't you know
how smart and talented you are?
You deserve this.
(Sighs) Yeah.
You know what? You're right.
(Chuckles)
I just gotta learn
how to be the boss. (Chuckles)
I don't even know
how to talk to employees.
Yeah, I think our gardener
would agree.
Oh, please. (Chuckles)
That sad sack was a moron.
So how you been feeling?
I've been craving chocolate
constantly.
But that's okay, right?
Within moderation,
but I'm not worried.
You look great.
Mm, thank you.
You know,
Julie is getting her PhD,
so soon she'll be a doctor, too.
Maybe you two should have lunch
sometime and talk shop.
(Pager beeps)
Yeah, that would be nice.
Uh, I'm sorry. I have to take
this. Uh, I'll be right back.
(Door opens)
What the hell was that?
- (Door closes)
- He was flirting with you.
He is my obstetrician.
Well, he knows you're fertile.
Men like that.
Enough. I don't need you
to fix me up.
I'm just worried about you.
I don't want you to be lonely.
Well, good news.
In three weeks, I will have
a permanent houseguest.
I'm talking about
the other kind of lonely.
Even single mothers
have needs.
Childbirth can't possibly be
as painful as this conversation.
You don't know
how hard it's gonna be.
Having a kid is exhausting.
You have no time to exercise
or eat right.
The great news is, you don't
have to let yourself go.
I'll be there,
helping with the baby.
So you'll have time
to go to the gym.
I'll let myself go.
I don't mind.
Mom, I just felt the baby
tap out "make her stop"
in Morse code.
It's hard to find a man
when you're a single mom.
That's my point. I'm done.
As I remember,
you found Mike.
Yes. Well...
I was very lucky.
You sure were.
(Sighs)
There you go.
(Groans)
Oh, beautiful day,
isn't it?
One of the nice things about dying
is every day seems beautiful.
You always wince
when I say things like that.
I don't mean to.
Its just... hard for me.
For you? Hey, you wanna
switch places with her?
Be nice, Roy.
By the way, Karen,
I got that song you wanted
for your... funeral.
Oh, thank you, Bree.
Johnny Mathis.
My girlfriends and I
taught each other to dance
listening to
"Wonderful! Wonderful!"
Aw. Oh, I was only able
to get it on a CD.
No, no.
It's gotta be on a 45 that I can
play on a record player,
just like I did
when I was a kid.
By the way, I'll also need
the record player.
You know, it's really hard
to find those 45s.
But I'm gonna keep looking.
(Cell phone rings)
(Beep)
Hello?
Oh. Hello, Trip.
I already told you,
I'm not interested.
Please, stop calling.
(Beep)
Is that your lawyer friend?
Well, you're half right.
I thought you liked him.
I did, more than I've liked
anybody in a very long time.
But then I realized that
he just manipulates people
so that he can get
what he wants.
Can't trust him.
All right, you two,
I will check in on you later.
Roy, be a peach and look up
a phone number for me.
Karen, what are you up to?
I don't know.
I thought it would be fun
to screw with people's lives
one last time
before I check out.
(Chuckles)
(Laughs)
Wow. It sounds like
you are doing pretty good.
I mean, your own company?
Yeah, I didn't want to brag
in front of the girls,
but it's worth a few bucks.
That was you not bragging?
Well, just look at our last
financial statement.
- (Gasps)
- Ha! I love doing that!
Oh! (Laughs) Have a seat.
In fact, we are doing so well
that we are looking to expand
worldwide,
and I would like you to head
our U.S. division
in New York.
Oh, my God.
That's a huge job.
Why me?
Because you're the smartest
businesswoman I know.
And when I heard
that you and Tom split,
I thought, there's nothing
tying you to Fairview.
Well, here's the thing...
20 minutes
until my job interview,
and I lose a button. Can you...
Katherine?
That's the thing.
What brings you back
to the states?
Your wife, actually.
I came to offer her a job
in New York.
- Wow.
- But obviously, I'm not taking it.
- (Chuckles)
We just got back together,
and I couldn't be happier.
Mmm. Sorry, Katherine. I know how
painful it is to lose Lynette,
and how sweet it is
to get her back.
(Chuckles)
Here, leave the shirt with me,
babe. I got it.
Thanks.
Well...
I'm in town for three days if you
wanna keep talking about this.
No. I feel pretty comfortable
with my decision.
Okay, but the Lynette
that I knew
was never happy with a life
of... sewing buttons.
(Door closes)
Hey, hey! Sorry I'm late. I'm starving!
What are we having?
I had a lovely steak.
Then an hour later,
I had your lovely steak.
So I guess you're having...
Cereal.
Oh, come on. You know how it is.
First day of a new job... it was crazy.
And what? (Sighs)
You lost your phone?
(Sighs) I know, I know.
I'm a terrible, awful person.
But maybe you can
find a way to forgive me
after you see this.
Whoa.
(Laughs)
I know. I saw it,
and all I could think about
was how sexy it would look on
that big, strong wrist of yours.
(Both chuckle)
Well, I don't think
I've ever seen anyth...
Oh, my God. Wait a minute.
What?
I know this move.
I invented this move.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
It's what
I used to do to you.
I'd buy you jewelry
to compensate
for being a lousy husband.
And it worked beautifully,
so shut up and enjoy it.
I can't believe you're trying
to buy me off with a watch.
(Gasps) Ooh! When you shake
your wrist like that,
the diamonds really catch
the light.
Oh, my God,
you're even quoting me!
(Scoffs) You don't want
the watch? Fine.
But everyone has a price.
You name it.
Sex? Massage?
Three stooges marathon?
The price of my forgiveness
is you paying
a little more attention to me,
being more present, more respectful
of my feelings and needs.
- You want a new car.
- I'm going to bed.
What? No, come back!
You're sexy when you're angry.
Yep! That's mine, too!
Lynette Scavo?
Oh, my God!
- How long as it been?
- Oh! A long time.
- How are you doing, Natalie?
- I'm great.
The question is, how are you?
I heard about you and Tom.
Oh. Yeah, we went through
a rough patch,
but we're back together now,
and things are better than ever.
(Chuckles)
What a relief. I just kept
thinking, "poor Lynette..."
"sacrificed her whole career
for that man,
and then
it didn't even work out?"
Oh, just to be clear, I didn't
sacrifice my career for anyone.
Oh, I didn't mean anything
by it.
If anything,
I'm jealous of you.
Oh?
My company has branches
in 15 cities around the world.
I live out of a suitcase.
And you?
There must be days when
you don't even leave the house.
Oh, the simple life.
I got a job offer yesterday.
Really?
Yeah, this big
European food company is
taking its brand to the states,
and they want me to run it.
So...
Impressive.
When do you start?
Well, it's in New York, so it's
a lot to consider, and...
And that is the difference
between me and you.
I'd grab an opportunity
like that in a second,
but not you.
(Chuckles)
In your heart of hearts,
you're a wife and a mommy.
Congrats.
See ya.
(Dials)
Katherine, it's Lynette.
Call me back. We have to talk.
(Beep)
Hey, gotta run. Huge day. The e-mails
have been coming in since 7:00.
Just so you know,
our new gardener started today.
Great. Mind running defense for me? I really
don't have time to chitchat with the help.
It'll be my pleasure.
Oh. Hola.
I'm Carmen.
Uh-huh.
What the hell is that?
That's our new gardener.
She's gonna take care of everything
around here that's been neglected.
Oh, you think that's funny?
Just making a point.
You crossed a line,
Carlos.
You crossed a line!
Gaby, come on!
(Car door closes, engine starts)
- Gaby!
- (Tires peal)
(Sighs) Watch the dirt.
And watch the grass.
Focus, ladies!
This dress costs more than
your houses put together!
Okay, you know what, Renee? I know
this is your day, but it's only 10:00,
and you're already
a huge pain in the ass.
Well, then I'm running late. I should've
been a huge pain in the ass by 9:00.
You in the stupid
hat, open the door!
(Chuckles) Oh, wow!
Where are you going
all dolled up?
Renee's wedding. I just wanted
to check on Karen before I left.
She's sleeping.
I don't think
it'll be long now.
Oh, Roy.
I am... so sorry.
Would you like me to stay?
No. This is our
time together.
We'll be fine.
Oh, good!
You found Karen's record.
Not me. That lawyer guy.
- Trip? - Karen told him
she really wanted it.
The son of a gun must've gone
to 20 different record stores.
(Sighs)
Well, that's lovely.
You should've seen the smile on
her face when he brought it in.
Mm.
He's... a good guy.
(Inhales sharply)
Do you seriously need
to stretch out on her?
What do you want me to do?
Crease?
(Cell phone rings and beeps)
(Scoffs) Hello, Ben.
Hey, hey, hey.
Don't raise your voice to me.
Well, hair and makeup
took forever,
and then we had to wait
20 minutes for Susan, and...
I was totally on time.
(Lowered voice) He does not
need to know that.
(Normal voice)
Yeah, we're on our way now.
I promise we'll be there
no later than...
- Oh! We're going through a tunnel!
- (Beep)
How late are we?
I should've been
cutting the cake by now!
Okay, not a good day
to hand her a knife.
Mm.
(Exhales deeply)
Julie, are you okay?
- Oh, my God.
- What? What's wrong?
(Exhales sharply)
I think my water just broke.
(All gasp)
(Women scream)
- (Groans)
- Oh! Ah!
Aah! How could you do this
to me?!
She's in labor!
Oh! Nine months!
You had nine months, and this is
the moment you pick?!
Renee, I am so sorry. Aah! Aah!
Hold on.
Everything's gonna be fine.
How?! My dress is ruined!
- (Julie and Susan breathing deeply)
- Wait, I got an idea.
Hey, driver, we need you
to swing by Cumberly's.
My store has
an amazing bridal department.
Are you insane?!
Take us to the hospital!
- Oh, come on. She just started labor.
- (Groans)
Keep your legs together,
honey.
Look, we're just gonna run in
and grab a dress.
(Scoffs) And shoes.
You need shoes, too?
Thanks
to old faithful here.
My daughter is having a baby, and
you wanna go on a shopping spree?!
Uh, could someone please
just tell me where to go?
- Cumberly's!
- Hospital!
(Breathing deeply)
Let's just go to Cumberly's.
- Julie!
- Mom, my contractions just started.
We have time. Aah!
Ohh! Do you have to keep
doing that?
(Brakes screech)
Okay,
size 6s are over there.
- Hey!
- Oh, don't lie to me!
(Scoffs) No.
No.
God, no.
(Gasps)
Now that is beautiful.
My daughter's looking at this.
- When's her wedding?
- Three months.
Mine's in five minutes.
Unzip me.
(Zip)
Oh! Hi. Hi. (Chuckles)
I'm, uh, Gabrielle Solis,
head of V.I.P. Sales
here at Cumberly's.
I'm Kent, minimum wage worker
stuck here on a Saturday.
Can I help you?
Uh, I need to borrow
a bridal gown.
- Borrow?
- Just for the afternoon.
We don't lend bridal dresses.
Well... (Chuckles)
I know it's not policy,
but can't you do a favor
for a fellow worker?
Ma'am,
I've never heard of you.
Do you have
your employee I.D. Card?
No. I'm not
one of those nerds
who carries her I.D. Card
on a...
Handsome Lanyard. (Chuckles)
So you want me to give you
a $6,000 wedding dress?
$5,000 with
my employee discount. (Chuckles)
Go away, ma'am.
- Ow!
- Ohh! Oh, that was a big one!
Oh! They seem to be coming
a lot faster.
Oh. (Sighs)
Excuse me,
would you mind going in
and finding out
what's keeping them?
Things seem to be
speeding up a bit back here.
Right away.
(Exhales sharply)
Mom, what are you doing?
You are not having my granddaughter
in the back of a limousine!
(Grunts)
Ooh!
(Exhales deeply) Keep breathing!
(Starts engine)
(Tires peal)
(Speaking inaudibly)
- Oh.
- Ahh. So we set?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Told you I was
a big shot here. (Chuckles)
Now walk with me. Um, there's
only one tiny hiccup.
(Kent) Hey, where you going
with that dress?!
- And now we run.
- (Gasps)
(Both panting)
Where... where's the limo?
- I don't know. It was right here.
- (Alarm blaring)
And we're running again!
Aah!
(Both panting)
Do you... not have a car?
Does it look like
we have a car, huh?
- Does it?!
- Aah!
Okay, all right, again,
late for your own wedding.
- (Grunts)
- Maybe kill this guy later.
(Breathing heavily)
Don't say a word.
You hear me?!
You have no idea what I had
to go through to get here,
so if you even give me
one syllable of grief,
I will kick your sorry ass
all the way back to Australia!
(Breathing heavily)
I've never seen anyone
look so beautiful.
(Sobbing)
(Renee laughs)
(Chuckles)
Let's go inside and get started
on our wedded bliss, eh?
(Jazz playing,
indistinct conversations)
No, no, Katherine,
I am excited.
I just need
to talk to Tom first.
Well, can you give me till the end
of the day? Okay, thanks. Bye.
Talk to me about what?
(Chuckles)
- Hi!
- Hi. Mmm.
Oh, um, Katherine keeps
pushing me about this job thing.
- I thought you told her "no."
- I did,
but once she started talking
about compensation packages
and... (Chuckles)
You're negotiating a salary?
Lynette, we... (Sighs)
We just got back together.
What... what are you doing?
It could be the last time
an opportunity like this
comes along for me.
If I don't take it,
I'm... I'm afraid that...
You won't be happy.
Well...
Yeah.
Hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Lynette...
I would do anything, I would
go anywhere in the world
if I believed it would
finally make you happy.
But for as long as I have known
you, you've always thought
you needed something else
to make you complete.
And I'm starting to realize
nothing ever will.
(Indistinct conversations
and laughter)
(Piano playing light jazz)
Hello, Trip.
Ben invited me, so if you wanna
slug somebody, slug him.
(Chuckles) No.
I'm glad to see you.
I wanted to, uh, thank you for
what you did for Mrs. McCluskey.
That was very kind.
She's an awesome lady,
and she once helped out
a client of mine.
Well, that's all I wanted to say.
Enjoy the reception.
Really, you can't think
of anything else to say to me?
Like what?
I don't know. Like, um...
How about, "hey, Trip,
maybe you are a good guy."
I should give you
another chance"?
Is that why you found
that old record? (Chuckles)
To impress me?
Do you really think that?
Look...
I know I wanna be with you.
But if you don't think
you can ever trust me again...
Well, I'm not gonna beg.
Why?
Yes. Why do you want
to be with me?
You were my lawyer.
You know all the ugliest details
of my life...
my lying, my drinking,
my promiscuity.
I was actually relieved when you
put Gaby on the witness stand
because it explained
why you kissed me.
It was a manipulation.
I got it.
But to keep saying you want me
when you know how...
(Whispers)
Horribly flawed I am.
I don't trust you because
it just doesn't make sense.
How about...
I explain it?
Mmm.
Did that clear it up
for you?
Almost.
Look, Bree... (Sighs)
All those ugly details
you're talking about, I...
They just prove
that you're human.
I don't want to love
an ideal.
I wanna... I wanna love
a real person.
(Whispers)
So what happens now?
Well...
First, we're gonna walk out
onto that dance floor
and show your friends
how it's really done.
Hopefully by then,
I'll get up the courage
to once again ask you
to go out on a date me.
Of course,
even as I'm saying that,
I'm still not sure
what you're gonna say.
Did that clear it up
for you?
(Tango music playing)
Hey, you wanna dance?
They're playing a tango.
Wow. You're finally talking
to me again.
I must be out
of the doghouse.
No, I'm still pretty mad.
Why? It was a joke.
All those years ago,
when...
I did what I did
with John Rowland?
That is the most shameful thing
in my life.
You can't make jokes about it.
It's too painful.
Fair enough.
You know...
It was the most shameful thing
in my life, too.
I'm sorry.
No.
What's shameful
is that I neglected you.
I had this beautiful wife,
but I focused
on all the wrong things.
It was a tough time
for both of us.
I guess that's the point
I was making hiring Carmen.
Our roles are reversed now,
but we can't start drifting away
from each other.
I never want
to go back to that again.
We won't.
We've grown up since then.
(Chuckles)
Although,
for two smart grownups,
we sure seem
to fight a lot.
(Chuckles)
Why is it other couples
seem to waltz through life?
That's easy.
You and me?
We're doing a tango.
(Kisses)
- (Exhales sharply)
- (Knocks on doorframe)
Hey. I hear someone's having
a baby.
Oh, yes, a little
ahead of schedule. Sorry.
No, it's no problem. I was just
playing hoops down the block.
Don't worry. I'm gonna wash up, and then
we'll get this show on the road. Okay?
- Okay.
- All right.
Did you see his legs?
How can you not want
to be married to those legs?
(Groans) Oh, mom, please.
Right. I'm annoying. Sorry.
You know, in honor
of this special day,
I promise to never again bug you
about finding a husband.
Oh. Ohh. (lnhales sharply)
Even the baby knows
you're lying.
(Chuckles)
- Ohh.
- (Sighs)
What about you?
Do you think you'll ever
get married again?
Julie...
No, I'm serious.
You're still young
and gorgeous.
(Laughs) Oh, I don't know.
(Inhales and exhales deeply)
There's a saying...
"you know
you've hit middle age
"when your memories become
more important to you
than your dreams."
And I have
such wonderful memories...
of Mike,
and you kids growing up,
all of our friends
on the Lane.
Mm.
Oh, do I have
one last torrid romance in me?
Maybe.
(Chuckles)
But I know if I am
ever cold and lonely,
I can wrap myself up
in all those memories,
and I will be content.
(Sighs deeply)
(Amplified voice)
So, Renee and Ben,
never forget
that it takes a lot of love
to make a house a home.
And when you're in the market
for a new home,
consider Lee McDermott,
1-800...
- Give me that!
- (Feedback whines)
(Amplified voice) Okay.
Matron of honor's turn.
Lynette Scavo, give us a toast.
- Oh!
- (Applause)
(Amplified voice)
Renee and Ben,
your wedding is one
of the best days of your life
because it's the day
you realize,
"I finally have the thing I need
to be happy."
And then you forget.
So... then what happens is,
instead of waking up
every morning
and shouting,
"somebody loves me!"
You start looking around
and thinking,
"what do I want now?
What's the next thing I need
to be happy?"
So...
You look and you look,
and you keep thinking you've
found it, but nothing works.
And the reason
that nothing works
is because...
That hole in your heart
that you're trying to fill...
Is already filled.
You just forgot.
(Chuckles)
Don't ever forget.
Always remember how much
you wanted to be loved,
and how much you are loved.
And I think if you can do that...
and it isn't easy...
you will stop looking
and realize
you already are happy.
To Renee and Ben,
and to remembering. (Chuckles)
- Cheers.
- (Clinking)
(Whispers) I love you.
(Mouths words)
♪♪♪
(Indistinct conversations)
So... you meant that?
I'm happy.
Right here, right now.
I bet someone like that
could be happy anywhere.
- (Chuckles)
- Mmm.
Even New York.
(Crackling)
Again?
(Johnny Mathis'
"wonderful! Wonderful!" Plays)
♪ Ooh, ooh ♪
♪ sometimes we stand
on the top of a hill ♪
♪ and we gaze at the earth
and the sky ♪
♪ ahh, ahh, ahh ♪
♪ I turn to you,
and you melt in my arms ♪
♪ there we are, darling,
only you and I ♪
♪ ahh, ahh, ahh ♪
♪ what a moment to share ♪
♪ it's wonderful, wonderful ♪
♪ oh, so wonderful, my love ♪
♪ ahh, ahh, ahh, ahh ♪
♪ the world is full
of wondrous things, it's true ♪
♪ but they wouldn't have
much meaning without you ♪
♪ some quiet evening,
I sit by your side ♪
♪ and we're lost in a world
of our own ♪
♪ ahh, ahh, ahh ♪
♪ I feel the glow
of your unspoken love ♪
♪ I'm aware of the treasure
that I own ♪
♪ ahh, ahh, ahh, ahh ♪
♪ and I say to myself ♪
♪ it's wonderful, wonderful ♪
♪ oh, so wonderful, my love ♪
♪ and I say to myself ♪
♪ it's wonderful, wonderful ♪
♪ oh, so wonderful ♪
♪ my love ♪
♪ ooh, ooh ♪
♪ ooh ♪
(Songs ends)
(Crackling)
Susan Delfino moved from
Wisteria Lane on a Thursday.
But before she left,
she went to spend a few more
moments with her friends,
doing what they loved best.
I see your 25...
(Chip thuds)
- And I raise you 50.
- (Clink)
(Clink)
- I know you're bluffing.
- How?
For the last ten years,
every time you have a bad hand,
you tap the side of your glass.
No, I don't.
Yeah, you do.
- You totally do.
- Absolutely.
I have a tell,
and you guys never told me?
All right,
you each owe me $12,000.
- (All chuckle)
- (Chips clinking)
I just realized
this might be the last time
we'll play poker together.
- Oh, don't say that
. Well, you're moving,
and Lynette's talking about
taking that job in New York.
Oh, we'll still get together.
I guess. It's just...
What?
I just always had
this fantasy,
the four of us staying here,
growing old together.
You know, our grandkids coming
to visit,
me staying gorgeous while
the three of you age horribly.
(Laughing loudly)
You know she's actually
dreamed about that.
Of course she has.
No, seriously,
I'm gonna miss this so much.
I'm gonna miss us.
It's funny.
Some people never get to know
the folks next door.
They share a fence
and nothing else.
And we've shared everything.
(Sighs) How did we get to be
so lucky?
I am so crazy nuts
about you guys.
Promise me
this is not the last time
we're gonna
play poker together.
Absolutely not.
- We'll just have to make the time.
- Of course we will.
It was a promise made
in all sincerity,
but sadly,
it was not meant to be.
Lynette and Tom Scavo
left the Lane four weeks later.
They moved to New York,
where Lynette learned
the joy of being a C.E.O.
She and Tom soon bought a penthouse
overlooking Central Park...
Where, years later, she'd take
her six grandchildren
and yell at them.
Gabrielle and Carlos Solis
left the neighborhood
the following year.
This was after Carlos
helped her develop
a personal shopping web site,
which led to Gabrielle
getting her own show
on the home shopping network.
They soon bought a mansion
in California,
where they argued
happily ever after.
Two years later,
Bree and her new husband
left Fairview.
They moved to Louisville,
where Bree joined a club
for conservative women.
Trip then encouraged her
to enter into local politics.
The following November,
Bree was elected to
the Kentucky state legislature.
But Susan Delfino
was the first to move
from Wisteria Lane.
And this is how it ended.
She introduced herself
to the woman
who was moving in.
- You must be Jennifer.
- And you must be Susan.
- (Chuckles) Nice to meet you.
- Sorry if I'm early.
I, uh, made better time
than I thought I would.
We were just about to leave.
My house is your house.
(Both laugh)
I mean, legally,
this is your house.
(Sighs) Ahh.
(Laughs)
Hey, I hope
that you'll be happy here.
Thanks. Steve's so excited
to finally live in the suburbs.
I'm a little worried
it's going to be boring.
Oh, I wouldn't worry
about that.
Now this street is
a lot of things.
- Boring is not one of them.
- (Laughs)
(Sighs)
- Can we go now?
- Yeah, we're going.
(Seat belt clicks)
(Starts engine)
(Sighs)
Hey, do you guys mind if I take
one last spin around the block?
Go for it.
(Shifts gears)
As Susan left her driveway,
she had a feeling
she was being watched...
And she was.
The ghosts of people who had
been a part of Wisteria Lane
were gazing upon her
as she passed.
They watched her,
as they watch everyone,
always hoping
the living could learn
to put aside rage and sorrow,
bitterness and regret.
These ghosts watch,
wanting people to remember
that even
the most desperate life...
Is oh... so wonderful.
But only a lucky few realize
the gift they've been given.
Most people just go on
day after day,
trying in vain...
To keep secrets...
That will never stay hidden.
Sync & corrections:
UKsubtitles.ru