- Previously on
- Desperate Housewives...
Susan had a secret.
Have you told
the girls you're moving?
Not yet.
I got an offer on your house.
Carlos and Gaby got competitive.
I'll see you tonight.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
I can't take the girls
to school.
You always take them.
I have to go to
work early today.
Well, I'm at work right now.
Renee made her wedding plans.
That's a cake
I made for a wedding
a few years ago.
I know what you're gonna say,
it's too extravagant.
It's not big enough.
Oh. Well,
I suppose we could
add another tier.
Make it two.
Bree ended her relationship
with her lawyer.
You've lied to me.
To win this case.
You're just pretending
there's something between us
so you could get
information from me.
I wasn't trying to get...
And you are not
welcome in my home.
And Tom and Lynette
finally got back together.
This is how it started.
The woman who had lived
on the street for years
came outside
and introduced herself
to the woman
who was moving in next door.
Welcome to the neighborhood!
I'm Martha Huber.
Mary Alice Young.
So, you got a husband?
Mine's dead.
I'm sorry.
Me, too, in theory.
Oh.
I have a husband and a son.
They're in the other van.
They'll be here soon.
Oh! I used to have
a chair just like that.
It kept breaking,
so I threw it away.
I hate cheap furniture.
Yes. Well,
I should go help the movers.
Nice to meet you.
Wait! I hardly know
anything about you.
You didn't even mention
where you folks are from.
Up north.
"Up north."
That doesn't tell me anything.
Where exactly?
Small town.
You wouldn't know it.
Try me.
Why do you need to know that?
Why don't you wanna tell me?
Well, it's no big deal.
It's just...
And just like that,
Martha Huber figured out
I was hiding something.
Oh. You're busy.
We'll just have a long chat
once you've settled in. Okay?
And my new neighbor
made it her mission
to find out
what my secret was.
And this was the beginning
of the end.
It was just after breakfast
when Susan Delfino
told her friends
she'd soon be moving
from Wisteria Lane.
They were shocked
their old friend
was actually leaving.
So shocked, it took them
a moment to notice
another old friend had returned.
Oh, my God.
Hello, ladies.
Did you miss me?
So, three months
after we got to Paris,
Robin and I broke up.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, a long distance move
can be tough
on a relationship.
That, and I decided
I just wasn't
into women anymore.
Although, in Paris,
it's hard to
tell the difference.
The women don't shave,
and the men carry purses.
So, what team are
you playing for now?
I'm out of the game.
I decided to channel
my sexual frustration
into starting my own business,
a line of frozen
French pastries.
Bree, you remember
how my croissants
were always
the best on the lane.
I remember you thinking that.
So, basically, you sell
microwavable French food
to the French?
Yep.
As they got lazier and fatter,
I got thinner and richer.
Now my accountant
has me buying chateaus
just to do something
with all my money.
So, other than wanting to
rub your success in our faces,
what brings you back?
I have a little
business proposition
for Lynette.
Tighter.
If I go any tighter,
you won't be able to breathe.
Jean, you're talking
to a woman
who gave herself salmonella
to lose 10 pounds before prom.
Beauty is suffering.
Now, tighter!
Hey.
What are you doing here?
You can't see me
before the wedding.
It's bad luck!
So, I picked up the programs
from the printer.
Oh, my God.
Do I have to do everything?
This is ivory.
I told you to get beige.
Are you color-blind?
You do know I'm black, right?
Honey,
I can't help but notice,
you seem a little...
Bitchy?
No, I was gonna say,
less angelic than usual.
I am busting my ass
to plan the happiest day
of your life.
So let's ditch the sarcasm,
shall we?
You know what?
It is bad luck for the groom
to see the bride
before the wedding.
And I just realized why.
Jean, I told you, tighter.
I don't care if I can breathe.
At this point, neither do I.
What was going on out there?
Katherine came back for a visit.
And before you get too excited,
no, she's not a lesbian anymore.
Really? Damn.
Hey, while you were out
dishing with your friends,
our gardener quit.
He wouldn't name names,
but apparently,
one of us is
a little too hard to please.
Yeah, you should work on that.
So you're gonna get a new one?
When?
I have a job, too, you know.
Carlos, you help the poor
and downtrodden,
a group with a very
flexible schedule.
I'm working crazy hours.
House stuff is up to you now.
Oh! It's my boss.
Hello, Mr. Hoffman.
Really? Me?
Yes, I'm very interested.
Thank you.
I don't know what to say.
Okay, I'll see you then, sir.
What was that about?
I just got a huge promotion.
I'm the new head of VIP Sales.
Seriously?
Babe, that's amazing.
What's wrong?
I don't know. It's so big.
It's a whole department.
They're really trusting me.
What if I can't do it?
Gabby, don't you know how
smart and talented you are?
You deserve this.
Yeah. You know what,
you're right.
I just gotta learn
how to be the boss.
I don't even know
how to talk to employees.
Yeah, I think
our gardener would agree.
Please.
That sad sack was a moron.
So, how you been feeling?
I've been craving
chocolate constantly.
But that's okay, right?
Within moderation,
but I'm not worried.
You look great.
Thank you.
You know,
Julie is getting her Ph.D.
So soon,
she'll be a doctor, too.
Maybe you two
should have lunch
sometime and talk shop.
Yeah, that would be nice.
I'm sorry,
I have to take this.
I'll be right back.
What the hell was that?
He was flirting with you.
He's my obstetrician.
Well, he knows you're fertile.
Men like that.
Enough. I don't need you
to fix me up.
I'm just worried about you.
I don't want you to be lonely.
Well, good news.
In three weeks,
I will have
a permanent house guest.
I'm talking about
the other kind of lonely.
Even single mothers have needs.
Childbirth can't possibly
be as painful as
this conversation.
You don't know
how hard it's gonna be.
Having a kid is exhausting.
You have no time to exercise
or eat right.
The great news is,
you don't have to
let yourself go.
I'll be there,
helping with the baby.
So you'll have time
to go to the gym.
I'll let myself go.
I don't mind.
Mom, I just felt the baby
tap out "Make her stop"
in Morse Code.
It's hard to find a man
when you're a single mom.
That's my point. I'm done.
As I remember, you found Mike.
Yes, well, I was very lucky.
You sure were.
There you go.
Beautiful day, isn't it?
One of the nice things
about dying is,
every day seems beautiful.
You always wince
when I say things like that.
I don't mean to.
It's just hard for me.
For you?
You wanna switch places
with her?
Be nice, Roy.
By the way, Karen,
I got that song you wanted
for your funeral.
Thank you, Bree.
Johnny Mathis.
My girlfriends and I
taught each other to dance
listening to
Wonderful! Wonderful!
I was only able
to get it on a CD.
No, no. It's gotta be
on a 45 that I can play
on a record player,
just like I did
when I was a kid.
By the way,
I'll also need
the record player.
You know,
it's really hard
to find those 45s.
But I'm gonna keep looking.
Hello.
Oh. Hello, Trip.
I already told you,
I'm not interested.
Please stop calling.
Is that your lawyer friend?
Well, you're half right.
I thought you liked him.
I did, more than
I've liked anybody
in a very long time.
But then I realized
that he just
manipulates people
so that he can
get what he wants.
I can't trust him.
All right, you two,
I will check in on you later.
Roy, be a peach
and look up
a phone number for me.
Karen, what are you up to?
I don't know.
I thought it would be fun to
screw with people's lives
one last time
before I check out.
Wow.
Sounds like you're doing
pretty good.
I mean, your own company?
Yeah.
I didn't wanna brag
in front of the girls,
but it's worth a few bucks.
That was you not bragging?
Well, just look at
our last financial statement.
I love doing that!
Have a seat.
In fact, we are doing so well
that we are looking
to expand worldwide.
And I would like you to
head our US division
in New York.
Oh, my God.
That's a huge job.
Why me?
Because you're the smartest
businesswoman I know.
And when I heard
that you and Tom split,
I thought there's nothing
tying you to Fairview.
Well, here's the thing...
Twenty minutes
until my job interview,
and I lose a button.
Can you... Katherine.
That's the thing.
What brings you back
to the States?
Your wife, actually.
I came to offer her a job
in New York.
Wow!
But obviously,
I'm not taking it.
We just got back together,
and I couldn't be happier.
Sorry, Katherine.
I know how painful
it is to lose Lynette,
and how sweet it is
to get her back.
Here.
Leave the shirt with me, babe.
I got it.
Thanks.
Well, I'm in town for three days
if you wanna keep
talking about this.
No. I feel pretty comfortable
with my decision.
Okay.
But the Lynette that I knew
was never happy with
a life of sewing buttons.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Sorry I'm late.
I'm starving.
What are we having?
I had a lovely steak.
Then, an hour later,
I had your lovely steak.
So I guess you're having cereal.
Come on, you know how it is.
First day of a new job?
It was crazy.
And what, you lost your phone?
I know, I know.
I'm a terrible, awful person.
But maybe you can
find a way to forgive me
after you see this.
Whoa!
I know. I saw it,
and all I could
think about was
how sexy it would look
on that big, strong
wrist of yours.
I don't think I've
ever seen anything...
Oh, my God. Wait a minute.
What?
I know this move.
I invented this move.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
It's what I used to do to you.
I'd buy you jewelry
to compensate for
being a lousy husband.
And it worked beautifully.
So shut up and enjoy.
I can't believe
you're trying to
buy me off with a watch.
Oh! When you shake
your wrist like that,
the diamonds
really catch the light.
Oh, my God!
You're even quoting me!
You don't want the watch?
Fine.
But everyone has a price.
You name it.
Sex, massage,
Three Stooges marathon.
The price for my forgiveness
is you paying
a little more attention
to me.
Being more present,
more respectful
of my feelings and needs.
You want a new car.
I'm going to bed.
What? No, come back.
You're sexy
when you're angry.
Yep, that's mine, too!
Lynette Scavo?
Oh, my God.
How long has it been?
Oh! A long time.
How are you doing, Natalie?
I'm great.
The question is, how are you?
I heard about you and Tom.
Oh! Yeah, we went
through a rough patch.
But we're back together now,
and things are
better than ever.
What a relief.
I just kept thinking,
"Poor Lynette.
"Sacrificed her whole career
for that man,
"and then
it didn't even work out?"
Just to be clear,
I didn't sacrifice
my career for anyone.
Well, I didn't mean
anything by it.
If anything, I'm jealous of you.
Oh?
My company has branches in
15 cities around the world.
I live out of a suitcase.
And you?
There must be days
when you don't even
leave the house.
The simple life.
I got a job offer yesterday.
Really?
Yeah. This big
European food company
is taking its brand
to the States,
and they want me
to run it, so...
Impressive.
When do you start?
Well, it's in New York,
so it's a lot
to consider, and...
And that is the difference
between me and you.
I'd grab
an opportunity like that
in a second.
But not you.
In your heart of hearts,
you're a wife and a mommy.
Congrats.
See you.
Katherine, it's Lynette.
Call me back.
We have to talk.
Hey, gotta run.
Huge day.
E-mails have been coming in
since 7:00.
Just so you know,
our new gardener
started today.
Great.
Mind running defense for me?
I really don't have time
to chit-chat with the help.
It'll be my pleasure.
Oh! Hola!
I'm Carmen.
Uh-huh.
What the hell is that?
That's our new gardener.
She's gonna take care of
everything around here
that's been neglected.
You think that's funny?
Just making a point.
You crossed the line, Carlos.
You've crossed the line!
Gabby, come on.
Gabby!
Watch the dirt.
And watch the grass.
Focus, ladies!
This dress costs
more than your houses,
put together!
Okay. You know what, Renee,
I know this is your day,
but it's only 10:00
and you're already
a huge pain in the ass.
Well, then, I'm running late.
I should've been
a huge pain in the ass
by 9:00.
You in the stupid hat,
open the door!
Oh! Wow!
Where you going all dolled up?
Renee's wedding.
I just wanted
to check on Karen
before I left.
She's sleeping.
I don't think it'll be long now.
Roy, I'm so sorry.
Would you like me to stay?
No.
This is our time together.
We'll be fine.
Good, you found Karen's record.
Not me, that lawyer guy.
Trip?
Karen told him
she really wanted it.
The son of a gun
must have gone to
20 different record stores.
Well, that's lovely.
You should have seen
the smile on her face
when he brought it in.
He's a good guy.
Do you seriously need to
stretch out on her?
What do you want
me to do, crease?
Hello, Ben.
Hey, hey, hey.
Don't raise your voice to me.
Hair and make-up took forever,
and then we had
to wait 20 minutes
for Susan and...
I was totally on time.
He does not need to know that.
Yeah, we're on our way now.
I promise we'll be
there no later than...
We're going through a tunnel!
How late are we?
I should have been
cutting the cake by now!
Okay, not a good day
to hand her a knife.
Julie, are you okay?
Oh, my God.
What? What's wrong?
I think my water just broke.
How could you do this to me?
She's in labor!
Nine months!
You had nine months,
and this is the moment
you pick?
Renee, I am so sorry.
Hold on.
Everything's gonna be fine.
How? My dress is ruined!
I got an idea.
Hey, driver, we need you to
swing by Cumberly's.
My store has
an amazing bridal department.
Are you insane?
Take us to the hospital!
Come on.
She just started labor.
Keep your legs together, honey.
We're just gonna run in
and grab a dress.
And shoes.
You need shoes, too?
Thanks to Old Faithful here.
My daughter is having a baby,
and you wanna go
on a shopping spree?
Could someone please
just tell me where to go?
Cumberly's!
Hospital!
Let's just go to Cumberly's.
Julie!
Mom,
my contractions just started.
We have time. Ah!
Ugh! Do you have
to keep doing that?
Okay, size sixes are over there.
Hey.
Don't lie to me.
Ugh.
No. No.
God, no.
Now, that is beautiful.
My daughter's looking at this.
When's her wedding?
Three months.
Mine's in five minutes.
Unzip me.
Oh! Hi, hi.
I'm Gabrielle Solis,
Head of VIP Sales
here at Cumberly's.
I'm Kent, minimum wage worker
stuck here on a Saturday.
Can I help you?
I need to borrow a bridal gown.
"Borrow"?
Just for the afternoon.
We don't lend bridal dresses.
Well, I know it's not policy,
but can't you do a favor
for a fellow worker?
Ma'am, I've never heard of you.
Do you have your
employee ID card?
No. I'm not one
of those nerds
who carries her ID card on
a handsome lanyard.
So, you want me to give you
a $6,000 wedding dress?
Five thousand
with my employee discount.
Go away, ma'am.
Oh!
That was a big one.
They seem to be
coming a lot faster.
Excuse me,
would you mind going in
and finding out
what's keeping them?
Things seem to be
speeding up a bit back here.
Right away.
Mom, what are you doing?
You are not
having my granddaughter
in the back of a limousine.
Keep breathing!
So, are we set?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Told you I was
a big shot here.
Now walk with me.
There's only one tiny hiccup.
Hey, where are you going
with that dress?
And now we run.
Where... Where's the limo?
I don't know, it was right here.
And we're running again.
Do you not have a car?
Does it look like
we have a car? Huh?
Does it?
Okay, all right.
Again,
late for your own wedding.
Maybe kill this guy later.
Don't say a word.
You hear me?
You have no idea
what I had to go through
to get here,
so if you even give me
one syllable of grief,
I will kick your sorry ass
all the way
back to Australia!
I've never seen anyone
look so beautiful.
Let's go inside
and get started on
our wedded bliss.
No, no, Katherine, I am excited.
I just need to
talk to Tom first.
Well, can you give me
till the end of the day?
Okay, thanks. Bye.
Talk to me about what?
Hi.
Oh, um...
Katherine keeps pushing me
about this job thing.
I thought you told her no.
I did,
but once she
started talking about
compensation packages and the...
You're negotiating a salary?
Lynette, we...
We just got back together.
What are you doing?
It could be
the last time an opportunity
like this comes along for me.
If I don't take it,
I'm afraid that...
You won't be happy?
Well...
Yeah.
Hey. Hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey!
Lynette, I would do anything,
I would go anywhere in the world
if I believed it would
finally make you happy.
But for as long as
I have known you,
you've always thought you needed
something else
to make you complete.
And I'm starting to realize,
nothing ever will.
Hello, Trip.
Ben invited me.
So if you wanna slug somebody,
slug him.
No. I'm glad to see you.
I wanted to thank you
for what you did
for Mrs. McCluskey.
That was very kind.
She's an awesome lady.
And she once helped out
a client of mine.
Well,
that's all I wanted to say.
Enjoy the reception.
Really? You can't think of
anything else to say to me?
Like what?
I don't know. Like...
How about, "Hey, Trip.
"Maybe you are a good guy.
I should give you
another chance."
Is that why you
found that old record?
To impress me?
Do you really think that?
Look,
I know I wanna be with you.
But if you don't think
you can ever trust me again,
well, I'm not gonna beg.
Why?
Yes.
Why do you wanna be with me?
You were my lawyer.
You know all the ugliest
details of my life,
my lying, my drinking,
my promiscuity.
I was actually relieved
when you put Gabby
on the witness stand,
because it explained
why you kissed me.
It was a manipulation, I got it.
But to keep saying you want me
when you know
how horribly flawed I am.
I don't trust you because
it just doesn't make sense.
How about
I explain it?
That clear it up for you?
Almost.
Look, Bree,
all those ugly details
you're talking about,
they just prove
that you're human.
Okay?
I don't wanna love an ideal.
I wanna love a real person.
So, what happens now?
Well,
first, we're gonna
walk out onto
that dance floor
and show your friends
how it's really done.
Hopefully, by then,
I'll get up the courage to
once again ask you to
go out on a date with me.
Of course,
even as I'm saying that,
I'm still not sure
what you're gonna say.
Did that clear it up for you?
Hey. You wanna dance?
They're playing a tango.
Wow, you're finally
talking to me again.
I must be out of the doghouse.
No, I'm still pretty mad.
Why? It was a joke.
All those years ago, when I...
I did what I did
with John Rowland,
that's the most
shameful thing in my life.
You can't make jokes about it.
It's too painful.
Fair enough.
You know,
it was
the most shameful thing
in my life, too.
I'm sorry.
No.
What's shameful is
that I neglected you.
I had this beautiful wife,
but I focused on
all the wrong things.
It was a tough time
for both of us.
I guess that's the point
I was making hiring Carmen.
Our roles are reversed now,
but we can't start
drifting away
from each other.
I never want to go
back to that again.
We won't.
We've grown up since then.
Although,
for two smart grown-ups,
we sure seem to fight a lot.
Why is it other couples
seem to waltz through life?
Well, that's easy.
You and me?
We're doing a tango.
Hey. I hear
someone's having a baby.
Yes, a little ahead
of schedule. Sorry.
No, it's no problem.
I was just playing
hoops down the block.
Don't worry, I'm gonna wash up
and then we'll get
this show on the road.
Okay?
Okay.
All right.
Did you see his legs?
How can you not wanna be
married to those legs?
Mom, please.
Right. I'm annoying. Sorry.
You know,
in honor of this special day,
I promise to
never again bug you
about finding a husband.
Even the baby
knows you're lying.
What about you?
Do you think
you'll ever get married again?
Julie.
No, I'm serious.
You're still young,
and gorgeous.
I don't know.
There's a saying,
"You know
you've hit middle-age
when your memories become
"more important to you
than your dreams."
And I have such
wonderful memories,
of Mike,
and you kids growing up,
all our friends on the lane.
Do I have one last
torrid romance in me?
Maybe.
But I know if I am
ever cold and lonely,
I can wrap myself up
in all those memories,
and I will be content.
So, Renee and Ben, never forget
that it takes
a lot of love to make
a house a home.
And when you're in the market
for a new home,
consider Lee McDermott, 1-800...
Give me that!
Okay, matron of honor's turn.
Lynette Scavo, give us a toast.
Renee and Ben,
your wedding
is one of the best days
of your life.
'Cause it's the day you realize,
"I finally have the thing
I need to be happy."
And then you forget.
So then what happens is,
instead of waking up
every morning and shouting,
"Somebody loves me,"
you start looking around
and thinking,
"What do I want now?
"What's the next thing
I need to be happy?"
So you look and you look,
and you keep thinking
you've found it,
but nothing works.
And the reason
that nothing works,
is because
that hole in your heart
that you're trying to fill
is already filled.
You just forgot.
Don't ever forget.
Always remember
how much you
wanted to be loved
and how much you are loved.
And I think
if you can do that,
and it isn't easy,
you will stop
looking and realize
you already are happy.
To Renee and Ben,
and to remembering.
Cheers.
I love you.
So, you meant that?
I'm happy.
Right here, right now.
I bet someone like that
could be happy anywhere.
Even New York.
Again?
Susan Delfino
moved from Wisteria Lane
on a Thursday.
But before she left,
she went to spend
a few more moments
with her friends,
doing what they loved best.
I see your $25,
and I raise you $50.
I know you're bluffing.
How?
For the last 10 years,
every time
you have a bad hand,
you tap the side of your glass.
No, I don't.
Yeah, you do.
You totally do.
Absolutely.
I have a tell,
and you guys never told me?
All right,
you each owe me $12,000.
I just realized this might be
the last time we'll
play poker together.
Don't say that.
Well, you're moving,
and Lynette's talking about
taking that job in New York.
We'll still get together.
I guess. It's just...
What?
I just always had this fantasy.
The four of us staying here,
growing old together.
You know, our grandkids
coming to visit.
Me staying gorgeous
while the three of you
age horribly.
You know,
she's actually
dreamed about that.
Of course she has.
No, seriously,
I'm gonna miss this so much.
I'm gonna miss us.
It's funny.
Some people never get to know
the folks next door.
They share a fence
and nothing else.
And we've shared everything.
How did we get to be so lucky?
I am so crazy nuts
about you guys.
Promise me this is
not the last time
we're gonna play poker together.
Absolutely not.
We'll just have
to make the time.
Of course we will.
It was a promise
made in all sincerity.
But, sadly,
it was not meant to be.
Lynette and Tom Scavo
left the lane
four weeks later.
They moved to New York
where Lynette learned
the joy of being a CEO.
She and Tom
soon bought a penthouse
overlooking Central Park
where years later
she'd take her
six grandchildren
and yell at them.
Gabrielle and Carlos Solis
left the neighborhood
the following year.
This was after
Carlos helped her develop
a personal shopping web site
which led to Gabrielle
getting her own show
on the Home Shopping Network.
They soon bought
a mansion in California
where they argued
happily ever after.
Two years later,
Bree and her new husband
left Fairview.
They moved to Louisville,
where Bree joined a club
for conservative women.
Trip then encouraged her
to enter into local politics.
The following November,
Bree was elected
to the Kentucky
State Legislature.
But Susan Delfino
was the first to move
from Wisteria Lane.
And this is how it ended:
she introduced herself to
the woman who was moving in.
You must be Jennifer.
And you must be Susan.
Nice to meet you.
Sorry if I'm early.
I made better time
than I thought I would.
We were just about to leave.
My house is your house.
I mean, legally,
this is your house.
Hey, I hope that
you'll be happy here.
Thanks. Steve's so excited to
finally live in the suburbs.
I'm a little worried
it's going to be boring.
I wouldn't worry about that.
Yeah, this street
is a lot of things.
Boring is not one of them.
Can we go now?
Yeah, we're going.
Hey, you guys mind
if I take one last spin
around the block?
Go for it.
As Susan left her driveway,
she had a feeling
she was being watched.
And she was.
The ghosts of people
who had been a part
of Wisteria Lane
were gazing upon her
as she passed.
They watched her,
as they watch everyone,
always hoping the living
could learn to
put aside rage and sorrow,
bitterness and regret.
These ghosts watch,
wanting people to remember
that even
the most desperate life
is, oh, so wonderful.
But only a lucky few realize
the gift they've been given.
Most people just go on,
day after day,
trying in vain
to keep secrets
that will never stay hidden.